<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-08-25T17:17:15-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/08/25/2023-08-10-King-of-the-Hill-Actor-Johnny-Hardwick-Passes/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-08-25T17:17:15-04:00</published><updated>2023-08-25T17:17:15-04:00</updated><id>/2023/08/25/2023-08-10-King-of-the-Hill-Actor-Johnny-Hardwick-Passes</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/08/25/2023-08-10-King-of-the-Hill-Actor-Johnny-Hardwick-Passes/">&lt;p&gt;The entertainment industry is mourning the loss of Johnny Hardwick, the acclaimed voice actor renowned for his portrayal of Dale Gribble in the popular animated series “King of the Hill.” At the age of 64, Hardwick’s demise has left many in shock.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The distressing news was confirmed by the Austin (Texas) Police Department, which attended a welfare check on Tuesday, leading to the tragic discovery of Hardwick’s lifeless body. While the circumstances surrounding his death are still shrouded in mystery, the Austin police have categorically stated that it isn’t a homicide case. Further details pertaining to the cause will be unveiled once the Travis County Medical Examiner finalizes their findings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hardwick’s role as Dale Gribble began in 1997 with the show’s premiere episode and lasted until its conclusion in 2010, spanning an impressive 259 episodes. His outstanding contribution to “King of the Hill” earned him an Emmy Award in 1999, followed by nominations in 2001 and 2002. The animated masterpiece was the brainchild of creators Mike Judge and Greg Daniels, with a cast ensemble including talents like Judge himself, Kathy Najimy, Stephen Root, and Pamela Adlon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earlier this year, fans rejoiced upon learning about a forthcoming revival of “King of the Hill,” with Hardwick’s involvement confirmed. Craig Erwich, the executive at the helm of ABC Entertainment, Hulu, and Disney Branded Television Streaming Originals, expressed enthusiasm about resuming the show’s narrative to reflect on our contemporary world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond his notable voice acting career, Hardwick was also a gifted stand-up comedian, making a mark in the comedy circuits during the 1990s.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/08/25/2023-08-12-Ian-Watkins-Assault/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-08-25T17:17:15-04:00</published><updated>2023-08-25T17:17:15-04:00</updated><id>/2023/08/25/2023-08-12-Ian-Watkins-Assault</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/08/25/2023-08-12-Ian-Watkins-Assault/">&lt;p&gt;Ian Watkins, the controversial former lead singer of the rock band Lostprophets, faced a brutal assault inside HMP Wakefield, where he’s currently serving a 29-year sentence for grave child sex crimes. According to sources, Watkins is in critical condition following the incident.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reports from the Mirror shed light on the gruesome nature of the assault. Allegedly, Watkins was accosted and held hostage by three inmates, subjected to hours of physical abuse, and eventually stabbed multiple times. Officers discovered the critically injured singer only hours later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Watkins was held for a lengthy period by the prisoners and endured a severe beating before the stabbing. The entire ordeal is under investigation,” conveyed the officials from HMP Wakefield. Fortunately, in a subsequent update from law enforcement, it was clarified that Watkins’ injuries, while severe, were not life-threatening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lostprophets, active from the late ’90s to the early 2000s, witnessed their downfall following the shocking revelations of Watkins’ depravities. In 2013, he faced charges for thirteen appalling sex offenses against children, which included the attempted rape of a one-year-old girl. The case revealed that Watkins administered drugs to children, plotting their sexual abuse, and even filmed some of his heinous acts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Confronted with overwhelming evidence, Watkins pleaded guilty to multiple counts of rape, sex with minors, and the possession of disturbing explicit content. His conviction in December 2013 led to the disintegration of the Lostprophets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jo Mjadzelics, one of Watkins’ former partners, expressed her shock at the recent attack, stating to the Mirror, “It’s surprising that such a brutal attack took so long, especially in a prison like Wakefield.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The broader implications of the attack on Watkins underline the volatile dynamics within prison systems, especially for individuals convicted of particularly reviled crimes. The repercussions of his crimes, it seems, continue to echo both for Watkins and for those who were once associated with him.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Banker’s Dark Secret - How $10,000 and Facebook Could’ve Ended a Life</title><link href="/news/2023/08/25/Banker-Plot/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Banker’s Dark Secret - How $10,000 and Facebook Could’ve Ended a Life" /><published>2023-08-25T17:03:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-08-25T17:03:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/08/25/Banker-Plot</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/08/25/Banker-Plot/">&lt;p&gt;In an unprecedented mix of high-tech communication and old-world crime, a New York banker stands accused of hatching a plot straight out of a crime thriller - a murder-for-hire scheme brokered over Facebook Messenger.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reshma Massarone, a seemingly innocuous branch manager at a New York credit union, is at the center of a chilling investigation involving her alleged attempt to eliminate her own brother-in-law during a family trip to Guyana. The alleged price for the hit? A cool $10,000.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From July 20 to August 16, the cold digital confines of Facebook Messenger became the setting for Massarone’s machinations. She allegedly reached out to an old friend, urging him to “take care of business.” The friend, opting not to get his hands dirty, reportedly offered to act as the middleman, finding a hitman to execute the grim deed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The narrative deepens as surveillance footage shows Massarone physically withdrawing the funds – a down payment for death. The next scene? A Walgreen’s store, where Massarone can be seen making a wire transfer at a Western Union kiosk, sending over 25 $100 bills - a sum of $2,500, presumably a deposit for the hitman.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her commitment to this dark path seemed clear when she chillingly penned, “No turning back,” in a message on July 25, urging the deletion of her contact for fear of being caught.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But like all tales of crime and mystery, the plot was eventually uncovered. How authorities caught wind of this intricate web is still shrouded in secrecy. What remains evident is the unyielding power of digital trails in modern crime-solving.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Currently incarcerated and perceived as a clear and present danger to society, Massarone awaits the next chapter in this riveting saga. Calls to her attorney, Mark Gombiner, have gone unanswered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a world increasingly connected by technology, this harrowing tale serves as a stark reminder: the digital realm can be both a tool for connection and, in the wrong hands, a weapon of destruction.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In an unprecedented mix of high-tech communication and old-world crime, a New York banker stands accused of hatching a plot straight out of a crime thriller - a murder-for-hire scheme brokered over Facebook Messenger. Reshma Massarone, a seemingly innocuous branch manager at a New York credit union, is at the center of a chilling investigation involving her alleged attempt to eliminate her own brother-in-law during a family trip to Guyana. The alleged price for the hit? A cool $10,000. From July 20 to August 16, the cold digital confines of Facebook Messenger became the setting for Massarone’s machinations. She allegedly reached out to an old friend, urging him to “take care of business.” The friend, opting not to get his hands dirty, reportedly offered to act as the middleman, finding a hitman to execute the grim deed. The narrative deepens as surveillance footage shows Massarone physically withdrawing the funds – a down payment for death. The next scene? A Walgreen’s store, where Massarone can be seen making a wire transfer at a Western Union kiosk, sending over 25 $100 bills - a sum of $2,500, presumably a deposit for the hitman. Her commitment to this dark path seemed clear when she chillingly penned, “No turning back,” in a message on July 25, urging the deletion of her contact for fear of being caught. But like all tales of crime and mystery, the plot was eventually uncovered. How authorities caught wind of this intricate web is still shrouded in secrecy. What remains evident is the unyielding power of digital trails in modern crime-solving. Currently incarcerated and perceived as a clear and present danger to society, Massarone awaits the next chapter in this riveting saga. Calls to her attorney, Mark Gombiner, have gone unanswered. In a world increasingly connected by technology, this harrowing tale serves as a stark reminder: the digital realm can be both a tool for connection and, in the wrong hands, a weapon of destruction.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Rising Tensions - Taiwan Detects Renewed Chinese Military Maneuvers</title><link href="/news/2023/08/25/Chinese-Military-Activity/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rising Tensions - Taiwan Detects Renewed Chinese Military Maneuvers" /><published>2023-08-25T16:07:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-08-25T16:07:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/08/25/Chinese-Military-Activity</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/08/25/Chinese-Military-Activity/">&lt;p&gt;In a fresh escalation of tensions between China and Taiwan, the latter’s defense ministry has reported increased Chinese military activity around its airspace and waters. On Friday, Taiwan’s surveillance systems picked up 13 aircraft entering its designated “response” zone, signaling Beijing’s continued military assertiveness in the region.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;China, which firmly regards Taiwan as an integral part of its territory despite the island’s democratic governance, has ratcheted up military pressure over the past three years. Recent events, including stop-overs by Taiwan’s Vice President William Lai in the United States, appear to have further inflamed the situation. China, in what was perceived as a retaliatory move, conducted a series of military drills around Taiwan this Saturday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to the Taiwanese defense ministry, early detections on Friday morning revealed a mix of 22 Chinese aircraft, comprising fighters, bombers, early warning aircraft, and drones. While 13 of these entered Taiwan’s immediate “response” zone, exact details about their operations remain unclear. In response to these incursions, Taiwan dispatched its own aircraft and naval vessels to monitor the situation closely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, even though Beijing has not officially announced any further military drills post-Saturday, history suggests China’s penchant for initiating such missions without prior or post acknowledgment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the specter of geopolitical tensions continues to loom over the Taiwan Strait, the international community will be closely observing these developments, hoping for diplomatic channels to prevail over military confrontations.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a fresh escalation of tensions between China and Taiwan, the latter’s defense ministry has reported increased Chinese military activity around its airspace and waters. On Friday, Taiwan’s surveillance systems picked up 13 aircraft entering its designated “response” zone, signaling Beijing’s continued military assertiveness in the region. China, which firmly regards Taiwan as an integral part of its territory despite the island’s democratic governance, has ratcheted up military pressure over the past three years. Recent events, including stop-overs by Taiwan’s Vice President William Lai in the United States, appear to have further inflamed the situation. China, in what was perceived as a retaliatory move, conducted a series of military drills around Taiwan this Saturday. According to the Taiwanese defense ministry, early detections on Friday morning revealed a mix of 22 Chinese aircraft, comprising fighters, bombers, early warning aircraft, and drones. While 13 of these entered Taiwan’s immediate “response” zone, exact details about their operations remain unclear. In response to these incursions, Taiwan dispatched its own aircraft and naval vessels to monitor the situation closely. Interestingly, even though Beijing has not officially announced any further military drills post-Saturday, history suggests China’s penchant for initiating such missions without prior or post acknowledgment. As the specter of geopolitical tensions continues to loom over the Taiwan Strait, the international community will be closely observing these developments, hoping for diplomatic channels to prevail over military confrontations.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Debate Ratings Take a Dive - Missing the Trump Effect?</title><link href="/politics/2023/08/25/Debate-Rating-Dip/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Debate Ratings Take a Dive - Missing the Trump Effect?" /><published>2023-08-25T15:02:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-08-25T15:02:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/08/25/Debate-Rating-Dip</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/08/25/Debate-Rating-Dip/">&lt;p&gt;The recent Republican primary debate broadcasted by Fox News experienced a pronounced drop in viewership, with Nielsen Media Research data indicating that only 12.8 million tuned in. This figure starkly contrasts with former President Donald Trump’s debate debut in 2015, which garnered attention from about 25.8 million viewers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comparative Viewer Engagement&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When zeroing in on the key advertising demographic, ages 25-54, the debate managed to secure 2.8 million viewers. Despite the numbers appearing lackluster compared to Trump’s debut, Fox News accentuated the silver lining. The network underscored that this debate outperformed more than 70% of all presidential primary debates during the 2016 and 2020 cycles. Furthermore, it emerged as the highest-rated nonsports cable telecast of 2023.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, in juxtaposition with the Democrat primary debates of 2020, the recent GOP debate appears to lag. The initial two Democrat debates recorded 19 million and 15 million viewers, respectively. The third debate tallied at 10 million.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trump’s Absence: A Vital Factor?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speculation arises on whether the dip in viewership metrics can be attributed to Trump’s decision to skip the event. Offering an explanation for his absence, Trump pointed to significant leads in polling, implying a debate appearance might not be essential to his campaign strategy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adding another twist to the narrative, just five minutes prior to the debate’s commencement, Tucker Carlson aired an exclusive interview with Trump. This move could have potentially diverted a substantial portion of potential debate viewers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Implications for the GOP&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Viewer metrics and ratings serve as a crucial barometer in gauging public interest and engagement with political events. The recent GOP debate’s viewership numbers might prompt Republican strategists to introspect on the factors influencing public attention and the potential role of notable personalities like Trump in driving viewership.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the dynamic landscape of political campaigns, the ability to seize and sustain the audience’s attention can often translate to momentum on the ground. The GOP will likely be keenly analyzing these numbers to fine-tune their approach as the election season intensifies.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">The recent Republican primary debate broadcasted by Fox News experienced a pronounced drop in viewership, with Nielsen Media Research data indicating that only 12.8 million tuned in. This figure starkly contrasts with former President Donald Trump’s debate debut in 2015, which garnered attention from about 25.8 million viewers. Comparative Viewer Engagement When zeroing in on the key advertising demographic, ages 25-54, the debate managed to secure 2.8 million viewers. Despite the numbers appearing lackluster compared to Trump’s debut, Fox News accentuated the silver lining. The network underscored that this debate outperformed more than 70% of all presidential primary debates during the 2016 and 2020 cycles. Furthermore, it emerged as the highest-rated nonsports cable telecast of 2023. However, in juxtaposition with the Democrat primary debates of 2020, the recent GOP debate appears to lag. The initial two Democrat debates recorded 19 million and 15 million viewers, respectively. The third debate tallied at 10 million. Trump’s Absence: A Vital Factor? Speculation arises on whether the dip in viewership metrics can be attributed to Trump’s decision to skip the event. Offering an explanation for his absence, Trump pointed to significant leads in polling, implying a debate appearance might not be essential to his campaign strategy. Adding another twist to the narrative, just five minutes prior to the debate’s commencement, Tucker Carlson aired an exclusive interview with Trump. This move could have potentially diverted a substantial portion of potential debate viewers. Implications for the GOP Viewer metrics and ratings serve as a crucial barometer in gauging public interest and engagement with political events. The recent GOP debate’s viewership numbers might prompt Republican strategists to introspect on the factors influencing public attention and the potential role of notable personalities like Trump in driving viewership. In the dynamic landscape of political campaigns, the ability to seize and sustain the audience’s attention can often translate to momentum on the ground. The GOP will likely be keenly analyzing these numbers to fine-tune their approach as the election season intensifies.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Elle King’s Triumphant Transformation - From Postpartum Struggles to Newfound Strength</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/08/25/Elle-King-Weight-Loss-Journey/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Elle King’s Triumphant Transformation - From Postpartum Struggles to Newfound Strength" /><published>2023-08-25T14:11:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-08-25T14:11:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/08/25/Elle-King-Weight-Loss-Journey</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/08/25/Elle-King-Weight-Loss-Journey/">&lt;p&gt;Country star Elle King’s recent Instagram post not only stunned fans with her remarkable weight loss but also resonated with many for its candid and vulnerable portrayal of her battle with postpartum depression.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From Darkness to Light:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After welcoming her son, Lucky, in September 2021, King’s weight scaled to 284 pounds. Fast forward to 2023, and the singer has undergone a noticeable physical transformation. However, she’s quick to clarify: it wasn’t a product of any medication.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“From pregnancy in 2021 to now in 2023, it’s been a journey,” she shared on Instagram. “Weight loss doesn’t happen overnight. It’s been an ever-evolving process.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Facing Postpartum Depression:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;King delved deeper into her struggles during and post-pregnancy. “I fell deep into depression during my pregnancy. The intensity of postpartum depression was overwhelming,” she recounted. Feeling entrapped in her own body, King’s passion – her singing – also suffered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Path to Healing:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Daughter to comedian Rob Schneider, King decided to tackle her health issues head-on. “I began slow, incorporating metabolic workouts and light cardio. Over time, my body, voice, and spirit felt rejuvenated,” she stated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her journey wasn’t solo. Partnering with personal trainer @pauldominic_, King underscored the importance of self-motivation. “Find what you love - music, cycling, swimming. It started as a desire to lose weight but transformed into a holistic wellness approach. My mind functions better when my body is active.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Beyond Physical Transformation:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Elle King’s commitment extends beyond the scales. She shared snippets of her skincare routine and behind-the-scenes clips preparing for concerts. But, she firmly declared, “Today, I’m healthy. I’m neither tiny nor huge. Most importantly, I’m not on any weight loss medication.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her motivation also finds roots in her family history, recalling her diabetic grandfather. “I’ve seen him struggle. I’m pre-diabetic with PCOS. But my journey is mine, and I only wish for a long, content life,” she concluded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In sharing her authentic journey, Elle King not only sets a gold standard for celebrities navigating personal struggles in the public eye but also inspires countless others grappling with similar issues.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Country star Elle King’s recent Instagram post not only stunned fans with her remarkable weight loss but also resonated with many for its candid and vulnerable portrayal of her battle with postpartum depression. From Darkness to Light: After welcoming her son, Lucky, in September 2021, King’s weight scaled to 284 pounds. Fast forward to 2023, and the singer has undergone a noticeable physical transformation. However, she’s quick to clarify: it wasn’t a product of any medication. “From pregnancy in 2021 to now in 2023, it’s been a journey,” she shared on Instagram. “Weight loss doesn’t happen overnight. It’s been an ever-evolving process.” Facing Postpartum Depression: King delved deeper into her struggles during and post-pregnancy. “I fell deep into depression during my pregnancy. The intensity of postpartum depression was overwhelming,” she recounted. Feeling entrapped in her own body, King’s passion – her singing – also suffered. The Path to Healing: Daughter to comedian Rob Schneider, King decided to tackle her health issues head-on. “I began slow, incorporating metabolic workouts and light cardio. Over time, my body, voice, and spirit felt rejuvenated,” she stated. Her journey wasn’t solo. Partnering with personal trainer @pauldominic_, King underscored the importance of self-motivation. “Find what you love - music, cycling, swimming. It started as a desire to lose weight but transformed into a holistic wellness approach. My mind functions better when my body is active.” Beyond Physical Transformation: Elle King’s commitment extends beyond the scales. She shared snippets of her skincare routine and behind-the-scenes clips preparing for concerts. But, she firmly declared, “Today, I’m healthy. I’m neither tiny nor huge. Most importantly, I’m not on any weight loss medication.” Her motivation also finds roots in her family history, recalling her diabetic grandfather. “I’ve seen him struggle. I’m pre-diabetic with PCOS. But my journey is mine, and I only wish for a long, content life,” she concluded. In sharing her authentic journey, Elle King not only sets a gold standard for celebrities navigating personal struggles in the public eye but also inspires countless others grappling with similar issues.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Whispers and Warlords - Putin Breaks Silence on Mysterious Plane Crash</title><link href="/news/2023/08/25/Putin-Prigozhin/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Whispers and Warlords - Putin Breaks Silence on Mysterious Plane Crash" /><published>2023-08-25T13:04:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-08-25T13:04:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/08/25/Putin-Prigozhin</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/08/25/Putin-Prigozhin/">&lt;p&gt;In an atmosphere charged with uncertainty and speculation, Russian President Vladimir Putin has finally voiced his sentiments on the reported death of the Wagner Group leader, Yevgeny Prigozhin, in a recent plane crash. Prigozhin, known for his influence and ties with Putin, was reportedly one of the victims in an aircraft explosion that occurred within Russian airspace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking during a meeting with Denis Pushilin, leader of the Donetsk People’s Republic (a separatist state aligning with Russian interests in Ukraine), Putin extended his condolences, saying, “It is always a tragedy.” Without directly addressing international conjectures hinting at Russian government’s involvement in Prigozhin’s demise, he emphasized the significance of Prigozhin’s contributions to combating what he described as the “neo-Nazi regime in Ukraine.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Putin’s personal relationship with Prigozhin dates back to the early 1990s. He acknowledged Prigozhin’s complex nature, alluding to both his mistakes and his undeniable talent as a businessman. Prigozhin’s business endeavors spanned not only Russia but also territories in Africa, dealing in oil, gas, and precious metals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given the magnitude of the situation and its geopolitical implications, the air is rife with speculative theories. While some suspect an assassination orchestrated by Putin, others speculate a fabricated tale of Prigozhin’s death intended for clandestine purposes. Rebekah Koffler, a former U.S. Defense Intelligence Agency official, highlighted the skepticism around Russian state media’s reporting, suggesting potential disinformation operations at play.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further adding to the intrigue, the U.S. President Joe Biden, when queried about Prigozhin’s alleged presence on the ill-fated plane, remarked, “Not much happens in Russia that Putin’s not behind. I don’t know enough to know the answer.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the wake of this uncertainty, Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskyy swiftly dispelled notions of Ukraine’s involvement in Prigozhin’s apparent death, cryptically adding, “I think everyone is aware of who is involved.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the world watches closely, the saga surrounding the plane crash and its high-profile victim promises further twists and turns, with truth being the ultimate casualty in this intricate game of power and politics.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In an atmosphere charged with uncertainty and speculation, Russian President Vladimir Putin has finally voiced his sentiments on the reported death of the Wagner Group leader, Yevgeny Prigozhin, in a recent plane crash. Prigozhin, known for his influence and ties with Putin, was reportedly one of the victims in an aircraft explosion that occurred within Russian airspace. Speaking during a meeting with Denis Pushilin, leader of the Donetsk People’s Republic (a separatist state aligning with Russian interests in Ukraine), Putin extended his condolences, saying, “It is always a tragedy.” Without directly addressing international conjectures hinting at Russian government’s involvement in Prigozhin’s demise, he emphasized the significance of Prigozhin’s contributions to combating what he described as the “neo-Nazi regime in Ukraine.” Putin’s personal relationship with Prigozhin dates back to the early 1990s. He acknowledged Prigozhin’s complex nature, alluding to both his mistakes and his undeniable talent as a businessman. Prigozhin’s business endeavors spanned not only Russia but also territories in Africa, dealing in oil, gas, and precious metals. Given the magnitude of the situation and its geopolitical implications, the air is rife with speculative theories. While some suspect an assassination orchestrated by Putin, others speculate a fabricated tale of Prigozhin’s death intended for clandestine purposes. Rebekah Koffler, a former U.S. Defense Intelligence Agency official, highlighted the skepticism around Russian state media’s reporting, suggesting potential disinformation operations at play. Further adding to the intrigue, the U.S. President Joe Biden, when queried about Prigozhin’s alleged presence on the ill-fated plane, remarked, “Not much happens in Russia that Putin’s not behind. I don’t know enough to know the answer.” In the wake of this uncertainty, Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskyy swiftly dispelled notions of Ukraine’s involvement in Prigozhin’s apparent death, cryptically adding, “I think everyone is aware of who is involved.” As the world watches closely, the saga surrounding the plane crash and its high-profile victim promises further twists and turns, with truth being the ultimate casualty in this intricate game of power and politics.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Cost of Wokeness - Disney’s Troubling Stock Plunge</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/08/25/Disney-Woke-Backlash/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Cost of Wokeness - Disney’s Troubling Stock Plunge" /><published>2023-08-25T12:05:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-08-25T12:05:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/08/25/Disney-Woke-Backlash</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/08/25/Disney-Woke-Backlash/">&lt;p&gt;Disney, once a beacon of timeless entertainment, has recently found itself in stormy seas, and its stock performance tells a tale of questionable corporate decisions. Closing at a nearly decade-low price of $82.47, one can’t help but question the wisdom of some of the company’s recent strategies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Woke Agenda:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Disney’s decision to be more “woke,” or socially conscious, has been pinpointed by many as a significant contributor to its decline. What was once a cherished escape from reality for families worldwide has now become a hotbed for modern political and societal debates. For many longtime fans, Disney’s pivot to more progressive narratives feels less like genuine evolution and more like a calculated move to appease a vocal minority.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Factors in the Decline:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Box Office Misfires:&lt;/strong&gt; Movies are no longer the surefire hits they once were. As Disney attempts to integrate contemporary social agendas into its storylines, it seems the magic may have dimmed for a considerable segment of its audience.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disney+ Stumbles:&lt;/strong&gt; While many anticipated Disney’s streaming platform to be a game-changer, its overtly progressive content has arguably alienated a large chunk of potential subscribers.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Compromised Brand Image:&lt;/strong&gt; Disney’s longstanding reputation for wholesome, family-friendly content is under scrutiny. Their efforts to be at the forefront of modern societal changes may have backfired, distancing them from a once-loyal audience base.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s not just the inclusion of diverse characters and narratives that’s at issue here—it’s the perception that Disney is forcing a particular viewpoint on audiences, overshadowing the primary objective of providing quality entertainment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While change and evolution are integral parts of growth, corporations like Disney must tread carefully. The balance between staying relevant and maintaining the core essence that made them iconic in the first place is delicate. As Disney’s stock reflects, sometimes, the cost of wokeness can be high, especially when it seems to come at the expense of timeless storytelling.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Disney, once a beacon of timeless entertainment, has recently found itself in stormy seas, and its stock performance tells a tale of questionable corporate decisions. Closing at a nearly decade-low price of $82.47, one can’t help but question the wisdom of some of the company’s recent strategies. The Woke Agenda: Disney’s decision to be more “woke,” or socially conscious, has been pinpointed by many as a significant contributor to its decline. What was once a cherished escape from reality for families worldwide has now become a hotbed for modern political and societal debates. For many longtime fans, Disney’s pivot to more progressive narratives feels less like genuine evolution and more like a calculated move to appease a vocal minority. Factors in the Decline: Box Office Misfires: Movies are no longer the surefire hits they once were. As Disney attempts to integrate contemporary social agendas into its storylines, it seems the magic may have dimmed for a considerable segment of its audience. Disney+ Stumbles: While many anticipated Disney’s streaming platform to be a game-changer, its overtly progressive content has arguably alienated a large chunk of potential subscribers. Compromised Brand Image: Disney’s longstanding reputation for wholesome, family-friendly content is under scrutiny. Their efforts to be at the forefront of modern societal changes may have backfired, distancing them from a once-loyal audience base. It’s not just the inclusion of diverse characters and narratives that’s at issue here—it’s the perception that Disney is forcing a particular viewpoint on audiences, overshadowing the primary objective of providing quality entertainment. While change and evolution are integral parts of growth, corporations like Disney must tread carefully. The balance between staying relevant and maintaining the core essence that made them iconic in the first place is delicate. As Disney’s stock reflects, sometimes, the cost of wokeness can be high, especially when it seems to come at the expense of timeless storytelling.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump Defies Radical Left - Owens Speaks Out</title><link href="/politics/2023/08/25/Trump-Challenge/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump Defies Radical Left - Owens Speaks Out" /><published>2023-08-25T11:15:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-08-25T11:15:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/08/25/Trump-Challenge</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/08/25/Trump-Challenge/">&lt;p&gt;In a bold proclamation, Rep. Burgess Owens, R-Utah, put forth that former President Donald Trump remains a stalwart defender against radical left ideologies. Expressing his views on “Rob Schmitt Tonight,” Owens championed Trump’s unwavering spirit amidst current political adversities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trump’s Significance in Modern Politics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Highlighting Trump’s significance in the contemporary political landscape, Owens stated that Trump is, in essence, the “middle finger” to the radical left. This sentiment resonates with many conservatives who believe that Trump’s audacious stance often rattles the core of the more extreme left factions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Donald Trump’s presence and influence unsettle those who are accustomed to having their way unchallenged,” Owens elaborated. He emphasized that the left, often seen as bullies, is met with formidable resistance in Trump, a factor that exacerbates their antagonism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Call to Unity Among Conservatives&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Addressing fellow Republicans, Owens urged unity, especially in these turbulent times. Pointing out the gravity of the nation’s political climate, he mentioned that Republicans and conservatives need leaders who genuinely understand and represent the values they uphold. He further added that supporting Trump is paramount in this endeavor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It’s a pivotal moment in our nation’s history. We need stalwarts who can rally us and fight for the very ideals America was built on,” the congressman stressed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Challenging Times Ahead&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the outpour of support from conservatives and allies, Trump currently faces legal challenges. Recently, he was booked at the Fulton County Jail on charges related to the 2020 elections. However, this hasn’t deterred the former president or his supporters, showcasing their indomitable spirit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s worth noting that several of Trump’s close allies, such as Rudy Giuliani and Mark Meadows, have faced similar situations but remain committed to their shared values and principles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the words of Owens, it’s a fight for the very essence of America. And as the nation watches keenly, leaders like Trump and Owens continue to stand as pillars of hope for many conservatives.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a bold proclamation, Rep. Burgess Owens, R-Utah, put forth that former President Donald Trump remains a stalwart defender against radical left ideologies. Expressing his views on “Rob Schmitt Tonight,” Owens championed Trump’s unwavering spirit amidst current political adversities. Trump’s Significance in Modern Politics Highlighting Trump’s significance in the contemporary political landscape, Owens stated that Trump is, in essence, the “middle finger” to the radical left. This sentiment resonates with many conservatives who believe that Trump’s audacious stance often rattles the core of the more extreme left factions. “Donald Trump’s presence and influence unsettle those who are accustomed to having their way unchallenged,” Owens elaborated. He emphasized that the left, often seen as bullies, is met with formidable resistance in Trump, a factor that exacerbates their antagonism. A Call to Unity Among Conservatives Addressing fellow Republicans, Owens urged unity, especially in these turbulent times. Pointing out the gravity of the nation’s political climate, he mentioned that Republicans and conservatives need leaders who genuinely understand and represent the values they uphold. He further added that supporting Trump is paramount in this endeavor. “It’s a pivotal moment in our nation’s history. We need stalwarts who can rally us and fight for the very ideals America was built on,” the congressman stressed. Challenging Times Ahead Despite the outpour of support from conservatives and allies, Trump currently faces legal challenges. Recently, he was booked at the Fulton County Jail on charges related to the 2020 elections. However, this hasn’t deterred the former president or his supporters, showcasing their indomitable spirit. It’s worth noting that several of Trump’s close allies, such as Rudy Giuliani and Mark Meadows, have faced similar situations but remain committed to their shared values and principles. In the words of Owens, it’s a fight for the very essence of America. And as the nation watches keenly, leaders like Trump and Owens continue to stand as pillars of hope for many conservatives.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Elusive Cartel Operator Apprehended - Breitbart’s Investigation Plays Key Role</title><link href="/news/2023/08/25/Cartel-Arrest/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Elusive Cartel Operator Apprehended - Breitbart’s Investigation Plays Key Role" /><published>2023-08-25T10:10:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-08-25T10:10:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/08/25/Cartel-Arrest</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/08/25/Cartel-Arrest/">&lt;p&gt;In a significant development, Mexican state police officers have successfully arrested Jose “El Amarillo” Leyva, a shadowy cartel figure responsible for multiple terror-style attacks in the border state of Nuevo Leon. This elusive cartel operator became widely recognized after Breitbart Texas released his photograph and specific details in 2021.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aged 57, El Amarillo was associated with the Cartel Del Noreste faction of Los Zetas. He had been commanding several squads of armed men in northern Nuevo Leon, with their primary targets being police forces and rival gang members. The apprehension of El Amarillo was a collaborative effort by Nuevo Leon’s Fuerza Civil Police, leveraging intelligence and initial investigations conducted by the State Investigations Agency (AEI). During the arrest, the police also confiscated a weapon and a small drug stash.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Breitbart Texas had shed light on El Amarillo’s ominous activities in 2021. He had masterminded and executed various strike missions that targeted local police officers in northern Nuevo Leon. One of the most heinous crimes tied to El Amarillo and his henchmen was the 2021 assassination of the local police chief in Dr. Coss, Francisco Leonides Cruz. Breitbart Texas had detailed the chilling episode where the police chief was ambushed and taken down in a calculated surprise attack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since that report, El Amarillo expanded his sphere of influence, and his footprints were evident in numerous terror-themed assaults on both police and civilians in the Nuevo Leon-Tamaulipas region.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Breitbart Texas’s sources in law enforcement described El Amarillo as a hard-to-catch figure primarily because he was native to the region. His in-depth understanding of the local rural areas allowed him to move his personnel stealthily, thereby evading law enforcement’s gaze for an extended period.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a significant development, Mexican state police officers have successfully arrested Jose “El Amarillo” Leyva, a shadowy cartel figure responsible for multiple terror-style attacks in the border state of Nuevo Leon. This elusive cartel operator became widely recognized after Breitbart Texas released his photograph and specific details in 2021. Aged 57, El Amarillo was associated with the Cartel Del Noreste faction of Los Zetas. He had been commanding several squads of armed men in northern Nuevo Leon, with their primary targets being police forces and rival gang members. The apprehension of El Amarillo was a collaborative effort by Nuevo Leon’s Fuerza Civil Police, leveraging intelligence and initial investigations conducted by the State Investigations Agency (AEI). During the arrest, the police also confiscated a weapon and a small drug stash. Breitbart Texas had shed light on El Amarillo’s ominous activities in 2021. He had masterminded and executed various strike missions that targeted local police officers in northern Nuevo Leon. One of the most heinous crimes tied to El Amarillo and his henchmen was the 2021 assassination of the local police chief in Dr. Coss, Francisco Leonides Cruz. Breitbart Texas had detailed the chilling episode where the police chief was ambushed and taken down in a calculated surprise attack. Since that report, El Amarillo expanded his sphere of influence, and his footprints were evident in numerous terror-themed assaults on both police and civilians in the Nuevo Leon-Tamaulipas region. Breitbart Texas’s sources in law enforcement described El Amarillo as a hard-to-catch figure primarily because he was native to the region. His in-depth understanding of the local rural areas allowed him to move his personnel stealthily, thereby evading law enforcement’s gaze for an extended period.</summary></entry></feed>