<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-08-28T13:24:43-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/08/28/2023-08-10-King-of-the-Hill-Actor-Johnny-Hardwick-Passes/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-08-28T13:24:43-04:00</published><updated>2023-08-28T13:24:43-04:00</updated><id>/2023/08/28/2023-08-10-King-of-the-Hill-Actor-Johnny-Hardwick-Passes</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/08/28/2023-08-10-King-of-the-Hill-Actor-Johnny-Hardwick-Passes/">&lt;p&gt;The entertainment industry is mourning the loss of Johnny Hardwick, the acclaimed voice actor renowned for his portrayal of Dale Gribble in the popular animated series “King of the Hill.” At the age of 64, Hardwick’s demise has left many in shock.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The distressing news was confirmed by the Austin (Texas) Police Department, which attended a welfare check on Tuesday, leading to the tragic discovery of Hardwick’s lifeless body. While the circumstances surrounding his death are still shrouded in mystery, the Austin police have categorically stated that it isn’t a homicide case. Further details pertaining to the cause will be unveiled once the Travis County Medical Examiner finalizes their findings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hardwick’s role as Dale Gribble began in 1997 with the show’s premiere episode and lasted until its conclusion in 2010, spanning an impressive 259 episodes. His outstanding contribution to “King of the Hill” earned him an Emmy Award in 1999, followed by nominations in 2001 and 2002. The animated masterpiece was the brainchild of creators Mike Judge and Greg Daniels, with a cast ensemble including talents like Judge himself, Kathy Najimy, Stephen Root, and Pamela Adlon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earlier this year, fans rejoiced upon learning about a forthcoming revival of “King of the Hill,” with Hardwick’s involvement confirmed. Craig Erwich, the executive at the helm of ABC Entertainment, Hulu, and Disney Branded Television Streaming Originals, expressed enthusiasm about resuming the show’s narrative to reflect on our contemporary world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond his notable voice acting career, Hardwick was also a gifted stand-up comedian, making a mark in the comedy circuits during the 1990s.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/08/28/2023-08-12-Ian-Watkins-Assault/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-08-28T13:24:43-04:00</published><updated>2023-08-28T13:24:43-04:00</updated><id>/2023/08/28/2023-08-12-Ian-Watkins-Assault</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/08/28/2023-08-12-Ian-Watkins-Assault/">&lt;p&gt;Ian Watkins, the controversial former lead singer of the rock band Lostprophets, faced a brutal assault inside HMP Wakefield, where he’s currently serving a 29-year sentence for grave child sex crimes. According to sources, Watkins is in critical condition following the incident.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reports from the Mirror shed light on the gruesome nature of the assault. Allegedly, Watkins was accosted and held hostage by three inmates, subjected to hours of physical abuse, and eventually stabbed multiple times. Officers discovered the critically injured singer only hours later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Watkins was held for a lengthy period by the prisoners and endured a severe beating before the stabbing. The entire ordeal is under investigation,” conveyed the officials from HMP Wakefield. Fortunately, in a subsequent update from law enforcement, it was clarified that Watkins’ injuries, while severe, were not life-threatening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lostprophets, active from the late ’90s to the early 2000s, witnessed their downfall following the shocking revelations of Watkins’ depravities. In 2013, he faced charges for thirteen appalling sex offenses against children, which included the attempted rape of a one-year-old girl. The case revealed that Watkins administered drugs to children, plotting their sexual abuse, and even filmed some of his heinous acts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Confronted with overwhelming evidence, Watkins pleaded guilty to multiple counts of rape, sex with minors, and the possession of disturbing explicit content. His conviction in December 2013 led to the disintegration of the Lostprophets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jo Mjadzelics, one of Watkins’ former partners, expressed her shock at the recent attack, stating to the Mirror, “It’s surprising that such a brutal attack took so long, especially in a prison like Wakefield.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The broader implications of the attack on Watkins underline the volatile dynamics within prison systems, especially for individuals convicted of particularly reviled crimes. The repercussions of his crimes, it seems, continue to echo both for Watkins and for those who were once associated with him.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/08/28/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-08-28T13:24:43-04:00</published><updated>2023-08-28T13:24:43-04:00</updated><id>/2023/08/28/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/08/28/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Nationwide Consensus - Is Biden Too Aged for a Second Term?</title><link href="/politics/2023/08/28/Biden-Age-Concerns/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Nationwide Consensus - Is Biden Too Aged for a Second Term?" /><published>2023-08-28T11:50:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-08-28T11:50:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/08/28/Biden-Age-Concerns</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/08/28/Biden-Age-Concerns/">&lt;p&gt;In a striking sign of the times, President Joe Biden appears to have united much of the nation, though perhaps not in the manner he would have anticipated. According to a recent poll by The Associated Press-NORC Center for Public Affairs Research, there’s a sweeping consensus across party lines suggesting that Biden’s age might be a hindrance to his capability of effectively serving another term.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A staggering 77% of the respondents in the poll agreed on the sentiment that Biden is perhaps too advanced in years to execute the office’s responsibilities for another four. Breaking it down, while 89% of Republican respondents shared this view, even the Democratic base showcased significant reservations, with 69% echoing the same concerns. Importantly, this isn’t an ageist perspective limited to the younger generation. Respondents from varied age groups expressed these concerns, although older Democrats were observed to be slightly more supportive of Biden’s potential 2024 candidacy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Drawing a parallel, roughly 50% of the surveyed U.S. adults opined that former President Trump might also be too old for the office. However, partisan lines were clearer here, with Democrats more inclined to emphasize Trump’s age as a disqualifying factor compared to Republicans.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The AP-NORC poll, conducted from August 10 to 14, 2023, surveyed 1,165 adults and carries a margin of error of plus or minus 3.8 percentage points. One significant takeaway from the poll is a possible shift in public sentiment, leaning towards younger leadership as opposed to the seasoned 80-year-old Democrat currently helming the White House.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This isn’t the first time concerns regarding Biden’s age have been raised. Being the oldest serving U.S. president, if Biden were to secure a reelection in 2024, he would exit office at the ripe age of 86 in 2029.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a similar vein, a Redfield &amp;amp; Wilton Strategies survey for Newsweek earlier in August accentuated these concerns. Their findings showcased a prevailing apprehension among Democrats regarding Biden’s ability to execute his duties. Interestingly, while most Biden voters acknowledged these concerns, there was even deeper division on whether his age should be a definitive factor against his candidacy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In another related study in June, nearly half of the independent voters expressed reservations about Biden’s age and health, suggesting that these could “severely limit” his capabilities as the President. An Economist-YouGov poll revealed that 45% of the adults surveyed were skeptical about the President’s health and age impacting his ability to perform his duties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the 2024 elections loom, these age-related concerns are likely to play a pivotal role in shaping the political narratives and campaign strategies.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a striking sign of the times, President Joe Biden appears to have united much of the nation, though perhaps not in the manner he would have anticipated. According to a recent poll by The Associated Press-NORC Center for Public Affairs Research, there’s a sweeping consensus across party lines suggesting that Biden’s age might be a hindrance to his capability of effectively serving another term. A staggering 77% of the respondents in the poll agreed on the sentiment that Biden is perhaps too advanced in years to execute the office’s responsibilities for another four. Breaking it down, while 89% of Republican respondents shared this view, even the Democratic base showcased significant reservations, with 69% echoing the same concerns. Importantly, this isn’t an ageist perspective limited to the younger generation. Respondents from varied age groups expressed these concerns, although older Democrats were observed to be slightly more supportive of Biden’s potential 2024 candidacy. Drawing a parallel, roughly 50% of the surveyed U.S. adults opined that former President Trump might also be too old for the office. However, partisan lines were clearer here, with Democrats more inclined to emphasize Trump’s age as a disqualifying factor compared to Republicans. The AP-NORC poll, conducted from August 10 to 14, 2023, surveyed 1,165 adults and carries a margin of error of plus or minus 3.8 percentage points. One significant takeaway from the poll is a possible shift in public sentiment, leaning towards younger leadership as opposed to the seasoned 80-year-old Democrat currently helming the White House. This isn’t the first time concerns regarding Biden’s age have been raised. Being the oldest serving U.S. president, if Biden were to secure a reelection in 2024, he would exit office at the ripe age of 86 in 2029. In a similar vein, a Redfield &amp;amp; Wilton Strategies survey for Newsweek earlier in August accentuated these concerns. Their findings showcased a prevailing apprehension among Democrats regarding Biden’s ability to execute his duties. Interestingly, while most Biden voters acknowledged these concerns, there was even deeper division on whether his age should be a definitive factor against his candidacy. In another related study in June, nearly half of the independent voters expressed reservations about Biden’s age and health, suggesting that these could “severely limit” his capabilities as the President. An Economist-YouGov poll revealed that 45% of the adults surveyed were skeptical about the President’s health and age impacting his ability to perform his duties. As the 2024 elections loom, these age-related concerns are likely to play a pivotal role in shaping the political narratives and campaign strategies.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hidden Room Revelation - New Mexico Mother’s Disturbing Past Resurfaces in Colorado</title><link href="/news/2023/08/28/Hidden-Room-Revelation/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hidden Room Revelation - New Mexico Mother’s Disturbing Past Resurfaces in Colorado" /><published>2023-08-28T10:45:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-08-28T10:45:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/08/28/Hidden-Room-Revelation</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/08/28/Hidden-Room-Revelation/">&lt;p&gt;Authorities in Walsenburg, Colorado, have made a troubling discovery that links back to a notorious New Mexico mother with a history of child and animal abuse. &lt;strong&gt;Martha Crouch&lt;/strong&gt;, who had reportedly faked her own death and went missing in 2021, was found hiding in a concealed room behind a trailer wall.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The series of events unfolded when officials in Walsenburg received a call about a medical emergency, resulting in the discovery of 62-year-old Timothy Crouch dead on his lawn. While the cause of his death was initially believed to be related to pre-existing health concerns, further investigation revealed a far more complex narrative.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Martha, who had earlier pleaded guilty to heinous acts of abuse involving her children and animals, was subsequently linked to the residence in Colorado. Officials were denied access to the trailer home initially and were met with resistance when they attempted a welfare check. However, upon realizing that Martha had an outstanding felony warrant for her arrest in New Mexico, the sheriff’s office took action.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-dark-past-emerges&quot;&gt;A Dark Past Emerges&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Martha’s past is riddled with acts of severe cruelty. Accused by her own children of physical abuse using kitchen utensils, chaining them, causing a miscarriage through beating, and even shooting a child’s dog as a form of punishment, Martha’s history painted a grim picture. Shockingly, she was also said to have boiled puppies alive, a claim that was made before her 2019 plea deal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her association with the trailer home in Colorado became evident when the sheriff’s team uncovered a running oxygen tank, dentures, and old medicine bottles – all linked to her. An astute observation about potential “false walls” in the home led to the most disturbing revelation: a hidden room in the trailer, where Martha and a 14-year-old girl, previously unaccounted for in the past three years, were found alive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-current-situation&quot;&gt;The Current Situation&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The chilling discovery has added a new chapter to Martha Crouch’s already extensive criminal record. With the outstanding 2021 warrant against her for probation violation and new probable charges on the horizon, her path is leading straight to the courts once more. Currently, she is being held at the Huerfano County jail with a bond set at $5,000, awaiting potential extradition to New Mexico. The 14-year-old girl, meanwhile, has been placed under the Department of Social Services’ care.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It remains to be seen how the legal proceedings against Martha will unfold, but the uncovering of her hiding spot behind a trailer wall has brought to light further evidence of her disturbing actions and the dark secrets she hoped would remain hidden.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Authorities in Walsenburg, Colorado, have made a troubling discovery that links back to a notorious New Mexico mother with a history of child and animal abuse. Martha Crouch, who had reportedly faked her own death and went missing in 2021, was found hiding in a concealed room behind a trailer wall. The series of events unfolded when officials in Walsenburg received a call about a medical emergency, resulting in the discovery of 62-year-old Timothy Crouch dead on his lawn. While the cause of his death was initially believed to be related to pre-existing health concerns, further investigation revealed a far more complex narrative. Martha, who had earlier pleaded guilty to heinous acts of abuse involving her children and animals, was subsequently linked to the residence in Colorado. Officials were denied access to the trailer home initially and were met with resistance when they attempted a welfare check. However, upon realizing that Martha had an outstanding felony warrant for her arrest in New Mexico, the sheriff’s office took action. A Dark Past Emerges Martha’s past is riddled with acts of severe cruelty. Accused by her own children of physical abuse using kitchen utensils, chaining them, causing a miscarriage through beating, and even shooting a child’s dog as a form of punishment, Martha’s history painted a grim picture. Shockingly, she was also said to have boiled puppies alive, a claim that was made before her 2019 plea deal. Her association with the trailer home in Colorado became evident when the sheriff’s team uncovered a running oxygen tank, dentures, and old medicine bottles – all linked to her. An astute observation about potential “false walls” in the home led to the most disturbing revelation: a hidden room in the trailer, where Martha and a 14-year-old girl, previously unaccounted for in the past three years, were found alive. The Current Situation The chilling discovery has added a new chapter to Martha Crouch’s already extensive criminal record. With the outstanding 2021 warrant against her for probation violation and new probable charges on the horizon, her path is leading straight to the courts once more. Currently, she is being held at the Huerfano County jail with a bond set at $5,000, awaiting potential extradition to New Mexico. The 14-year-old girl, meanwhile, has been placed under the Department of Social Services’ care. It remains to be seen how the legal proceedings against Martha will unfold, but the uncovering of her hiding spot behind a trailer wall has brought to light further evidence of her disturbing actions and the dark secrets she hoped would remain hidden.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Farewell to Bob Barker - The TV Titan Who Defined a Generation</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/08/27/Legendary-Bob-Barker/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Farewell to Bob Barker - The TV Titan Who Defined a Generation" /><published>2023-08-27T17:15:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-08-27T17:15:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/08/27/Legendary-Bob-Barker</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/08/27/Legendary-Bob-Barker/">&lt;p&gt;Bob Barker, a towering figure in the annals of television history, passed away at 99. Known for his charismatic presence as the host of “The Price Is Right” and an ardent animal rights advocate, Barker’s impact on pop culture and animal welfare is indelible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Journey of 50 Years on Screen:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Starting as the captivating host of “The Price Is Right” in 1972, Barker’s stint continued until 2007. During this period, he bagged 19 Daytime Emmy awards, an achievement signifying his prowess in the industry. Beyond hosting, Barker also showcased his humor and acting chops in “Happy Gilmore,” in a memorable scene with Adam Sandler.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over a span of 35 years, Barker presided over 6,586 episodes of “The Price Is Right.” It wasn’t just about guessing product prices. With his affable nature, Barker became the heart of the show, inviting contestants with the iconic phrase, “Come on down!” His banter with participants, especially ones overtaken by excitement, became legendary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Legacy Beyond Television:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, Bob Barker wasn’t only about the glitz and glamour of TV. He was a passionate animal rights advocate. His contribution to the cause includes donating $5 million for the Bob Barker ship, operated by the Sea Shepherd Conservation Society. This vessel played a crucial role in preventing the slaughter of whales in Antarctica.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His pro-animal campaigns extended to the TV sets as well. Barker ensured his audience took home more than just entertainment. He regularly implored viewers to get their pets spayed and neutered. Moreover, Barker’s firm stance against animal cruelty led him to adopt vegetarianism in 1979 and quit hosting beauty pageants that used fur.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;An Unforgettable Presence:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apart from hosting, Barker made headlines with appearances in films and promotional videos, displaying his humorous and lively spirit. Whether it was “Happy Gilmore” or a faux brawl with Sandler for a promotional video at 91, Barker was inimitable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Barker’s journey, which began on Dec. 12, 1923, in Darrington, Washington, saw him transition from radio to the grandeur of television, defining a golden era for TV enthusiasts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While his wife, Dorothy, passed away in 1981, Barker chose not to remarry. As we bid adieu to this legend, it’s essential to recognize that Barker was more than just a TV personality; he was a cultural phenomenon whose legacy will continue to inspire and entertain generations.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Bob Barker, a towering figure in the annals of television history, passed away at 99. Known for his charismatic presence as the host of “The Price Is Right” and an ardent animal rights advocate, Barker’s impact on pop culture and animal welfare is indelible. A Journey of 50 Years on Screen: Starting as the captivating host of “The Price Is Right” in 1972, Barker’s stint continued until 2007. During this period, he bagged 19 Daytime Emmy awards, an achievement signifying his prowess in the industry. Beyond hosting, Barker also showcased his humor and acting chops in “Happy Gilmore,” in a memorable scene with Adam Sandler. Over a span of 35 years, Barker presided over 6,586 episodes of “The Price Is Right.” It wasn’t just about guessing product prices. With his affable nature, Barker became the heart of the show, inviting contestants with the iconic phrase, “Come on down!” His banter with participants, especially ones overtaken by excitement, became legendary. A Legacy Beyond Television: However, Bob Barker wasn’t only about the glitz and glamour of TV. He was a passionate animal rights advocate. His contribution to the cause includes donating $5 million for the Bob Barker ship, operated by the Sea Shepherd Conservation Society. This vessel played a crucial role in preventing the slaughter of whales in Antarctica. His pro-animal campaigns extended to the TV sets as well. Barker ensured his audience took home more than just entertainment. He regularly implored viewers to get their pets spayed and neutered. Moreover, Barker’s firm stance against animal cruelty led him to adopt vegetarianism in 1979 and quit hosting beauty pageants that used fur. An Unforgettable Presence: Apart from hosting, Barker made headlines with appearances in films and promotional videos, displaying his humorous and lively spirit. Whether it was “Happy Gilmore” or a faux brawl with Sandler for a promotional video at 91, Barker was inimitable. Barker’s journey, which began on Dec. 12, 1923, in Darrington, Washington, saw him transition from radio to the grandeur of television, defining a golden era for TV enthusiasts. While his wife, Dorothy, passed away in 1981, Barker chose not to remarry. As we bid adieu to this legend, it’s essential to recognize that Barker was more than just a TV personality; he was a cultural phenomenon whose legacy will continue to inspire and entertain generations.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Unraveling Threads - Canada Probes Global Giants for Alleged Ties to Uyghur Slavery</title><link href="/news/2023/08/27/Canada-Slavery-Investigation/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Unraveling Threads - Canada Probes Global Giants for Alleged Ties to Uyghur Slavery" /><published>2023-08-27T16:10:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-08-27T16:10:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/08/27/Canada-Slavery-Investigation</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/08/27/Canada-Slavery-Investigation/">&lt;p&gt;In a significant development, the Canadian Ombudsman for Responsible Enterprise (CORE) has declared its intent to investigate potential connections between the Canadian branches of global brands - Walmart, Hugo Boss, and Diesel, and the alleged use of Uyghur slavery in their supply chains.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CORE, a potent human rights watchdog, has the authority to scrutinize human rights infringements linked to global supply chains of corporations that operate within Canadian territory. Their interventions can be a result of referrals or be self-initiated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The latest move from CORE arises from accusations made by human rights groups suggesting that Chinese suppliers, associated with the aforementioned companies, might have tapped into the oppressed Uyghur Muslim workforce from East Turkistan, commonly referred to as Xinjiang by China.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given China’s dominant presence in the cotton industry - supplying a significant portion of global cotton, the fact that Xinjiang alone contributes to almost 90% of the country’s cotton output raises pertinent questions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The heart of the matter, Sheri Meyerhoffer, CORE’s primary spokesperson, highlights, revolves around the reluctance of the three giants, Walmart, Hugo Boss, and Diesel, to be part of a preliminary examination into reports of slavery. This impelled CORE to undertake a more comprehensive investigation. Meyerhoffer states, “We are hopeful that the investigation findings will provide the companies with information to support their ability to strengthen their due diligence practices.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While all three entities have fervently denied sourcing goods tinged by forced labor, a spokesperson for Hugo Boss went on record to state that they have no direct supply links originating from the Xinjiang region. However, past ties with the Changji Esquel Group, a prominent Chinese cotton supplier known to camouflage its Xinjiang-sourced cotton, are hard to ignore. Hugo Boss’s relationship with the supplier came to a silent end in early 2022.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, revelations from human rights alliances suggest evidence of intricate connections between Hugo Boss Canada and a subsidiary in Xinjiang, revealing a complex web of cotton sourcing and potential human rights infringements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Diesel, known for its fashion-forward stance, also finds itself in the crosshairs. Allegations point towards its business ties with Jiangsu Guotai Guosheng, another supplier purportedly employing Uyghur slaves. Similarly, Walmart’s dealings with multiple companies suspected of leveraging forced labor have come under the scanner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In response, Diesel emphasized its commitment to ethical sourcing, vowing to adhere to global human rights standards across its supply chain. Walmart Canada mirrored this stance, underlining its zero-tolerance policy towards any form of forced labor within its supply chain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, CORE remains undeterred. Comments on Diesel’s evasion from preliminary assessments raise “questions related to the degree of transparency in its human rights due diligence practices,” while Hugo Boss’s approach is criticized for not acknowledging the intricate nature of garment supply chains.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ongoing investigation underscores the importance of ethical sourcing and supply chain transparency in an increasingly interconnected global marketplace. As these big names await CORE’s findings, the world watches with bated breath, hoping for a future where human rights triumph over corporate interests.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a significant development, the Canadian Ombudsman for Responsible Enterprise (CORE) has declared its intent to investigate potential connections between the Canadian branches of global brands - Walmart, Hugo Boss, and Diesel, and the alleged use of Uyghur slavery in their supply chains. CORE, a potent human rights watchdog, has the authority to scrutinize human rights infringements linked to global supply chains of corporations that operate within Canadian territory. Their interventions can be a result of referrals or be self-initiated. The latest move from CORE arises from accusations made by human rights groups suggesting that Chinese suppliers, associated with the aforementioned companies, might have tapped into the oppressed Uyghur Muslim workforce from East Turkistan, commonly referred to as Xinjiang by China. Given China’s dominant presence in the cotton industry - supplying a significant portion of global cotton, the fact that Xinjiang alone contributes to almost 90% of the country’s cotton output raises pertinent questions. The heart of the matter, Sheri Meyerhoffer, CORE’s primary spokesperson, highlights, revolves around the reluctance of the three giants, Walmart, Hugo Boss, and Diesel, to be part of a preliminary examination into reports of slavery. This impelled CORE to undertake a more comprehensive investigation. Meyerhoffer states, “We are hopeful that the investigation findings will provide the companies with information to support their ability to strengthen their due diligence practices.” While all three entities have fervently denied sourcing goods tinged by forced labor, a spokesperson for Hugo Boss went on record to state that they have no direct supply links originating from the Xinjiang region. However, past ties with the Changji Esquel Group, a prominent Chinese cotton supplier known to camouflage its Xinjiang-sourced cotton, are hard to ignore. Hugo Boss’s relationship with the supplier came to a silent end in early 2022. Furthermore, revelations from human rights alliances suggest evidence of intricate connections between Hugo Boss Canada and a subsidiary in Xinjiang, revealing a complex web of cotton sourcing and potential human rights infringements. Diesel, known for its fashion-forward stance, also finds itself in the crosshairs. Allegations point towards its business ties with Jiangsu Guotai Guosheng, another supplier purportedly employing Uyghur slaves. Similarly, Walmart’s dealings with multiple companies suspected of leveraging forced labor have come under the scanner. In response, Diesel emphasized its commitment to ethical sourcing, vowing to adhere to global human rights standards across its supply chain. Walmart Canada mirrored this stance, underlining its zero-tolerance policy towards any form of forced labor within its supply chain. However, CORE remains undeterred. Comments on Diesel’s evasion from preliminary assessments raise “questions related to the degree of transparency in its human rights due diligence practices,” while Hugo Boss’s approach is criticized for not acknowledging the intricate nature of garment supply chains. The ongoing investigation underscores the importance of ethical sourcing and supply chain transparency in an increasingly interconnected global marketplace. As these big names await CORE’s findings, the world watches with bated breath, hoping for a future where human rights triumph over corporate interests.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump Campaign’s Financial Boost - Mugshot Adds Millions</title><link href="/politics/2023/08/27/Trump-Fundraising/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump Campaign’s Financial Boost - Mugshot Adds Millions" /><published>2023-08-27T15:49:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-08-27T15:49:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/08/27/Trump-Fundraising</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/08/27/Trump-Fundraising/">&lt;p&gt;The fundraising prowess of the Trump 2024 campaign demonstrated itself in a massive financial uptick following the release of Donald Trump’s mugshot. According to data provided by the Trump campaign to Fox News, the campaign has raked in nearly $20 million over the past three weeks. This fundraising surge aligns notably with the timeline of Trump’s federal indictment in Washington, D.C., and the now-infamous mugshot from Atlanta that’s making rounds globally.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The campaign shed light on the fact that out of the nearly $20 million, an impressive $7.1 million came in after Trump’s mugshot became public on Thursday evening. What’s even more intriguing is the record-breaking financial influx the next day – $4.18 million on Friday alone, making it the most lucrative day of Trump’s 2024 campaign thus far.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, this is not just about sympathy donations following the mugshot. The campaign reported: “Organic money has skyrocketed, especially after President Trump tweeted out the picture along with the website.” Moreover, it’s not only direct donations driving these numbers up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Merchandising, an old strength of Trump’s political brand, seems to have played its part. Shortly after Trump was taken into custody, the campaign was quick to seize the marketing opportunity. They began selling an array of products, ranging from shirts to posters and even beverage coolers, all branded with Trump’s mugshot. Accompanying these items is the emphatic tagline, “NEVER SURRENDER!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This fresh stream of merchandise sales, combined with direct contributions, indicates the campaign is likely to cross the $20 million fundraising threshold in just a matter of days. As the Trump campaign continues to capitalize on every event, it provides a vivid reminder of the unique political phenomenon that is Donald Trump, whose brand and appeal, for many of his supporters, seem only to grow stronger in the face of adversity.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">The fundraising prowess of the Trump 2024 campaign demonstrated itself in a massive financial uptick following the release of Donald Trump’s mugshot. According to data provided by the Trump campaign to Fox News, the campaign has raked in nearly $20 million over the past three weeks. This fundraising surge aligns notably with the timeline of Trump’s federal indictment in Washington, D.C., and the now-infamous mugshot from Atlanta that’s making rounds globally. The campaign shed light on the fact that out of the nearly $20 million, an impressive $7.1 million came in after Trump’s mugshot became public on Thursday evening. What’s even more intriguing is the record-breaking financial influx the next day – $4.18 million on Friday alone, making it the most lucrative day of Trump’s 2024 campaign thus far. Interestingly, this is not just about sympathy donations following the mugshot. The campaign reported: “Organic money has skyrocketed, especially after President Trump tweeted out the picture along with the website.” Moreover, it’s not only direct donations driving these numbers up. Merchandising, an old strength of Trump’s political brand, seems to have played its part. Shortly after Trump was taken into custody, the campaign was quick to seize the marketing opportunity. They began selling an array of products, ranging from shirts to posters and even beverage coolers, all branded with Trump’s mugshot. Accompanying these items is the emphatic tagline, “NEVER SURRENDER!” This fresh stream of merchandise sales, combined with direct contributions, indicates the campaign is likely to cross the $20 million fundraising threshold in just a matter of days. As the Trump campaign continues to capitalize on every event, it provides a vivid reminder of the unique political phenomenon that is Donald Trump, whose brand and appeal, for many of his supporters, seem only to grow stronger in the face of adversity.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Welded Open - The Curious Case of Arizona’s Border Wall Gates</title><link href="/news/2023/08/27/Arizona-Border/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welded Open - The Curious Case of Arizona’s Border Wall Gates" /><published>2023-08-27T14:30:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-08-27T14:30:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/08/27/Arizona-Border</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/08/27/Arizona-Border/">&lt;p&gt;A recent report has shone a spotlight on an alarming situation on the U.S.-Mexico border. The Biden administration, in what some critics view as a perplexing move, has allegedly welded border wall gates open near Lukeville, Arizona. This has paved the way for migrants to simply walk into the Arizona desert, unimpeded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to the &lt;em&gt;New York Post&lt;/em&gt;, Border Patrol officials eventually owned up to the decision to weld open flood gates in sections of the border wall near Lukeville. Initially, attempts were made to redirect blame onto other federal bodies. This move has coincided with a surge in migration, making this area the most active border sector in the country.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Data underscores the gravity of the situation. In July, the Tucson Sector marked the highest migrant apprehensions nationwide. With close to 40,000 migrants apprehended, it showed a dramatic hike - a whopping 136% over July 2022’s figures. Moreover, U.S. Customs and Border Protection reports indicate that the sector has been in the spotlight, with year-to-date apprehensions trailing only slightly, logging in an arrest of around 274,000 migrants. This represents a 59% jump from the previous year’s numbers for the same time span.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For many migrants, the unexpected opening came as a surprise. One migrant from Ecuador remarked, “We thought the agents were going to say something to us, but we just got in.” Meanwhile, a Cuban migrant found it easier to enter the U.S. than navigating through Mexico, expecting more security on the U.S. side.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The official reason for the gates in the border wall is to allow passage for monsoon-season floodwaters and migratory animals. CBP officials stated, “High water flow combined with excessive sediment and debris buildup can stress or comprise the design integrity of the barrier.” However, Brandon Judd, the President of the National Border Patrol Council, highlights the rapid adaptability of Mexican cartels. They swiftly identify these wall vulnerabilities and capitalize on them, monetizing these gaps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Judd expounds, “Because the cartels are constantly surveilling what we do, the moment something gets left open, it gets exploited.” The immediacy of the exploitation underlines the efficiency of these criminal cartels in leveraging any apparent lapses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;em&gt;New York Post&lt;/em&gt; feature was complemented by multiple photographs, vividly capturing the welded-open gates and migrants freely traversing through. One particularly jarring image showcases a steel spike affixed to the ground, ensuring the gate remains open.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the numbers indicating an uptick — from an average of 821 migrants apprehended daily in June to about 1,200 in July, and a projected 1,483 migrant apprehensions per day in the first fortnight of August — the question remains: Was this a calculated move or a mere oversight?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Only time will tell if the administration addresses these concerns and what measures, if any, will be implemented to manage the situation.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">A recent report has shone a spotlight on an alarming situation on the U.S.-Mexico border. The Biden administration, in what some critics view as a perplexing move, has allegedly welded border wall gates open near Lukeville, Arizona. This has paved the way for migrants to simply walk into the Arizona desert, unimpeded. According to the New York Post, Border Patrol officials eventually owned up to the decision to weld open flood gates in sections of the border wall near Lukeville. Initially, attempts were made to redirect blame onto other federal bodies. This move has coincided with a surge in migration, making this area the most active border sector in the country. Data underscores the gravity of the situation. In July, the Tucson Sector marked the highest migrant apprehensions nationwide. With close to 40,000 migrants apprehended, it showed a dramatic hike - a whopping 136% over July 2022’s figures. Moreover, U.S. Customs and Border Protection reports indicate that the sector has been in the spotlight, with year-to-date apprehensions trailing only slightly, logging in an arrest of around 274,000 migrants. This represents a 59% jump from the previous year’s numbers for the same time span. For many migrants, the unexpected opening came as a surprise. One migrant from Ecuador remarked, “We thought the agents were going to say something to us, but we just got in.” Meanwhile, a Cuban migrant found it easier to enter the U.S. than navigating through Mexico, expecting more security on the U.S. side. The official reason for the gates in the border wall is to allow passage for monsoon-season floodwaters and migratory animals. CBP officials stated, “High water flow combined with excessive sediment and debris buildup can stress or comprise the design integrity of the barrier.” However, Brandon Judd, the President of the National Border Patrol Council, highlights the rapid adaptability of Mexican cartels. They swiftly identify these wall vulnerabilities and capitalize on them, monetizing these gaps. Judd expounds, “Because the cartels are constantly surveilling what we do, the moment something gets left open, it gets exploited.” The immediacy of the exploitation underlines the efficiency of these criminal cartels in leveraging any apparent lapses. The New York Post feature was complemented by multiple photographs, vividly capturing the welded-open gates and migrants freely traversing through. One particularly jarring image showcases a steel spike affixed to the ground, ensuring the gate remains open. With the numbers indicating an uptick — from an average of 821 migrants apprehended daily in June to about 1,200 in July, and a projected 1,483 migrant apprehensions per day in the first fortnight of August — the question remains: Was this a calculated move or a mere oversight? Only time will tell if the administration addresses these concerns and what measures, if any, will be implemented to manage the situation.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Two Years On - The Kabul Airport Tragedy That Shook America</title><link href="/politics/2023/08/27/Lawmakers-Reflect-Afghanistan/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Two Years On - The Kabul Airport Tragedy That Shook America" /><published>2023-08-27T13:15:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-08-27T13:15:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/08/27/Lawmakers-Reflect-Afghanistan</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/08/27/Lawmakers-Reflect-Afghanistan/">&lt;p&gt;Two years have passed since a fateful day in Afghanistan. The nation remembers the 13 brave U.S. service members who lost their lives during a tragic suicide bombing amid what many call the Biden administration’s “disastrous” and “botched” withdrawal from the country.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the second anniversary of this devastating event, lawmakers from all sides took to social media platforms to commemorate the service and sacrifice of those who lost their lives in Kabul’s Hamid Karzai International Airport. The attack not only took 13 American lives but also resulted in injuries to almost two dozen others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The tragedy saw 10 Marines, two Army soldiers, and a Navy corpsman fall victim to an assault that will remain etched in the nation’s memory. The bombing was followed by a shootout initiated by Islamic State militants, exacerbating the chaos outside Kabul’s airport. The preceding night saw nearly 5,000 Afghans, alongside potential Americans, trying to access the airport in a desperate attempt to flee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;U.S. Representative Rob Wittman pointed out the significance of the date, stating, “Two years ago today, we witnessed the deadliest attack on U.S. forces in over a decade.” Adding fuel to the already heated topic, he highlighted that no member of the Biden administration has yet been held accountable for their handling of the Afghanistan withdrawal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Echoing this sentiment, House GOP conference chair Elise Stefanik honored the brave 13, criticizing President Biden’s withdrawal strategy as the direct reason for the “deadliest attack on Americans in Afghanistan since 2011.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;House Armed Services Committee Chair Rep. Mike Rogers took the criticism a step further, expressing it was “unfathomable” that no one from the Biden administration faced consequences for the mismanaged retreat. Rep. Steve Womack and several other leaders joined the chorus, emphasizing the importance of remembering the fallen heroes and ensuring accountability for the tragedy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But amidst the political wrangling, it’s essential to remember the sacrifice of these 13 brave souls. As the nation recalls the Kabul airport attack, it serves as a reminder of the cost of freedom and the sacrifice made by those who defend it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the words of Rep. Cory Mills, the day is not just about holding leaders accountable, but also standing with the “Gold Star families” and demanding transparency. It’s about remembering, honoring, and ensuring that such a tragedy is never repeated.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Two years have passed since a fateful day in Afghanistan. The nation remembers the 13 brave U.S. service members who lost their lives during a tragic suicide bombing amid what many call the Biden administration’s “disastrous” and “botched” withdrawal from the country. On the second anniversary of this devastating event, lawmakers from all sides took to social media platforms to commemorate the service and sacrifice of those who lost their lives in Kabul’s Hamid Karzai International Airport. The attack not only took 13 American lives but also resulted in injuries to almost two dozen others. The tragedy saw 10 Marines, two Army soldiers, and a Navy corpsman fall victim to an assault that will remain etched in the nation’s memory. The bombing was followed by a shootout initiated by Islamic State militants, exacerbating the chaos outside Kabul’s airport. The preceding night saw nearly 5,000 Afghans, alongside potential Americans, trying to access the airport in a desperate attempt to flee. U.S. Representative Rob Wittman pointed out the significance of the date, stating, “Two years ago today, we witnessed the deadliest attack on U.S. forces in over a decade.” Adding fuel to the already heated topic, he highlighted that no member of the Biden administration has yet been held accountable for their handling of the Afghanistan withdrawal. Echoing this sentiment, House GOP conference chair Elise Stefanik honored the brave 13, criticizing President Biden’s withdrawal strategy as the direct reason for the “deadliest attack on Americans in Afghanistan since 2011.” House Armed Services Committee Chair Rep. Mike Rogers took the criticism a step further, expressing it was “unfathomable” that no one from the Biden administration faced consequences for the mismanaged retreat. Rep. Steve Womack and several other leaders joined the chorus, emphasizing the importance of remembering the fallen heroes and ensuring accountability for the tragedy. But amidst the political wrangling, it’s essential to remember the sacrifice of these 13 brave souls. As the nation recalls the Kabul airport attack, it serves as a reminder of the cost of freedom and the sacrifice made by those who defend it. In the words of Rep. Cory Mills, the day is not just about holding leaders accountable, but also standing with the “Gold Star families” and demanding transparency. It’s about remembering, honoring, and ensuring that such a tragedy is never repeated.</summary></entry></feed>