<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-08-25T09:24:58-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/08/25/2023-08-10-King-of-the-Hill-Actor-Johnny-Hardwick-Passes/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-08-25T09:24:58-04:00</published><updated>2023-08-25T09:24:58-04:00</updated><id>/2023/08/25/2023-08-10-King-of-the-Hill-Actor-Johnny-Hardwick-Passes</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/08/25/2023-08-10-King-of-the-Hill-Actor-Johnny-Hardwick-Passes/">&lt;p&gt;The entertainment industry is mourning the loss of Johnny Hardwick, the acclaimed voice actor renowned for his portrayal of Dale Gribble in the popular animated series “King of the Hill.” At the age of 64, Hardwick’s demise has left many in shock.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The distressing news was confirmed by the Austin (Texas) Police Department, which attended a welfare check on Tuesday, leading to the tragic discovery of Hardwick’s lifeless body. While the circumstances surrounding his death are still shrouded in mystery, the Austin police have categorically stated that it isn’t a homicide case. Further details pertaining to the cause will be unveiled once the Travis County Medical Examiner finalizes their findings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hardwick’s role as Dale Gribble began in 1997 with the show’s premiere episode and lasted until its conclusion in 2010, spanning an impressive 259 episodes. His outstanding contribution to “King of the Hill” earned him an Emmy Award in 1999, followed by nominations in 2001 and 2002. The animated masterpiece was the brainchild of creators Mike Judge and Greg Daniels, with a cast ensemble including talents like Judge himself, Kathy Najimy, Stephen Root, and Pamela Adlon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earlier this year, fans rejoiced upon learning about a forthcoming revival of “King of the Hill,” with Hardwick’s involvement confirmed. Craig Erwich, the executive at the helm of ABC Entertainment, Hulu, and Disney Branded Television Streaming Originals, expressed enthusiasm about resuming the show’s narrative to reflect on our contemporary world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond his notable voice acting career, Hardwick was also a gifted stand-up comedian, making a mark in the comedy circuits during the 1990s.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/08/25/2023-08-12-Ian-Watkins-Assault/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-08-25T09:24:58-04:00</published><updated>2023-08-25T09:24:58-04:00</updated><id>/2023/08/25/2023-08-12-Ian-Watkins-Assault</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/08/25/2023-08-12-Ian-Watkins-Assault/">&lt;p&gt;Ian Watkins, the controversial former lead singer of the rock band Lostprophets, faced a brutal assault inside HMP Wakefield, where he’s currently serving a 29-year sentence for grave child sex crimes. According to sources, Watkins is in critical condition following the incident.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reports from the Mirror shed light on the gruesome nature of the assault. Allegedly, Watkins was accosted and held hostage by three inmates, subjected to hours of physical abuse, and eventually stabbed multiple times. Officers discovered the critically injured singer only hours later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Watkins was held for a lengthy period by the prisoners and endured a severe beating before the stabbing. The entire ordeal is under investigation,” conveyed the officials from HMP Wakefield. Fortunately, in a subsequent update from law enforcement, it was clarified that Watkins’ injuries, while severe, were not life-threatening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lostprophets, active from the late ’90s to the early 2000s, witnessed their downfall following the shocking revelations of Watkins’ depravities. In 2013, he faced charges for thirteen appalling sex offenses against children, which included the attempted rape of a one-year-old girl. The case revealed that Watkins administered drugs to children, plotting their sexual abuse, and even filmed some of his heinous acts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Confronted with overwhelming evidence, Watkins pleaded guilty to multiple counts of rape, sex with minors, and the possession of disturbing explicit content. His conviction in December 2013 led to the disintegration of the Lostprophets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jo Mjadzelics, one of Watkins’ former partners, expressed her shock at the recent attack, stating to the Mirror, “It’s surprising that such a brutal attack took so long, especially in a prison like Wakefield.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The broader implications of the attack on Watkins underline the volatile dynamics within prison systems, especially for individuals convicted of particularly reviled crimes. The repercussions of his crimes, it seems, continue to echo both for Watkins and for those who were once associated with him.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump Stands Tall - Surrenders to Fulton County Jail</title><link href="/politics/2023/08/25/Trump-Support/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump Stands Tall - Surrenders to Fulton County Jail" /><published>2023-08-25T09:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-08-25T09:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/08/25/Trump-Support</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/08/25/Trump-Support/">&lt;p&gt;In an unprecedented event in American history, former President Donald Trump surrendered to the Fulton County Jail in Atlanta on Thursday. His unwavering strength and commitment to the legal process exemplified his consistent dedication to the nation, even amidst challenging circumstances.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unwavering in the Face of Adversity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This move marks a historic event as it’s the first time a former U.S. president has been booked. The charges relate to Trump’s alleged efforts regarding the 2020 presidential election results in Georgia. The 13 counts span from violations of the Georgia RICO Act to allegations of conspiracies to commit various offenses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it’s worth noting that Thursday’s surrender was not his first brush with legal complexities this year. Trump faced similar situations multiple times but remained consistent in adhering to legal protocols, emphasizing his faith in the country’s justice system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Supporters Rally, Demonstrating Undying Loyalty&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As news spread of Trump’s imminent surrender, supporters gathered outside the Fulton County Jail, showcasing a vast sea of loyalty and solidarity. The atmosphere outside the jail was palpable, emphasizing the strong connection between the former president and his loyal base, which has remained steadfast through highs and lows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump’s co-defendants, including renowned figures like Rudy Giuliani, Sidney Powell, and Jenna Ellis, followed a similar path, turning themselves in at the jail earlier in the week. The united front displayed by Trump and his close allies stands as a testament to their commitment to face challenges head-on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Short Stay and a Future of Possibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After flying into Atlanta, Trump’s stay at the jail was brief, lasting about 20 minutes post his surrender. As the situation unfolds, it remains to be seen how the legal proceedings progress. However, one thing remains clear – Trump’s determination and the unwavering support of his base will continue to be influential factors in American politics.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In an unprecedented event in American history, former President Donald Trump surrendered to the Fulton County Jail in Atlanta on Thursday. His unwavering strength and commitment to the legal process exemplified his consistent dedication to the nation, even amidst challenging circumstances. Unwavering in the Face of Adversity This move marks a historic event as it’s the first time a former U.S. president has been booked. The charges relate to Trump’s alleged efforts regarding the 2020 presidential election results in Georgia. The 13 counts span from violations of the Georgia RICO Act to allegations of conspiracies to commit various offenses. However, it’s worth noting that Thursday’s surrender was not his first brush with legal complexities this year. Trump faced similar situations multiple times but remained consistent in adhering to legal protocols, emphasizing his faith in the country’s justice system. Supporters Rally, Demonstrating Undying Loyalty As news spread of Trump’s imminent surrender, supporters gathered outside the Fulton County Jail, showcasing a vast sea of loyalty and solidarity. The atmosphere outside the jail was palpable, emphasizing the strong connection between the former president and his loyal base, which has remained steadfast through highs and lows. Trump’s co-defendants, including renowned figures like Rudy Giuliani, Sidney Powell, and Jenna Ellis, followed a similar path, turning themselves in at the jail earlier in the week. The united front displayed by Trump and his close allies stands as a testament to their commitment to face challenges head-on. A Short Stay and a Future of Possibilities After flying into Atlanta, Trump’s stay at the jail was brief, lasting about 20 minutes post his surrender. As the situation unfolds, it remains to be seen how the legal proceedings progress. However, one thing remains clear – Trump’s determination and the unwavering support of his base will continue to be influential factors in American politics.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">UFO Revelations - Congress Presses for Truth on Secret Programs</title><link href="/news/2023/08/24/UFO-Secrets/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="UFO Revelations - Congress Presses for Truth on Secret Programs" /><published>2023-08-24T21:45:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-08-24T21:45:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/08/24/UFO-Secrets</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/08/24/UFO-Secrets/">&lt;p&gt;Lawmakers are demanding transparency from the intelligence community about alleged covert operations concerning UFOs - specifically, the retrieval of crashed UFOs and subsequent efforts to reverse-engineer their technology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whistleblower David Grusch has made significant claims under oath regarding such secret programs. During a House Oversight Committee hearing on July 26, Grusch suggested that the government has been engaging in such activities for decades. Yet, due to ongoing reprisal cases against him, Grusch refrained from divulging further details in the public hearing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The push for truth intensified as six Congress members, including Reps. Tim Burchett (R-Tenn.), Jared Moskowitz (D-Florida), Anna Paulina Luna (R-Florida), Nancy Mace (R-S.C.), Eric Burlison (R-Mo.), and Andy Ogles (R-Tenn), jointly signed a letter on August 21 to Inspector General Thomas Monheim, seeking answers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the controversial UAP hearing, Grusch, a former intelligence officer and Air Force veteran, claimed firsthand knowledge about the existence of UFO technology and “biologics” of “non-human origins” dating back to the 1930s. He attested that he could provide details, albeit in a classified setting. Following the hearing, Grusch’s personal medical records surfaced in a move seen by many as an attempt to discredit his testimony.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ross Coulthart, the reporter who initially covered Grusch’s statements about a concealed UFO-retrieval operation, posted Grusch’s full remarks on Twitter on August 8. This elicited a fervent response from Rep. Burchett, condemning the leak of Grusch’s medical details as a desperate ploy to conceal the truth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The July 26 hearing also featured testimony from former military pilots, Ryan Graves and David Fravor, who recounted their encounters with unidentified anomalous phenomena (UAP) while airborne. Fravor, a retired Navy pilot, described observing the now-infamous “Tic Tac UFO” during a 2004 training mission.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Concluding a two-hour-long hearing on July 26, Rep. Ogles expressed concerns about the potential national security implications. This concern has led to bipartisan efforts in the Senate to declassify and release UFO-related documents, uniting political adversaries in a quest for truth about these unidentified phenomena.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Lawmakers are demanding transparency from the intelligence community about alleged covert operations concerning UFOs - specifically, the retrieval of crashed UFOs and subsequent efforts to reverse-engineer their technology. Whistleblower David Grusch has made significant claims under oath regarding such secret programs. During a House Oversight Committee hearing on July 26, Grusch suggested that the government has been engaging in such activities for decades. Yet, due to ongoing reprisal cases against him, Grusch refrained from divulging further details in the public hearing. The push for truth intensified as six Congress members, including Reps. Tim Burchett (R-Tenn.), Jared Moskowitz (D-Florida), Anna Paulina Luna (R-Florida), Nancy Mace (R-S.C.), Eric Burlison (R-Mo.), and Andy Ogles (R-Tenn), jointly signed a letter on August 21 to Inspector General Thomas Monheim, seeking answers. During the controversial UAP hearing, Grusch, a former intelligence officer and Air Force veteran, claimed firsthand knowledge about the existence of UFO technology and “biologics” of “non-human origins” dating back to the 1930s. He attested that he could provide details, albeit in a classified setting. Following the hearing, Grusch’s personal medical records surfaced in a move seen by many as an attempt to discredit his testimony. Ross Coulthart, the reporter who initially covered Grusch’s statements about a concealed UFO-retrieval operation, posted Grusch’s full remarks on Twitter on August 8. This elicited a fervent response from Rep. Burchett, condemning the leak of Grusch’s medical details as a desperate ploy to conceal the truth. The July 26 hearing also featured testimony from former military pilots, Ryan Graves and David Fravor, who recounted their encounters with unidentified anomalous phenomena (UAP) while airborne. Fravor, a retired Navy pilot, described observing the now-infamous “Tic Tac UFO” during a 2004 training mission. Concluding a two-hour-long hearing on July 26, Rep. Ogles expressed concerns about the potential national security implications. This concern has led to bipartisan efforts in the Senate to declassify and release UFO-related documents, uniting political adversaries in a quest for truth about these unidentified phenomena.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump’s Top Priority - A Watertight US Border</title><link href="/politics/2023/08/24/Trump-Border-Issue/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump’s Top Priority - A Watertight US Border" /><published>2023-08-24T20:35:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-08-24T20:35:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/08/24/Trump-Border-Issue</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/08/24/Trump-Border-Issue/">&lt;p&gt;Amidst the whirlwind of political events, former President Donald Trump made headlines once again in an exclusive interview with Tucker Carlson. In what seemed to be counter-programming to the first Republican primary debate, Trump voiced his most pressing concern: the southern border.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Top Concern Amidst Global Issues&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When Carlson probed about his prime priority if re-elected, Trump was quick to spotlight the border. “Let’s say number one is a border and taking hundreds of thousands of criminals that have been allowed into our country and getting them out and bringing them back to their country,” he stated. This reveals Trump’s consistent focus on border security, echoing his previous election’s commitments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Multinational Migration Concern&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump continued to detail the diversity of the migrants, mentioning, “Last month, we had 149 countries represented.” He emphasized the influx from regions some might find surprising, elaborating on the various origins and backgrounds of the immigrants. According to Trump, not only South American prisons but also mental institutions are being emptied out, resulting in a mix of individuals entering the US.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Promise for a Stronger Border&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Revisiting his previous term, Trump proudly stated the achievements on border control, highlighting the construction of nearly 500 miles of wall. Challenging the narratives that downplay his accomplishments, he emphasized, “I built 500 miles.” He also alluded to plans for an additional 200-mile extension that was halted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In his concluding remarks, the former president laid out a promise familiar to his previous election campaigns, with a renewed vigor: “The first thing I would do would be, I would seal up the border good and tight, except for people that want to come in legally,” assuring Americans of his undeterred focus on border security.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Amidst the whirlwind of political events, former President Donald Trump made headlines once again in an exclusive interview with Tucker Carlson. In what seemed to be counter-programming to the first Republican primary debate, Trump voiced his most pressing concern: the southern border. A Top Concern Amidst Global Issues When Carlson probed about his prime priority if re-elected, Trump was quick to spotlight the border. “Let’s say number one is a border and taking hundreds of thousands of criminals that have been allowed into our country and getting them out and bringing them back to their country,” he stated. This reveals Trump’s consistent focus on border security, echoing his previous election’s commitments. A Multinational Migration Concern Trump continued to detail the diversity of the migrants, mentioning, “Last month, we had 149 countries represented.” He emphasized the influx from regions some might find surprising, elaborating on the various origins and backgrounds of the immigrants. According to Trump, not only South American prisons but also mental institutions are being emptied out, resulting in a mix of individuals entering the US. A Promise for a Stronger Border Revisiting his previous term, Trump proudly stated the achievements on border control, highlighting the construction of nearly 500 miles of wall. Challenging the narratives that downplay his accomplishments, he emphasized, “I built 500 miles.” He also alluded to plans for an additional 200-mile extension that was halted. In his concluding remarks, the former president laid out a promise familiar to his previous election campaigns, with a renewed vigor: “The first thing I would do would be, I would seal up the border good and tight, except for people that want to come in legally,” assuring Americans of his undeterred focus on border security.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Fresh Leads in BTK Serial Killer’s Legacy - New Findings from Former Kansas Property</title><link href="/news/2023/08/24/BTK-Investigation/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Fresh Leads in BTK Serial Killer’s Legacy - New Findings from Former Kansas Property" /><published>2023-08-24T19:07:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-08-24T19:07:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/08/24/BTK-Investigation</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/08/24/BTK-Investigation/">&lt;p&gt;In a recent revelation exclusive to Fox News, law enforcement officials have discovered “items of interest” during a two-day search operation at the erstwhile Park City, Kansas, residence of the infamous BTK serial killer, Dennis Rader.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;digging-deeper-into-cold-cases&quot;&gt;Digging Deeper into Cold Cases&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While investigating unsolved murders and chilling disappearances, authorities were drawn to Rader’s former property. Osage County Sheriff Eddie Virden expressed to Fox News Digital: “Through the investigation, we developed information of some possible trophies of Dennis Rader’s. Following up on those leads with Park City, we did recover some items of interest.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The current probe specifically throws light on the mysterious 1976 disappearance of Cynthia “Cyndi” Dawn Kinney in Osage County, Oklahoma. Given the proximity to Rader’s activities during that period, investigators are delving into potential connections between him and other unresolved cases.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;kinneys-disappearance-and-raders-denial&quot;&gt;Kinney’s Disappearance and Rader’s Denial&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kinney’s last known whereabouts trace back to her aunt and uncle’s laundromat in Pawhuska, a mere two-hour commute from Rader’s residence at the time. While Rader confessed and was convicted for 10 murders following his 2005 apprehension, he vehemently denies any association with other crimes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Referring to the recent findings, Sheriff Virden commented, “We weren’t looking for bodies, we were looking for items. We did find some items. We can’t release what they are.” It remains ambiguous whether this evidence ties back to Rader’s confessed crimes or unveils new skeletons in his closet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;trophies-buried-in-the-past&quot;&gt;Trophies Buried in the Past?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rader’s proclivity for “trophies” from his victims came into sharp focus as his daughter, Kerri Rawson, hinted at the possibility of concealed evidence on the property. “The theory is he could have placed evidence of cases under stone pavers under the metal shed he built early to mid ’90s, like drivers licenses in jars,” she mused.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As anticipation builds, authorities are gearing up to share more insights later today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;treading-with-empathy&quot;&gt;Treading with Empathy&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the investigation progresses, authorities are mindful of the trauma revisited by the victims’ families. Sheriff Virden empathetically remarked, “Our concern is more for the families. I hate tearing open old wounds, but we’ve still got to follow the leads we’ve got, where they go, and we’ll try and be as respectful as we can to everybody involved and still do our job.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the world watches, the hope remains that these findings provide closure to families and unravel the remaining mysteries surrounding the BTK killer’s dark legacy.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a recent revelation exclusive to Fox News, law enforcement officials have discovered “items of interest” during a two-day search operation at the erstwhile Park City, Kansas, residence of the infamous BTK serial killer, Dennis Rader. Digging Deeper into Cold Cases While investigating unsolved murders and chilling disappearances, authorities were drawn to Rader’s former property. Osage County Sheriff Eddie Virden expressed to Fox News Digital: “Through the investigation, we developed information of some possible trophies of Dennis Rader’s. Following up on those leads with Park City, we did recover some items of interest.” The current probe specifically throws light on the mysterious 1976 disappearance of Cynthia “Cyndi” Dawn Kinney in Osage County, Oklahoma. Given the proximity to Rader’s activities during that period, investigators are delving into potential connections between him and other unresolved cases. Kinney’s Disappearance and Rader’s Denial Kinney’s last known whereabouts trace back to her aunt and uncle’s laundromat in Pawhuska, a mere two-hour commute from Rader’s residence at the time. While Rader confessed and was convicted for 10 murders following his 2005 apprehension, he vehemently denies any association with other crimes. Referring to the recent findings, Sheriff Virden commented, “We weren’t looking for bodies, we were looking for items. We did find some items. We can’t release what they are.” It remains ambiguous whether this evidence ties back to Rader’s confessed crimes or unveils new skeletons in his closet. Trophies Buried in the Past? Rader’s proclivity for “trophies” from his victims came into sharp focus as his daughter, Kerri Rawson, hinted at the possibility of concealed evidence on the property. “The theory is he could have placed evidence of cases under stone pavers under the metal shed he built early to mid ’90s, like drivers licenses in jars,” she mused. As anticipation builds, authorities are gearing up to share more insights later today. Treading with Empathy While the investigation progresses, authorities are mindful of the trauma revisited by the victims’ families. Sheriff Virden empathetically remarked, “Our concern is more for the families. I hate tearing open old wounds, but we’ve still got to follow the leads we’ve got, where they go, and we’ll try and be as respectful as we can to everybody involved and still do our job.” As the world watches, the hope remains that these findings provide closure to families and unravel the remaining mysteries surrounding the BTK killer’s dark legacy.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Trump Dilemma - GOP Candidates Grapple with Loyalty Questions</title><link href="/politics/2023/08/24/Trump-Debate-Question/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Trump Dilemma - GOP Candidates Grapple with Loyalty Questions" /><published>2023-08-24T18:15:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-08-24T18:15:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/08/24/Trump-Debate-Question</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/08/24/Trump-Debate-Question/">&lt;p&gt;In a dramatic turn during Wednesday’s GOP debate, the proverbial elephant in the room - former President Donald Trump’s looming indictments - came front and center.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Direct Confrontation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The intensity peaked almost an hour into the debate when Fox News Channel showcased a live feed from Atlanta’s Fulton County jail, the very location where Trump is slated to turn himself in on Thursday. This visual, met with a chorus of boos from the audience, made it clear: Trump’s legal troubles couldn’t be ignored, even if he wasn’t present at the debate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Addressing the conspicuous absence, the moderators took a bold step, choosing to allocate a “brief moment about the elephant not in the room” to discuss the charges against the former president.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Test of Allegiance&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The candidates, already on their toes, were then presented with a direct and potentially divisive query. Would they support Trump if he emerged as the GOP presidential nominee, despite his legal entanglements? The responses were mixed, revealing the nuances and divisions within the party. Six candidates showcased unambiguous support by raising their hands. However, Chris Christie’s tentative half-raise and Asa Hutchinson’s refusal to lift his hand spoke volumes about the intricacies of the current political landscape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s important to note that all candidates had previously committed to support the eventual GOP nominee by signing a pledge prior to the debate. This gesture was seen as a unity move, emphasizing solidarity within the party. Yet, when confronted with the real-time implications of that pledge, reactions were varied.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Defining Moment for the GOP&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The GOP stands at a crossroads. With Trump’s indictments casting a long shadow, the party grapples with its identity and the weight of its past endorsements. This debate and the allegiances shown, or withheld, might very well shape the trajectory of the Republican party in the 2024 elections and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a dramatic turn during Wednesday’s GOP debate, the proverbial elephant in the room - former President Donald Trump’s looming indictments - came front and center. A Direct Confrontation The intensity peaked almost an hour into the debate when Fox News Channel showcased a live feed from Atlanta’s Fulton County jail, the very location where Trump is slated to turn himself in on Thursday. This visual, met with a chorus of boos from the audience, made it clear: Trump’s legal troubles couldn’t be ignored, even if he wasn’t present at the debate. Addressing the conspicuous absence, the moderators took a bold step, choosing to allocate a “brief moment about the elephant not in the room” to discuss the charges against the former president. A Test of Allegiance The candidates, already on their toes, were then presented with a direct and potentially divisive query. Would they support Trump if he emerged as the GOP presidential nominee, despite his legal entanglements? The responses were mixed, revealing the nuances and divisions within the party. Six candidates showcased unambiguous support by raising their hands. However, Chris Christie’s tentative half-raise and Asa Hutchinson’s refusal to lift his hand spoke volumes about the intricacies of the current political landscape. It’s important to note that all candidates had previously committed to support the eventual GOP nominee by signing a pledge prior to the debate. This gesture was seen as a unity move, emphasizing solidarity within the party. Yet, when confronted with the real-time implications of that pledge, reactions were varied. A Defining Moment for the GOP The GOP stands at a crossroads. With Trump’s indictments casting a long shadow, the party grapples with its identity and the weight of its past endorsements. This debate and the allegiances shown, or withheld, might very well shape the trajectory of the Republican party in the 2024 elections and beyond.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Iran’s New Drone Power Play - Mohajer-10 Unveiled With Striking Resemblance to US’s MQ-9 Reaper</title><link href="/news/2023/08/24/Iranian-Drone/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Iran’s New Drone Power Play - Mohajer-10 Unveiled With Striking Resemblance to US’s MQ-9 Reaper" /><published>2023-08-24T17:04:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-08-24T17:04:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/08/24/Iranian-Drone</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/08/24/Iranian-Drone/">&lt;p&gt;In a move that underscores its technological ambitions, Iran unveiled its newest armed drone on Tuesday, the Mohajer-10. Strikingly, this drone bears a close resemblance to America’s renowned MQ-9 Reaper. Moreover, state media sources are asserting that this new addition to Iran’s aerial arsenal has the operational prowess to reach as far as Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;showcasing-the-mohajer-10&quot;&gt;Showcasing the Mohajer-10&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The debut of the Mohajer-10 took place during an event marking the Islamic Republic’s Defense Industry Day. The drone’s specs, as outlined by the state-run IRNA News Agency, are certainly impressive. It can continuously soar the skies for 24 hours and has an operational reach of approximately 1,200 miles. The Mohajer-10 is also capable of bearing a bomb load that weighs up to 660 pounds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In terms of speed, this drone can hit a peak of 130 mph and, according to IRNA, is furnished with “electronic warfare and intelligence-gathering systems.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-iranian-stance&quot;&gt;The Iranian Stance&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the event, Iranian President Ebrahim Raisi lauded the country’s technological achievements, proclaiming on state television: “Today, we can firmly introduce Iran as an advanced and technologic nation to the world.” Footage disseminated by IRNA illustrated the drone making its rounds on a moving platform, with subsequent visuals showing it allegedly taking off from an unspecified location.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the veracity of this footage is yet to be ascertained independently.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;historical-context&quot;&gt;Historical Context&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The nomenclature “Mohajer” translates to “immigrant” in Farsi. The Mohajer-10 represents the newest generation in a drone series that Iran has been producing since 1985. Historically, Iran has managed to capture U.S. drones or parts of them. However, no proof currently indicates Iran’s possession of a General Atomics’ Reaper.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s worth noting that in the past, North Korea had flaunted drones echoing the Reaper’s design, presumably based on publicly accessible data about the aircraft.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;looking-back&quot;&gt;Looking Back&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Iran’s history with drones, particularly those of the U.S., has been marked by contentious incidents. In December 2011, the nation intercepted an RQ-170 Sentinel operated by the CIA, purposed to survey Iranian nuclear establishments. This drone had breached Iranian airspace from the adjacent Afghanistan. Subsequent to this event, Iran reverse-engineered the drone, crafting their indigenous versions. Additionally, in 2019, during escalating tensions over a defunct nuclear agreement with global superpowers, Iran brought down a U.S. Navy RQ-4A Global Hawk in the Strait of Hormuz.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The unveiling of the Mohajer-10 is a clear testament to Iran’s growing technological might and its determination to be a significant player in global aerial warfare.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a move that underscores its technological ambitions, Iran unveiled its newest armed drone on Tuesday, the Mohajer-10. Strikingly, this drone bears a close resemblance to America’s renowned MQ-9 Reaper. Moreover, state media sources are asserting that this new addition to Iran’s aerial arsenal has the operational prowess to reach as far as Israel. Showcasing the Mohajer-10 The debut of the Mohajer-10 took place during an event marking the Islamic Republic’s Defense Industry Day. The drone’s specs, as outlined by the state-run IRNA News Agency, are certainly impressive. It can continuously soar the skies for 24 hours and has an operational reach of approximately 1,200 miles. The Mohajer-10 is also capable of bearing a bomb load that weighs up to 660 pounds. In terms of speed, this drone can hit a peak of 130 mph and, according to IRNA, is furnished with “electronic warfare and intelligence-gathering systems.” The Iranian Stance During the event, Iranian President Ebrahim Raisi lauded the country’s technological achievements, proclaiming on state television: “Today, we can firmly introduce Iran as an advanced and technologic nation to the world.” Footage disseminated by IRNA illustrated the drone making its rounds on a moving platform, with subsequent visuals showing it allegedly taking off from an unspecified location. However, the veracity of this footage is yet to be ascertained independently. Historical Context The nomenclature “Mohajer” translates to “immigrant” in Farsi. The Mohajer-10 represents the newest generation in a drone series that Iran has been producing since 1985. Historically, Iran has managed to capture U.S. drones or parts of them. However, no proof currently indicates Iran’s possession of a General Atomics’ Reaper. It’s worth noting that in the past, North Korea had flaunted drones echoing the Reaper’s design, presumably based on publicly accessible data about the aircraft. Looking Back Iran’s history with drones, particularly those of the U.S., has been marked by contentious incidents. In December 2011, the nation intercepted an RQ-170 Sentinel operated by the CIA, purposed to survey Iranian nuclear establishments. This drone had breached Iranian airspace from the adjacent Afghanistan. Subsequent to this event, Iran reverse-engineered the drone, crafting their indigenous versions. Additionally, in 2019, during escalating tensions over a defunct nuclear agreement with global superpowers, Iran brought down a U.S. Navy RQ-4A Global Hawk in the Strait of Hormuz. The unveiling of the Mohajer-10 is a clear testament to Iran’s growing technological might and its determination to be a significant player in global aerial warfare.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Daylight Siege in Pittsburgh - Shooter’s Rampage Ends After Prolonged Standoff</title><link href="/news/2023/08/24/Pittsburgh-Standoff/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Daylight Siege in Pittsburgh - Shooter’s Rampage Ends After Prolonged Standoff" /><published>2023-08-24T16:14:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-08-24T16:14:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/08/24/Pittsburgh-Standoff</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/08/24/Pittsburgh-Standoff/">&lt;p&gt;A quiet neighborhood in Pittsburgh turned into a battleground when a man facing eviction responded with gunfire, launching a day-long standoff with authorities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;from-eviction-to-violence&quot;&gt;From Eviction to Violence&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The tense standoff took place in Pittsburgh’s Garfield neighborhood and began when deputies from the Allegheny County Sheriff’s department attempted to serve an eviction notice. The seemingly routine task escalated when they were met with unexpected gunfire upon making contact at the door.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sheriff Kevin Kraus narrated the intensity of the situation, saying, “They began to take cover, return fire — engaged in a pretty significant gun battle.” While initial reports suggested a deputy had been shot, it later turned out to be a minor injury sustained during the chaos.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kraus was taken aback by the unforeseen violence, stating they had no indication of the individual’s potential to engage in such dangerous behavior or knowledge of firearms inside the residence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;hours-of-tension-and-gunfire&quot;&gt;Hours of Tension and Gunfire&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As shots continued to ring through the neighborhood, witnesses described hearing what sounded like hundreds of bullets being fired. Additional gun battles ensued as the hours dragged on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a tactical response, SWAT teams, alongside federal agencies like the FBI and the Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, Firearms and Explosives, swiftly arrived to defuse the situation. Their combined efforts, according to Police Chief Larry Scirotto, undoubtedly “saved many officers’ lives in a very tense and rapidly uncertain environment” while also ensuring the safety of the local residents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Scirotto emphasized that authorities provided the shooter with multiple opportunities to surrender without further conflict. They even deployed drones in attempts to communicate and assess the situation inside the house. However, each drone became a target, with the shooter taking them down every time they approached.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-final-moments&quot;&gt;The Final Moments&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The standoff, which had begun in the morning, came to a grim conclusion around 5 p.m. when city emergency medical responders pronounced the shooter dead. The exact circumstances surrounding his death remain unclear as officials have yet to release further details or his identity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the dust settles in the Garfield neighborhood, a community and its law enforcement agencies are left to reckon with the unpredictable dangers they might face even in seemingly mundane tasks, like serving an eviction notice.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">A quiet neighborhood in Pittsburgh turned into a battleground when a man facing eviction responded with gunfire, launching a day-long standoff with authorities. From Eviction to Violence The tense standoff took place in Pittsburgh’s Garfield neighborhood and began when deputies from the Allegheny County Sheriff’s department attempted to serve an eviction notice. The seemingly routine task escalated when they were met with unexpected gunfire upon making contact at the door. Sheriff Kevin Kraus narrated the intensity of the situation, saying, “They began to take cover, return fire — engaged in a pretty significant gun battle.” While initial reports suggested a deputy had been shot, it later turned out to be a minor injury sustained during the chaos. Kraus was taken aback by the unforeseen violence, stating they had no indication of the individual’s potential to engage in such dangerous behavior or knowledge of firearms inside the residence. Hours of Tension and Gunfire As shots continued to ring through the neighborhood, witnesses described hearing what sounded like hundreds of bullets being fired. Additional gun battles ensued as the hours dragged on. In a tactical response, SWAT teams, alongside federal agencies like the FBI and the Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, Firearms and Explosives, swiftly arrived to defuse the situation. Their combined efforts, according to Police Chief Larry Scirotto, undoubtedly “saved many officers’ lives in a very tense and rapidly uncertain environment” while also ensuring the safety of the local residents. Scirotto emphasized that authorities provided the shooter with multiple opportunities to surrender without further conflict. They even deployed drones in attempts to communicate and assess the situation inside the house. However, each drone became a target, with the shooter taking them down every time they approached. The Final Moments The standoff, which had begun in the morning, came to a grim conclusion around 5 p.m. when city emergency medical responders pronounced the shooter dead. The exact circumstances surrounding his death remain unclear as officials have yet to release further details or his identity. As the dust settles in the Garfield neighborhood, a community and its law enforcement agencies are left to reckon with the unpredictable dangers they might face even in seemingly mundane tasks, like serving an eviction notice.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Out of Bounds - Spanish Soccer Faces Backlash After Inappropriate Act</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/08/24/Soccer-Controversy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Out of Bounds - Spanish Soccer Faces Backlash After Inappropriate Act" /><published>2023-08-24T15:02:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-08-24T15:02:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/08/24/Soccer-Controversy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/08/24/Soccer-Controversy/">&lt;p&gt;As the spotlight shone brightly on the Spanish Women’s World Cup victory over England, it wasn’t the triumphant team that stole the headlines but rather a controversial act by Spanish Soccer Federation (RFEF) President, Luis Rubiales. His unsolicited kiss on star player Jennifer Hermoso’s mouth post-victory has elicited outrage from the global soccer community, emphasizing a need for change in the sport’s culture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Former U.S. Women’s National Team (USWNT) powerhouse, Megan Rapinoe, never one to shy away from a battle for justice, was among the most vociferous of critics. She took the opportunity to reflect on the broader issues plaguing women’s soccer in Spain, stating, “It made me think about how much we are required to endure.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last year, the Spanish women’s team became a focal point of controversy when 15 senior members sent an ultimatum letter, demanding significant changes within the coaching staff. This plea was brushed off by the federation, amplifying the apparent disconnect between the players and the administration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rapinoe was direct in her criticism of Rubiales’ actions, calling it a clear representation of the “deep level of misogyny and sexism” evident in the Spanish side. More so, she didn’t mince her words labeling the act as a form of “assault.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Spain’s Prime Minister, Pedro Sanchez, too joined the chorus of voices demanding more accountability. He critiqued Rubiales’ apology as inadequate and called for introspection into the systemic sexism prevalent in Spanish sports.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In response to the spiraling controversy, the RFEF will convene a general assembly to discuss the future of Rubiales and potentially broader reforms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the world of soccer continues to evolve and fight for equal rights and representation, incidents like this serve as poignant reminders of the underlying battles that persist off the field. The hope is that the global outcry will serve as a catalyst for positive change, ensuring that future victories can be celebrated without the overshadowing specter of prejudice.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">As the spotlight shone brightly on the Spanish Women’s World Cup victory over England, it wasn’t the triumphant team that stole the headlines but rather a controversial act by Spanish Soccer Federation (RFEF) President, Luis Rubiales. His unsolicited kiss on star player Jennifer Hermoso’s mouth post-victory has elicited outrage from the global soccer community, emphasizing a need for change in the sport’s culture. Former U.S. Women’s National Team (USWNT) powerhouse, Megan Rapinoe, never one to shy away from a battle for justice, was among the most vociferous of critics. She took the opportunity to reflect on the broader issues plaguing women’s soccer in Spain, stating, “It made me think about how much we are required to endure.” Last year, the Spanish women’s team became a focal point of controversy when 15 senior members sent an ultimatum letter, demanding significant changes within the coaching staff. This plea was brushed off by the federation, amplifying the apparent disconnect between the players and the administration. Rapinoe was direct in her criticism of Rubiales’ actions, calling it a clear representation of the “deep level of misogyny and sexism” evident in the Spanish side. More so, she didn’t mince her words labeling the act as a form of “assault.” Spain’s Prime Minister, Pedro Sanchez, too joined the chorus of voices demanding more accountability. He critiqued Rubiales’ apology as inadequate and called for introspection into the systemic sexism prevalent in Spanish sports. In response to the spiraling controversy, the RFEF will convene a general assembly to discuss the future of Rubiales and potentially broader reforms. As the world of soccer continues to evolve and fight for equal rights and representation, incidents like this serve as poignant reminders of the underlying battles that persist off the field. The hope is that the global outcry will serve as a catalyst for positive change, ensuring that future victories can be celebrated without the overshadowing specter of prejudice.</summary></entry></feed>