<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-08-26T19:18:30-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/08/26/2023-08-10-King-of-the-Hill-Actor-Johnny-Hardwick-Passes/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-08-26T19:18:30-04:00</published><updated>2023-08-26T19:18:30-04:00</updated><id>/2023/08/26/2023-08-10-King-of-the-Hill-Actor-Johnny-Hardwick-Passes</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/08/26/2023-08-10-King-of-the-Hill-Actor-Johnny-Hardwick-Passes/">&lt;p&gt;The entertainment industry is mourning the loss of Johnny Hardwick, the acclaimed voice actor renowned for his portrayal of Dale Gribble in the popular animated series “King of the Hill.” At the age of 64, Hardwick’s demise has left many in shock.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The distressing news was confirmed by the Austin (Texas) Police Department, which attended a welfare check on Tuesday, leading to the tragic discovery of Hardwick’s lifeless body. While the circumstances surrounding his death are still shrouded in mystery, the Austin police have categorically stated that it isn’t a homicide case. Further details pertaining to the cause will be unveiled once the Travis County Medical Examiner finalizes their findings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hardwick’s role as Dale Gribble began in 1997 with the show’s premiere episode and lasted until its conclusion in 2010, spanning an impressive 259 episodes. His outstanding contribution to “King of the Hill” earned him an Emmy Award in 1999, followed by nominations in 2001 and 2002. The animated masterpiece was the brainchild of creators Mike Judge and Greg Daniels, with a cast ensemble including talents like Judge himself, Kathy Najimy, Stephen Root, and Pamela Adlon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earlier this year, fans rejoiced upon learning about a forthcoming revival of “King of the Hill,” with Hardwick’s involvement confirmed. Craig Erwich, the executive at the helm of ABC Entertainment, Hulu, and Disney Branded Television Streaming Originals, expressed enthusiasm about resuming the show’s narrative to reflect on our contemporary world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond his notable voice acting career, Hardwick was also a gifted stand-up comedian, making a mark in the comedy circuits during the 1990s.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/08/26/2023-08-12-Ian-Watkins-Assault/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-08-26T19:18:30-04:00</published><updated>2023-08-26T19:18:30-04:00</updated><id>/2023/08/26/2023-08-12-Ian-Watkins-Assault</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/08/26/2023-08-12-Ian-Watkins-Assault/">&lt;p&gt;Ian Watkins, the controversial former lead singer of the rock band Lostprophets, faced a brutal assault inside HMP Wakefield, where he’s currently serving a 29-year sentence for grave child sex crimes. According to sources, Watkins is in critical condition following the incident.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reports from the Mirror shed light on the gruesome nature of the assault. Allegedly, Watkins was accosted and held hostage by three inmates, subjected to hours of physical abuse, and eventually stabbed multiple times. Officers discovered the critically injured singer only hours later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Watkins was held for a lengthy period by the prisoners and endured a severe beating before the stabbing. The entire ordeal is under investigation,” conveyed the officials from HMP Wakefield. Fortunately, in a subsequent update from law enforcement, it was clarified that Watkins’ injuries, while severe, were not life-threatening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lostprophets, active from the late ’90s to the early 2000s, witnessed their downfall following the shocking revelations of Watkins’ depravities. In 2013, he faced charges for thirteen appalling sex offenses against children, which included the attempted rape of a one-year-old girl. The case revealed that Watkins administered drugs to children, plotting their sexual abuse, and even filmed some of his heinous acts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Confronted with overwhelming evidence, Watkins pleaded guilty to multiple counts of rape, sex with minors, and the possession of disturbing explicit content. His conviction in December 2013 led to the disintegration of the Lostprophets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jo Mjadzelics, one of Watkins’ former partners, expressed her shock at the recent attack, stating to the Mirror, “It’s surprising that such a brutal attack took so long, especially in a prison like Wakefield.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The broader implications of the attack on Watkins underline the volatile dynamics within prison systems, especially for individuals convicted of particularly reviled crimes. The repercussions of his crimes, it seems, continue to echo both for Watkins and for those who were once associated with him.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Explosive Accusations - Former Ukraine Prosecutor Targets Bidens</title><link href="/politics/2023/08/26/Explosive-Claims-Against-Bidens/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Explosive Accusations - Former Ukraine Prosecutor Targets Bidens" /><published>2023-08-26T07:25:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-08-26T07:25:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/08/26/Explosive-Claims-Against-Bidens</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/08/26/Explosive-Claims-Against-Bidens/">&lt;p&gt;Recent waves in the political arena were created as former Ukrainian Prosecutor General Viktor Shokin accused both Joe and Hunter Biden of receiving bribes. This, he alleges, is connected to the Burisma investigation, which took place while Hunter Biden served on the energy firm’s board of directors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shokin’s explosive claims suggest that his 2016 firing was a direct result of him probing into the dealings of Burisma. He told Fox News that he has always maintained Poroshenko’s decision to fire him was influenced by the then Vice President Biden. “They were engaging in corrupt activities,” Shokin mentioned, pointing fingers not just at Hunter Biden but also at Devon Archer and more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the evidence to support Shokin’s serious allegations remains thin. He himself admitted, “I do not want to deal in unproven facts.” Still, he believes that Joe Biden’s move to withhold $1 billion in U.S. aid for Ukraine until Shokin was removed is proof enough of foul play.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The White House promptly dismissed these accusations, citing them as the words of a man whose own deputy called his office ‘a hotbed of corruption.’ Ian Sams, a White House spokesperson, mentioned that these “false claims have been debunked,” regardless of the amount of airtime given to them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What makes these allegations even more intricate is Biden’s own admission about his role in Shokin’s dismissal. He openly discussed how he influenced Poroshenko’s decision by leveraging U.S. aid. While Biden presents it as a move against corruption, Shokin’s interpretation paints a different picture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The timing of these allegations is crucial. Devon Archer, Hunter Biden’s former business partner and fellow board member at Burisma, has provided testimony which seems to align with some of Shokin’s claims. Archer indicated that during the height of the investigations against Burisma, company leaders sought Hunter Biden’s intervention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet, it’s essential to consider all facets of the story. The White House emphasized that Shokin’s office was not actively investigating Burisma or Hunter at the time of his firing. This stance was corroborated by reports from reputed news organizations such as The Washington Post, Associated Press, and New York Times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, other reputable sources, including the former Assistant Secretary of State for European and Eurasian Affairs Victoria Nuland, have testified against Shokin. They indicated that Shokin was seen as a protector of corrupt officials and not as a crusader against them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the waves from these explosive claims continue to ripple, a thorough and unbiased investigation will be crucial to distinguish fact from fiction. The American public deserves clarity on the matter, ensuring that the truth, whatever it may be, emerges from the murky waters of political allegations.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Recent waves in the political arena were created as former Ukrainian Prosecutor General Viktor Shokin accused both Joe and Hunter Biden of receiving bribes. This, he alleges, is connected to the Burisma investigation, which took place while Hunter Biden served on the energy firm’s board of directors. Shokin’s explosive claims suggest that his 2016 firing was a direct result of him probing into the dealings of Burisma. He told Fox News that he has always maintained Poroshenko’s decision to fire him was influenced by the then Vice President Biden. “They were engaging in corrupt activities,” Shokin mentioned, pointing fingers not just at Hunter Biden but also at Devon Archer and more. However, the evidence to support Shokin’s serious allegations remains thin. He himself admitted, “I do not want to deal in unproven facts.” Still, he believes that Joe Biden’s move to withhold $1 billion in U.S. aid for Ukraine until Shokin was removed is proof enough of foul play. The White House promptly dismissed these accusations, citing them as the words of a man whose own deputy called his office ‘a hotbed of corruption.’ Ian Sams, a White House spokesperson, mentioned that these “false claims have been debunked,” regardless of the amount of airtime given to them. What makes these allegations even more intricate is Biden’s own admission about his role in Shokin’s dismissal. He openly discussed how he influenced Poroshenko’s decision by leveraging U.S. aid. While Biden presents it as a move against corruption, Shokin’s interpretation paints a different picture. The timing of these allegations is crucial. Devon Archer, Hunter Biden’s former business partner and fellow board member at Burisma, has provided testimony which seems to align with some of Shokin’s claims. Archer indicated that during the height of the investigations against Burisma, company leaders sought Hunter Biden’s intervention. Yet, it’s essential to consider all facets of the story. The White House emphasized that Shokin’s office was not actively investigating Burisma or Hunter at the time of his firing. This stance was corroborated by reports from reputed news organizations such as The Washington Post, Associated Press, and New York Times. Furthermore, other reputable sources, including the former Assistant Secretary of State for European and Eurasian Affairs Victoria Nuland, have testified against Shokin. They indicated that Shokin was seen as a protector of corrupt officials and not as a crusader against them. As the waves from these explosive claims continue to ripple, a thorough and unbiased investigation will be crucial to distinguish fact from fiction. The American public deserves clarity on the matter, ensuring that the truth, whatever it may be, emerges from the murky waters of political allegations.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Blue State’s Soft Crime Policies - Protecting Perpetrators Over Victims?</title><link href="/news/2023/08/25/Critical-Blue-State-Crime-Policies/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Blue State’s Soft Crime Policies - Protecting Perpetrators Over Victims?" /><published>2023-08-25T20:14:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-08-25T20:14:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/08/25/Critical-Blue-State-Crime-Policies</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/08/25/Critical-Blue-State-Crime-Policies/">&lt;p&gt;Karol Markowicz, a New York Post columnist, recently shined a light on the increasing trend of Americans fleeing blue states due to concerns over rising crime rates. Such concerns were tragically validated when Julia Fatum, a 25-year-old New York City EMT, was brutally attacked in the back of her ambulance while trying to help a patient.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the fateful evening of July 19, while tending to Rudy Garcia, a 48-year-old with a felonious past, Fatum faced a horrifying ordeal. According to prosecutors, upon being told not to throw a gum wrapper, Garcia responded by stabbing her multiple times. While she continues her grueling road to recovery, the larger question remains: Are New York State’s crime policies enabling criminals at the expense of victims?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-mothers-outcry&quot;&gt;A Mother’s Outcry&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cara Fatum-Grant, Julia’s mother, voiced her grave concerns regarding the state’s crime policies. In her statement to Fox News Digital, she expressed her fears about Garcia facing “minimal consequences” due to the state’s lenient bail reform and sentencing guidelines. Such policies, in her view, prioritize the criminal over the victim.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Indeed, Garcia’s criminal record is extensive. His history includes felonies for assaulting police officers, multiple misdemeanors, and at least two failures to appear in court. In the recent past, he was apprehended for fare evasion and possession of a weapon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Garcia currently remains in custody, Fatum-Grant is left with lingering questions about the system’s effectiveness. “People are literally getting away with murder in this state,” she lamented.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;bail-reform-backlash&quot;&gt;Bail Reform Backlash&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;New York State’s bail reform, which began in 2020, has drawn criticism from many, especially after violent incidents like Fatum’s attack. Critics argue that the policy enables those charged with non-violent crimes to evade jail time before their court appearance, potentially endangering the public.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fatum-Grant’s frustration mirrors that of many New Yorkers. “We’ve become a ‘protect the criminal’ type of state,” she remarked, capturing the sentiment of those who believe the state’s policies lack adequate consideration for public safety.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;hope-amidst-tragedy&quot;&gt;Hope Amidst Tragedy&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the horrifying circumstances, Julia Fatum displays remarkable resilience. Although her road to recovery is long, and she still grapples with severe physical and emotional scars, she remains “determined to make it back to life before the attack.” Her aspirations to further her education and possibly return to her role as an EMT speaks volumes about her indomitable spirit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-ongoing-debate&quot;&gt;The Ongoing Debate&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This tragic incident shines a spotlight on the broader debate over crime policies in blue states. While the intentions behind bail reform and other policies may be noble - to prevent the unnecessary jailing of non-violent offenders and address systemic issues - there’s an urgent need to reassess their implications. The safety and well-being of the public must always be paramount.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If New York and other states with similar policies hope to regain the trust of their citizens, they must strike a balance between progressive reforms and safeguarding public safety. The attack on Julia Fatum serves as a harrowing reminder of the stakes.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Karol Markowicz, a New York Post columnist, recently shined a light on the increasing trend of Americans fleeing blue states due to concerns over rising crime rates. Such concerns were tragically validated when Julia Fatum, a 25-year-old New York City EMT, was brutally attacked in the back of her ambulance while trying to help a patient. On the fateful evening of July 19, while tending to Rudy Garcia, a 48-year-old with a felonious past, Fatum faced a horrifying ordeal. According to prosecutors, upon being told not to throw a gum wrapper, Garcia responded by stabbing her multiple times. While she continues her grueling road to recovery, the larger question remains: Are New York State’s crime policies enabling criminals at the expense of victims? A Mother’s Outcry Cara Fatum-Grant, Julia’s mother, voiced her grave concerns regarding the state’s crime policies. In her statement to Fox News Digital, she expressed her fears about Garcia facing “minimal consequences” due to the state’s lenient bail reform and sentencing guidelines. Such policies, in her view, prioritize the criminal over the victim. Indeed, Garcia’s criminal record is extensive. His history includes felonies for assaulting police officers, multiple misdemeanors, and at least two failures to appear in court. In the recent past, he was apprehended for fare evasion and possession of a weapon. While Garcia currently remains in custody, Fatum-Grant is left with lingering questions about the system’s effectiveness. “People are literally getting away with murder in this state,” she lamented. Bail Reform Backlash New York State’s bail reform, which began in 2020, has drawn criticism from many, especially after violent incidents like Fatum’s attack. Critics argue that the policy enables those charged with non-violent crimes to evade jail time before their court appearance, potentially endangering the public. Fatum-Grant’s frustration mirrors that of many New Yorkers. “We’ve become a ‘protect the criminal’ type of state,” she remarked, capturing the sentiment of those who believe the state’s policies lack adequate consideration for public safety. Hope Amidst Tragedy Despite the horrifying circumstances, Julia Fatum displays remarkable resilience. Although her road to recovery is long, and she still grapples with severe physical and emotional scars, she remains “determined to make it back to life before the attack.” Her aspirations to further her education and possibly return to her role as an EMT speaks volumes about her indomitable spirit. The Ongoing Debate This tragic incident shines a spotlight on the broader debate over crime policies in blue states. While the intentions behind bail reform and other policies may be noble - to prevent the unnecessary jailing of non-violent offenders and address systemic issues - there’s an urgent need to reassess their implications. The safety and well-being of the public must always be paramount. If New York and other states with similar policies hope to regain the trust of their citizens, they must strike a balance between progressive reforms and safeguarding public safety. The attack on Julia Fatum serves as a harrowing reminder of the stakes.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Power of the Nuclear Family - Ramaswamy’s Stand Resonates</title><link href="/politics/2023/08/25/Fatherless-Epidemic/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Power of the Nuclear Family - Ramaswamy’s Stand Resonates" /><published>2023-08-25T19:16:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-08-25T19:16:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/08/25/Fatherless-Epidemic</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/08/25/Fatherless-Epidemic/">&lt;p&gt;Vivek Ramaswamy, the entrepreneur-turned-political contender, became the talk of the town following his noteworthy remarks on fatherlessness in America. The conversation took place during the inaugural GOP primary debate in Milwaukee, Wisconsin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ramaswamy voiced, “&lt;strong&gt;The word privilege gets used a lot&lt;/strong&gt;. Well, you know what? I did have the ultimate privilege of two parents in the house with a focus on educational achievement, and I want every kid to enjoy that.” He then went on to address a critical issue. According to him, the federal government’s policies unintentionally incentivize single women to remain without a partner, further exacerbating the fatherlessness epidemic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Addressing this poignant issue, Ramaswamy also linked it with the broader challenges in education, stating, “education starts with the family, and the nuclear family is the greatest form of governance known to mankind.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This comment particularly struck a chord across the board. Numerous conservatives took to social media to laud Ramaswamy for shedding light on the unraveling of the nuclear family. This sentiment directly correlates with issues such as education and poverty, making his point even more pressing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GOP operative, Matt Mackowiak, was quick to express his support, tweeting, “&lt;strong&gt;Good for Vivek for bringing up fatherlessness as a major issue&lt;/strong&gt;.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the praise wasn’t restricted to just conservatives. Larry Elder, a fellow GOP presidential candidate, joined the chorus, tweeting, “I’m happy that Vivek recognizes there is an ‘epidemic of fatherlessness.’ It’s about time.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Echoing his sentiments from earlier, Ramaswamy, during his closing statement, reiterated, “The nuclear family is the greatest form of governance known to man.” He further emphasized the importance of capitalism in elevating society out of poverty and extolled the virtues of the U.S. Constitution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tricia McLaughlin, Ramaswamy’s spokesperson, later provided a statement elaborating on his stance. “True ‘privilege’ is not based on the color of your skin,” she stated, “It’s being raised in a stable family with two parents.” She urged the federal government to act, suggesting it could start by removing the ‘progressive boot’ from the family’s neck.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Vivek Ramaswamy, the entrepreneur-turned-political contender, became the talk of the town following his noteworthy remarks on fatherlessness in America. The conversation took place during the inaugural GOP primary debate in Milwaukee, Wisconsin. Ramaswamy voiced, “The word privilege gets used a lot. Well, you know what? I did have the ultimate privilege of two parents in the house with a focus on educational achievement, and I want every kid to enjoy that.” He then went on to address a critical issue. According to him, the federal government’s policies unintentionally incentivize single women to remain without a partner, further exacerbating the fatherlessness epidemic. Addressing this poignant issue, Ramaswamy also linked it with the broader challenges in education, stating, “education starts with the family, and the nuclear family is the greatest form of governance known to mankind.” This comment particularly struck a chord across the board. Numerous conservatives took to social media to laud Ramaswamy for shedding light on the unraveling of the nuclear family. This sentiment directly correlates with issues such as education and poverty, making his point even more pressing. GOP operative, Matt Mackowiak, was quick to express his support, tweeting, “Good for Vivek for bringing up fatherlessness as a major issue.” However, the praise wasn’t restricted to just conservatives. Larry Elder, a fellow GOP presidential candidate, joined the chorus, tweeting, “I’m happy that Vivek recognizes there is an ‘epidemic of fatherlessness.’ It’s about time.” Echoing his sentiments from earlier, Ramaswamy, during his closing statement, reiterated, “The nuclear family is the greatest form of governance known to man.” He further emphasized the importance of capitalism in elevating society out of poverty and extolled the virtues of the U.S. Constitution. Tricia McLaughlin, Ramaswamy’s spokesperson, later provided a statement elaborating on his stance. “True ‘privilege’ is not based on the color of your skin,” she stated, “It’s being raised in a stable family with two parents.” She urged the federal government to act, suggesting it could start by removing the ‘progressive boot’ from the family’s neck.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Tensions Rise - Georgia Senator Seeks to Defund DA’s Office</title><link href="/politics/2023/08/25/Defunding-Call/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tensions Rise - Georgia Senator Seeks to Defund DA’s Office" /><published>2023-08-25T18:21:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-08-25T18:21:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/08/25/Defunding-Call</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/08/25/Defunding-Call/">&lt;p&gt;In an impassioned outcry against what he views as a biased pursuit of justice against former President Donald Trump, GOP Georgia State Sen. Colton Moore has made a call to action. His demand? An emergency special session of the Georgia state Legislature with the goal to halt state tax dollars flowing to the office of Fulton County District Attorney Fani Willis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Funding Controversies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to Moore’s conversation with Newsmax, while DA Fani Willis serves only one of Georgia’s 159 counties, her office benefits from taxpayer funds spanning the entire state. This arrangement has stoked the flames of contention for Moore, especially given recent legal actions targeting Trump and his allies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, Moore’s battle uphill becomes evident when considering the response from his fellow Republicans. Just one, among the 32 GOP members in the 56-seat Senate, has signaled any form of support for such a special session.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expressing his frustrations, Moore lamented, “It’s hard to soar like an eagle when you are dealing with a bunch of buzzards.” By this, he pointed to the reluctance of his peers to convene and debate over the redirection of funds away from Willis’ office. Instead, many have shown a preference to let a forthcoming Prosecutorial Oversight Commission handle any alleged mismanagement of the Trump case by Willis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The freshman senator displayed his exasperation, commenting, “So they would rather trust unelected bureaucrats than the elected representatives of the people of Georgia.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Governor Kemp Under Fire&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But Moore’s discontent isn’t limited to his immediate colleagues. He reserved some sharp criticisms for Gov. Brian Kemp, whom he referred to as a “disgrace to this situation.” Moore’s bone of contention lies in Kemp’s alleged lack of action when others, such as Hillary Clinton and Stacey Abrams, contested election results. Yet, when Trump exercised his First Amendment rights to voice his beliefs about the 2020 Georgia elections, criminal charges followed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moore’s fervent belief is that “Fani Willis is a domestic threat,” and he adamantly feels that taxes originating outside Fulton County should not support her prosecutorial endeavors. He passionately concluded, “I would rather be tarred and feathered if I allow Fani Willis to go on as she has.”&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In an impassioned outcry against what he views as a biased pursuit of justice against former President Donald Trump, GOP Georgia State Sen. Colton Moore has made a call to action. His demand? An emergency special session of the Georgia state Legislature with the goal to halt state tax dollars flowing to the office of Fulton County District Attorney Fani Willis. Funding Controversies According to Moore’s conversation with Newsmax, while DA Fani Willis serves only one of Georgia’s 159 counties, her office benefits from taxpayer funds spanning the entire state. This arrangement has stoked the flames of contention for Moore, especially given recent legal actions targeting Trump and his allies. However, Moore’s battle uphill becomes evident when considering the response from his fellow Republicans. Just one, among the 32 GOP members in the 56-seat Senate, has signaled any form of support for such a special session. Expressing his frustrations, Moore lamented, “It’s hard to soar like an eagle when you are dealing with a bunch of buzzards.” By this, he pointed to the reluctance of his peers to convene and debate over the redirection of funds away from Willis’ office. Instead, many have shown a preference to let a forthcoming Prosecutorial Oversight Commission handle any alleged mismanagement of the Trump case by Willis. The freshman senator displayed his exasperation, commenting, “So they would rather trust unelected bureaucrats than the elected representatives of the people of Georgia.” Governor Kemp Under Fire But Moore’s discontent isn’t limited to his immediate colleagues. He reserved some sharp criticisms for Gov. Brian Kemp, whom he referred to as a “disgrace to this situation.” Moore’s bone of contention lies in Kemp’s alleged lack of action when others, such as Hillary Clinton and Stacey Abrams, contested election results. Yet, when Trump exercised his First Amendment rights to voice his beliefs about the 2020 Georgia elections, criminal charges followed. Moore’s fervent belief is that “Fani Willis is a domestic threat,” and he adamantly feels that taxes originating outside Fulton County should not support her prosecutorial endeavors. He passionately concluded, “I would rather be tarred and feathered if I allow Fani Willis to go on as she has.”</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Banker’s Dark Secret - How $10,000 and Facebook Could’ve Ended a Life</title><link href="/news/2023/08/25/Banker-Plot/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Banker’s Dark Secret - How $10,000 and Facebook Could’ve Ended a Life" /><published>2023-08-25T17:03:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-08-25T17:03:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/08/25/Banker-Plot</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/08/25/Banker-Plot/">&lt;p&gt;In an unprecedented mix of high-tech communication and old-world crime, a New York banker stands accused of hatching a plot straight out of a crime thriller - a murder-for-hire scheme brokered over Facebook Messenger.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reshma Massarone, a seemingly innocuous branch manager at a New York credit union, is at the center of a chilling investigation involving her alleged attempt to eliminate her own brother-in-law during a family trip to Guyana. The alleged price for the hit? A cool $10,000.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From July 20 to August 16, the cold digital confines of Facebook Messenger became the setting for Massarone’s machinations. She allegedly reached out to an old friend, urging him to “take care of business.” The friend, opting not to get his hands dirty, reportedly offered to act as the middleman, finding a hitman to execute the grim deed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The narrative deepens as surveillance footage shows Massarone physically withdrawing the funds – a down payment for death. The next scene? A Walgreen’s store, where Massarone can be seen making a wire transfer at a Western Union kiosk, sending over 25 $100 bills - a sum of $2,500, presumably a deposit for the hitman.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her commitment to this dark path seemed clear when she chillingly penned, “No turning back,” in a message on July 25, urging the deletion of her contact for fear of being caught.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But like all tales of crime and mystery, the plot was eventually uncovered. How authorities caught wind of this intricate web is still shrouded in secrecy. What remains evident is the unyielding power of digital trails in modern crime-solving.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Currently incarcerated and perceived as a clear and present danger to society, Massarone awaits the next chapter in this riveting saga. Calls to her attorney, Mark Gombiner, have gone unanswered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a world increasingly connected by technology, this harrowing tale serves as a stark reminder: the digital realm can be both a tool for connection and, in the wrong hands, a weapon of destruction.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In an unprecedented mix of high-tech communication and old-world crime, a New York banker stands accused of hatching a plot straight out of a crime thriller - a murder-for-hire scheme brokered over Facebook Messenger. Reshma Massarone, a seemingly innocuous branch manager at a New York credit union, is at the center of a chilling investigation involving her alleged attempt to eliminate her own brother-in-law during a family trip to Guyana. The alleged price for the hit? A cool $10,000. From July 20 to August 16, the cold digital confines of Facebook Messenger became the setting for Massarone’s machinations. She allegedly reached out to an old friend, urging him to “take care of business.” The friend, opting not to get his hands dirty, reportedly offered to act as the middleman, finding a hitman to execute the grim deed. The narrative deepens as surveillance footage shows Massarone physically withdrawing the funds – a down payment for death. The next scene? A Walgreen’s store, where Massarone can be seen making a wire transfer at a Western Union kiosk, sending over 25 $100 bills - a sum of $2,500, presumably a deposit for the hitman. Her commitment to this dark path seemed clear when she chillingly penned, “No turning back,” in a message on July 25, urging the deletion of her contact for fear of being caught. But like all tales of crime and mystery, the plot was eventually uncovered. How authorities caught wind of this intricate web is still shrouded in secrecy. What remains evident is the unyielding power of digital trails in modern crime-solving. Currently incarcerated and perceived as a clear and present danger to society, Massarone awaits the next chapter in this riveting saga. Calls to her attorney, Mark Gombiner, have gone unanswered. In a world increasingly connected by technology, this harrowing tale serves as a stark reminder: the digital realm can be both a tool for connection and, in the wrong hands, a weapon of destruction.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Rising Tensions - Taiwan Detects Renewed Chinese Military Maneuvers</title><link href="/news/2023/08/25/Chinese-Military-Activity/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rising Tensions - Taiwan Detects Renewed Chinese Military Maneuvers" /><published>2023-08-25T16:07:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-08-25T16:07:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/08/25/Chinese-Military-Activity</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/08/25/Chinese-Military-Activity/">&lt;p&gt;In a fresh escalation of tensions between China and Taiwan, the latter’s defense ministry has reported increased Chinese military activity around its airspace and waters. On Friday, Taiwan’s surveillance systems picked up 13 aircraft entering its designated “response” zone, signaling Beijing’s continued military assertiveness in the region.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;China, which firmly regards Taiwan as an integral part of its territory despite the island’s democratic governance, has ratcheted up military pressure over the past three years. Recent events, including stop-overs by Taiwan’s Vice President William Lai in the United States, appear to have further inflamed the situation. China, in what was perceived as a retaliatory move, conducted a series of military drills around Taiwan this Saturday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to the Taiwanese defense ministry, early detections on Friday morning revealed a mix of 22 Chinese aircraft, comprising fighters, bombers, early warning aircraft, and drones. While 13 of these entered Taiwan’s immediate “response” zone, exact details about their operations remain unclear. In response to these incursions, Taiwan dispatched its own aircraft and naval vessels to monitor the situation closely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, even though Beijing has not officially announced any further military drills post-Saturday, history suggests China’s penchant for initiating such missions without prior or post acknowledgment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the specter of geopolitical tensions continues to loom over the Taiwan Strait, the international community will be closely observing these developments, hoping for diplomatic channels to prevail over military confrontations.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a fresh escalation of tensions between China and Taiwan, the latter’s defense ministry has reported increased Chinese military activity around its airspace and waters. On Friday, Taiwan’s surveillance systems picked up 13 aircraft entering its designated “response” zone, signaling Beijing’s continued military assertiveness in the region. China, which firmly regards Taiwan as an integral part of its territory despite the island’s democratic governance, has ratcheted up military pressure over the past three years. Recent events, including stop-overs by Taiwan’s Vice President William Lai in the United States, appear to have further inflamed the situation. China, in what was perceived as a retaliatory move, conducted a series of military drills around Taiwan this Saturday. According to the Taiwanese defense ministry, early detections on Friday morning revealed a mix of 22 Chinese aircraft, comprising fighters, bombers, early warning aircraft, and drones. While 13 of these entered Taiwan’s immediate “response” zone, exact details about their operations remain unclear. In response to these incursions, Taiwan dispatched its own aircraft and naval vessels to monitor the situation closely. Interestingly, even though Beijing has not officially announced any further military drills post-Saturday, history suggests China’s penchant for initiating such missions without prior or post acknowledgment. As the specter of geopolitical tensions continues to loom over the Taiwan Strait, the international community will be closely observing these developments, hoping for diplomatic channels to prevail over military confrontations.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Debate Ratings Take a Dive - Missing the Trump Effect?</title><link href="/politics/2023/08/25/Debate-Rating-Dip/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Debate Ratings Take a Dive - Missing the Trump Effect?" /><published>2023-08-25T15:02:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-08-25T15:02:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/08/25/Debate-Rating-Dip</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/08/25/Debate-Rating-Dip/">&lt;p&gt;The recent Republican primary debate broadcasted by Fox News experienced a pronounced drop in viewership, with Nielsen Media Research data indicating that only 12.8 million tuned in. This figure starkly contrasts with former President Donald Trump’s debate debut in 2015, which garnered attention from about 25.8 million viewers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comparative Viewer Engagement&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When zeroing in on the key advertising demographic, ages 25-54, the debate managed to secure 2.8 million viewers. Despite the numbers appearing lackluster compared to Trump’s debut, Fox News accentuated the silver lining. The network underscored that this debate outperformed more than 70% of all presidential primary debates during the 2016 and 2020 cycles. Furthermore, it emerged as the highest-rated nonsports cable telecast of 2023.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, in juxtaposition with the Democrat primary debates of 2020, the recent GOP debate appears to lag. The initial two Democrat debates recorded 19 million and 15 million viewers, respectively. The third debate tallied at 10 million.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trump’s Absence: A Vital Factor?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speculation arises on whether the dip in viewership metrics can be attributed to Trump’s decision to skip the event. Offering an explanation for his absence, Trump pointed to significant leads in polling, implying a debate appearance might not be essential to his campaign strategy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adding another twist to the narrative, just five minutes prior to the debate’s commencement, Tucker Carlson aired an exclusive interview with Trump. This move could have potentially diverted a substantial portion of potential debate viewers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Implications for the GOP&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Viewer metrics and ratings serve as a crucial barometer in gauging public interest and engagement with political events. The recent GOP debate’s viewership numbers might prompt Republican strategists to introspect on the factors influencing public attention and the potential role of notable personalities like Trump in driving viewership.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the dynamic landscape of political campaigns, the ability to seize and sustain the audience’s attention can often translate to momentum on the ground. The GOP will likely be keenly analyzing these numbers to fine-tune their approach as the election season intensifies.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">The recent Republican primary debate broadcasted by Fox News experienced a pronounced drop in viewership, with Nielsen Media Research data indicating that only 12.8 million tuned in. This figure starkly contrasts with former President Donald Trump’s debate debut in 2015, which garnered attention from about 25.8 million viewers. Comparative Viewer Engagement When zeroing in on the key advertising demographic, ages 25-54, the debate managed to secure 2.8 million viewers. Despite the numbers appearing lackluster compared to Trump’s debut, Fox News accentuated the silver lining. The network underscored that this debate outperformed more than 70% of all presidential primary debates during the 2016 and 2020 cycles. Furthermore, it emerged as the highest-rated nonsports cable telecast of 2023. However, in juxtaposition with the Democrat primary debates of 2020, the recent GOP debate appears to lag. The initial two Democrat debates recorded 19 million and 15 million viewers, respectively. The third debate tallied at 10 million. Trump’s Absence: A Vital Factor? Speculation arises on whether the dip in viewership metrics can be attributed to Trump’s decision to skip the event. Offering an explanation for his absence, Trump pointed to significant leads in polling, implying a debate appearance might not be essential to his campaign strategy. Adding another twist to the narrative, just five minutes prior to the debate’s commencement, Tucker Carlson aired an exclusive interview with Trump. This move could have potentially diverted a substantial portion of potential debate viewers. Implications for the GOP Viewer metrics and ratings serve as a crucial barometer in gauging public interest and engagement with political events. The recent GOP debate’s viewership numbers might prompt Republican strategists to introspect on the factors influencing public attention and the potential role of notable personalities like Trump in driving viewership. In the dynamic landscape of political campaigns, the ability to seize and sustain the audience’s attention can often translate to momentum on the ground. The GOP will likely be keenly analyzing these numbers to fine-tune their approach as the election season intensifies.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Elle King’s Triumphant Transformation - From Postpartum Struggles to Newfound Strength</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/08/25/Elle-King-Weight-Loss-Journey/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Elle King’s Triumphant Transformation - From Postpartum Struggles to Newfound Strength" /><published>2023-08-25T14:11:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-08-25T14:11:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/08/25/Elle-King-Weight-Loss-Journey</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/08/25/Elle-King-Weight-Loss-Journey/">&lt;p&gt;Country star Elle King’s recent Instagram post not only stunned fans with her remarkable weight loss but also resonated with many for its candid and vulnerable portrayal of her battle with postpartum depression.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From Darkness to Light:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After welcoming her son, Lucky, in September 2021, King’s weight scaled to 284 pounds. Fast forward to 2023, and the singer has undergone a noticeable physical transformation. However, she’s quick to clarify: it wasn’t a product of any medication.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“From pregnancy in 2021 to now in 2023, it’s been a journey,” she shared on Instagram. “Weight loss doesn’t happen overnight. It’s been an ever-evolving process.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Facing Postpartum Depression:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;King delved deeper into her struggles during and post-pregnancy. “I fell deep into depression during my pregnancy. The intensity of postpartum depression was overwhelming,” she recounted. Feeling entrapped in her own body, King’s passion – her singing – also suffered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Path to Healing:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Daughter to comedian Rob Schneider, King decided to tackle her health issues head-on. “I began slow, incorporating metabolic workouts and light cardio. Over time, my body, voice, and spirit felt rejuvenated,” she stated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her journey wasn’t solo. Partnering with personal trainer @pauldominic_, King underscored the importance of self-motivation. “Find what you love - music, cycling, swimming. It started as a desire to lose weight but transformed into a holistic wellness approach. My mind functions better when my body is active.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Beyond Physical Transformation:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Elle King’s commitment extends beyond the scales. She shared snippets of her skincare routine and behind-the-scenes clips preparing for concerts. But, she firmly declared, “Today, I’m healthy. I’m neither tiny nor huge. Most importantly, I’m not on any weight loss medication.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her motivation also finds roots in her family history, recalling her diabetic grandfather. “I’ve seen him struggle. I’m pre-diabetic with PCOS. But my journey is mine, and I only wish for a long, content life,” she concluded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In sharing her authentic journey, Elle King not only sets a gold standard for celebrities navigating personal struggles in the public eye but also inspires countless others grappling with similar issues.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Country star Elle King’s recent Instagram post not only stunned fans with her remarkable weight loss but also resonated with many for its candid and vulnerable portrayal of her battle with postpartum depression. From Darkness to Light: After welcoming her son, Lucky, in September 2021, King’s weight scaled to 284 pounds. Fast forward to 2023, and the singer has undergone a noticeable physical transformation. However, she’s quick to clarify: it wasn’t a product of any medication. “From pregnancy in 2021 to now in 2023, it’s been a journey,” she shared on Instagram. “Weight loss doesn’t happen overnight. It’s been an ever-evolving process.” Facing Postpartum Depression: King delved deeper into her struggles during and post-pregnancy. “I fell deep into depression during my pregnancy. The intensity of postpartum depression was overwhelming,” she recounted. Feeling entrapped in her own body, King’s passion – her singing – also suffered. The Path to Healing: Daughter to comedian Rob Schneider, King decided to tackle her health issues head-on. “I began slow, incorporating metabolic workouts and light cardio. Over time, my body, voice, and spirit felt rejuvenated,” she stated. Her journey wasn’t solo. Partnering with personal trainer @pauldominic_, King underscored the importance of self-motivation. “Find what you love - music, cycling, swimming. It started as a desire to lose weight but transformed into a holistic wellness approach. My mind functions better when my body is active.” Beyond Physical Transformation: Elle King’s commitment extends beyond the scales. She shared snippets of her skincare routine and behind-the-scenes clips preparing for concerts. But, she firmly declared, “Today, I’m healthy. I’m neither tiny nor huge. Most importantly, I’m not on any weight loss medication.” Her motivation also finds roots in her family history, recalling her diabetic grandfather. “I’ve seen him struggle. I’m pre-diabetic with PCOS. But my journey is mine, and I only wish for a long, content life,” she concluded. In sharing her authentic journey, Elle King not only sets a gold standard for celebrities navigating personal struggles in the public eye but also inspires countless others grappling with similar issues.</summary></entry></feed>