<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-09-13T11:16:15-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/09/13/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-09-13T11:16:15-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-13T11:16:15-04:00</updated><id>/2023/09/13/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/13/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Beshear’s Decision Backfires - Early Release of Convicted Child Molester Ignites Controversy</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/13/Beshear-Prisoner-Release/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Beshear’s Decision Backfires - Early Release of Convicted Child Molester Ignites Controversy" /><published>2023-09-13T10:25:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-13T10:25:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/13/Beshear-Prisoner-Release</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/13/Beshear-Prisoner-Release/">&lt;p&gt;As the Kentucky gubernatorial election looms closer, incumbent Democratic Governor Andy Beshear finds himself at the center of a scathing new television advertisement campaign. The ad, released by the conservative-aligned School Freedom Fund, sharply criticizes Beshear for his decision to potentially release certain prisoners at the onset of the coronavirus pandemic. Among these prisoners was James Hamlin, who was accused and later convicted of sodomizing a six-year-old child.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-details&quot;&gt;The Details&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the early stages of the pandemic, amidst concerns of virus spread in crowded facilities, Governor Beshear signed an order titled “Conditional Commutation of Sentence.” The order aimed at reducing the inmate population in Kentucky’s overcrowded prisons. This action was taken in response to the heightened risk presented by the COVID-19 pandemic. The order detailed a list of 697 inmates convicted of “non-violent, non-sexual offenses” whose sentences were set to expire by the end of September 2020. However, included in this list was James Hamlin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hamlin, whose Facebook page contained disturbing comments about minors, was rearrested shortly after the order and subsequently convicted of heinous charges. He is now slated to remain behind bars until 2044, with a possibility for parole in 2039.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;broader-implications&quot;&gt;Broader Implications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The advertisement equates the decision to release such prisoners as putting “deviant predators before innocent kids” and describes such choices as “not just wrong, it’s unforgivable.” Drawing parallels to the controversial Willie Horton ads from the 1988 presidential election, this new campaign against Beshear has the potential to drastically affect the outcome of the upcoming election.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Current public polls suggest a favorable leaning towards Beshear, but the provocative nature of the advertisement might sway public opinion. Governor Beshear’s potential missteps during the early days of the pandemic have previously been highlighted by the School Freedom Fund in another advertisement, spotlighting criminals with “means and motive.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A 2021 report from Kentucky’s Administrative Office of Courts added more fuel to the fire. It pointed out that of the 1,704 individuals who had their sentences commuted by Beshear, 553 were later charged with felonies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-larger-picture&quot;&gt;The Larger Picture&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This controversy comes at a crucial time, with only three major gubernatorial elections slated for 2023. Apart from Kentucky, Louisiana and Mississippi are the other states headed for a gubernatorial showdown. With the Republicans eager to turn the tables after a lackluster 2022 midterm, flipping Kentucky’s and Louisiana’s governor’s mansions from blue to red would offer a significant boost.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Insiders believe that this is just the beginning and that more such ads can be expected as election day nears, raising the stakes in an already high-voltage political atmosphere.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">As the Kentucky gubernatorial election looms closer, incumbent Democratic Governor Andy Beshear finds himself at the center of a scathing new television advertisement campaign. The ad, released by the conservative-aligned School Freedom Fund, sharply criticizes Beshear for his decision to potentially release certain prisoners at the onset of the coronavirus pandemic. Among these prisoners was James Hamlin, who was accused and later convicted of sodomizing a six-year-old child. The Details In the early stages of the pandemic, amidst concerns of virus spread in crowded facilities, Governor Beshear signed an order titled “Conditional Commutation of Sentence.” The order aimed at reducing the inmate population in Kentucky’s overcrowded prisons. This action was taken in response to the heightened risk presented by the COVID-19 pandemic. The order detailed a list of 697 inmates convicted of “non-violent, non-sexual offenses” whose sentences were set to expire by the end of September 2020. However, included in this list was James Hamlin. Hamlin, whose Facebook page contained disturbing comments about minors, was rearrested shortly after the order and subsequently convicted of heinous charges. He is now slated to remain behind bars until 2044, with a possibility for parole in 2039. Broader Implications The advertisement equates the decision to release such prisoners as putting “deviant predators before innocent kids” and describes such choices as “not just wrong, it’s unforgivable.” Drawing parallels to the controversial Willie Horton ads from the 1988 presidential election, this new campaign against Beshear has the potential to drastically affect the outcome of the upcoming election. Current public polls suggest a favorable leaning towards Beshear, but the provocative nature of the advertisement might sway public opinion. Governor Beshear’s potential missteps during the early days of the pandemic have previously been highlighted by the School Freedom Fund in another advertisement, spotlighting criminals with “means and motive.” A 2021 report from Kentucky’s Administrative Office of Courts added more fuel to the fire. It pointed out that of the 1,704 individuals who had their sentences commuted by Beshear, 553 were later charged with felonies. The Larger Picture This controversy comes at a crucial time, with only three major gubernatorial elections slated for 2023. Apart from Kentucky, Louisiana and Mississippi are the other states headed for a gubernatorial showdown. With the Republicans eager to turn the tables after a lackluster 2022 midterm, flipping Kentucky’s and Louisiana’s governor’s mansions from blue to red would offer a significant boost. Insiders believe that this is just the beginning and that more such ads can be expected as election day nears, raising the stakes in an already high-voltage political atmosphere.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Aerosmith’s Farewell Tour Hits a Snag - Steven Tyler’s Vocal Cord Injury</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/13/Aerosmith-Tour-Postponement/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Aerosmith’s Farewell Tour Hits a Snag - Steven Tyler’s Vocal Cord Injury" /><published>2023-09-13T09:14:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-13T09:14:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/13/Aerosmith-Tour-Postponement</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/13/Aerosmith-Tour-Postponement/">&lt;p&gt;The rock world was met with a jolt of concern after legendary Aerosmith frontman, Steven Tyler, revealed that he had suffered from vocal cord damage during a recent concert in New York. This has subsequently led to the postponement of several shows from their much-anticipated “Peace Out” farewell tour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sharing his distress over the situation, Tyler took to the band’s social media platforms, stating, “I’m heartbroken to say I have received strict doctor’s orders not to sing for the next thirty days… We’ll need to postpone a few dates so that we can come back and give you the performance you deserve.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aerosmith’s “Peace Out” tour, marking a capstone for the band’s illustrious 50-year career in the industry, commenced earlier this month in Philadelphia. The tour was set to feature 40 shows, bringing the iconic band’s journey to a close.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In light of Tyler’s injury, concert dates in cities including Detroit, Chicago, Washington, D.C., Toronto, Raleigh, and Cleveland will be rescheduled. The band has assured fans that all previously acquired tickets will be valid for the rearranged dates. Additionally, for those fans unable to adjust to the new dates, refunds have been made available.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This isn’t the first time concerns surrounding Tyler’s health have come to the forefront. In December 2022, Aerosmith had to cancel the concluding shows of their Las Vegas residency. As per the band’s statement at the time, “On the advice of doctors, Steven has to sit these out.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, a few months ago, the band’s Las Vegas residency shows scheduled for June and July were also canceled due to a concerning relapse by Tyler following a foot surgery. The band had then expressed their unwavering support for Tyler’s focus on his health and recovery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the band grapples with the current setback, Steven Tyler is also presently contending with legal issues. He is dealing with a sexual assault lawsuit, an allegation he has vehemently denied.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For now, fans worldwide send their well wishes to Tyler for a swift recovery, hoping to see him back on stage, delivering those iconic performances that have made Aerosmith a global rock phenomenon.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">The rock world was met with a jolt of concern after legendary Aerosmith frontman, Steven Tyler, revealed that he had suffered from vocal cord damage during a recent concert in New York. This has subsequently led to the postponement of several shows from their much-anticipated “Peace Out” farewell tour. Sharing his distress over the situation, Tyler took to the band’s social media platforms, stating, “I’m heartbroken to say I have received strict doctor’s orders not to sing for the next thirty days… We’ll need to postpone a few dates so that we can come back and give you the performance you deserve.” Aerosmith’s “Peace Out” tour, marking a capstone for the band’s illustrious 50-year career in the industry, commenced earlier this month in Philadelphia. The tour was set to feature 40 shows, bringing the iconic band’s journey to a close. In light of Tyler’s injury, concert dates in cities including Detroit, Chicago, Washington, D.C., Toronto, Raleigh, and Cleveland will be rescheduled. The band has assured fans that all previously acquired tickets will be valid for the rearranged dates. Additionally, for those fans unable to adjust to the new dates, refunds have been made available. This isn’t the first time concerns surrounding Tyler’s health have come to the forefront. In December 2022, Aerosmith had to cancel the concluding shows of their Las Vegas residency. As per the band’s statement at the time, “On the advice of doctors, Steven has to sit these out.” Furthermore, a few months ago, the band’s Las Vegas residency shows scheduled for June and July were also canceled due to a concerning relapse by Tyler following a foot surgery. The band had then expressed their unwavering support for Tyler’s focus on his health and recovery. While the band grapples with the current setback, Steven Tyler is also presently contending with legal issues. He is dealing with a sexual assault lawsuit, an allegation he has vehemently denied. For now, fans worldwide send their well wishes to Tyler for a swift recovery, hoping to see him back on stage, delivering those iconic performances that have made Aerosmith a global rock phenomenon.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Granholm’s EV Promotion Hits a Snag - Georgia Family Calls Police Over Inconsiderate Parking</title><link href="/news/2023/09/13/Granholm-EV-Debacle/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Granholm’s EV Promotion Hits a Snag - Georgia Family Calls Police Over Inconsiderate Parking" /><published>2023-09-13T08:12:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-13T08:12:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/13/Granholm-EV-Debacle</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/13/Granholm-EV-Debacle/">&lt;p&gt;Energy Secretary Jennifer Granholm’s ambitious road trip to propagate the benefits of electric vehicles (EVs) hit an unexpected stumbling block. Instead of serving as a successful promotional campaign, the tour, unfortunately, ended up showcasing the evident loopholes in America’s current EV infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Energy Department found itself in a peculiar situation outside a Walmart in Grovetown, Georgia. Intending to charge their fleet of electric vehicles, Granholm’s entourage found the charging stations either occupied or malfunctioning. Ironically, to reserve a spot amidst this chaotic scene, a staff member used a gas-powered vehicle to block an EV charging station.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This seemingly minor decision took a dramatic turn when a family, eager to charge their vehicle, found their access obstructed by the gas-guzzling car. On an oppressively hot day, with an infant in tow, their frustration was entirely justified. Their grievance escalated to the point where they felt compelled to call law enforcement to report the glaring violation of EV charging etiquette.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The whole incident exposes the chinks in the armor of the Biden administration’s push towards promoting EVs. While the Energy Department may be generously doling out billions in grants and loans to foster the transition to electric vehicles, incidents like these shed light on the on-ground challenges that consumers face daily. It’s a pointed reminder that increasing EV production without a simultaneous ramp-up in infrastructure will lead to bottlenecks and dissatisfied users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;John Ryan, an electric BMW driver caught up in the Grovetown fracas, aptly summarized the situation, stating, “They’ll get it together at some point.” However, this episode makes one question whether the administration is truly in tune with the immediate needs and concerns of the average EV user.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ford CEO Jim Farley’s recent “reality check” in California, where he spent 40 minutes at a rest stop charging his EV only to achieve a 40% charge, further amplifies the message: We are not yet ready for the EV revolution if these are the kinds of challenges users encounter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s crucial for the Biden administration and Energy Secretary Jennifer Granholm to understand that mere financial incentives and promotional road trips won’t suffice. The real work lies in creating a robust, user-friendly infrastructure that can support the vision of an EV-dominant future.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Energy Secretary Jennifer Granholm’s ambitious road trip to propagate the benefits of electric vehicles (EVs) hit an unexpected stumbling block. Instead of serving as a successful promotional campaign, the tour, unfortunately, ended up showcasing the evident loopholes in America’s current EV infrastructure. The Energy Department found itself in a peculiar situation outside a Walmart in Grovetown, Georgia. Intending to charge their fleet of electric vehicles, Granholm’s entourage found the charging stations either occupied or malfunctioning. Ironically, to reserve a spot amidst this chaotic scene, a staff member used a gas-powered vehicle to block an EV charging station. This seemingly minor decision took a dramatic turn when a family, eager to charge their vehicle, found their access obstructed by the gas-guzzling car. On an oppressively hot day, with an infant in tow, their frustration was entirely justified. Their grievance escalated to the point where they felt compelled to call law enforcement to report the glaring violation of EV charging etiquette. The whole incident exposes the chinks in the armor of the Biden administration’s push towards promoting EVs. While the Energy Department may be generously doling out billions in grants and loans to foster the transition to electric vehicles, incidents like these shed light on the on-ground challenges that consumers face daily. It’s a pointed reminder that increasing EV production without a simultaneous ramp-up in infrastructure will lead to bottlenecks and dissatisfied users. John Ryan, an electric BMW driver caught up in the Grovetown fracas, aptly summarized the situation, stating, “They’ll get it together at some point.” However, this episode makes one question whether the administration is truly in tune with the immediate needs and concerns of the average EV user. Ford CEO Jim Farley’s recent “reality check” in California, where he spent 40 minutes at a rest stop charging his EV only to achieve a 40% charge, further amplifies the message: We are not yet ready for the EV revolution if these are the kinds of challenges users encounter. It’s crucial for the Biden administration and Energy Secretary Jennifer Granholm to understand that mere financial incentives and promotional road trips won’t suffice. The real work lies in creating a robust, user-friendly infrastructure that can support the vision of an EV-dominant future.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Tim Burton Sounds Alarm on AI - Questions Humanity’s Fate</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/13/Tim-Burton-AI-Warning/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tim Burton Sounds Alarm on AI - Questions Humanity’s Fate" /><published>2023-09-13T07:26:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-13T07:26:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/13/Tim-Burton-AI-Warning</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/13/Tim-Burton-AI-Warning/">&lt;p&gt;Acclaimed filmmaker Tim Burton has raised concerns regarding the rising dominance of artificial intelligence, describing its effect as akin to a robot draining humanity of its essence. This sentiment emerged in light of an experiment where AI-generated images imitated the distinct style Burton is known for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reacting to a Buzzfeed study that employed AI to recreate Disney characters reminiscent of his signature aesthetic, Burton admitted to being deeply unsettled. “When I saw AI’s take on what’s essentially my artistic essence, it felt intrusive, almost as if a piece of my soul was being appropriated,” the director elucidated during an interview with The Independent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Burton’s response to the AI’s replication of his style was visceral. “The notion is somewhat reminiscent of certain cultural beliefs, where capturing a photograph is feared as it’s believed to seize a part of one’s soul,” he explained. He firmly believes that such advancements in technology are verging on extracting the very humanity from individuals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Burton’s apprehensions about AI technology are not solitary in the realm of Hollywood. Notable directors, including James Cameron and Wes Anderson, have previously communicated their reservations about the unchecked advancement of AI. Cameron, known for his futuristic works, voiced concerns that AI might catalyze a global conflict steered not by humans, but algorithms, echoing themes from his own “Terminator” series. He predicted a dire situation where battle theaters could be dominated by AI, operating at a speed beyond human intervention and control.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moreover, director Christopher Nolan also weighed in on the debate, emphasizing the urgency of an “Oppenheimer moment” in AI’s trajectory—a tipping point that, once crossed, would be irreversible. Nolan’s emphasis on accountability resonates with the growing consensus that AI development must be pursued with caution and oversight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a world that’s increasingly dependent on technology, these prominent voices from the entertainment industry reiterate the significance of drawing boundaries and ensuring that human essence remains uncompromised.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Acclaimed filmmaker Tim Burton has raised concerns regarding the rising dominance of artificial intelligence, describing its effect as akin to a robot draining humanity of its essence. This sentiment emerged in light of an experiment where AI-generated images imitated the distinct style Burton is known for. Reacting to a Buzzfeed study that employed AI to recreate Disney characters reminiscent of his signature aesthetic, Burton admitted to being deeply unsettled. “When I saw AI’s take on what’s essentially my artistic essence, it felt intrusive, almost as if a piece of my soul was being appropriated,” the director elucidated during an interview with The Independent. Burton’s response to the AI’s replication of his style was visceral. “The notion is somewhat reminiscent of certain cultural beliefs, where capturing a photograph is feared as it’s believed to seize a part of one’s soul,” he explained. He firmly believes that such advancements in technology are verging on extracting the very humanity from individuals. Burton’s apprehensions about AI technology are not solitary in the realm of Hollywood. Notable directors, including James Cameron and Wes Anderson, have previously communicated their reservations about the unchecked advancement of AI. Cameron, known for his futuristic works, voiced concerns that AI might catalyze a global conflict steered not by humans, but algorithms, echoing themes from his own “Terminator” series. He predicted a dire situation where battle theaters could be dominated by AI, operating at a speed beyond human intervention and control. Moreover, director Christopher Nolan also weighed in on the debate, emphasizing the urgency of an “Oppenheimer moment” in AI’s trajectory—a tipping point that, once crossed, would be irreversible. Nolan’s emphasis on accountability resonates with the growing consensus that AI development must be pursued with caution and oversight. In a world that’s increasingly dependent on technology, these prominent voices from the entertainment industry reiterate the significance of drawing boundaries and ensuring that human essence remains uncompromised.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Unveiling the Biden Saga - Allegations that Rattle the White House</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/13/Biden-Impeachment-Inquiry/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Unveiling the Biden Saga - Allegations that Rattle the White House" /><published>2023-09-13T06:08:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-13T06:08:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/13/Biden-Impeachment-Inquiry</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/13/Biden-Impeachment-Inquiry/">&lt;p&gt;In a shocking twist to the political landscape, House Speaker Kevin McCarthy on Tuesday launched a formal impeachment inquiry against President Biden. The move, announced at the Capitol, underscores a range of serious allegations tied to “abuse of power, obstruction, and corruption.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;McCarthy’s statement sheds light on deeply unsettling details, many of which focus on the Biden family’s foreign business dealings. “Eyewitnesses have testified that the president joined multiple phone calls, interactions, and even dinners, resulting in substantial financial benefits for his sons and their business associates,” McCarthy outlined.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s more, McCarthy presented alarming financial figures. Nearly $20 million, according to bank records, were directed to the Biden family through various shell companies. The Treasury Department itself, he asserted, registered over 150 transactions involving Biden’s family that were flagged as suspicious by U.S. banks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the more disconcerting claims was about a supposed bribe to the Biden family, brought to light by a trusted FBI informant. Moreover, McCarthy alleges that Biden coordinated with his son, Hunter Biden’s business partners, concerning Hunter’s role in Burisma, the well-known Ukrainian energy company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Equally notable was McCarthy’s contention regarding the apparent preferential treatment extended to the Biden family by the current administration. If these allegations hold weight, such favoritism could represent a clear abuse of presidential power.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the midst of these grave allegations, a counter narrative emerged from White House spokesman for oversight and investigations, Ian Sams. Sams labeled the impeachment effort as a politically motivated witch hunt, mentioning, “House Republicans have been investigating the President for 9 months, and they’ve turned up no evidence of wrongdoing.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the gravity and specificity of the allegations presented by McCarthy cast a long shadow of doubt. With the commencement of the impeachment inquiry, the American public looks forward to a thorough, unbiased, and transparent investigation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The impeachment process is significant; it’s not just a political tool but a mechanism to ensure the integrity and accountability of the highest office in the land. For the sake of the nation’s future and to uphold the principles of justice and transparency, it is imperative that the truth behind these allegations comes to light.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a shocking twist to the political landscape, House Speaker Kevin McCarthy on Tuesday launched a formal impeachment inquiry against President Biden. The move, announced at the Capitol, underscores a range of serious allegations tied to “abuse of power, obstruction, and corruption.” McCarthy’s statement sheds light on deeply unsettling details, many of which focus on the Biden family’s foreign business dealings. “Eyewitnesses have testified that the president joined multiple phone calls, interactions, and even dinners, resulting in substantial financial benefits for his sons and their business associates,” McCarthy outlined. What’s more, McCarthy presented alarming financial figures. Nearly $20 million, according to bank records, were directed to the Biden family through various shell companies. The Treasury Department itself, he asserted, registered over 150 transactions involving Biden’s family that were flagged as suspicious by U.S. banks. One of the more disconcerting claims was about a supposed bribe to the Biden family, brought to light by a trusted FBI informant. Moreover, McCarthy alleges that Biden coordinated with his son, Hunter Biden’s business partners, concerning Hunter’s role in Burisma, the well-known Ukrainian energy company. Equally notable was McCarthy’s contention regarding the apparent preferential treatment extended to the Biden family by the current administration. If these allegations hold weight, such favoritism could represent a clear abuse of presidential power. In the midst of these grave allegations, a counter narrative emerged from White House spokesman for oversight and investigations, Ian Sams. Sams labeled the impeachment effort as a politically motivated witch hunt, mentioning, “House Republicans have been investigating the President for 9 months, and they’ve turned up no evidence of wrongdoing.” However, the gravity and specificity of the allegations presented by McCarthy cast a long shadow of doubt. With the commencement of the impeachment inquiry, the American public looks forward to a thorough, unbiased, and transparent investigation. The impeachment process is significant; it’s not just a political tool but a mechanism to ensure the integrity and accountability of the highest office in the land. For the sake of the nation’s future and to uphold the principles of justice and transparency, it is imperative that the truth behind these allegations comes to light.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">NYPD Under Siege - Mayor Eric Adams Cuts Police Overtime Amid Mounting Challenges</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/12/NYC-Police-Overtime-Cut/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="NYPD Under Siege - Mayor Eric Adams Cuts Police Overtime Amid Mounting Challenges" /><published>2023-09-12T17:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-12T17:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/12/NYC-Police-Overtime-Cut</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/12/NYC-Police-Overtime-Cut/">&lt;p&gt;Under the pretext of addressing New York City’s growing migrant crisis, Mayor Eric Adams has taken a contentious step by slashing overtime pay for essential city departments, most notably for the police. This move comes at a time when the police department is already grappling with understaffing, reflecting a wider trend of miscalculated priorities in city leadership.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;policy-decisions-in-question&quot;&gt;Policy Decisions in Question&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the movement to reallocate police funding has gained some traction, the consequences of such decisions are manifesting on the streets. The NYPD, already under pressure from rising crime rates and budgetary constraints, now faces further challenges with the recent policy changes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“If City Hall wants to save money without jeopardizing public safety, it needs to invest in keeping experienced cops on the job,” states Patrick Hendry of the Police Benevolent Association, echoing the concerns of many.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;juggling-priorities-with-safety-at-stake&quot;&gt;Juggling Priorities with Safety at Stake&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rather than formulating comprehensive solutions to the migrant issue, Adams’ administration seems to have resorted to a short-sighted approach. The vast resources being directed towards migrant housing is starting to overshadow essential city services. While some migrants might express satisfaction with their housing amenities in NYC, it begs the question: at what cost? The balance between fiscal responsibility and maintaining public safety seems to be tipping in an unfavorable direction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moreover, the lack of a coherent strategy in managing the influx is evident in Mayor Adams’ varied descriptions of the situation - from a “financial tsunami” to the potential risks in shelters. The reactive nature of these policies points to a lack of foresight and strategic planning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-call-for-thoughtful-governance&quot;&gt;A Call for Thoughtful Governance&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cities like New York need leadership that places safety, security, and fiscal prudence at the forefront. Addressing the migrant crisis with humane and effective solutions is vital, but not at the expense of public safety.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mayor Adams’ recent decisions underscore the challenges of city governance, where abstract ideals can sometimes overshadow the practical needs of the people. NYC residents deserve well-thought-out policies that prioritize their well-being.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Under the pretext of addressing New York City’s growing migrant crisis, Mayor Eric Adams has taken a contentious step by slashing overtime pay for essential city departments, most notably for the police. This move comes at a time when the police department is already grappling with understaffing, reflecting a wider trend of miscalculated priorities in city leadership. Policy Decisions in Question While the movement to reallocate police funding has gained some traction, the consequences of such decisions are manifesting on the streets. The NYPD, already under pressure from rising crime rates and budgetary constraints, now faces further challenges with the recent policy changes. “If City Hall wants to save money without jeopardizing public safety, it needs to invest in keeping experienced cops on the job,” states Patrick Hendry of the Police Benevolent Association, echoing the concerns of many. Juggling Priorities with Safety at Stake Rather than formulating comprehensive solutions to the migrant issue, Adams’ administration seems to have resorted to a short-sighted approach. The vast resources being directed towards migrant housing is starting to overshadow essential city services. While some migrants might express satisfaction with their housing amenities in NYC, it begs the question: at what cost? The balance between fiscal responsibility and maintaining public safety seems to be tipping in an unfavorable direction. Moreover, the lack of a coherent strategy in managing the influx is evident in Mayor Adams’ varied descriptions of the situation - from a “financial tsunami” to the potential risks in shelters. The reactive nature of these policies points to a lack of foresight and strategic planning. A Call for Thoughtful Governance Cities like New York need leadership that places safety, security, and fiscal prudence at the forefront. Addressing the migrant crisis with humane and effective solutions is vital, but not at the expense of public safety. Mayor Adams’ recent decisions underscore the challenges of city governance, where abstract ideals can sometimes overshadow the practical needs of the people. NYC residents deserve well-thought-out policies that prioritize their well-being.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Desperate Days for Pennsylvania Fugitive</title><link href="/news/2023/09/12/Desperate-Escape/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Desperate Days for Pennsylvania Fugitive" /><published>2023-09-12T16:01:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-12T16:01:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/12/Desperate-Escape</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/12/Desperate-Escape/">&lt;p&gt;As days go by, the desperation seems to grow for Danelo Cavalcante, a fugitive in Pennsylvania who has been evading authorities for almost two weeks. Pennsylvania police indicate that their net might be closing in, but Cavalcante is pulling out all stops to remain a step ahead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cavalcante’s escape from Chester County Prison, near Philadelphia, took place on August 31, following his conviction for the murder of his ex-girlfriend in 2021. The 34-year-old’s tactics to remain hidden seem to grow more daring with each passing day. Not only did he manage to slip past a heavily guarded police perimeter around Longwood Gardens botanical park, but he also took the audacious step of reaching out to former colleagues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2023/09/720/405/Danelo-Cavalcante-clean-shaven-thumb.jpg?ve=1&amp;amp;tl=1&quot; alt=&quot;Manhunt Continues&quot; /&gt;(Pennsylvania State Police / Chester County Prison)
&lt;em&gt;The search intensifies as Cavalcante’s desperation becomes evident.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lt. Col. George Bivens of the Pennsylvania State Police weighed in on the situation. “His actions speak volumes about his desperation,” Bivens said. “It seems there wasn’t much premeditation in his escape. He’s now on the run, possibly without a strong support system, given that he’s reaching out to people he hasn’t been in touch with for a long time.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A recent encounter provides a glimpse into his current situation. Cavalcante altered his appearance, stole a van from a dairy farm, and drove over 20 miles, reaching out to two of his former co-workers in East Pikeland Township and Phoenixville. His changed look, comprising a clean shave, a colored hoodie, green prison pants, and white shoes, was captured on a doorbell camera.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2023/09/720/405/Cavalcante.jpg?ve=1&amp;amp;tl=1&quot; alt=&quot;Surveillance Image&quot; /&gt;(AP Photo/Matt Rourke)
&lt;em&gt;Security footage aids law enforcement in tracking Cavalcante’s movements.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a twist, immigration authorities have detained Eleni Cavalcante, the fugitive’s sister. However, she seems less than inclined to assist in tracking her brother down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cavalcante’s escape has had repercussions for prison staff as well. The guard on duty during Cavalcante’s dramatic exit – seen on surveillance footage as he adeptly crab-walked a wall in the prison yard – has been dismissed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Authorities remain on high alert, given Cavalcante’s history. “Given his background, it’s only prudent to assume he might be armed and dangerous,” Bivens commented.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back in his native Brazil, Cavalcante is no stranger to the law. He’s sought for a “double qualified homicide” over a vehicle repair-related debt that culminated in the death of Válter Júnior Moreira dos Reis in 2017.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the manhunt intensifies, the central message from the authorities remains clear: aiding Cavalcante in any form could have dire consequences, and the desperate fugitive should be approached with utmost caution.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">As days go by, the desperation seems to grow for Danelo Cavalcante, a fugitive in Pennsylvania who has been evading authorities for almost two weeks. Pennsylvania police indicate that their net might be closing in, but Cavalcante is pulling out all stops to remain a step ahead. Cavalcante’s escape from Chester County Prison, near Philadelphia, took place on August 31, following his conviction for the murder of his ex-girlfriend in 2021. The 34-year-old’s tactics to remain hidden seem to grow more daring with each passing day. Not only did he manage to slip past a heavily guarded police perimeter around Longwood Gardens botanical park, but he also took the audacious step of reaching out to former colleagues. (Pennsylvania State Police / Chester County Prison) The search intensifies as Cavalcante’s desperation becomes evident. Lt. Col. George Bivens of the Pennsylvania State Police weighed in on the situation. “His actions speak volumes about his desperation,” Bivens said. “It seems there wasn’t much premeditation in his escape. He’s now on the run, possibly without a strong support system, given that he’s reaching out to people he hasn’t been in touch with for a long time.” A recent encounter provides a glimpse into his current situation. Cavalcante altered his appearance, stole a van from a dairy farm, and drove over 20 miles, reaching out to two of his former co-workers in East Pikeland Township and Phoenixville. His changed look, comprising a clean shave, a colored hoodie, green prison pants, and white shoes, was captured on a doorbell camera. (AP Photo/Matt Rourke) Security footage aids law enforcement in tracking Cavalcante’s movements. In a twist, immigration authorities have detained Eleni Cavalcante, the fugitive’s sister. However, she seems less than inclined to assist in tracking her brother down. Cavalcante’s escape has had repercussions for prison staff as well. The guard on duty during Cavalcante’s dramatic exit – seen on surveillance footage as he adeptly crab-walked a wall in the prison yard – has been dismissed. Authorities remain on high alert, given Cavalcante’s history. “Given his background, it’s only prudent to assume he might be armed and dangerous,” Bivens commented. Back in his native Brazil, Cavalcante is no stranger to the law. He’s sought for a “double qualified homicide” over a vehicle repair-related debt that culminated in the death of Válter Júnior Moreira dos Reis in 2017. While the manhunt intensifies, the central message from the authorities remains clear: aiding Cavalcante in any form could have dire consequences, and the desperate fugitive should be approached with utmost caution.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Fact Check - Did Biden Visit Ground Zero on September 12, 2001?</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/12/Biden-Ground-Zero-Claim/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Fact Check - Did Biden Visit Ground Zero on September 12, 2001?" /><published>2023-09-12T15:02:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-12T15:02:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/12/Biden-Ground-Zero-Claim</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/12/Biden-Ground-Zero-Claim/">&lt;p&gt;President Joe Biden, during a recent address at Joint Base Elmendorf-Richardson in Anchorage, Alaska, made a claim that raised eyebrows. He stated that he was present at Ground Zero in New York City on September 12, 2001, a day after the horrific attacks on the World Trade Centers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I remember standing there the next day and looking at the building,” the President recollected. The vivid description he offered was as if “looking through the gates of hell.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, records and archival material from that time tell a different story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On September 12, 2001, Biden, then a U.S. Senator, was with his Senate colleagues and delivered a 10-minute speech addressing the attacks. He was recorded stating, “Some have said, yesterday and today, that all has changed for America… but I pray that is not true … the one thing we cannot allow to change are the values upon which this country is built, for if that were to occur, then they would be able to declare victory.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Additionally, Biden, in unity with all his Senate colleagues, voted to pass a resolution that officially condemned the acts of terror on that fateful day. It wasn’t until September 20, 2001, that Biden made his first confirmed visit to Ground Zero, joining a group of senators to witness the aftermath of the terror strike.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These inconsistencies have brought Biden’s comments under scrutiny. Furthermore, Biden’s decision to commemorate the 9/11 anniversary in Alaska, instead of at the actual attack sites in New York City, Virginia, or Pennsylvania, has also generated debate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given the sensitive nature and the magnitude of the events surrounding 9/11, it remains essential to maintain the accuracy of accounts related to it. As the nation remembers and pays tribute to the lives lost, ensuring a factual retelling of events honors their memory.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">President Joe Biden, during a recent address at Joint Base Elmendorf-Richardson in Anchorage, Alaska, made a claim that raised eyebrows. He stated that he was present at Ground Zero in New York City on September 12, 2001, a day after the horrific attacks on the World Trade Centers. “I remember standing there the next day and looking at the building,” the President recollected. The vivid description he offered was as if “looking through the gates of hell.” However, records and archival material from that time tell a different story. On September 12, 2001, Biden, then a U.S. Senator, was with his Senate colleagues and delivered a 10-minute speech addressing the attacks. He was recorded stating, “Some have said, yesterday and today, that all has changed for America… but I pray that is not true … the one thing we cannot allow to change are the values upon which this country is built, for if that were to occur, then they would be able to declare victory.” Additionally, Biden, in unity with all his Senate colleagues, voted to pass a resolution that officially condemned the acts of terror on that fateful day. It wasn’t until September 20, 2001, that Biden made his first confirmed visit to Ground Zero, joining a group of senators to witness the aftermath of the terror strike. These inconsistencies have brought Biden’s comments under scrutiny. Furthermore, Biden’s decision to commemorate the 9/11 anniversary in Alaska, instead of at the actual attack sites in New York City, Virginia, or Pennsylvania, has also generated debate. Given the sensitive nature and the magnitude of the events surrounding 9/11, it remains essential to maintain the accuracy of accounts related to it. As the nation remembers and pays tribute to the lives lost, ensuring a factual retelling of events honors their memory.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The AI Detection Dilemma - ChatGPT Developer Spills the Beans</title><link href="/news/2023/09/12/AI-Detection-Fallacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The AI Detection Dilemma - ChatGPT Developer Spills the Beans" /><published>2023-09-12T14:05:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-12T14:05:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/12/AI-Detection-Fallacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/12/AI-Detection-Fallacy/">&lt;p&gt;OpenAI, the genius minds behind the widely-used AI chatbot ChatGPT, recently dropped a truth bomb on the tech community. AI writing detectors, hailed as the tools of the future, aren’t as adept at their jobs as we once believed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to a disclosure in an FAQ section attached to an educational promotional blog, OpenAI confirmed a long-held suspicion within the industry - AI writing detectors are underperformers. “While some organizations, including ours, have rolled out tools claiming to detect AI-generated content, none have consistently demonstrated an ability to distinguish AI-written text from human prose,” stated OpenAI.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This news isn’t entirely a shock. Detectors, earlier labeled as “mostly illusionary solutions,” have been under the scanner for often marking false positives. Their shaky credibility arises from their dependency on untested detection methods. OpenAI’s short-lived experiment, the AI Classifier, intended to spot AI-crafted content, was discarded after a lackluster performance rate of 26%. This debacle draws even more attention when considering that certain educators have failed whole student batches, accusing them of employing ChatGPT for academic essays.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;OpenAI’s FAQ further dispelled a widespread myth: ChatGPT’s capability to recognize AI-generated content. The company clarified, “ChatGPT doesn’t possess the ‘awareness’ to determine if a text is AI-created. Its answers to queries such as ‘did you pen this [paper]?’ or ‘could AI have authored this?’ are whimsical and lack factual grounding.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The firm also advised against exclusively depending on ChatGPT for research-oriented tasks. “ChatGPT may sound persuasive at times, but it can occasionally relay incorrect or misleading data (often termed a ‘hallucination’ in scholarly circles),” OpenAI warned. This advisory emerges after a lawyer cited non-existent legal cases, misled by ChatGPT’s responses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet, all’s not lost. While automated AI sniffers might falter, human discernment remains invaluable. Educators acquainted with a student’s writing flair can frequently spot abrupt shifts. Additionally, certain AI-generated content, especially from ChatGPT, can betray itself with characteristic hints, such as repetitive phrases, hinting at a copy-paste job.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">OpenAI, the genius minds behind the widely-used AI chatbot ChatGPT, recently dropped a truth bomb on the tech community. AI writing detectors, hailed as the tools of the future, aren’t as adept at their jobs as we once believed. According to a disclosure in an FAQ section attached to an educational promotional blog, OpenAI confirmed a long-held suspicion within the industry - AI writing detectors are underperformers. “While some organizations, including ours, have rolled out tools claiming to detect AI-generated content, none have consistently demonstrated an ability to distinguish AI-written text from human prose,” stated OpenAI. This news isn’t entirely a shock. Detectors, earlier labeled as “mostly illusionary solutions,” have been under the scanner for often marking false positives. Their shaky credibility arises from their dependency on untested detection methods. OpenAI’s short-lived experiment, the AI Classifier, intended to spot AI-crafted content, was discarded after a lackluster performance rate of 26%. This debacle draws even more attention when considering that certain educators have failed whole student batches, accusing them of employing ChatGPT for academic essays. OpenAI’s FAQ further dispelled a widespread myth: ChatGPT’s capability to recognize AI-generated content. The company clarified, “ChatGPT doesn’t possess the ‘awareness’ to determine if a text is AI-created. Its answers to queries such as ‘did you pen this [paper]?’ or ‘could AI have authored this?’ are whimsical and lack factual grounding.” The firm also advised against exclusively depending on ChatGPT for research-oriented tasks. “ChatGPT may sound persuasive at times, but it can occasionally relay incorrect or misleading data (often termed a ‘hallucination’ in scholarly circles),” OpenAI warned. This advisory emerges after a lawyer cited non-existent legal cases, misled by ChatGPT’s responses. Yet, all’s not lost. While automated AI sniffers might falter, human discernment remains invaluable. Educators acquainted with a student’s writing flair can frequently spot abrupt shifts. Additionally, certain AI-generated content, especially from ChatGPT, can betray itself with characteristic hints, such as repetitive phrases, hinting at a copy-paste job.</summary></entry></feed>