<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-10-20T13:12:32-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/20/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-20T13:12:32-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-20T13:12:32-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/20/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/20/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/20/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-20T13:12:32-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-20T13:12:32-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/20/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/20/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/">&lt;p&gt;Recent surprise attacks by Hamas on Israel has fueled ongoing tensions between staunchly conservative commentators and the progressive “Squad” Democrats known for criticizing Israel. The intensity of the backlash highlights the deep political divide over foreign policy in the Middle East.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Hamas’ shocking attack, several members of the “Squad,” including Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.), called for a “ceasefire and de-escalation,” condemning the violence. The absence of a statement from Rep. Rashida Tlaib (D-Mich.) was notably called out by conservative media outlets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;South Carolina GOP Rep. Nancy Mace quickly labeled Ocasio-Cortez a “Hamas apologist” in response to her call for peace and de-escalation. Rep. Ilhan Omar (D-Minn.), no stranger to controversy surrounding her views on Israel, echoed the call for de-escalation and ceasefire. Omar’s prior statements comparing the US and Israel to terrorist groups like Hamas and the Taliban resurfaced in the debate, fueling more criticisms. Omar’s 2019 tweet, where she opined that “Israel has hypnotized the world,” also continues to haunt her political career, often cited by critics to challenge her stance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conservative commentators have been especially vocal. “FOX &amp;amp; Friends Weekend” co-host Rachel Campos-Duffy took aim at Omar, saying she fails to recognize the peace in the Middle East under Trump’s administration. Conservative pundit John Hasson also called out Omar, claiming she insinuated that attacks on IDF forces were acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Massachusetts Democrat Rep. Ayanna Pressley’s concerns over the “devastating attacks on Israelis” were met with skepticism. A prominent conservative online personality, Comfortably Smug, accused the “Squad” of advising Israel to back down after the nation suffered massive attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Jamaal Bowman’s call for an end to the Gaza blockade, in addition to condemning the Hamas attacks, was met with criticism from conservative radio host Jason Rantz. He accused Bowman of pairing his condemnation of terrorism with unwarranted criticisms of Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Cori Bush emphasized the urgent need for a ceasefire, while pushing for an end to “U.S. support for Israeli military occupation and apartheid.” Defense attorney Marina Medvin criticized Bush, suggesting that she equates the death of Palestinian terrorists to the horrific acts committed against Jewish civilians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amidst the political turmoil and intense debate, the attacks have taken a heavy toll. Israeli media report over 300 dead due to the wide-ranging assault. Gaza health officials note that at least 200 Palestinians have perished in the retaliatory Israeli air strikes following the initial Hamas attack. As the situation remains volatile, both sides continue to count their casualties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This divisive issue showcases the challenge America faces in crafting a unified approach to foreign policy, with deeply entrenched political divides at play. As the situation develops, the debate is bound to intensify, shedding light on the complexities of U.S. politics in the global arena.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Biden’s Alarming Silence: US Forces Under Attack</title><link href="/news/2023/10/20/Biden-Silence-Attacks/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Biden’s Alarming Silence: US Forces Under Attack" /><published>2023-10-20T13:04:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-20T13:04:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/20/Biden-Silence-Attacks</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/20/Biden-Silence-Attacks/">&lt;p&gt;In a shocking display of seeming negligence, President Joe Biden has failed to publicly address a series of attacks on U.S. forces in Iraq and Syria. Within the past 48 hours, our troops have faced at least seven targeted aggressions, and the nation’s Commander in Chief has been eerily silent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reports confirm that U.S. officials have been aware of the continued attacks in the region, particularly with the ongoing tensions sparked by the Israel-Hamas conflict. A drone strike resulted in minor injuries for U.S. forces stationed in Syria. Another alarming incident involved a false alarm at the Al-Asad airbase in Iraq, during which a civilian contractor tragically succumbed to a cardiac arrest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite dispatching naval reinforcements to the Middle East, including two aircraft carriers, warships, and approximately 2,000 Marines, Biden has yet to comment on the situation or offer a strategic response. The pressing question is: Why the conspicuous silence?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Ain al-Asad airbase, hosting U.S. and other international forces, has been at the epicenter of these attacks. The base experienced a barrage of drones and rockets, with multiple explosions reported within its confines. Another U.S. military base near Baghdad’s international airport has also been targeted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pentagon spokesperson, Brigadier General Patrick Ryder, refrained from speculating about potential reactions to these onslaughts. However, he assured that the U.S. would take all necessary steps to protect its forces and coalition allies. Ryder emphasized that any potential response would occur “at a time in a manner of our choosing.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As tensions flare in the region, it’s essential to underscore the considerable civilian casualties. Since Hamas’s assault on southern Israel, approximately 1,400 individuals, primarily civilians, have lost their lives. The Palestinian enclave of the Gaza Strip has faced nonstop bombardments, resulting in significant Palestinian casualties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Ryder has stated that there isn’t a direct connection between the increase in attacks on U.S. troops and the Israel-Hamas conflict, the correlation is hard to ignore. Tensions in Iraq regarding the war in Gaza have notably surged, with influential figures condemning Israel’s actions and calling for global intervention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Iranian-backed militias, known for targeting U.S. forces in Iraq and the U.S. embassy in Baghdad in the past, might be behind these recent drone strikes. Such militias had previously adhered to a truce, allowing Iraq to experience a period of relative calm. But the current circumstances and heightened sentiments could easily disrupt this fragile peace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With U.S. forces enduring consistent attacks and mounting regional tensions, President Biden’s silence is concerning. The nation looks to its leader for reassurance, strategy, and action during times of crisis. But as our brave soldiers stand their ground overseas, they await a word from their Commander in Chief.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a shocking display of seeming negligence, President Joe Biden has failed to publicly address a series of attacks on U.S. forces in Iraq and Syria. Within the past 48 hours, our troops have faced at least seven targeted aggressions, and the nation’s Commander in Chief has been eerily silent. Reports confirm that U.S. officials have been aware of the continued attacks in the region, particularly with the ongoing tensions sparked by the Israel-Hamas conflict. A drone strike resulted in minor injuries for U.S. forces stationed in Syria. Another alarming incident involved a false alarm at the Al-Asad airbase in Iraq, during which a civilian contractor tragically succumbed to a cardiac arrest. Despite dispatching naval reinforcements to the Middle East, including two aircraft carriers, warships, and approximately 2,000 Marines, Biden has yet to comment on the situation or offer a strategic response. The pressing question is: Why the conspicuous silence? The Ain al-Asad airbase, hosting U.S. and other international forces, has been at the epicenter of these attacks. The base experienced a barrage of drones and rockets, with multiple explosions reported within its confines. Another U.S. military base near Baghdad’s international airport has also been targeted. Pentagon spokesperson, Brigadier General Patrick Ryder, refrained from speculating about potential reactions to these onslaughts. However, he assured that the U.S. would take all necessary steps to protect its forces and coalition allies. Ryder emphasized that any potential response would occur “at a time in a manner of our choosing.” As tensions flare in the region, it’s essential to underscore the considerable civilian casualties. Since Hamas’s assault on southern Israel, approximately 1,400 individuals, primarily civilians, have lost their lives. The Palestinian enclave of the Gaza Strip has faced nonstop bombardments, resulting in significant Palestinian casualties. While Ryder has stated that there isn’t a direct connection between the increase in attacks on U.S. troops and the Israel-Hamas conflict, the correlation is hard to ignore. Tensions in Iraq regarding the war in Gaza have notably surged, with influential figures condemning Israel’s actions and calling for global intervention. Iranian-backed militias, known for targeting U.S. forces in Iraq and the U.S. embassy in Baghdad in the past, might be behind these recent drone strikes. Such militias had previously adhered to a truce, allowing Iraq to experience a period of relative calm. But the current circumstances and heightened sentiments could easily disrupt this fragile peace. With U.S. forces enduring consistent attacks and mounting regional tensions, President Biden’s silence is concerning. The nation looks to its leader for reassurance, strategy, and action during times of crisis. But as our brave soldiers stand their ground overseas, they await a word from their Commander in Chief.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Governor Sanders’ Bold Move Against ‘Woke’ Language</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/20/Sanders-Woke-Language/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Governor Sanders’ Bold Move Against ‘Woke’ Language" /><published>2023-10-20T11:57:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-20T11:57:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/20/Sanders-Woke-Language</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/20/Sanders-Woke-Language/">&lt;p&gt;In a decisive move against what many term as “woke” language, Gov. Sarah Huckabee Sanders of Arkansas is introducing an executive order that mandates the use of gender-specific language, specifically when addressing women. This act emerges as a strong stand against the increasing trend of adopting gender-neutral terms in governmental communication.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The science is clear and real; There are things only women can do, like perform the miracle of birth,” Sanders expressed in the executive order. She emphasized that government documentation should “celebrate gender distinctions between men and women — not erase them.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This order is primarily a reaction to the nation-wide effort to adopt what is dubbed as “culturally conscious” or “inclusive” language. Such changes frequently attempt to remove traditional gender associations from words. One specific instance this spring showcased the Arkansas Department of Health describing potential negative effects on “pregnant people.” Sanders’ order will now necessitate the usage of the terms “pregnant women” or “pregnant mom.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The executive order further clarifies the preferred language for other scenarios:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Instead of “menstruating person” or “menstruating people”, use “woman” or “women.”&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Rather than “birthing person”, the term should be “birth mom.”&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;“Chestfeeding” should be replaced with “breastfeeding.”&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Instead of “laboring person,” use “birth mom,” and “woman” in place of “birth-giver.”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sanders, who holds the distinction of being the first female governor of Arkansas, has been consistently vocal against the removal of feminine associations from terms traditionally used for women. She notably criticized President Biden, stating that he became “the first man to surrender his presidency to a woke mob that can’t tell you what a woman is.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The trend of adjusting gender-specific terms is not unique to Arkansas. For instance, Portland, Oregon, recently encouraged its city staff to embrace a more “culturally conscious” vocabulary. This adjustment included avoiding the use of words like “women,” “Caucasian,” and “citizen.” Similarly, educational institutions across the nation are adapting their curriculums to mirror this trend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sanders, however, is determined to push back against these changes, voicing her concerns at the executive order’s signing ceremony. She is expected to state, “Enough trying to erase women and girls. Enough denying our biological differences from men.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This bold step by Gov. Sanders is sure to spark extensive debate both in Arkansas and across the nation. With tensions rising over the balance between tradition and inclusivity, this executive order may serve as a tipping point in the ongoing discourse about “woke” language in America.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a decisive move against what many term as “woke” language, Gov. Sarah Huckabee Sanders of Arkansas is introducing an executive order that mandates the use of gender-specific language, specifically when addressing women. This act emerges as a strong stand against the increasing trend of adopting gender-neutral terms in governmental communication. “The science is clear and real; There are things only women can do, like perform the miracle of birth,” Sanders expressed in the executive order. She emphasized that government documentation should “celebrate gender distinctions between men and women — not erase them.” This order is primarily a reaction to the nation-wide effort to adopt what is dubbed as “culturally conscious” or “inclusive” language. Such changes frequently attempt to remove traditional gender associations from words. One specific instance this spring showcased the Arkansas Department of Health describing potential negative effects on “pregnant people.” Sanders’ order will now necessitate the usage of the terms “pregnant women” or “pregnant mom.” The executive order further clarifies the preferred language for other scenarios: Instead of “menstruating person” or “menstruating people”, use “woman” or “women.” Rather than “birthing person”, the term should be “birth mom.” “Chestfeeding” should be replaced with “breastfeeding.” Instead of “laboring person,” use “birth mom,” and “woman” in place of “birth-giver.” Sanders, who holds the distinction of being the first female governor of Arkansas, has been consistently vocal against the removal of feminine associations from terms traditionally used for women. She notably criticized President Biden, stating that he became “the first man to surrender his presidency to a woke mob that can’t tell you what a woman is.” The trend of adjusting gender-specific terms is not unique to Arkansas. For instance, Portland, Oregon, recently encouraged its city staff to embrace a more “culturally conscious” vocabulary. This adjustment included avoiding the use of words like “women,” “Caucasian,” and “citizen.” Similarly, educational institutions across the nation are adapting their curriculums to mirror this trend. Sanders, however, is determined to push back against these changes, voicing her concerns at the executive order’s signing ceremony. She is expected to state, “Enough trying to erase women and girls. Enough denying our biological differences from men.” This bold step by Gov. Sanders is sure to spark extensive debate both in Arkansas and across the nation. With tensions rising over the balance between tradition and inclusivity, this executive order may serve as a tipping point in the ongoing discourse about “woke” language in America.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Biden’s Incoherence: Spotlight on the Israel Press Conference</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/20/Biden-Israel-Conference/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Biden’s Incoherence: Spotlight on the Israel Press Conference" /><published>2023-10-20T10:34:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-20T10:34:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/20/Biden-Israel-Conference</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/20/Biden-Israel-Conference/">&lt;p&gt;In a recent press conference held in Tel Aviv, President Joe Biden’s cognitive abilities have been brought into sharp focus. Critics, including Oscar-nominated actor James Woods, voiced significant concerns regarding Biden’s apparent inability to maintain coherence during his speech.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While seated next to Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu, Biden, despite relying on prepared notecards, seemed to drift off-topic, ultimately appearing to lose his way entirely. Such instances intensify worries surrounding his mental fitness, with Woods even pointing to Biden’s “obvious dementia”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Woods, who has never been one to mince his words, labeled Biden as a “crooked hack” following this event. He further criticized Biden for his ambiguous terminology, particularly his use of the term “other team” in lieu of directly addressing the terrorists affecting Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond these remarks, the conference’s content itself was newsworthy. Biden announced a whopping $100 million in humanitarian aid for Gaza and the West Bank. This move is seen by some as further evidence of Biden’s shifting stance on Israel. Recent works, such as Alex Marlow’s book “Breaking Biden”, highlight alleged harm the current US President has directed towards Israel, including efforts to rejuvenate the Iran Nuclear Deal. Moreover, claims have been made of Biden staffing the Pentagon with so-called “experts” who were later revealed to have ties to Iran.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Critics argue that this is not merely an isolated event, but rather a continued pattern of Biden’s inadequacy to govern effectively, with Woods even suggesting that “the fate of mankind is at stake” with Biden at the helm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s imperative to stay informed, critically assess our leaders, and ensure transparency and efficacy in governance. Only through scrutiny and holding our leaders accountable can we hope to pave a path forward that aligns with the best interests of the people.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">In a recent press conference held in Tel Aviv, President Joe Biden’s cognitive abilities have been brought into sharp focus. Critics, including Oscar-nominated actor James Woods, voiced significant concerns regarding Biden’s apparent inability to maintain coherence during his speech. While seated next to Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu, Biden, despite relying on prepared notecards, seemed to drift off-topic, ultimately appearing to lose his way entirely. Such instances intensify worries surrounding his mental fitness, with Woods even pointing to Biden’s “obvious dementia”. Woods, who has never been one to mince his words, labeled Biden as a “crooked hack” following this event. He further criticized Biden for his ambiguous terminology, particularly his use of the term “other team” in lieu of directly addressing the terrorists affecting Israel. Beyond these remarks, the conference’s content itself was newsworthy. Biden announced a whopping $100 million in humanitarian aid for Gaza and the West Bank. This move is seen by some as further evidence of Biden’s shifting stance on Israel. Recent works, such as Alex Marlow’s book “Breaking Biden”, highlight alleged harm the current US President has directed towards Israel, including efforts to rejuvenate the Iran Nuclear Deal. Moreover, claims have been made of Biden staffing the Pentagon with so-called “experts” who were later revealed to have ties to Iran. Critics argue that this is not merely an isolated event, but rather a continued pattern of Biden’s inadequacy to govern effectively, with Woods even suggesting that “the fate of mankind is at stake” with Biden at the helm. It’s imperative to stay informed, critically assess our leaders, and ensure transparency and efficacy in governance. Only through scrutiny and holding our leaders accountable can we hope to pave a path forward that aligns with the best interests of the people.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Louisiana Upset: A Red Tide Rising?</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/20/Louisiana-Election-Shockwave/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Louisiana Upset: A Red Tide Rising?" /><published>2023-10-20T09:24:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-20T09:24:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/20/Louisiana-Election-Shockwave</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/20/Louisiana-Election-Shockwave/">&lt;p&gt;In a twist that has sent shockwaves through the political arena, Governor-Elect Jeff Landry’s (R-LA) recent victory in Louisiana’s open gubernatorial primary has cast new shadows over the Democrats’ national aspirations. Landry’s win is seen not just as a singular event, but as a barometer of the political climate shifting in favor of the Republicans as 2024 approaches.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Previously serving as Louisiana’s attorney general, Landry took the spotlight with an impressive 52 percent majority, eliminating the need for a November runoff. This outright win is made more significant by the fact that he had been endorsed by former President Donald Trump.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Various factors played into Landry’s win. A reported low turnout, not seen in a decade, along with a lackluster response to his top Democrat opponent, Shawn Wilson, made the Republican’s ascent all the more notable. Surprisingly, turnout among black voters was low, but those who did vote showed substantial support for Landry, a Republican.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Longtime grassroots Republican activist, Debbie Dooley, shed light on the broader implications of this victory for both Democrats and Republicans. Highlighting the lack of enthusiasm among black voters for Democrats and Landry’s unexpected support from the black community, she points to current President Joe Biden’s policies, which many critics argue are detrimental to working-class Americans.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The narrative is clear: widespread dissatisfaction with rising inflation and diminishing purchasing power. With mounting gas and food prices, Dooley emphasizes a crucial question: Why would the average American support policies causing such discomfort?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moreover, Dooley stresses an alarming enthusiasm among MAGA voters in Louisiana, suggesting that Democrats should be concerned. The overwhelming support for an amendment banning private funds in election facilitation is an indicator of shifting sands in voter preferences and priorities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Several pundits argue that Landry’s victory, given his endorsement by Trump, signifies a strong rallying call for Republicans to unite behind Trump’s leadership. After all, polls leading up to the election had not predicted Landry’s outright win, which brings into question the reliability of current polling methodologies, especially with respect to “silent” Trump supporters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Political adviser to Landry, Brent Littlefield, commented on the unique combination of national dissatisfaction with the Biden administration and local issues that Landry championed, making his campaign successful. He also highlighted Landry’s unwavering commitment to addressing concerns closest to the hearts of Louisiana’s residents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Democrats grapple with the implications of this unexpected turn of events, Republicans view it as a herald of a resurgent red tide. The shifting allegiances and priorities of voters, even in traditionally blue areas, indicate an evolving political landscape as we head towards 2024. With the winds of change blowing, all eyes are now on how both parties will recalibrate their strategies in the coming months.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a twist that has sent shockwaves through the political arena, Governor-Elect Jeff Landry’s (R-LA) recent victory in Louisiana’s open gubernatorial primary has cast new shadows over the Democrats’ national aspirations. Landry’s win is seen not just as a singular event, but as a barometer of the political climate shifting in favor of the Republicans as 2024 approaches. Previously serving as Louisiana’s attorney general, Landry took the spotlight with an impressive 52 percent majority, eliminating the need for a November runoff. This outright win is made more significant by the fact that he had been endorsed by former President Donald Trump. Various factors played into Landry’s win. A reported low turnout, not seen in a decade, along with a lackluster response to his top Democrat opponent, Shawn Wilson, made the Republican’s ascent all the more notable. Surprisingly, turnout among black voters was low, but those who did vote showed substantial support for Landry, a Republican. Longtime grassroots Republican activist, Debbie Dooley, shed light on the broader implications of this victory for both Democrats and Republicans. Highlighting the lack of enthusiasm among black voters for Democrats and Landry’s unexpected support from the black community, she points to current President Joe Biden’s policies, which many critics argue are detrimental to working-class Americans. The narrative is clear: widespread dissatisfaction with rising inflation and diminishing purchasing power. With mounting gas and food prices, Dooley emphasizes a crucial question: Why would the average American support policies causing such discomfort? Moreover, Dooley stresses an alarming enthusiasm among MAGA voters in Louisiana, suggesting that Democrats should be concerned. The overwhelming support for an amendment banning private funds in election facilitation is an indicator of shifting sands in voter preferences and priorities. Several pundits argue that Landry’s victory, given his endorsement by Trump, signifies a strong rallying call for Republicans to unite behind Trump’s leadership. After all, polls leading up to the election had not predicted Landry’s outright win, which brings into question the reliability of current polling methodologies, especially with respect to “silent” Trump supporters. Political adviser to Landry, Brent Littlefield, commented on the unique combination of national dissatisfaction with the Biden administration and local issues that Landry championed, making his campaign successful. He also highlighted Landry’s unwavering commitment to addressing concerns closest to the hearts of Louisiana’s residents. While Democrats grapple with the implications of this unexpected turn of events, Republicans view it as a herald of a resurgent red tide. The shifting allegiances and priorities of voters, even in traditionally blue areas, indicate an evolving political landscape as we head towards 2024. With the winds of change blowing, all eyes are now on how both parties will recalibrate their strategies in the coming months.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Capitol Hill Uproar: Pro-Palestinian Jews Call for Cease-Fire</title><link href="/news/2023/10/20/Capitol-Hill-Protest/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Capitol Hill Uproar: Pro-Palestinian Jews Call for Cease-Fire" /><published>2023-10-20T08:16:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-20T08:16:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/20/Capitol-Hill-Protest</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/20/Capitol-Hill-Protest/">&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON – Capitol Hill was the epicenter of fervor and passion as protesters from all over the U.S. gathered, demanding an end to the ongoing conflict between Israel and Hamas. Their cries for a cease-fire culminated in the arrest of hundreds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These demonstrators, many of whom identified as Jewish, bore shirts with a powerful message: “Jews say ceasefire now!” Their strong commitment to peace was evident when Liv, a participant from the activist group &lt;strong&gt;Jewish Voice for Peace&lt;/strong&gt;, proclaimed, “We were raised saying ‘Never again.’ That time is now!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the demonstration, approximately 300 protesters were taken into custody, with the U.S. Capitol Police confirming charges of illegal protest inside a House office building for some. Three individuals also faced assault on a police officer charges. But for many demonstrators, this was a necessary act of civil disobedience. Louisa, one of the protesters, emphasized the importance of their message reaching both Congress and President Biden. She fervently expressed the need for U.S. intervention to facilitate a cease-fire and prevent further loss of life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The magnitude of the demonstration was palpable. Among the sea of protesters were rabbis, children of Holocaust survivors, and supporters from far and wide. One member even traveled from Kansas City after the demonstration was planned merely three days in advance. The objective was clear: convey a strong message to the U.S. leadership that they must act. Michael, another participant, voiced a call for the U.S. to use its significant influence to de-escalate the situation, suggesting a stop in financial support and troop stationing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The demonstration wasn’t without its critics. The Anti-Defamation League’s D.C. chapter voiced concerns, asserting that while these groups claim representation, they do not embody the majority Jewish sentiment. The ADL D.C. Regional Director, Meredith R. Weisel, strongly indicated that challenging Israel’s right to exist, as these anti-Zionist groups do, equates to antisemitism. However, many protesters countered this, emphasizing the diverse perspectives within the Jewish community and their empathy for the Palestinian cause.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The echoes of the protest weren’t limited to Capitol Hill. Activists from the group &lt;strong&gt;IfNotNow&lt;/strong&gt; reported similar acts of civil disobedience in Boston, targeting the office of Sen. Elizabeth Warren, pressing her to advocate for a cease-fire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With emotions running high, this demonstration highlights the complexities of the Israel-Palestine conflict and the passionate voices on all sides seeking resolution and peace.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">WASHINGTON – Capitol Hill was the epicenter of fervor and passion as protesters from all over the U.S. gathered, demanding an end to the ongoing conflict between Israel and Hamas. Their cries for a cease-fire culminated in the arrest of hundreds. These demonstrators, many of whom identified as Jewish, bore shirts with a powerful message: “Jews say ceasefire now!” Their strong commitment to peace was evident when Liv, a participant from the activist group Jewish Voice for Peace, proclaimed, “We were raised saying ‘Never again.’ That time is now!” During the demonstration, approximately 300 protesters were taken into custody, with the U.S. Capitol Police confirming charges of illegal protest inside a House office building for some. Three individuals also faced assault on a police officer charges. But for many demonstrators, this was a necessary act of civil disobedience. Louisa, one of the protesters, emphasized the importance of their message reaching both Congress and President Biden. She fervently expressed the need for U.S. intervention to facilitate a cease-fire and prevent further loss of life. The magnitude of the demonstration was palpable. Among the sea of protesters were rabbis, children of Holocaust survivors, and supporters from far and wide. One member even traveled from Kansas City after the demonstration was planned merely three days in advance. The objective was clear: convey a strong message to the U.S. leadership that they must act. Michael, another participant, voiced a call for the U.S. to use its significant influence to de-escalate the situation, suggesting a stop in financial support and troop stationing. The demonstration wasn’t without its critics. The Anti-Defamation League’s D.C. chapter voiced concerns, asserting that while these groups claim representation, they do not embody the majority Jewish sentiment. The ADL D.C. Regional Director, Meredith R. Weisel, strongly indicated that challenging Israel’s right to exist, as these anti-Zionist groups do, equates to antisemitism. However, many protesters countered this, emphasizing the diverse perspectives within the Jewish community and their empathy for the Palestinian cause. The echoes of the protest weren’t limited to Capitol Hill. Activists from the group IfNotNow reported similar acts of civil disobedience in Boston, targeting the office of Sen. Elizabeth Warren, pressing her to advocate for a cease-fire. With emotions running high, this demonstration highlights the complexities of the Israel-Palestine conflict and the passionate voices on all sides seeking resolution and peace.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Rep. Bill Johnson Speaks Out: Trump’s Policies Stand Tall in the Wake of Global Challenges</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/20/Trump-Policies-Success/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rep. Bill Johnson Speaks Out: Trump’s Policies Stand Tall in the Wake of Global Challenges" /><published>2023-10-20T07:02:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-20T07:02:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/20/Trump-Policies-Success</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/20/Trump-Policies-Success/">&lt;p&gt;Recent global events have thrust U.S. political decisions into the spotlight, with many contrasting the approaches of former President Donald Trump and current President Joe Biden. Rep. Bill Johnson (R-Ohio) shared his insights with Newsmax on Thursday, lauding Trump’s policies while pointing out the pitfalls of the Biden administration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to Johnson, the efficacy of Trump’s strategies on various matters is evident now more than ever. “The successes stemming from Trump’s policies on border security, boosting the economy, and asserting a strong international presence are undeniable,” Johnson asserted on “The Chris Salcedo Show.” He added, “During Trump’s tenure, we witnessed the pinnacle of our economy in the past half-century.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Johnson went on to highlight Trump’s triumphs on the international stage, emphasizing the stark contrast between Trump’s and Biden’s tenures. “Under Trump, the world witnessed a more restrained Iran, a Russia that didn’t venture into Ukrainian territory, and a China that, rather than posturing aggressively, collaborated with the U.S. to keep North Korea in check,” he elaborated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Congressman from Ohio did not stop at praising Trump’s accomplishments. He also shared his perspective on how the political landscape can be further improved, spotlighting one glaring issue that remains a bone of contention for many. “The unchecked fiscal habits in Washington, D.C., stand as a major concern,” Johnson expressed. “Even though Republicans have trimmed discretionary spending by vast amounts over the past decade or so, the alarming debt continues to loom large.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Johnson identified the Biden administration’s impulsive expenditure patterns as a significant driver behind this escalating debt. While the Republicans have managed to cut down hundreds of billions over the years, Johnson suggests that the “out-of-cycle” splurging endorsed by the current administration is exacerbating the nation’s financial woes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In wrapping up, Rep. Bill Johnson’s comments resonate as a clarion call for a more judicious and reflective approach to policy-making. With the world watching closely, the decisions made in Washington will undeniably have ripple effects, shaping not only America’s future but also the global political tapestry.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Recent global events have thrust U.S. political decisions into the spotlight, with many contrasting the approaches of former President Donald Trump and current President Joe Biden. Rep. Bill Johnson (R-Ohio) shared his insights with Newsmax on Thursday, lauding Trump’s policies while pointing out the pitfalls of the Biden administration. According to Johnson, the efficacy of Trump’s strategies on various matters is evident now more than ever. “The successes stemming from Trump’s policies on border security, boosting the economy, and asserting a strong international presence are undeniable,” Johnson asserted on “The Chris Salcedo Show.” He added, “During Trump’s tenure, we witnessed the pinnacle of our economy in the past half-century.” Johnson went on to highlight Trump’s triumphs on the international stage, emphasizing the stark contrast between Trump’s and Biden’s tenures. “Under Trump, the world witnessed a more restrained Iran, a Russia that didn’t venture into Ukrainian territory, and a China that, rather than posturing aggressively, collaborated with the U.S. to keep North Korea in check,” he elaborated. The Congressman from Ohio did not stop at praising Trump’s accomplishments. He also shared his perspective on how the political landscape can be further improved, spotlighting one glaring issue that remains a bone of contention for many. “The unchecked fiscal habits in Washington, D.C., stand as a major concern,” Johnson expressed. “Even though Republicans have trimmed discretionary spending by vast amounts over the past decade or so, the alarming debt continues to loom large.” Johnson identified the Biden administration’s impulsive expenditure patterns as a significant driver behind this escalating debt. While the Republicans have managed to cut down hundreds of billions over the years, Johnson suggests that the “out-of-cycle” splurging endorsed by the current administration is exacerbating the nation’s financial woes. In wrapping up, Rep. Bill Johnson’s comments resonate as a clarion call for a more judicious and reflective approach to policy-making. With the world watching closely, the decisions made in Washington will undeniably have ripple effects, shaping not only America’s future but also the global political tapestry.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Florida GameStop Shooting: Employee Charged Over Fatal Shooting with Pokemon Card Thief</title><link href="/news/2023/10/20/GameStop-Shooting/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Florida GameStop Shooting: Employee Charged Over Fatal Shooting with Pokemon Card Thief" /><published>2023-10-20T06:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-20T06:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/20/GameStop-Shooting</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/20/GameStop-Shooting/">&lt;p&gt;A dramatic event unfolded in a GameStop store located in Pembroke, Florida, as an employee faced a deadly altercation with an alleged shoplifter. The suspect, reportedly attempting to flee with five boxes of the coveted Pokemon Scarlet and Violet “ultra-premium” trading cards, was shot by the store’s clerk, Derrick Guerrero, 33.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reports from 1 News detail how the situation rapidly escalated. The suspected thief, having grabbed the Pokemon cards, was making a dash for it when Guerrero intervened with fatal consequences. The story took a further tragic turn when it emerged that the wounded suspect managed to reach a car driven by his girlfriend. But, as they sped away from the scene, the girlfriend discerned the seriousness of her boyfriend’s injuries. Pulling over, she promptly dialed 911.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Local authorities, upon arrival, ensured the injured man received immediate medical attention. Despite the quick response, the suspect was declared dead at the hospital.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The incident is made more complex given recent history. Maj. Al Xiques from the Pembroke Pines police provided some crucial context: “This very GameStop faced a robbery on September 11th of this year, involving different suspects. Interestingly, the victim of that prior incident is the same suspect in the current shooting.” The connection prompts deeper reflections on self-defense and personal safety. It was revealed that, after the September robbery, Guerrero had procured a firearm for his protection— the very same weapon used during this tragic encounter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Consequently, Derrick Guerrero, the GameStop clerk at the heart of this event, now faces legal proceedings. He has been officially arrested and charged with manslaughter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This incident, deeply saddening and layered, throws into sharp relief the questions of self-defense rights and the ever-growing popularity of collectible items like Pokemon cards. The fact that a seemingly minor theft escalated to such fatal consequences will undoubtedly be a topic of intense debate and scrutiny in the days to come.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">A dramatic event unfolded in a GameStop store located in Pembroke, Florida, as an employee faced a deadly altercation with an alleged shoplifter. The suspect, reportedly attempting to flee with five boxes of the coveted Pokemon Scarlet and Violet “ultra-premium” trading cards, was shot by the store’s clerk, Derrick Guerrero, 33. Reports from 1 News detail how the situation rapidly escalated. The suspected thief, having grabbed the Pokemon cards, was making a dash for it when Guerrero intervened with fatal consequences. The story took a further tragic turn when it emerged that the wounded suspect managed to reach a car driven by his girlfriend. But, as they sped away from the scene, the girlfriend discerned the seriousness of her boyfriend’s injuries. Pulling over, she promptly dialed 911. Local authorities, upon arrival, ensured the injured man received immediate medical attention. Despite the quick response, the suspect was declared dead at the hospital. The incident is made more complex given recent history. Maj. Al Xiques from the Pembroke Pines police provided some crucial context: “This very GameStop faced a robbery on September 11th of this year, involving different suspects. Interestingly, the victim of that prior incident is the same suspect in the current shooting.” The connection prompts deeper reflections on self-defense and personal safety. It was revealed that, after the September robbery, Guerrero had procured a firearm for his protection— the very same weapon used during this tragic encounter. Consequently, Derrick Guerrero, the GameStop clerk at the heart of this event, now faces legal proceedings. He has been officially arrested and charged with manslaughter. This incident, deeply saddening and layered, throws into sharp relief the questions of self-defense rights and the ever-growing popularity of collectible items like Pokemon cards. The fact that a seemingly minor theft escalated to such fatal consequences will undoubtedly be a topic of intense debate and scrutiny in the days to come.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Explosion Rocks Cruise Ship in Maine: Hundreds Evacuated</title><link href="/news/2023/10/19/Cruise-Ship-Explosion/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Explosion Rocks Cruise Ship in Maine: Hundreds Evacuated" /><published>2023-10-19T16:43:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-19T16:43:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/19/Cruise-Ship-Explosion</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/19/Cruise-Ship-Explosion/">&lt;p&gt;An unsettling explosion on the American Queen Voyages’ Ocean Navigator, a popular cruise ship docked in Maine’s Portland Harbor, prompted the immediate evacuation of hundreds aboard. The explosion, originating from the engine room, sent shockwaves throughout the community and the wider cruise industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to local reports, a crew member faced grave injuries following the incident and was rushed to a nearby hospital. This individual suffered serious burns to the arms and hands, as cited by the Daily Mail. In addition to the injured crew member, 128 passengers were hurriedly escorted off the ship. The remainder, 82 in total, were the ship’s employees, as confirmed by WGME, a local TV station.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Taking a closer look at the Ocean Navigator, this 286-foot cruise vessel can accommodate 202 people. On that fateful Wednesday, the ship had just positioned itself at the Ocean Gateway Terminal when, around 7:25 a.m., a fire broke out in a generator within the engine room. Thankfully, swift actions by the Portland firefighters and the ship’s own crew ensured the flames were doused quickly. Presently, efforts are underway to clear the smoke from the ship. However, the U.S. Coast Guard has stated that passengers will not be permitted to reboard, as reported by WPFO.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Ocean Navigator, constructed in 2001 and subsequently refurbished in 2019, now faces an extensive investigation to pinpoint the exact cause of the explosion. While the inquiry remains ongoing, American Queen Voyages released a statement addressing the event: “Ocean Navigator encountered a generator fire this morning in Portland, ME. Thankfully, no passengers were harmed. Due to our crew’s rapid response, everyone was evacuated safely. One crew member, unfortunately, sustained injuries and is under medical care. The fire has been managed, and we’re working closely with the local fire department to gauge the damage. Currently, guests have been accommodated in a local hotel.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;American Queen Voyages, headquartered in Fort Lauderdale, Florida, is recognized for its diverse cruising options. They offer an array of journeys, spanning river cruises, lake cruises, and expansive ocean voyages. Their reach extends to various destinations, including the Southeast, the Great Lakes, Alaska, New England, Canada, Mexico, and even Costa Rica.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With safety at the forefront of concerns, all eyes are now on the investigative results and the measures that will be undertaken to prevent such incidents in the future.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">An unsettling explosion on the American Queen Voyages’ Ocean Navigator, a popular cruise ship docked in Maine’s Portland Harbor, prompted the immediate evacuation of hundreds aboard. The explosion, originating from the engine room, sent shockwaves throughout the community and the wider cruise industry. According to local reports, a crew member faced grave injuries following the incident and was rushed to a nearby hospital. This individual suffered serious burns to the arms and hands, as cited by the Daily Mail. In addition to the injured crew member, 128 passengers were hurriedly escorted off the ship. The remainder, 82 in total, were the ship’s employees, as confirmed by WGME, a local TV station. Taking a closer look at the Ocean Navigator, this 286-foot cruise vessel can accommodate 202 people. On that fateful Wednesday, the ship had just positioned itself at the Ocean Gateway Terminal when, around 7:25 a.m., a fire broke out in a generator within the engine room. Thankfully, swift actions by the Portland firefighters and the ship’s own crew ensured the flames were doused quickly. Presently, efforts are underway to clear the smoke from the ship. However, the U.S. Coast Guard has stated that passengers will not be permitted to reboard, as reported by WPFO. The Ocean Navigator, constructed in 2001 and subsequently refurbished in 2019, now faces an extensive investigation to pinpoint the exact cause of the explosion. While the inquiry remains ongoing, American Queen Voyages released a statement addressing the event: “Ocean Navigator encountered a generator fire this morning in Portland, ME. Thankfully, no passengers were harmed. Due to our crew’s rapid response, everyone was evacuated safely. One crew member, unfortunately, sustained injuries and is under medical care. The fire has been managed, and we’re working closely with the local fire department to gauge the damage. Currently, guests have been accommodated in a local hotel.” American Queen Voyages, headquartered in Fort Lauderdale, Florida, is recognized for its diverse cruising options. They offer an array of journeys, spanning river cruises, lake cruises, and expansive ocean voyages. Their reach extends to various destinations, including the Southeast, the Great Lakes, Alaska, New England, Canada, Mexico, and even Costa Rica. With safety at the forefront of concerns, all eyes are now on the investigative results and the measures that will be undertaken to prevent such incidents in the future.</summary></entry></feed>