<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-10-12T13:14:30-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/12/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-12T13:14:30-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-12T13:14:30-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/12/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/12/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/12/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-12T13:14:30-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-12T13:14:30-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/12/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/12/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/">&lt;p&gt;Recent surprise attacks by Hamas on Israel has fueled ongoing tensions between staunchly conservative commentators and the progressive “Squad” Democrats known for criticizing Israel. The intensity of the backlash highlights the deep political divide over foreign policy in the Middle East.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Hamas’ shocking attack, several members of the “Squad,” including Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.), called for a “ceasefire and de-escalation,” condemning the violence. The absence of a statement from Rep. Rashida Tlaib (D-Mich.) was notably called out by conservative media outlets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;South Carolina GOP Rep. Nancy Mace quickly labeled Ocasio-Cortez a “Hamas apologist” in response to her call for peace and de-escalation. Rep. Ilhan Omar (D-Minn.), no stranger to controversy surrounding her views on Israel, echoed the call for de-escalation and ceasefire. Omar’s prior statements comparing the US and Israel to terrorist groups like Hamas and the Taliban resurfaced in the debate, fueling more criticisms. Omar’s 2019 tweet, where she opined that “Israel has hypnotized the world,” also continues to haunt her political career, often cited by critics to challenge her stance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conservative commentators have been especially vocal. “FOX &amp;amp; Friends Weekend” co-host Rachel Campos-Duffy took aim at Omar, saying she fails to recognize the peace in the Middle East under Trump’s administration. Conservative pundit John Hasson also called out Omar, claiming she insinuated that attacks on IDF forces were acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Massachusetts Democrat Rep. Ayanna Pressley’s concerns over the “devastating attacks on Israelis” were met with skepticism. A prominent conservative online personality, Comfortably Smug, accused the “Squad” of advising Israel to back down after the nation suffered massive attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Jamaal Bowman’s call for an end to the Gaza blockade, in addition to condemning the Hamas attacks, was met with criticism from conservative radio host Jason Rantz. He accused Bowman of pairing his condemnation of terrorism with unwarranted criticisms of Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Cori Bush emphasized the urgent need for a ceasefire, while pushing for an end to “U.S. support for Israeli military occupation and apartheid.” Defense attorney Marina Medvin criticized Bush, suggesting that she equates the death of Palestinian terrorists to the horrific acts committed against Jewish civilians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amidst the political turmoil and intense debate, the attacks have taken a heavy toll. Israeli media report over 300 dead due to the wide-ranging assault. Gaza health officials note that at least 200 Palestinians have perished in the retaliatory Israeli air strikes following the initial Hamas attack. As the situation remains volatile, both sides continue to count their casualties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This divisive issue showcases the challenge America faces in crafting a unified approach to foreign policy, with deeply entrenched political divides at play. As the situation develops, the debate is bound to intensify, shedding light on the complexities of U.S. politics in the global arena.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Jada Pinkett Smith Reveals 7-Year Separation from Will Smith</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/12/Jada-Will-Separation/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Jada Pinkett Smith Reveals 7-Year Separation from Will Smith" /><published>2023-10-12T13:01:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-12T13:01:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/12/Jada-Will-Separation</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/12/Jada-Will-Separation/">&lt;p&gt;In a recent revelation, actress Jada Pinkett Smith has shared that she and Hollywood superstar Will Smith have been living separate lives since 2016, despite still making public appearances as a couple.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During an interview on the “Today” show with Hoda Kotb, Pinkett Smith made the disclosure while discussing her new book titled “Worthy.” She stated, “&lt;em&gt;We live separately&lt;/em&gt;,” emphasizing that despite the separation, the idea of divorce is off the table. “&lt;em&gt;I made a promise that there will never be a reason for us to get a divorce. We will work through whatever. And I just haven’t been able to break that promise,&lt;/em&gt;” she explained.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The separation came about in 2016 after the couple “were just exhausted with trying” to maintain their union. Both had varying expectations of each other, leading them to drift apart. Yet, despite the challenges, they chose not to publicize their separation, even amidst intense media scrutiny. This scrutiny peaked when rumors circulated about Jada’s relationship with family friend, August Alsina. The actress confirmed this relationship in 2021 on her show, “Red Table Talk,” referring to her involvement with Alsina as an “entanglement.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, the revelation also indicates that the couple was separated during Will Smith’s notorious 2022 Oscar incident, wherein he slapped comedian Chris Rock. The incident occurred after Rock made a joke referencing Jada’s alopecia condition. Recalling the event, Jada expressed her disbelief, “&lt;em&gt;I thought, ‘This is a skit. I was like, ‘There’s no way that Will hit him.’ It wasn’t until Will started to walk back to his chair that I even realized it wasn’t a skit.&lt;/em&gt;”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the complexities in their relationship, the bond between the two remains strong. “&lt;em&gt;We’ve been doing some really heavy-duty work together. We just got deep love for each other and we are going to figure out what that looks like for us,&lt;/em&gt;” Pinkett Smith said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The couple, who tied the knot in 1997, share two children: Jaden, 25, and Willow, 22. Will Smith also has a son, Trey, 30, from a previous marriage to Sheree Zampino, whom Jada lovingly refers to as her “bonus son.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This unexpected revelation from Jada Pinkett Smith offers a fresh perspective on the couple’s relationship, further illustrating the uniqueness of their bond and the strength they share in navigating through life’s challenges.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">In a recent revelation, actress Jada Pinkett Smith has shared that she and Hollywood superstar Will Smith have been living separate lives since 2016, despite still making public appearances as a couple. During an interview on the “Today” show with Hoda Kotb, Pinkett Smith made the disclosure while discussing her new book titled “Worthy.” She stated, “We live separately,” emphasizing that despite the separation, the idea of divorce is off the table. “I made a promise that there will never be a reason for us to get a divorce. We will work through whatever. And I just haven’t been able to break that promise,” she explained. The separation came about in 2016 after the couple “were just exhausted with trying” to maintain their union. Both had varying expectations of each other, leading them to drift apart. Yet, despite the challenges, they chose not to publicize their separation, even amidst intense media scrutiny. This scrutiny peaked when rumors circulated about Jada’s relationship with family friend, August Alsina. The actress confirmed this relationship in 2021 on her show, “Red Table Talk,” referring to her involvement with Alsina as an “entanglement.” Interestingly, the revelation also indicates that the couple was separated during Will Smith’s notorious 2022 Oscar incident, wherein he slapped comedian Chris Rock. The incident occurred after Rock made a joke referencing Jada’s alopecia condition. Recalling the event, Jada expressed her disbelief, “I thought, ‘This is a skit. I was like, ‘There’s no way that Will hit him.’ It wasn’t until Will started to walk back to his chair that I even realized it wasn’t a skit.” Despite the complexities in their relationship, the bond between the two remains strong. “We’ve been doing some really heavy-duty work together. We just got deep love for each other and we are going to figure out what that looks like for us,” Pinkett Smith said. The couple, who tied the knot in 1997, share two children: Jaden, 25, and Willow, 22. Will Smith also has a son, Trey, 30, from a previous marriage to Sheree Zampino, whom Jada lovingly refers to as her “bonus son.” This unexpected revelation from Jada Pinkett Smith offers a fresh perspective on the couple’s relationship, further illustrating the uniqueness of their bond and the strength they share in navigating through life’s challenges.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump Surpasses Biden by 9 Points in Pennsylvania: New Poll Reveals</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/12/Trump-Lead-Pennsylvania/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump Surpasses Biden by 9 Points in Pennsylvania: New Poll Reveals" /><published>2023-10-12T11:52:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-12T11:52:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/12/Trump-Lead-Pennsylvania</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/12/Trump-Lead-Pennsylvania/">&lt;p&gt;Pennsylvania, often considered a critical battleground state in U.S. elections, seems to be leaning towards former President Donald Trump over the incumbent, President Joe Biden. According to a recent Emerson College poll, Trump leads by a significant 9-point margin in a potential face-off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Takeaways from the Poll:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trump’s Lead:&lt;/strong&gt; 45% of the registered voters in Pennsylvania expressed support for Trump, compared to Biden’s 36%. Interestingly, this shows a shift in voter sentiment, as 43% voted for Biden and 42% for Trump in the 2020 elections.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Independent Voters:&lt;/strong&gt; Trump appears to resonate with independent voters, securing a remarkable 44% of their support, while Biden trails at 14%. The remaining voters are split between other candidates or are still making up their minds.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Biden’s Approval Rating:&lt;/strong&gt; Notably, Biden’s approval rating in the state is at a concerning low. Only 31% of Pennsylvanians have a positive view of his presidency, while a significant 51% disapprove, rendering his net approval rating at -20.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Loyalty among Supporters:&lt;/strong&gt; Half of Trump’s supporters firmly assert that nothing could deter their support for him in the 2024 presidential race. On the flip side, 53% of Biden’s supporters echo the same unwavering loyalty.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senate Race Insights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though Trump is soaring in popularity, it’s interesting to note that this surge isn’t necessarily translating to other Republicans. In a potential U.S. Senate race, the Democratic Senator Bob Casey leads over Republican Dave McCormick by eight points, standing at 41% to McCormick’s 33%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Emerson College Polling’s Executive Director, Spencer Kimball, shed light on these variances, especially concerning age demographics. Biden holds an edge over Trump among voters under 40 (44% to 39%). Yet, among those below 30, Trump gains traction, leading 45% to 39%. Senator Casey, however, retains dominance across both age brackets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Education also plays a significant role. Voters with a high school degree or less significantly favor Trump (53% to 27%). Yet, when it comes to the Senate race, Casey just slightly outpaces McCormick among the same group.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the 2024 elections approaching, these poll results, derived from 430 registered Pennsylvanian voters, will be pivotal for campaign strategies. The poll’s credibility interval is ±4.7%, and it follows another by the Marketing Resource Group, where Trump had a seven-point lead over Biden.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given the ever-shifting political landscape and the critical role Pennsylvania has played in recent elections, it remains to be seen how these preliminary sentiments translate to votes in the coming year.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Pennsylvania, often considered a critical battleground state in U.S. elections, seems to be leaning towards former President Donald Trump over the incumbent, President Joe Biden. According to a recent Emerson College poll, Trump leads by a significant 9-point margin in a potential face-off. Key Takeaways from the Poll: Trump’s Lead: 45% of the registered voters in Pennsylvania expressed support for Trump, compared to Biden’s 36%. Interestingly, this shows a shift in voter sentiment, as 43% voted for Biden and 42% for Trump in the 2020 elections. Independent Voters: Trump appears to resonate with independent voters, securing a remarkable 44% of their support, while Biden trails at 14%. The remaining voters are split between other candidates or are still making up their minds. Biden’s Approval Rating: Notably, Biden’s approval rating in the state is at a concerning low. Only 31% of Pennsylvanians have a positive view of his presidency, while a significant 51% disapprove, rendering his net approval rating at -20. Loyalty among Supporters: Half of Trump’s supporters firmly assert that nothing could deter their support for him in the 2024 presidential race. On the flip side, 53% of Biden’s supporters echo the same unwavering loyalty. Senate Race Insights: Though Trump is soaring in popularity, it’s interesting to note that this surge isn’t necessarily translating to other Republicans. In a potential U.S. Senate race, the Democratic Senator Bob Casey leads over Republican Dave McCormick by eight points, standing at 41% to McCormick’s 33%. Emerson College Polling’s Executive Director, Spencer Kimball, shed light on these variances, especially concerning age demographics. Biden holds an edge over Trump among voters under 40 (44% to 39%). Yet, among those below 30, Trump gains traction, leading 45% to 39%. Senator Casey, however, retains dominance across both age brackets. Education also plays a significant role. Voters with a high school degree or less significantly favor Trump (53% to 27%). Yet, when it comes to the Senate race, Casey just slightly outpaces McCormick among the same group. With the 2024 elections approaching, these poll results, derived from 430 registered Pennsylvanian voters, will be pivotal for campaign strategies. The poll’s credibility interval is ±4.7%, and it follows another by the Marketing Resource Group, where Trump had a seven-point lead over Biden. Given the ever-shifting political landscape and the critical role Pennsylvania has played in recent elections, it remains to be seen how these preliminary sentiments translate to votes in the coming year.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Steve Scalise Emerges as GOP’s Choice for House Speaker</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/12/Scalise-Nominee-Speaker/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Steve Scalise Emerges as GOP’s Choice for House Speaker" /><published>2023-10-12T10:45:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-12T10:45:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/12/Scalise-Nominee-Speaker</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/12/Scalise-Nominee-Speaker/">&lt;p&gt;In a significant political move, House Republicans have elected Majority Leader Steve Scalise, representing Louisiana, as their leading candidate for the esteemed role of House Speaker. This decision comes on the heels of an extensive, closed-door meeting that spanned more than two hours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The GOP’s decision-making process took the form of a secret ballot, wherein Scalise secured a notable 113 votes, outpacing Judiciary Committee Chairman Jim Jordan, who managed to garner 99 votes. Prior to this vote, House Republicans had deliberated and eventually voted against a motion that proposed elevating the threshold for electing the House speaker to 217 votes, amounting to a majority of the conference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This unfolding of events comes in the wake of the unanticipated ousting of former Speaker Kevin McCarthy, a California Republican. McCarthy’s removal marked an unparalleled moment in American political history, as it was the first occasion the U.S. House of Representatives made the collective decision to unseat its leader. Eight members of McCarthy’s party, in tandem with all House Democrats, catalyzed his fall from grace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the scramble to fill the speaker vacancy intensified, the spotlight inevitably narrowed down to two frontrunners: Scalise and Jordan, a Republican representative from Ohio. Scalise, a seasoned political figure, has been recognized as McCarthy’s right-hand man for a significant duration, notwithstanding the simmering rivalry that exists between the pair.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In contrast, Jordan, known for his closer ties to McCarthy, initially received an outpouring of support from influential conservatives within the GOP. Key figures like House Freedom Caucus Policy Chair Chip Roy, a Republican representative from Texas, openly endorsed Jordan. It’s worth noting that Jordan’s political career boasts of being a co-founder of the influential House Freedom Caucus group.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The political realm, as it stands, is rife with conjecture and anticipation regarding the future of the House’s leadership. As tensions simmer and factions within the GOP rally behind their preferred candidates, the stage is set for a monumental showdown in the race for the House Speaker position.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a significant political move, House Republicans have elected Majority Leader Steve Scalise, representing Louisiana, as their leading candidate for the esteemed role of House Speaker. This decision comes on the heels of an extensive, closed-door meeting that spanned more than two hours. The GOP’s decision-making process took the form of a secret ballot, wherein Scalise secured a notable 113 votes, outpacing Judiciary Committee Chairman Jim Jordan, who managed to garner 99 votes. Prior to this vote, House Republicans had deliberated and eventually voted against a motion that proposed elevating the threshold for electing the House speaker to 217 votes, amounting to a majority of the conference. This unfolding of events comes in the wake of the unanticipated ousting of former Speaker Kevin McCarthy, a California Republican. McCarthy’s removal marked an unparalleled moment in American political history, as it was the first occasion the U.S. House of Representatives made the collective decision to unseat its leader. Eight members of McCarthy’s party, in tandem with all House Democrats, catalyzed his fall from grace. As the scramble to fill the speaker vacancy intensified, the spotlight inevitably narrowed down to two frontrunners: Scalise and Jordan, a Republican representative from Ohio. Scalise, a seasoned political figure, has been recognized as McCarthy’s right-hand man for a significant duration, notwithstanding the simmering rivalry that exists between the pair. In contrast, Jordan, known for his closer ties to McCarthy, initially received an outpouring of support from influential conservatives within the GOP. Key figures like House Freedom Caucus Policy Chair Chip Roy, a Republican representative from Texas, openly endorsed Jordan. It’s worth noting that Jordan’s political career boasts of being a co-founder of the influential House Freedom Caucus group. The political realm, as it stands, is rife with conjecture and anticipation regarding the future of the House’s leadership. As tensions simmer and factions within the GOP rally behind their preferred candidates, the stage is set for a monumental showdown in the race for the House Speaker position.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hamas Declares Worldwide ‘Day of Jihad’ on Infamous Friday the 13th</title><link href="/news/2023/10/12/Hamas-Day-of-Jihad/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hamas Declares Worldwide ‘Day of Jihad’ on Infamous Friday the 13th" /><published>2023-10-12T09:34:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-12T09:34:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/12/Hamas-Day-of-Jihad</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/12/Hamas-Day-of-Jihad/">&lt;p&gt;In a chilling announcement, the Palestinian Hamas terror group, simply known as Hamas, has urged Muslims globally to mark a “Day of Jihad” on Friday, October 13th. Strikingly, this date is commonly associated with horror movies and the popular Halloween holiday, further deepening concerns about the group’s intentions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dubbing the day as “Al-Aqsa Flood” Friday, Hamas recalls their past operation, which resulted in the death of over 1,200 Israelis, leaving approximately 3,000 injured and more than 100 kidnapped.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Middle East Media Research Institute (MEMRI), in its report, cites Hamas stating:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“We declare next Friday, ‘The Friday of the Al-Aqsa Flood,’ as a day of general mobilization in our Arab and Islamic world and among the free people of the world. It is a day to rally support, offer aid, and participate actively. It is a day to expose the crimes of the occupation, isolate it, and foil all its aggressive schemes.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hamas continues to stress the importance of the day as an opportunity to express profound love for Palestine, Jerusalem, and Al-Aqsa, urging it to be a day of sacrifice, heroism, and dedication.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hamas has further beckoned Palestinians in the West Bank (which Israelis refer to as Judea and Samaria) to rise against Israeli forces. Moreover, they appeal to Arab citizens residing in Israel, referring to them as “our people within the occupied territories of 1948”, to rebel against the state.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In popular culture, particularly in the entertainment sector, Friday the 13th has long been a day linked with horror, often chosen for the launch of horror film releases, captivating audiences with fictional tales of terror. However, the atrocities committed by Hamas in Israel paint a stark and grim reality, far from fiction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It remains to be seen how the world will react to this ominous call to arms on a day already shrouded in superstition and horror. The global community must remain vigilant and united in the face of such threats, ensuring peace and security for all.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a chilling announcement, the Palestinian Hamas terror group, simply known as Hamas, has urged Muslims globally to mark a “Day of Jihad” on Friday, October 13th. Strikingly, this date is commonly associated with horror movies and the popular Halloween holiday, further deepening concerns about the group’s intentions. Dubbing the day as “Al-Aqsa Flood” Friday, Hamas recalls their past operation, which resulted in the death of over 1,200 Israelis, leaving approximately 3,000 injured and more than 100 kidnapped. The Middle East Media Research Institute (MEMRI), in its report, cites Hamas stating: “We declare next Friday, ‘The Friday of the Al-Aqsa Flood,’ as a day of general mobilization in our Arab and Islamic world and among the free people of the world. It is a day to rally support, offer aid, and participate actively. It is a day to expose the crimes of the occupation, isolate it, and foil all its aggressive schemes.” Hamas continues to stress the importance of the day as an opportunity to express profound love for Palestine, Jerusalem, and Al-Aqsa, urging it to be a day of sacrifice, heroism, and dedication. Hamas has further beckoned Palestinians in the West Bank (which Israelis refer to as Judea and Samaria) to rise against Israeli forces. Moreover, they appeal to Arab citizens residing in Israel, referring to them as “our people within the occupied territories of 1948”, to rebel against the state. In popular culture, particularly in the entertainment sector, Friday the 13th has long been a day linked with horror, often chosen for the launch of horror film releases, captivating audiences with fictional tales of terror. However, the atrocities committed by Hamas in Israel paint a stark and grim reality, far from fiction. It remains to be seen how the world will react to this ominous call to arms on a day already shrouded in superstition and horror. The global community must remain vigilant and united in the face of such threats, ensuring peace and security for all.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Pentagon Braces for Potential Iran-Backed Aggression in the Middle East</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/12/Pentagon-Iran-Proxy-Attacks/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Pentagon Braces for Potential Iran-Backed Aggression in the Middle East" /><published>2023-10-12T08:19:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-12T08:19:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/12/Pentagon-Iran-Proxy-Attacks</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/12/Pentagon-Iran-Proxy-Attacks/">&lt;p&gt;Amidst heightened tensions in the Middle East, the Pentagon is ramping up defenses against potential attacks backed by Iran. The U.S. military, deeply concerned about Iranian proxy groups operating in Iraq, Syria, and the Persian Gulf, is taking steps to shield American and allied forces from harm in the region’s increasingly volatile climate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An unnamed U.S. official commented on the unfolding scenario as presenting “an opportunity,” as Politico reported. Army Maj. Geoffrey Carmichael, who serves as a spokesperson for the U.S. military campaign against ISIS in Syria and Iraq, underscored the military’s commitment to remaining alert. He warned against “malign actors” eager to exploit the current unrest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although Carmichael didn’t explicitly name Iran in his remarks, he firmly stated the U.S. position. “Make no mistake, we reserve our inherent right to self-defense whenever faced with threats that place our forces in harm’s way,” he told Politico.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Defense Secretary, Lloyd Austin, further cautioned external entities trying to fuel the fire. Without directly naming Iran, he stressed the international community’s stand against attempts to widen the conflict in Israel. Echoing this sentiment, President Joe Biden made a resounding condemnation of Hamas, equating its violent actions with ISIS’s atrocities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a bid to strengthen the U.S. military’s presence and deter any potential Iranian or proxy offensives, the Pentagon has made strategic moves. These include dispatching an aircraft carrier strike group to the eastern Mediterranean and considering the deployment of a second carrier. Additional fighter aircraft have also been mobilized to the Middle East, ready to act swiftly against any Iranian-sponsored aggression.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s worth noting that while Iranian-backed groups have currently halted their attacks on U.S. troops, they remain a significant concern. This apprehension has been exacerbated by Turkish airstrikes targeting the Syrian Democratic Forces (SDF), whom Turkey views as terrorists. These airstrikes followed a terrorist incident in Ankara, believed to be the work of the Kurdistan Workers’ Party.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amid these complications, U.S. forces recently intercepted a threatening Turkish drone in northeast Syria. Nevertheless, according to another Pentagon official, there’s been a concerted effort from senior levels to avoid direct confrontations, especially after this incident.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gen. Mazloum Abdi, the SDF commander, highlighted the resulting instability from the Turkish airstrikes. He noted that this disruption has provided an opening for ISIS to launch new terrorist attacks in the region, directly jeopardizing the joint operations between U.S. forces and the SDF. Abdi called for global condemnation and swift action to counter these security threats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the Middle East at another critical juncture, the Pentagon’s vigilance serves as a crucial safeguard against the multifaceted challenges facing the region.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Amidst heightened tensions in the Middle East, the Pentagon is ramping up defenses against potential attacks backed by Iran. The U.S. military, deeply concerned about Iranian proxy groups operating in Iraq, Syria, and the Persian Gulf, is taking steps to shield American and allied forces from harm in the region’s increasingly volatile climate. An unnamed U.S. official commented on the unfolding scenario as presenting “an opportunity,” as Politico reported. Army Maj. Geoffrey Carmichael, who serves as a spokesperson for the U.S. military campaign against ISIS in Syria and Iraq, underscored the military’s commitment to remaining alert. He warned against “malign actors” eager to exploit the current unrest. Although Carmichael didn’t explicitly name Iran in his remarks, he firmly stated the U.S. position. “Make no mistake, we reserve our inherent right to self-defense whenever faced with threats that place our forces in harm’s way,” he told Politico. The Defense Secretary, Lloyd Austin, further cautioned external entities trying to fuel the fire. Without directly naming Iran, he stressed the international community’s stand against attempts to widen the conflict in Israel. Echoing this sentiment, President Joe Biden made a resounding condemnation of Hamas, equating its violent actions with ISIS’s atrocities. In a bid to strengthen the U.S. military’s presence and deter any potential Iranian or proxy offensives, the Pentagon has made strategic moves. These include dispatching an aircraft carrier strike group to the eastern Mediterranean and considering the deployment of a second carrier. Additional fighter aircraft have also been mobilized to the Middle East, ready to act swiftly against any Iranian-sponsored aggression. It’s worth noting that while Iranian-backed groups have currently halted their attacks on U.S. troops, they remain a significant concern. This apprehension has been exacerbated by Turkish airstrikes targeting the Syrian Democratic Forces (SDF), whom Turkey views as terrorists. These airstrikes followed a terrorist incident in Ankara, believed to be the work of the Kurdistan Workers’ Party. Amid these complications, U.S. forces recently intercepted a threatening Turkish drone in northeast Syria. Nevertheless, according to another Pentagon official, there’s been a concerted effort from senior levels to avoid direct confrontations, especially after this incident. Gen. Mazloum Abdi, the SDF commander, highlighted the resulting instability from the Turkish airstrikes. He noted that this disruption has provided an opening for ISIS to launch new terrorist attacks in the region, directly jeopardizing the joint operations between U.S. forces and the SDF. Abdi called for global condemnation and swift action to counter these security threats. With the Middle East at another critical juncture, the Pentagon’s vigilance serves as a crucial safeguard against the multifaceted challenges facing the region.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Dramatic Escape Attempt by Texas Yoga Instructor Accused in High-Profile Murder</title><link href="/news/2023/10/12/Texas-Yoga-Instructor-Escape-Attempt/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dramatic Escape Attempt by Texas Yoga Instructor Accused in High-Profile Murder" /><published>2023-10-12T07:06:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-12T07:06:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/12/Texas-Yoga-Instructor-Escape-Attempt</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/12/Texas-Yoga-Instructor-Escape-Attempt/">&lt;p&gt;Kaitlin Armstrong, an Austin, Texas yoga instructor, made headlines after being accused of the dramatic love-triangle murder of professional cyclist Anna Moriah “Mo” Wilson. But her story took yet another twist as she allegedly tried to escape custody during a medical appointment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Armstrong had previously captivated the media when she fled the U.S. during the early stages of the investigation into Wilson’s death, only to be apprehended after a 43-day manhunt on a Costa Rican beach. Despite the dramatic circumstances surrounding her capture, authorities did not anticipate what was to come next.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to the Travis County Sheriff’s Office (TCSO) spokesperson, Drew Knight, Armstrong tried to seize an opportunity to escape as she and two correction officers were leaving a medical facility. Thanks to her high school track and field background, Armstrong led officers on a 10-minute foot chase. However, her efforts were in vain, and she was quickly recaptured.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s essential to delve into the backstory to grasp the significance of this latest escape attempt. Armstrong stands accused of the fatal shooting of 25-year-old Mo Wilson. Wilson, after a night out with Armstrong’s live-in boyfriend, professional cyclist Colin Strickland, returned to a friend’s apartment. She was found hours later in a bathroom, lifeless, in a pool of her blood. This tragic event unraveled the tangled love-triangle narrative, with Armstrong allegedly seeing Wilson as a romantic rival.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Armstrong’s boyfriend, Strickland, however, defended her in interviews with detectives. He repeatedly vouched for her character, stating he could not believe she would be capable of such violence. Despite these assertions, surveillance footage and evidence, including a handgun from Armstrong’s residence that matched shell casings from the crime scene, pointed toward her involvement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Notably, Armstrong was questioned by the Austin Police on May 12, a day after the tragic event. But she was told she wasn’t under arrest and was released. Taking advantage of this freedom, Armstrong fled to New York and then jetted internationally from New Jersey.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Costa Rican authorities, after her capture, extradited her back to the U.S. due to an immigration violation. She has since been held at the Travis County Jail in Austin on a hefty $3.5 million bail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the midst of this ongoing saga, Armstrong’s defense has actively disputed the prosecution’s depiction of her seeing Wilson as a “romantic rival,” dismissing the notion as “misogynistic and fictitious.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As this case unfolds, it’s evident that the story of Kaitlin Armstrong and Mo Wilson is not just another crime narrative but a saga filled with intrigue, emotion, and unexpected turns.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Kaitlin Armstrong, an Austin, Texas yoga instructor, made headlines after being accused of the dramatic love-triangle murder of professional cyclist Anna Moriah “Mo” Wilson. But her story took yet another twist as she allegedly tried to escape custody during a medical appointment. Armstrong had previously captivated the media when she fled the U.S. during the early stages of the investigation into Wilson’s death, only to be apprehended after a 43-day manhunt on a Costa Rican beach. Despite the dramatic circumstances surrounding her capture, authorities did not anticipate what was to come next. According to the Travis County Sheriff’s Office (TCSO) spokesperson, Drew Knight, Armstrong tried to seize an opportunity to escape as she and two correction officers were leaving a medical facility. Thanks to her high school track and field background, Armstrong led officers on a 10-minute foot chase. However, her efforts were in vain, and she was quickly recaptured. It’s essential to delve into the backstory to grasp the significance of this latest escape attempt. Armstrong stands accused of the fatal shooting of 25-year-old Mo Wilson. Wilson, after a night out with Armstrong’s live-in boyfriend, professional cyclist Colin Strickland, returned to a friend’s apartment. She was found hours later in a bathroom, lifeless, in a pool of her blood. This tragic event unraveled the tangled love-triangle narrative, with Armstrong allegedly seeing Wilson as a romantic rival. Armstrong’s boyfriend, Strickland, however, defended her in interviews with detectives. He repeatedly vouched for her character, stating he could not believe she would be capable of such violence. Despite these assertions, surveillance footage and evidence, including a handgun from Armstrong’s residence that matched shell casings from the crime scene, pointed toward her involvement. Notably, Armstrong was questioned by the Austin Police on May 12, a day after the tragic event. But she was told she wasn’t under arrest and was released. Taking advantage of this freedom, Armstrong fled to New York and then jetted internationally from New Jersey. The Costa Rican authorities, after her capture, extradited her back to the U.S. due to an immigration violation. She has since been held at the Travis County Jail in Austin on a hefty $3.5 million bail. In the midst of this ongoing saga, Armstrong’s defense has actively disputed the prosecution’s depiction of her seeing Wilson as a “romantic rival,” dismissing the notion as “misogynistic and fictitious.” As this case unfolds, it’s evident that the story of Kaitlin Armstrong and Mo Wilson is not just another crime narrative but a saga filled with intrigue, emotion, and unexpected turns.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump Pledges to Bring Back Travel Ban</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/12/Trump-Travel-Ban-Return/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump Pledges to Bring Back Travel Ban" /><published>2023-10-12T06:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-12T06:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/12/Trump-Travel-Ban-Return</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/12/Trump-Travel-Ban-Return/">&lt;p&gt;In the wake of the recent conflict in Israel, former President Donald Trump has asserted his intention to reestablish the travel ban on “terror-afflicted countries,” stirring support among his base and reviving debates on the matter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Addressing Republican voters in New Hampshire, Trump was unequivocal in his commitment to revive the travel ban that he had previously put into effect in 2017. This executive order had restricted most legal immigration from nations like Iran, Libya, Syria, and Yemen, among others, on account of their alleged links to terrorism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“During my presidency, we took decisive actions like the TRAVEL BAN to ensure Radical Islamic Terrorists were kept away from American shores,” Trump confidently remarked. He further added, “We’ll halt funding to Palestinian terrorists immediately and reinstate the travel ban, ensuring the horrors we’ve seen recently will never touch American soil.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Trump-era travel ban, upheld by the U.S. Supreme Court in a tight decision, targeted countries that either withheld vital national security information or were identified as havens and patrons of terrorism. Renowned agencies like the State Department identified multiple nations, including North Korea and Iran, as “state sponsors of terrorism.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The effects of the travel ban were palpable and significant. Breitbart News reported a marked decline of around 80% in legal immigration from the affected countries by February 2019, compared to figures from 2016.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, in a move that contrasted Trump’s stringent approach, President Joe Biden nullified the travel ban in late January 2021, enabling the resumption of legal immigration from the previously barred countries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump’s strict stance on immigration, particularly from terror-afflicted countries, found significant resonance among Americans, even amidst criticism from several quarters. A survey conducted in November 2018 revealed that over four in nine U.S. voters endorsed the travel ban. Furthermore, by January 2019, a significant 80% of American voters expressed support for “tough” restrictions on legal immigration, similar to the travel ban, from countries associated with terrorism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the 2024 elections on the horizon, Trump’s renewed call to bring back the travel ban could well shape the discourse and debates on national security and immigration in the coming months.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In the wake of the recent conflict in Israel, former President Donald Trump has asserted his intention to reestablish the travel ban on “terror-afflicted countries,” stirring support among his base and reviving debates on the matter. Addressing Republican voters in New Hampshire, Trump was unequivocal in his commitment to revive the travel ban that he had previously put into effect in 2017. This executive order had restricted most legal immigration from nations like Iran, Libya, Syria, and Yemen, among others, on account of their alleged links to terrorism. “During my presidency, we took decisive actions like the TRAVEL BAN to ensure Radical Islamic Terrorists were kept away from American shores,” Trump confidently remarked. He further added, “We’ll halt funding to Palestinian terrorists immediately and reinstate the travel ban, ensuring the horrors we’ve seen recently will never touch American soil.” The Trump-era travel ban, upheld by the U.S. Supreme Court in a tight decision, targeted countries that either withheld vital national security information or were identified as havens and patrons of terrorism. Renowned agencies like the State Department identified multiple nations, including North Korea and Iran, as “state sponsors of terrorism.” The effects of the travel ban were palpable and significant. Breitbart News reported a marked decline of around 80% in legal immigration from the affected countries by February 2019, compared to figures from 2016. However, in a move that contrasted Trump’s stringent approach, President Joe Biden nullified the travel ban in late January 2021, enabling the resumption of legal immigration from the previously barred countries. Trump’s strict stance on immigration, particularly from terror-afflicted countries, found significant resonance among Americans, even amidst criticism from several quarters. A survey conducted in November 2018 revealed that over four in nine U.S. voters endorsed the travel ban. Furthermore, by January 2019, a significant 80% of American voters expressed support for “tough” restrictions on legal immigration, similar to the travel ban, from countries associated with terrorism. With the 2024 elections on the horizon, Trump’s renewed call to bring back the travel ban could well shape the discourse and debates on national security and immigration in the coming months.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Playboy Cuts Ties with Mia Khalifa Over Controversial Hamas Comments</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/11/Playboy-Hamas-Statement/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Playboy Cuts Ties with Mia Khalifa Over Controversial Hamas Comments" /><published>2023-10-11T15:45:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-11T15:45:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/11/Playboy-Hamas-Statement</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/11/Playboy-Hamas-Statement/">&lt;p&gt;In an unexpected twist in the entertainment world, Playboy Magazine has issued a robust statement condemning former porn star Mia Khalifa for her controversial remarks in support of Hamas terrorists. This move is starkly different from Harvard University’s rather subdued response to a similar issue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The magazine’s decision to sever ties with Khalifa came after she took to social media, making polarizing comments about the ongoing conflict in Israel. In her posts, she referred to terrorists as “freedom fighters” and went as far as suggesting they should improve their videography by capturing their horrific actions in a “wider camera shot.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Playboy responded swiftly to Khalifa’s remarks. In their statement, they expressed, “Over the past few days, Mia has made disgusting and reprehensible comments celebrating Hamas’ attacks on Israel and the murder of innocent men, women, and children.” Taking decisive action, Playboy announced the termination of their association with Khalifa, including the removal of her channel from their creator platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Juxtaposed with Playboy’s decisive action, Harvard University’s response to a similar situation seems muted. After more than 30 of its student organizations expressed support for terrorists, the Ivy League institution simply expressed its heartbreak over the violence in Israel. However, they remained silent on the collective endorsement of the Palestinian terror group Hamas by their student bodies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This stark contrast between an entertainment giant and a prestigious educational institution underscores the different stances entities can take in response to politically charged events. Playboy’s assertive stance might reflect a growing trend in the entertainment industry, where brands and influencers are expected to take firm stands on global issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a heartbreaking twist to the Israel conflict, reports surfaced about Itai and Hadar Berdichevsky. The couple were reportedly murdered during the Hamas attack after safeguarding their ten-month-old twins. In another shocking incident, Noa Argamani was attending a peace music festival when she was kidnapped by Hamas terrorists.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prominent figures like Harvard Law School Professor Emeritus Alan Dershowitz have criticized Harvard for its lack of acknowledgment concerning student group statements, especially in the aftermath of the severe attacks in Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The recent events in Israel and the subsequent reactions by global entities like Playboy and Harvard highlight the complexities surrounding political events and the varied responses they elicit.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">In an unexpected twist in the entertainment world, Playboy Magazine has issued a robust statement condemning former porn star Mia Khalifa for her controversial remarks in support of Hamas terrorists. This move is starkly different from Harvard University’s rather subdued response to a similar issue. The magazine’s decision to sever ties with Khalifa came after she took to social media, making polarizing comments about the ongoing conflict in Israel. In her posts, she referred to terrorists as “freedom fighters” and went as far as suggesting they should improve their videography by capturing their horrific actions in a “wider camera shot.” Playboy responded swiftly to Khalifa’s remarks. In their statement, they expressed, “Over the past few days, Mia has made disgusting and reprehensible comments celebrating Hamas’ attacks on Israel and the murder of innocent men, women, and children.” Taking decisive action, Playboy announced the termination of their association with Khalifa, including the removal of her channel from their creator platform. Juxtaposed with Playboy’s decisive action, Harvard University’s response to a similar situation seems muted. After more than 30 of its student organizations expressed support for terrorists, the Ivy League institution simply expressed its heartbreak over the violence in Israel. However, they remained silent on the collective endorsement of the Palestinian terror group Hamas by their student bodies. This stark contrast between an entertainment giant and a prestigious educational institution underscores the different stances entities can take in response to politically charged events. Playboy’s assertive stance might reflect a growing trend in the entertainment industry, where brands and influencers are expected to take firm stands on global issues. In a heartbreaking twist to the Israel conflict, reports surfaced about Itai and Hadar Berdichevsky. The couple were reportedly murdered during the Hamas attack after safeguarding their ten-month-old twins. In another shocking incident, Noa Argamani was attending a peace music festival when she was kidnapped by Hamas terrorists. Prominent figures like Harvard Law School Professor Emeritus Alan Dershowitz have criticized Harvard for its lack of acknowledgment concerning student group statements, especially in the aftermath of the severe attacks in Israel. The recent events in Israel and the subsequent reactions by global entities like Playboy and Harvard highlight the complexities surrounding political events and the varied responses they elicit.</summary></entry></feed>