<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-11-06T17:14:36-05:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/11/06/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-11-06T17:14:36-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-06T17:14:36-05:00</updated><id>/2023/11/06/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/11/06/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/11/06/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-11-06T17:14:36-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-06T17:14:36-05:00</updated><id>/2023/11/06/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/11/06/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/">&lt;p&gt;Recent surprise attacks by Hamas on Israel has fueled ongoing tensions between staunchly conservative commentators and the progressive “Squad” Democrats known for criticizing Israel. The intensity of the backlash highlights the deep political divide over foreign policy in the Middle East.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Hamas’ shocking attack, several members of the “Squad,” including Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.), called for a “ceasefire and de-escalation,” condemning the violence. The absence of a statement from Rep. Rashida Tlaib (D-Mich.) was notably called out by conservative media outlets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;South Carolina GOP Rep. Nancy Mace quickly labeled Ocasio-Cortez a “Hamas apologist” in response to her call for peace and de-escalation. Rep. Ilhan Omar (D-Minn.), no stranger to controversy surrounding her views on Israel, echoed the call for de-escalation and ceasefire. Omar’s prior statements comparing the US and Israel to terrorist groups like Hamas and the Taliban resurfaced in the debate, fueling more criticisms. Omar’s 2019 tweet, where she opined that “Israel has hypnotized the world,” also continues to haunt her political career, often cited by critics to challenge her stance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conservative commentators have been especially vocal. “FOX &amp;amp; Friends Weekend” co-host Rachel Campos-Duffy took aim at Omar, saying she fails to recognize the peace in the Middle East under Trump’s administration. Conservative pundit John Hasson also called out Omar, claiming she insinuated that attacks on IDF forces were acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Massachusetts Democrat Rep. Ayanna Pressley’s concerns over the “devastating attacks on Israelis” were met with skepticism. A prominent conservative online personality, Comfortably Smug, accused the “Squad” of advising Israel to back down after the nation suffered massive attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Jamaal Bowman’s call for an end to the Gaza blockade, in addition to condemning the Hamas attacks, was met with criticism from conservative radio host Jason Rantz. He accused Bowman of pairing his condemnation of terrorism with unwarranted criticisms of Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Cori Bush emphasized the urgent need for a ceasefire, while pushing for an end to “U.S. support for Israeli military occupation and apartheid.” Defense attorney Marina Medvin criticized Bush, suggesting that she equates the death of Palestinian terrorists to the horrific acts committed against Jewish civilians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amidst the political turmoil and intense debate, the attacks have taken a heavy toll. Israeli media report over 300 dead due to the wide-ranging assault. Gaza health officials note that at least 200 Palestinians have perished in the retaliatory Israeli air strikes following the initial Hamas attack. As the situation remains volatile, both sides continue to count their casualties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This divisive issue showcases the challenge America faces in crafting a unified approach to foreign policy, with deeply entrenched political divides at play. As the situation develops, the debate is bound to intensify, shedding light on the complexities of U.S. politics in the global arena.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Biden’s Support Slipping Amongst Minority Voters Ahead of Election Year</title><link href="/politics/2023/11/06/Biden-Voter-Challenge/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Biden’s Support Slipping Amongst Minority Voters Ahead of Election Year" /><published>2023-11-06T15:48:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-06T15:48:00-05:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/11/06/Biden-Voter-Challenge</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/11/06/Biden-Voter-Challenge/">&lt;p&gt;President Joe Biden is witnessing a worrisome dip in support from Black and Hispanic voters, two cornerstone demographics that traditionally bolster Democratic candidacies. This decline, brought to light by recent polling data, could spell trouble for the Democratic party as it prepares for the 2024 presidential election.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A close look at the numbers reveals an uncomfortable reality for the current administration. A New York Times/Siena College poll delineates a 33-point drop in support from nonwhite voters compared to the robust backing Biden enjoyed in the 2020 election outcomes. Of note is that support among Black voters has decreased to 72 percent, while only 47 percent of Hispanic voters seem inclined to stand behind Biden, a stark contrast to the levels of support seen in the previous electoral cycle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The implications are particularly severe in pivotal swing states, where Biden’s stronghold on Hispanic voters is wavering, now teetering into single-digit leads. This is a substantial departure from the typical 30-plus point lead Democrats have come to expect from the Hispanic community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Biden’s faltering foothold among these voter groups is resonant of the challenges faced by Walter Mondale in 1984, a comparison that bodes poorly for the Democratic party, given Mondale’s historic loss. This parallel has not gone unnoticed, stirring debates within Democratic circles regarding Biden’s position as the potential nominee for the next election cycle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adding to the party’s concerns is a small but significant defection of nonwhite Biden voters to former President Donald Trump. Current estimations suggest that approximately 5 percent, including 8 percent of Biden’s previous Hispanic supporters, now express allegiance to Trump.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the daunting numbers, many Democrats express unwavering support for Biden, confident in his eventual nomination. However, some party insiders and observers like political strategist David Axelrod have taken to social platforms to voice their uncertainties, urging Biden to consider the broader implications of his run for reelection — implications that extend beyond party politics to the future well-being of the nation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Caught in a whirlwind of political anxiety, the Democratic party stands at a crossroads. Will it manage to reconnect with Black and Hispanic voters, or will it witness a seismic shift in voter loyalty that could redefine future electoral landscapes? As the Biden administration grapples with these questions, the outcome will not only determine the fate of a party but could also set the stage for a new chapter in American politics.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">President Joe Biden is witnessing a worrisome dip in support from Black and Hispanic voters, two cornerstone demographics that traditionally bolster Democratic candidacies. This decline, brought to light by recent polling data, could spell trouble for the Democratic party as it prepares for the 2024 presidential election. A close look at the numbers reveals an uncomfortable reality for the current administration. A New York Times/Siena College poll delineates a 33-point drop in support from nonwhite voters compared to the robust backing Biden enjoyed in the 2020 election outcomes. Of note is that support among Black voters has decreased to 72 percent, while only 47 percent of Hispanic voters seem inclined to stand behind Biden, a stark contrast to the levels of support seen in the previous electoral cycle. The implications are particularly severe in pivotal swing states, where Biden’s stronghold on Hispanic voters is wavering, now teetering into single-digit leads. This is a substantial departure from the typical 30-plus point lead Democrats have come to expect from the Hispanic community. Biden’s faltering foothold among these voter groups is resonant of the challenges faced by Walter Mondale in 1984, a comparison that bodes poorly for the Democratic party, given Mondale’s historic loss. This parallel has not gone unnoticed, stirring debates within Democratic circles regarding Biden’s position as the potential nominee for the next election cycle. Adding to the party’s concerns is a small but significant defection of nonwhite Biden voters to former President Donald Trump. Current estimations suggest that approximately 5 percent, including 8 percent of Biden’s previous Hispanic supporters, now express allegiance to Trump. Despite the daunting numbers, many Democrats express unwavering support for Biden, confident in his eventual nomination. However, some party insiders and observers like political strategist David Axelrod have taken to social platforms to voice their uncertainties, urging Biden to consider the broader implications of his run for reelection — implications that extend beyond party politics to the future well-being of the nation. Caught in a whirlwind of political anxiety, the Democratic party stands at a crossroads. Will it manage to reconnect with Black and Hispanic voters, or will it witness a seismic shift in voter loyalty that could redefine future electoral landscapes? As the Biden administration grapples with these questions, the outcome will not only determine the fate of a party but could also set the stage for a new chapter in American politics.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Climate Activists Hammer Home Their Message, Attacking Iconic Art in London</title><link href="/news/2023/11/06/Climate-Activism-Art/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Climate Activists Hammer Home Their Message, Attacking Iconic Art in London" /><published>2023-11-06T14:31:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-06T14:31:00-05:00</updated><id>/news/2023/11/06/Climate-Activism-Art</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/11/06/Climate-Activism-Art/">&lt;p&gt;Climate activists from Just Stop Oil took a hammer to more than just the glass protecting a famous piece of art at London’s National Gallery; they struck a nerve worldwide. The target of their protest was none other than the ‘Rokeby Venus’ by Diego Velázquez, a masterpiece valued at a staggering £72.5 million.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The activists, wielding “safety hammers,” not only smashed the protective glass of the 17th-century painting but also shattered the complacency surrounding climate discussions. Their bold actions came with a clear and thunderous message: cease new oil and gas projects to prevent looming environmental catastrophe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This isn’t the first time ‘Rokeby Venus’ has been at the center of political activism. Over a century ago, suffragettes, in their fight for women’s voting rights, also chose this artwork to make their statement. Echoing that sentiment, one of the protesters exclaimed, “Women did not get the vote by voting; it is time for deeds not words. It is time to Just Stop Oil.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The incident has drawn a parallel between past and present struggles for change, igniting a fiery debate on whether such extreme actions are necessary or effective catalysts for political or social reform. Despite the outcry, the Just Stop Oil activists sat peacefully after their deed, symbolizing their readiness for what may come next.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The National Gallery responded swiftly, the room was evacuated, and the pair who attacked the painting were arrested, facing charges of criminal damage. Yet, despite the shock and potential legal consequences, the activists’ message resonates with a sense of urgency in the fight against climate change—a cause that continues to mobilize young and old across the globe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In light of these events, the role of protest in society is once again under scrutiny. Is the destruction of property a legitimate form of advocacy, or does it cross a line that should not be breached? The debate rages on, with opinions as divided as ever.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s clear is that climate activism has taken a bold turn. As governments and corporations grapple with the pressing issues of our time, the voices of the people, sometimes quiet, sometimes with a hammer in hand, are echoing through the halls of history, art, and politics, reminding us that change is not always quiet, and often, it is not polite.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Climate activists from Just Stop Oil took a hammer to more than just the glass protecting a famous piece of art at London’s National Gallery; they struck a nerve worldwide. The target of their protest was none other than the ‘Rokeby Venus’ by Diego Velázquez, a masterpiece valued at a staggering £72.5 million. The activists, wielding “safety hammers,” not only smashed the protective glass of the 17th-century painting but also shattered the complacency surrounding climate discussions. Their bold actions came with a clear and thunderous message: cease new oil and gas projects to prevent looming environmental catastrophe. This isn’t the first time ‘Rokeby Venus’ has been at the center of political activism. Over a century ago, suffragettes, in their fight for women’s voting rights, also chose this artwork to make their statement. Echoing that sentiment, one of the protesters exclaimed, “Women did not get the vote by voting; it is time for deeds not words. It is time to Just Stop Oil.” The incident has drawn a parallel between past and present struggles for change, igniting a fiery debate on whether such extreme actions are necessary or effective catalysts for political or social reform. Despite the outcry, the Just Stop Oil activists sat peacefully after their deed, symbolizing their readiness for what may come next. The National Gallery responded swiftly, the room was evacuated, and the pair who attacked the painting were arrested, facing charges of criminal damage. Yet, despite the shock and potential legal consequences, the activists’ message resonates with a sense of urgency in the fight against climate change—a cause that continues to mobilize young and old across the globe. In light of these events, the role of protest in society is once again under scrutiny. Is the destruction of property a legitimate form of advocacy, or does it cross a line that should not be breached? The debate rages on, with opinions as divided as ever. What’s clear is that climate activism has taken a bold turn. As governments and corporations grapple with the pressing issues of our time, the voices of the people, sometimes quiet, sometimes with a hammer in hand, are echoing through the halls of history, art, and politics, reminding us that change is not always quiet, and often, it is not polite.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Country Star Jason Aldean Applauds Trump</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/11/06/Jason-Aldean-Trump/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Country Star Jason Aldean Applauds Trump" /><published>2023-11-06T13:15:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-06T13:15:00-05:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/11/06/Jason-Aldean-Trump</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/11/06/Jason-Aldean-Trump/">&lt;p&gt;As the political scene heats up with the approach of the 2024 presidential election, country music sensation Jason Aldean is voicing his support for former President Donald Trump. In a recent Los Angeles Times interview, the chart-topping singer of “Try That in a Small Town” expressed positive sentiments toward Trump, hinting at a harmonious rapport that extends beyond mere politics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aldean’s experiences with Trump have been more personal than political. Sharing moments on the golf course and ringing in the New Year together, the country star’s encounters with the former president have left a favorable impression. “I like Trump. Hung out with him a couple of times — been very cool to me. I have nothing but good things to say about the guy,” Aldean shared, painting a picture of camaraderie that may well translate into support as Trump’s potential run for the White House in 2024 becomes more of a talking point.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Photos of Aldean with Trump, circulating on social media, amplify the singer’s regard for the former president. With Trump reciprocating the sentiment, describing Aldean as a “fantastic guy,” the mutual admiration could signal a significant celebrity endorsement as Trump’s political ambitions gain momentum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The “Big Green Tractor” singer steered clear of controversy regarding Joe Biden’s presidential win, opting for a pragmatic stance rather than delving into the contentious debates over the legitimacy of the 2020 election. “I feel like that’s just old news at this point,” Aldean stated, recognizing Biden’s role as president over the past three years, despite differing opinions on the election’s outcome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Aldean shied away from election controversies, he firmly condemned the January 6 riot. His stance against lawlessness and chaos underscores a commitment to law and order that aligns closely with conservative Republican values.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a high-profile figure in the country music world, Aldean’s perspective carries weight, especially among fans who respect his artistry and share his values. His nod to Trump doesn’t just reflect personal sentiment; it resonates with a significant portion of the American electorate who remain loyal to the former president.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aldean’s commentary arrives at a pivotal moment, as the country speculates about the future political landscape. His favorable words toward Trump could be a harbinger of more overt support as the election looms closer, positioning him as a key player in the intersection of entertainment and politics. For now, fans and political analysts alike will be watching to see if Aldean’s words echo into endorsements, as the country star’s voice amplifies in the political arena.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">As the political scene heats up with the approach of the 2024 presidential election, country music sensation Jason Aldean is voicing his support for former President Donald Trump. In a recent Los Angeles Times interview, the chart-topping singer of “Try That in a Small Town” expressed positive sentiments toward Trump, hinting at a harmonious rapport that extends beyond mere politics. Aldean’s experiences with Trump have been more personal than political. Sharing moments on the golf course and ringing in the New Year together, the country star’s encounters with the former president have left a favorable impression. “I like Trump. Hung out with him a couple of times — been very cool to me. I have nothing but good things to say about the guy,” Aldean shared, painting a picture of camaraderie that may well translate into support as Trump’s potential run for the White House in 2024 becomes more of a talking point. Photos of Aldean with Trump, circulating on social media, amplify the singer’s regard for the former president. With Trump reciprocating the sentiment, describing Aldean as a “fantastic guy,” the mutual admiration could signal a significant celebrity endorsement as Trump’s political ambitions gain momentum. The “Big Green Tractor” singer steered clear of controversy regarding Joe Biden’s presidential win, opting for a pragmatic stance rather than delving into the contentious debates over the legitimacy of the 2020 election. “I feel like that’s just old news at this point,” Aldean stated, recognizing Biden’s role as president over the past three years, despite differing opinions on the election’s outcome. While Aldean shied away from election controversies, he firmly condemned the January 6 riot. His stance against lawlessness and chaos underscores a commitment to law and order that aligns closely with conservative Republican values. As a high-profile figure in the country music world, Aldean’s perspective carries weight, especially among fans who respect his artistry and share his values. His nod to Trump doesn’t just reflect personal sentiment; it resonates with a significant portion of the American electorate who remain loyal to the former president. Aldean’s commentary arrives at a pivotal moment, as the country speculates about the future political landscape. His favorable words toward Trump could be a harbinger of more overt support as the election looms closer, positioning him as a key player in the intersection of entertainment and politics. For now, fans and political analysts alike will be watching to see if Aldean’s words echo into endorsements, as the country star’s voice amplifies in the political arena.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">U.S. Strengthens Middle East Presence with Nuclear Sub amid Israel-Hamas Conflict</title><link href="/news/2023/11/06/Nuclear-Submarine-Middle-East/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="U.S. Strengthens Middle East Presence with Nuclear Sub amid Israel-Hamas Conflict" /><published>2023-11-06T11:21:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-06T11:21:00-05:00</updated><id>/news/2023/11/06/Nuclear-Submarine-Middle-East</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/11/06/Nuclear-Submarine-Middle-East/">&lt;p&gt;The United States military has dispatched a nuclear-powered submarine to the Middle East amidst escalating tensions. This strategic move comes as Israel’s conflict with Hamas—the U.S. designated terrorist organization—intensifies, marking one month since the devastating attacks in Israel on October 7.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The presence of this Ohio-class submarine, typically a silent and hidden deterrent, in the strategically vital Suez Canal near the Suez Canal Bridge, is not a common occurrence. The United States Central Command, in a rare disclosure, posted an image of the powerful vessel. Such revelations are scarce as the locations and movements of nuclear submarines are closely guarded secrets, indicating the gravity of the U.S.’ intent to show its commitment to security in the region.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These submarines are a cornerstone of America’s “nuclear triad,” which is composed of land-based missiles, strategic bombers, and submarine-launched ballistic missiles. All are integral to the United States’ defense strategy, ensuring a formidable and diverse array of deterrent capabilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While it is not immediately confirmed whether the submarine stationed near Israel is armed with nuclear ballistic missiles, the very capability of these submarines to carry a mix of nuclear and conventional weapons sends a clear message of deterrence to adversaries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bolstering of U.S. military assets in the Mediterranean Sea and surrounding areas underscores the ongoing high-stakes situation with Iran, which backs Hamas and Hezbollah. Both groups are known for their hostility towards Israel and have been implicated in numerous terrorist acts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, the U.S. has ramped up its military might in the region with the Eisenhower Carrier Strike Group conducting operations and over 17,350 personnel deployed or redirected since the October attacks. This significant buildup includes advanced fighter jets like F-35s, F-15s, F-16s, A-10s, and F-18s, representing an array of air power at the region’s disposal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite this show of strength, U.S. and coalition forces have faced repeated attacks in Iraq and Syria, with at least 28 incidences recorded since October 17. These attacks, consisting of drones and rockets, illustrate the volatile security environment American troops and coalition forces operate within.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;U.S. Secretary of State Antony Blinken and Defense Secretary Lloyd Austin have unequivocally stated that the U.S. is prepared to respond if American interests or personnel are targeted. Their message is a blend of caution and readiness, emphasizing the desire to avoid escalation but affirming a resolute stance on defending U.S. forces and allies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In reinforcing the nation’s unwavering support for Israel, Defense Secretary Austin recently reiterated America’s steadfast commitment to Israel’s right to self-defense and to preventing further escalation of the conflict. This commitment extends to deterring state or non-state actors from exacerbating the situation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the region braces for potential developments, the strategic deployment of U.S. military assets serves not just as a reassurance to allies but also as a stark warning to adversaries that aggression will be met with unwavering opposition. In these turbulent times, the U.S. is making it clear that while peace is preferable, readiness for conflict is non-negotiable.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">The United States military has dispatched a nuclear-powered submarine to the Middle East amidst escalating tensions. This strategic move comes as Israel’s conflict with Hamas—the U.S. designated terrorist organization—intensifies, marking one month since the devastating attacks in Israel on October 7. The presence of this Ohio-class submarine, typically a silent and hidden deterrent, in the strategically vital Suez Canal near the Suez Canal Bridge, is not a common occurrence. The United States Central Command, in a rare disclosure, posted an image of the powerful vessel. Such revelations are scarce as the locations and movements of nuclear submarines are closely guarded secrets, indicating the gravity of the U.S.’ intent to show its commitment to security in the region. These submarines are a cornerstone of America’s “nuclear triad,” which is composed of land-based missiles, strategic bombers, and submarine-launched ballistic missiles. All are integral to the United States’ defense strategy, ensuring a formidable and diverse array of deterrent capabilities. While it is not immediately confirmed whether the submarine stationed near Israel is armed with nuclear ballistic missiles, the very capability of these submarines to carry a mix of nuclear and conventional weapons sends a clear message of deterrence to adversaries. The bolstering of U.S. military assets in the Mediterranean Sea and surrounding areas underscores the ongoing high-stakes situation with Iran, which backs Hamas and Hezbollah. Both groups are known for their hostility towards Israel and have been implicated in numerous terrorist acts. Furthermore, the U.S. has ramped up its military might in the region with the Eisenhower Carrier Strike Group conducting operations and over 17,350 personnel deployed or redirected since the October attacks. This significant buildup includes advanced fighter jets like F-35s, F-15s, F-16s, A-10s, and F-18s, representing an array of air power at the region’s disposal. Despite this show of strength, U.S. and coalition forces have faced repeated attacks in Iraq and Syria, with at least 28 incidences recorded since October 17. These attacks, consisting of drones and rockets, illustrate the volatile security environment American troops and coalition forces operate within. U.S. Secretary of State Antony Blinken and Defense Secretary Lloyd Austin have unequivocally stated that the U.S. is prepared to respond if American interests or personnel are targeted. Their message is a blend of caution and readiness, emphasizing the desire to avoid escalation but affirming a resolute stance on defending U.S. forces and allies. In reinforcing the nation’s unwavering support for Israel, Defense Secretary Austin recently reiterated America’s steadfast commitment to Israel’s right to self-defense and to preventing further escalation of the conflict. This commitment extends to deterring state or non-state actors from exacerbating the situation. As the region braces for potential developments, the strategic deployment of U.S. military assets serves not just as a reassurance to allies but also as a stark warning to adversaries that aggression will be met with unwavering opposition. In these turbulent times, the U.S. is making it clear that while peace is preferable, readiness for conflict is non-negotiable.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Texas’ Bold Move: Over 63K Migrants Shuttled to Sanctuary Cities</title><link href="/news/2023/11/06/Migrant-Busing-Program/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Texas’ Bold Move: Over 63K Migrants Shuttled to Sanctuary Cities" /><published>2023-11-06T10:12:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-06T10:12:00-05:00</updated><id>/news/2023/11/06/Migrant-Busing-Program</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/11/06/Migrant-Busing-Program/">&lt;p&gt;Texas Governor Greg Abbott has spearheaded a program that’s transported over 63,000 migrants to various sanctuary cities across the United States. This bold initiative, part of Texas’ Operation Lone Star, challenges the immigration policies of the federal government and places the immigration debate at the forefront of national attention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Governor Abbott, taking to social media, detailed the extent of the program’s reach. With cities like New York and Chicago receiving upwards of 20,000 migrants each, the impact of Texas’ policy is resonating far beyond the Lone Star State’s borders. The move spotlights Texas’ proactive approach to immigration, a hot-button issue that remains a top concern for conservative audiences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This influx, unsurprisingly, has met with mixed reactions. While some view it as a necessary step in confronting the challenges posed by unchecked immigration, others perceive it as a political maneuver. Yet, the numbers are telling—a clear signal from Governor Abbott and Texas that the current immigration system necessitates more robust and immediate solutions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adding to the state’s proactive stance, Governor Abbott also shared updates on the ongoing construction of border walls within Texas. The visual evidence of these walls, rising in areas like Cameron County, underscores the state’s commitment to securing its boundaries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The transportation of migrants to sanctuary cities, which pride themselves on offering protection to undocumented immigrants, raises the stakes in the national discourse on immigration. It also poses critical questions about the responsibilities of states versus federal authorities in managing migrant populations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As Texas continues to escalate its efforts, sanctuary cities are finding themselves at a crossroads. The unexpected arrival of thousands of migrants calls into question the sustainability and logistics of sanctuary policies, particularly in the context of strained resources and infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Governor Abbott’s initiative, therefore, isn’t just a message about Texas’ immigration stance—it’s a catalyst for a broader dialogue on federal immigration reform and the efficacy of sanctuary city policies. For conservative audiences who prioritize immigration control and state sovereignty, Texas’ actions are emblematic of assertive leadership and pragmatism in the face of a persistent national challenge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As this story unfolds, all eyes are on Texas and the sanctuary cities, watching to see how this complex human and political issue will evolve. What’s clear is that Governor Abbott’s migrant busing program has shifted from being a mere policy decision to a significant movement, shaping the conversation around immigration and states’ rights in America today.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Texas Governor Greg Abbott has spearheaded a program that’s transported over 63,000 migrants to various sanctuary cities across the United States. This bold initiative, part of Texas’ Operation Lone Star, challenges the immigration policies of the federal government and places the immigration debate at the forefront of national attention. Governor Abbott, taking to social media, detailed the extent of the program’s reach. With cities like New York and Chicago receiving upwards of 20,000 migrants each, the impact of Texas’ policy is resonating far beyond the Lone Star State’s borders. The move spotlights Texas’ proactive approach to immigration, a hot-button issue that remains a top concern for conservative audiences. This influx, unsurprisingly, has met with mixed reactions. While some view it as a necessary step in confronting the challenges posed by unchecked immigration, others perceive it as a political maneuver. Yet, the numbers are telling—a clear signal from Governor Abbott and Texas that the current immigration system necessitates more robust and immediate solutions. Adding to the state’s proactive stance, Governor Abbott also shared updates on the ongoing construction of border walls within Texas. The visual evidence of these walls, rising in areas like Cameron County, underscores the state’s commitment to securing its boundaries. The transportation of migrants to sanctuary cities, which pride themselves on offering protection to undocumented immigrants, raises the stakes in the national discourse on immigration. It also poses critical questions about the responsibilities of states versus federal authorities in managing migrant populations. As Texas continues to escalate its efforts, sanctuary cities are finding themselves at a crossroads. The unexpected arrival of thousands of migrants calls into question the sustainability and logistics of sanctuary policies, particularly in the context of strained resources and infrastructure. Governor Abbott’s initiative, therefore, isn’t just a message about Texas’ immigration stance—it’s a catalyst for a broader dialogue on federal immigration reform and the efficacy of sanctuary city policies. For conservative audiences who prioritize immigration control and state sovereignty, Texas’ actions are emblematic of assertive leadership and pragmatism in the face of a persistent national challenge. As this story unfolds, all eyes are on Texas and the sanctuary cities, watching to see how this complex human and political issue will evolve. What’s clear is that Governor Abbott’s migrant busing program has shifted from being a mere policy decision to a significant movement, shaping the conversation around immigration and states’ rights in America today.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Polls Prompt Pondering: Is Biden’s 2024 Race a Risky Gamble?</title><link href="/politics/2023/11/06/Biden-Election-Chances/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Polls Prompt Pondering: Is Biden’s 2024 Race a Risky Gamble?" /><published>2023-11-06T09:06:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-06T09:06:00-05:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/11/06/Biden-Election-Chances</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/11/06/Biden-Election-Chances/">&lt;p&gt;In an electoral climate brimming with anticipation, former Obama adviser David Axelrod raises a pivotal question regarding the wisdom of President Biden’s intent to run for re-election in 2024. The spark for Axelrod’s contemplation comes from a New York Times-Siena College poll revealing former President Trump leading Biden by significant margins in several crucial battleground states—a stark reversal of the 2020 outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The crux of Axelrod’s concern pivots on whether it is in the best interest of not only Biden but the country for him to persist as the Democratic Party’s standard-bearer. With an unwavering Trump gaining ground, Axelrod’s remarks echo across the political landscape, suggesting a sober re-evaluation of the Democratic strategy moving forward.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This poll, which puts Trump ahead by double digits in states like Nevada, and showcases his unprecedented 22% approval among Black voters, presents a daunting forecast for Biden’s campaign. The battleground states, instrumental in determining the election’s outcome, are sounding alarms for the Democratic camp, signaling a potential shift in voter sentiment and demographic loyalties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The concerns are manifold, extending beyond electoral dynamics to encompass broader issues such as economic trustworthiness, where Trump seemingly holds an advantage. Voter discontent, exacerbated by the tangible impacts of presidential policies, feeds into the narrative of a nation yearning for economic stability and leadership decisiveness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s Biden’s age, however, that emerges as his “biggest liability,” as per Axelrod’s analysis. The Democratic strategist’s circumspect stance is shared by other party voices, including James Carville, who openly questions the electorate’s desire to see Biden at the helm come the next election cycle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And while some within the Democratic echelons might harbor aspirations for a presidential run, be it in 2024 or 2028, with figures like California Governor Gavin Newsom and Michigan Governor Gretchen Whitmer subtly positioning themselves, the immediate focus remains on Biden’s decision. The specter of a “dangerous, unhinged demagogue” in Trump, as Axelrod characterizes, versus the venerable yet politically vulnerable Biden frames a conundrum of profound implications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As conservative circles scrutinize these developments, the tension between staying the course with a seasoned incumbent and the risks such loyalty entails simmers at the heart of Democratic strategizing. This unfolding scenario—where the stakes of miscalculation are, in Axelrod’s view, “too dramatic to ignore”—is set to galvanize a constituency deeply invested in the nation’s trajectory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the political chessboard of the 2024 election comes into focus, Biden’s candidacy is under the microscope, and the GOP watches keenly, ready to capitalize on any sign of Democratic hesitation. The evolving discourse over Biden’s electability is more than a political rumination; it’s a harbinger of an election season that promises to be as unpredictable as it is pivotal.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In an electoral climate brimming with anticipation, former Obama adviser David Axelrod raises a pivotal question regarding the wisdom of President Biden’s intent to run for re-election in 2024. The spark for Axelrod’s contemplation comes from a New York Times-Siena College poll revealing former President Trump leading Biden by significant margins in several crucial battleground states—a stark reversal of the 2020 outcomes. The crux of Axelrod’s concern pivots on whether it is in the best interest of not only Biden but the country for him to persist as the Democratic Party’s standard-bearer. With an unwavering Trump gaining ground, Axelrod’s remarks echo across the political landscape, suggesting a sober re-evaluation of the Democratic strategy moving forward. This poll, which puts Trump ahead by double digits in states like Nevada, and showcases his unprecedented 22% approval among Black voters, presents a daunting forecast for Biden’s campaign. The battleground states, instrumental in determining the election’s outcome, are sounding alarms for the Democratic camp, signaling a potential shift in voter sentiment and demographic loyalties. The concerns are manifold, extending beyond electoral dynamics to encompass broader issues such as economic trustworthiness, where Trump seemingly holds an advantage. Voter discontent, exacerbated by the tangible impacts of presidential policies, feeds into the narrative of a nation yearning for economic stability and leadership decisiveness. It’s Biden’s age, however, that emerges as his “biggest liability,” as per Axelrod’s analysis. The Democratic strategist’s circumspect stance is shared by other party voices, including James Carville, who openly questions the electorate’s desire to see Biden at the helm come the next election cycle. And while some within the Democratic echelons might harbor aspirations for a presidential run, be it in 2024 or 2028, with figures like California Governor Gavin Newsom and Michigan Governor Gretchen Whitmer subtly positioning themselves, the immediate focus remains on Biden’s decision. The specter of a “dangerous, unhinged demagogue” in Trump, as Axelrod characterizes, versus the venerable yet politically vulnerable Biden frames a conundrum of profound implications. As conservative circles scrutinize these developments, the tension between staying the course with a seasoned incumbent and the risks such loyalty entails simmers at the heart of Democratic strategizing. This unfolding scenario—where the stakes of miscalculation are, in Axelrod’s view, “too dramatic to ignore”—is set to galvanize a constituency deeply invested in the nation’s trajectory. As the political chessboard of the 2024 election comes into focus, Biden’s candidacy is under the microscope, and the GOP watches keenly, ready to capitalize on any sign of Democratic hesitation. The evolving discourse over Biden’s electability is more than a political rumination; it’s a harbinger of an election season that promises to be as unpredictable as it is pivotal.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Luxury Home with a Catch: $1.5 Million Listing Includes Meth Lab</title><link href="/news/2023/11/05/Meth-Lab-Real-Estate/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Luxury Home with a Catch: $1.5 Million Listing Includes Meth Lab" /><published>2023-11-05T18:35:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-05T18:35:00-05:00</updated><id>/news/2023/11/05/Meth-Lab-Real-Estate</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/11/05/Meth-Lab-Real-Estate/">&lt;p&gt;A spacious Californian home has been put up for sale at $1.5 million, but there’s a catch: the property comes with an inactive meth lab. The San Jose house, boasting six bedrooms and four bathrooms, is nestled in a coveted location with amenities such as an attached garage and outdoor pool. However, the meth lab, complete with smoke contamination, remains a startling inclusion in the otherwise appealing listing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 2,743-square-foot residence, listed by Keller Williams Realty-Silicon Valley, seems to offer a lucrative opportunity for the savvy investor or an ambitious do-it-yourself enthusiast willing to tackle the decontamination process. Buyers are cautioned, however, that the property will be sold in its current state, with the cleanup and its associated costs firmly on their shoulders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This listing represents a broader trend in the Golden State, where a mix of high-priced homes and unique selling points speak to a diverse market. In recent times, California has seen a rise in residents seeking more affordable living conditions elsewhere, yet the San Jose neighborhood remains in high demand with properties averaging around $1,620,000 and typically lasting a mere five days on the market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prospective buyers are clearly informed: the house has not been cleared of contamination and will require clearance by Santa Clara County’s Health Department before it can be accessed. This means no prior inspections or walk-throughs, a stipulation that is undoubtedly causing a stir among interested parties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the listing does highlight the potential in the property, it also emphasizes that the “remediation process and subsequent costs associated” will be the responsibility of the new owner. It’s a daunting proposition, but for those looking to make a mark in San Jose’s prime real estate locale, this property might just be the diamond in the rough—or in this case, the crystal in the cache.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The sale of this home will likely become a landmark case study in the annals of real estate, challenging the norms of what buyers may or may not accept in their pursuit of property ownership. As the housing market continues to navigate post-pandemic conditions and fluctuating buyer expectations, unique listings like this one underscore the complex decisions and risks that come with the territory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those enticed by the challenge, the San Jose meth lab house awaits—a testament to the unpredictable nature of today’s real estate adventures.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">A spacious Californian home has been put up for sale at $1.5 million, but there’s a catch: the property comes with an inactive meth lab. The San Jose house, boasting six bedrooms and four bathrooms, is nestled in a coveted location with amenities such as an attached garage and outdoor pool. However, the meth lab, complete with smoke contamination, remains a startling inclusion in the otherwise appealing listing. The 2,743-square-foot residence, listed by Keller Williams Realty-Silicon Valley, seems to offer a lucrative opportunity for the savvy investor or an ambitious do-it-yourself enthusiast willing to tackle the decontamination process. Buyers are cautioned, however, that the property will be sold in its current state, with the cleanup and its associated costs firmly on their shoulders. This listing represents a broader trend in the Golden State, where a mix of high-priced homes and unique selling points speak to a diverse market. In recent times, California has seen a rise in residents seeking more affordable living conditions elsewhere, yet the San Jose neighborhood remains in high demand with properties averaging around $1,620,000 and typically lasting a mere five days on the market. Prospective buyers are clearly informed: the house has not been cleared of contamination and will require clearance by Santa Clara County’s Health Department before it can be accessed. This means no prior inspections or walk-throughs, a stipulation that is undoubtedly causing a stir among interested parties. While the listing does highlight the potential in the property, it also emphasizes that the “remediation process and subsequent costs associated” will be the responsibility of the new owner. It’s a daunting proposition, but for those looking to make a mark in San Jose’s prime real estate locale, this property might just be the diamond in the rough—or in this case, the crystal in the cache. The sale of this home will likely become a landmark case study in the annals of real estate, challenging the norms of what buyers may or may not accept in their pursuit of property ownership. As the housing market continues to navigate post-pandemic conditions and fluctuating buyer expectations, unique listings like this one underscore the complex decisions and risks that come with the territory. For those enticed by the challenge, the San Jose meth lab house awaits—a testament to the unpredictable nature of today’s real estate adventures.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ex-Biden Economic Official Admits: COVID Spending Spurred Inflation Surge</title><link href="/news/2023/11/05/COVID-Spending-Inflation/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ex-Biden Economic Official Admits: COVID Spending Spurred Inflation Surge" /><published>2023-11-05T17:18:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-05T17:18:00-05:00</updated><id>/news/2023/11/05/COVID-Spending-Inflation</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/11/05/COVID-Spending-Inflation/">&lt;p&gt;In a candid admission on Bloomberg’s “Wall Street Week,” Dr. Cecilia Rouse, former Chair of the Biden White House Council of Economic Advisers, recognized that the extensive federal support during COVID-19 significantly fueled the inflationary fires that have been eating away at American pocketbooks. This surprising concession from a former Biden administration official highlights a stark reality: the stimulus packages designed to buoy the economy through the pandemic also played a role in the current inflation crisis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The United States, along with governments worldwide, pumped an unprecedented level of financial aid into their economies to combat the pandemic-induced recession. This massive influx of funds sparked a demand that, as Rouse pointed out, was unmatched by supply, partly due to COVID-related disruptions in the labor force and supply chains. The mismatch led to the price surges that citizens across the country are now grappling with daily.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dr. Rouse’s analysis sheds light on a challenging economic puzzle. With no single, all-encompassing theory of inflation, economists have been piecing together the inflationary picture that has emerged post-pandemic. The Biden administration’s significant stimulus efforts, while providing short-term relief, are now under scrutiny as contributing factors to the long-term economic challenge of inflation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These inflationary pressures are not just numbers on a page; they translate to higher costs at the gas pump, increased grocery bills, and more expensive essentials for families nationwide. The economic decisions made to address the pandemic’s immediate fallout are now leading to a heated debate on fiscal responsibility and the effectiveness of government intervention in the economy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As Americans feel the tightening grip of inflation, the acknowledgement by a former top economic official of the previous administration’s role in this economic strain carries weight, particularly for fiscal conservatives who have long warned about the consequences of unchecked government spending.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the federal government and monetary authorities are now taking steps to normalize the economy, families and businesses across the nation are still facing the consequences of the inflationary spike. The ripple effects of the pandemic economic policies will likely be a topic of analysis and discussion for years to come, as policymakers and citizens alike seek a balanced approach to economic stability and growth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the backdrop of these economic discussions, the American public continues to navigate the realities of a post-pandemic economy—a balancing act of recovery and resilience, with the hopes of returning to a semblance of normalcy without the burden of soaring inflation.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a candid admission on Bloomberg’s “Wall Street Week,” Dr. Cecilia Rouse, former Chair of the Biden White House Council of Economic Advisers, recognized that the extensive federal support during COVID-19 significantly fueled the inflationary fires that have been eating away at American pocketbooks. This surprising concession from a former Biden administration official highlights a stark reality: the stimulus packages designed to buoy the economy through the pandemic also played a role in the current inflation crisis. The United States, along with governments worldwide, pumped an unprecedented level of financial aid into their economies to combat the pandemic-induced recession. This massive influx of funds sparked a demand that, as Rouse pointed out, was unmatched by supply, partly due to COVID-related disruptions in the labor force and supply chains. The mismatch led to the price surges that citizens across the country are now grappling with daily. Dr. Rouse’s analysis sheds light on a challenging economic puzzle. With no single, all-encompassing theory of inflation, economists have been piecing together the inflationary picture that has emerged post-pandemic. The Biden administration’s significant stimulus efforts, while providing short-term relief, are now under scrutiny as contributing factors to the long-term economic challenge of inflation. These inflationary pressures are not just numbers on a page; they translate to higher costs at the gas pump, increased grocery bills, and more expensive essentials for families nationwide. The economic decisions made to address the pandemic’s immediate fallout are now leading to a heated debate on fiscal responsibility and the effectiveness of government intervention in the economy. As Americans feel the tightening grip of inflation, the acknowledgement by a former top economic official of the previous administration’s role in this economic strain carries weight, particularly for fiscal conservatives who have long warned about the consequences of unchecked government spending. While the federal government and monetary authorities are now taking steps to normalize the economy, families and businesses across the nation are still facing the consequences of the inflationary spike. The ripple effects of the pandemic economic policies will likely be a topic of analysis and discussion for years to come, as policymakers and citizens alike seek a balanced approach to economic stability and growth. In the backdrop of these economic discussions, the American public continues to navigate the realities of a post-pandemic economy—a balancing act of recovery and resilience, with the hopes of returning to a semblance of normalcy without the burden of soaring inflation.</summary></entry></feed>