<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-11-05T18:14:47-05:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/11/05/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-11-05T18:14:47-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-05T18:14:47-05:00</updated><id>/2023/11/05/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/11/05/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/11/05/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-11-05T18:14:47-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-05T18:14:47-05:00</updated><id>/2023/11/05/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/11/05/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/">&lt;p&gt;Recent surprise attacks by Hamas on Israel has fueled ongoing tensions between staunchly conservative commentators and the progressive “Squad” Democrats known for criticizing Israel. The intensity of the backlash highlights the deep political divide over foreign policy in the Middle East.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Hamas’ shocking attack, several members of the “Squad,” including Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.), called for a “ceasefire and de-escalation,” condemning the violence. The absence of a statement from Rep. Rashida Tlaib (D-Mich.) was notably called out by conservative media outlets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;South Carolina GOP Rep. Nancy Mace quickly labeled Ocasio-Cortez a “Hamas apologist” in response to her call for peace and de-escalation. Rep. Ilhan Omar (D-Minn.), no stranger to controversy surrounding her views on Israel, echoed the call for de-escalation and ceasefire. Omar’s prior statements comparing the US and Israel to terrorist groups like Hamas and the Taliban resurfaced in the debate, fueling more criticisms. Omar’s 2019 tweet, where she opined that “Israel has hypnotized the world,” also continues to haunt her political career, often cited by critics to challenge her stance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conservative commentators have been especially vocal. “FOX &amp;amp; Friends Weekend” co-host Rachel Campos-Duffy took aim at Omar, saying she fails to recognize the peace in the Middle East under Trump’s administration. Conservative pundit John Hasson also called out Omar, claiming she insinuated that attacks on IDF forces were acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Massachusetts Democrat Rep. Ayanna Pressley’s concerns over the “devastating attacks on Israelis” were met with skepticism. A prominent conservative online personality, Comfortably Smug, accused the “Squad” of advising Israel to back down after the nation suffered massive attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Jamaal Bowman’s call for an end to the Gaza blockade, in addition to condemning the Hamas attacks, was met with criticism from conservative radio host Jason Rantz. He accused Bowman of pairing his condemnation of terrorism with unwarranted criticisms of Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Cori Bush emphasized the urgent need for a ceasefire, while pushing for an end to “U.S. support for Israeli military occupation and apartheid.” Defense attorney Marina Medvin criticized Bush, suggesting that she equates the death of Palestinian terrorists to the horrific acts committed against Jewish civilians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amidst the political turmoil and intense debate, the attacks have taken a heavy toll. Israeli media report over 300 dead due to the wide-ranging assault. Gaza health officials note that at least 200 Palestinians have perished in the retaliatory Israeli air strikes following the initial Hamas attack. As the situation remains volatile, both sides continue to count their casualties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This divisive issue showcases the challenge America faces in crafting a unified approach to foreign policy, with deeply entrenched political divides at play. As the situation develops, the debate is bound to intensify, shedding light on the complexities of U.S. politics in the global arena.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Ex-Biden Economic Official Admits: COVID Spending Spurred Inflation Surge</title><link href="/news/2023/11/05/COVID-Spending-Inflation/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ex-Biden Economic Official Admits: COVID Spending Spurred Inflation Surge" /><published>2023-11-05T17:18:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-05T17:18:00-05:00</updated><id>/news/2023/11/05/COVID-Spending-Inflation</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/11/05/COVID-Spending-Inflation/">&lt;p&gt;In a candid admission on Bloomberg’s “Wall Street Week,” Dr. Cecilia Rouse, former Chair of the Biden White House Council of Economic Advisers, recognized that the extensive federal support during COVID-19 significantly fueled the inflationary fires that have been eating away at American pocketbooks. This surprising concession from a former Biden administration official highlights a stark reality: the stimulus packages designed to buoy the economy through the pandemic also played a role in the current inflation crisis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The United States, along with governments worldwide, pumped an unprecedented level of financial aid into their economies to combat the pandemic-induced recession. This massive influx of funds sparked a demand that, as Rouse pointed out, was unmatched by supply, partly due to COVID-related disruptions in the labor force and supply chains. The mismatch led to the price surges that citizens across the country are now grappling with daily.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dr. Rouse’s analysis sheds light on a challenging economic puzzle. With no single, all-encompassing theory of inflation, economists have been piecing together the inflationary picture that has emerged post-pandemic. The Biden administration’s significant stimulus efforts, while providing short-term relief, are now under scrutiny as contributing factors to the long-term economic challenge of inflation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These inflationary pressures are not just numbers on a page; they translate to higher costs at the gas pump, increased grocery bills, and more expensive essentials for families nationwide. The economic decisions made to address the pandemic’s immediate fallout are now leading to a heated debate on fiscal responsibility and the effectiveness of government intervention in the economy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As Americans feel the tightening grip of inflation, the acknowledgement by a former top economic official of the previous administration’s role in this economic strain carries weight, particularly for fiscal conservatives who have long warned about the consequences of unchecked government spending.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the federal government and monetary authorities are now taking steps to normalize the economy, families and businesses across the nation are still facing the consequences of the inflationary spike. The ripple effects of the pandemic economic policies will likely be a topic of analysis and discussion for years to come, as policymakers and citizens alike seek a balanced approach to economic stability and growth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the backdrop of these economic discussions, the American public continues to navigate the realities of a post-pandemic economy—a balancing act of recovery and resilience, with the hopes of returning to a semblance of normalcy without the burden of soaring inflation.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a candid admission on Bloomberg’s “Wall Street Week,” Dr. Cecilia Rouse, former Chair of the Biden White House Council of Economic Advisers, recognized that the extensive federal support during COVID-19 significantly fueled the inflationary fires that have been eating away at American pocketbooks. This surprising concession from a former Biden administration official highlights a stark reality: the stimulus packages designed to buoy the economy through the pandemic also played a role in the current inflation crisis. The United States, along with governments worldwide, pumped an unprecedented level of financial aid into their economies to combat the pandemic-induced recession. This massive influx of funds sparked a demand that, as Rouse pointed out, was unmatched by supply, partly due to COVID-related disruptions in the labor force and supply chains. The mismatch led to the price surges that citizens across the country are now grappling with daily. Dr. Rouse’s analysis sheds light on a challenging economic puzzle. With no single, all-encompassing theory of inflation, economists have been piecing together the inflationary picture that has emerged post-pandemic. The Biden administration’s significant stimulus efforts, while providing short-term relief, are now under scrutiny as contributing factors to the long-term economic challenge of inflation. These inflationary pressures are not just numbers on a page; they translate to higher costs at the gas pump, increased grocery bills, and more expensive essentials for families nationwide. The economic decisions made to address the pandemic’s immediate fallout are now leading to a heated debate on fiscal responsibility and the effectiveness of government intervention in the economy. As Americans feel the tightening grip of inflation, the acknowledgement by a former top economic official of the previous administration’s role in this economic strain carries weight, particularly for fiscal conservatives who have long warned about the consequences of unchecked government spending. While the federal government and monetary authorities are now taking steps to normalize the economy, families and businesses across the nation are still facing the consequences of the inflationary spike. The ripple effects of the pandemic economic policies will likely be a topic of analysis and discussion for years to come, as policymakers and citizens alike seek a balanced approach to economic stability and growth. In the backdrop of these economic discussions, the American public continues to navigate the realities of a post-pandemic economy—a balancing act of recovery and resilience, with the hopes of returning to a semblance of normalcy without the burden of soaring inflation.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Navy SEAL and Senate Hopeful Sheehy Slams Dem Opponent as ‘Two-Faced Liberal’</title><link href="/politics/2023/11/05/Two-Faced-Opponent/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Navy SEAL and Senate Hopeful Sheehy Slams Dem Opponent as ‘Two-Faced Liberal’" /><published>2023-11-05T16:06:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-05T16:06:00-05:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/11/05/Two-Faced-Opponent</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/11/05/Two-Faced-Opponent/">&lt;p&gt;In the heated race for the U.S. Senate seat in Montana, Republican candidate Tim Sheehy has pulled no punches in calling out his Democratic opponent, Sen. Jon Tester, for what he labels a ‘two-faced’ approach to policy. Sheehy, a Navy SEAL turned political challenger, asserts that Tester is masquerading as a moderate only during election times after a track record of voting in line with President Biden’s agenda.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During a recent exclusive with Fox News Digital, Sheehy, armed with a no-nonsense reputation akin to his military service, claimed Tester’s political maneuvers reveal his true colors as a “dyed-in-the-wool liberal.” This allegation is bolstered by statistics from FiveThirtyEight showing Tester’s high percentage of alignment with Biden on key issues until recently, where he has made a noticeable pivot on topics like border security and foreign policy concerning Iran.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tester’s fluctuating stance on border control has been particularly under scrutiny. While historically opposing substantial funding for border security measures, the Democratic senator has now voiced opposition to Biden’s suspension of Title 42, pushing for a more secure border—a move that Sheehy suggests is a calculated attempt to appear more centrist in the eyes of Montana voters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Financial disclosures revealing campaign contributions from left-leaning figures like George Soros have also fueled Sheehy’s narrative that Tester’s moderate facade doesn’t match his actual political alliances and voting behavior.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This election is shaping up to be about more than just one seat; it’s a referendum on the Biden administration’s policies. Sheehy is tapping into the prevalent concerns of Montanans, from the economic squeeze to the border crisis and its accompanying challenges, including fentanyl deaths and rising cost of living. He promises to champion conservative priorities and restore what he sees as common sense to the Senate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The race in Montana is also set against the broader backdrop of national politics, where Republicans are eager to gain a majority in the Senate. With control of the Senate at stake and several seats up for grabs in states won by Trump, the outcome here is seen as pivotal for the future direction of the country.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sheehy’s campaign, already gathering momentum with endorsements from key political figures like Sen. Steve Daines and Rep. Ryan Zinke, signals a strong conservative pushback against what many Republicans perceive as the “crazy leftist” policies of the current administration. As Sheehy states, the Montana race is not just about one state; it’s a critical piece in the puzzle of national conservative strategy aiming to shape the United States Senate and, consequently, the country’s future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With his sights set on bringing a conservative majority to the Senate, Sheehy’s message is clear: It’s time to get serious about the national elections, and Montana is where the battle lines are being drawn.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In the heated race for the U.S. Senate seat in Montana, Republican candidate Tim Sheehy has pulled no punches in calling out his Democratic opponent, Sen. Jon Tester, for what he labels a ‘two-faced’ approach to policy. Sheehy, a Navy SEAL turned political challenger, asserts that Tester is masquerading as a moderate only during election times after a track record of voting in line with President Biden’s agenda. During a recent exclusive with Fox News Digital, Sheehy, armed with a no-nonsense reputation akin to his military service, claimed Tester’s political maneuvers reveal his true colors as a “dyed-in-the-wool liberal.” This allegation is bolstered by statistics from FiveThirtyEight showing Tester’s high percentage of alignment with Biden on key issues until recently, where he has made a noticeable pivot on topics like border security and foreign policy concerning Iran. Tester’s fluctuating stance on border control has been particularly under scrutiny. While historically opposing substantial funding for border security measures, the Democratic senator has now voiced opposition to Biden’s suspension of Title 42, pushing for a more secure border—a move that Sheehy suggests is a calculated attempt to appear more centrist in the eyes of Montana voters. Financial disclosures revealing campaign contributions from left-leaning figures like George Soros have also fueled Sheehy’s narrative that Tester’s moderate facade doesn’t match his actual political alliances and voting behavior. This election is shaping up to be about more than just one seat; it’s a referendum on the Biden administration’s policies. Sheehy is tapping into the prevalent concerns of Montanans, from the economic squeeze to the border crisis and its accompanying challenges, including fentanyl deaths and rising cost of living. He promises to champion conservative priorities and restore what he sees as common sense to the Senate. The race in Montana is also set against the broader backdrop of national politics, where Republicans are eager to gain a majority in the Senate. With control of the Senate at stake and several seats up for grabs in states won by Trump, the outcome here is seen as pivotal for the future direction of the country. Sheehy’s campaign, already gathering momentum with endorsements from key political figures like Sen. Steve Daines and Rep. Ryan Zinke, signals a strong conservative pushback against what many Republicans perceive as the “crazy leftist” policies of the current administration. As Sheehy states, the Montana race is not just about one state; it’s a critical piece in the puzzle of national conservative strategy aiming to shape the United States Senate and, consequently, the country’s future. With his sights set on bringing a conservative majority to the Senate, Sheehy’s message is clear: It’s time to get serious about the national elections, and Montana is where the battle lines are being drawn.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump Promises Advanced Missile Defense Shield, Echoes Reagan’s Vision</title><link href="/politics/2023/11/05/Missile-Defense-Shield/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump Promises Advanced Missile Defense Shield, Echoes Reagan’s Vision" /><published>2023-11-05T14:58:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-05T14:58:00-05:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/11/05/Missile-Defense-Shield</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/11/05/Missile-Defense-Shield/">&lt;p&gt;Amidst roaring applause at the Florida Republican Party’s Freedom Summit, former President Donald Trump pledged to reinforce America’s safety with a “state of the art missile defense shield.” This powerful promise aligns with a core conservative value: national security.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump’s announcement taps into the pioneering spirit of former President Ronald Reagan’s defense initiatives, envisioning a modern shield that leverages today’s unparalleled technological advancements. It’s a bold step forward from Israel’s Iron Dome, a move that Trump ensures will be “built in America” and will provide “jobs for America.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Critiquing the current administration, Trump highlighted what many Republicans view as President Joe Biden’s perceived failures in foreign policy. By positioning himself as the champion of a robust defense strategy, Trump aims to reassure citizens and reinforce the image of Republican leadership as the vanguard of American strength and security.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The envisioned defense shield is not just a military asset; it’s a symbol of innovation and technological dominance. Trump’s commitment to American-made defense solutions resonates with his audience’s patriotism and the GOP’s push for American manufacturing and job creation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Ronald Reagan wanted to do it,” Trump reflected on the ambitious defense plans of the past, “but at that time they really didn’t have the technology.” Trump asserts that now, with America’s advanced capabilities, it’s possible to create a defense system that could “shoot a needle out of the air.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The promise of a new-age “Trump star wars program” as some are calling it, touches on the nostalgia for Reagan-era defense policies while also promising a leap into the future of military defense. The focus on American ingenuity and the commitment to national defense are central themes that align closely with the Republican audience’s values.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump’s vow is more than a campaign promise; it’s a narrative about American resilience and the enduring call to protect the homeland. As Trump and other Republicans gear up for future elections, such pledges are designed to fortify their stance on national security and serve as a rallying cry for conservative voters who prioritize America’s defense readiness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the shadow of historical defense strategies and with an eye on future threats, Trump’s commitment to a missile defense shield cements his position as a leader who is ready to defend America at all costs. As tensions on the world stage persist, this promise of protection and strength may indeed be a central theme for Republican campaigns and a key factor for voters concerned with safeguarding American soil.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Amidst roaring applause at the Florida Republican Party’s Freedom Summit, former President Donald Trump pledged to reinforce America’s safety with a “state of the art missile defense shield.” This powerful promise aligns with a core conservative value: national security. Trump’s announcement taps into the pioneering spirit of former President Ronald Reagan’s defense initiatives, envisioning a modern shield that leverages today’s unparalleled technological advancements. It’s a bold step forward from Israel’s Iron Dome, a move that Trump ensures will be “built in America” and will provide “jobs for America.” Critiquing the current administration, Trump highlighted what many Republicans view as President Joe Biden’s perceived failures in foreign policy. By positioning himself as the champion of a robust defense strategy, Trump aims to reassure citizens and reinforce the image of Republican leadership as the vanguard of American strength and security. The envisioned defense shield is not just a military asset; it’s a symbol of innovation and technological dominance. Trump’s commitment to American-made defense solutions resonates with his audience’s patriotism and the GOP’s push for American manufacturing and job creation. “Ronald Reagan wanted to do it,” Trump reflected on the ambitious defense plans of the past, “but at that time they really didn’t have the technology.” Trump asserts that now, with America’s advanced capabilities, it’s possible to create a defense system that could “shoot a needle out of the air.” The promise of a new-age “Trump star wars program” as some are calling it, touches on the nostalgia for Reagan-era defense policies while also promising a leap into the future of military defense. The focus on American ingenuity and the commitment to national defense are central themes that align closely with the Republican audience’s values. Trump’s vow is more than a campaign promise; it’s a narrative about American resilience and the enduring call to protect the homeland. As Trump and other Republicans gear up for future elections, such pledges are designed to fortify their stance on national security and serve as a rallying cry for conservative voters who prioritize America’s defense readiness. In the shadow of historical defense strategies and with an eye on future threats, Trump’s commitment to a missile defense shield cements his position as a leader who is ready to defend America at all costs. As tensions on the world stage persist, this promise of protection and strength may indeed be a central theme for Republican campaigns and a key factor for voters concerned with safeguarding American soil.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Show of Strength: U.S. Doubles Down on Eastern Mediterranean Presence to Check Iran</title><link href="/news/2023/11/05/USS-Dwight-D-Eisenhower-Eastern-Mediterranean/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Show of Strength: U.S. Doubles Down on Eastern Mediterranean Presence to Check Iran" /><published>2023-11-05T13:45:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-05T13:45:00-05:00</updated><id>/news/2023/11/05/USS-Dwight-D-Eisenhower-Eastern-Mediterranean</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/11/05/USS-Dwight-D-Eisenhower-Eastern-Mediterranean/">&lt;p&gt;The United States has sent a strong message to Iran and its allies with the arrival of the second aircraft carrier, the USS Dwight D. Eisenhower, in the Eastern Mediterranean. This powerful deployment underscores America’s commitment to defending its allies and deterring aggression in a region rife with conflict and tension.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The USS Dwight D. Eisenhower joins the USS Gerald R. Ford, significantly bolstering the U.S. naval presence in waters that have long been a strategic flashpoint. The Eastern Mediterranean has witnessed increasing friction as Iran continues to exert influence, using groups like Hezbollah to threaten Israel, a key U.S. ally. The U.S. military’s move sends a clear signal of unwavering support for Israel, particularly in its ongoing conflict with Hamas and the broader struggle against terrorism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This show of force is a testament to the United States’ military capabilities and its readiness to act against threats. With both aircraft carriers in close proximity, the message to Tehran is unmistakable: any attempt to open a second front against Israel from Lebanon through proxy forces will be met with formidable resistance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The deployment of these carriers is not only about demonstrating military strength but also serves as a deterrent. Iran’s aspirations for regional dominance have been challenged by U.S. military power, ensuring the security of international waters and maintaining the balance of power in favor of U.S. interests and those of its allies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the carriers make their way through the Mediterranean, they serve as floating fortresses equipped with advanced fighter jets, including F/A-18F Super Hornets, ready to deliver rapid and decisive action if necessary. This flexing of naval muscle showcases the United States’ commitment to peace through strength, a principle that resonates strongly with conservative audiences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The swift movement of the USS Dwight D. Eisenhower through the Strait of Gibraltar and into the Eastern Mediterranean is also a strategic signal to America’s adversaries. The U.S. is willing to deploy its best assets to maintain stability and counter aggressive maneuvers by states like Iran that support terror activities through groups officially designated as terrorist organizations by the U.S. government.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Defense Secretary Lloyd Austin, with the backing of President Joe Biden, has placed additional troops on prepare-to-deploy orders, further highlighting the readiness of the U.S. to support its allies and protect its interests. This move, coupled with the carrier strike group’s presence, affirms the United States’ position as a decisive leader on the world stage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the world watches, the twin carriers’ presence in the Eastern Mediterranean stands as a bulwark against aggression and a guardian of the values that the United States and its allies hold dear. It is a bold statement that America will steadfastly protect its friends and maintain a vigilant watch over regions critical to global security.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">The United States has sent a strong message to Iran and its allies with the arrival of the second aircraft carrier, the USS Dwight D. Eisenhower, in the Eastern Mediterranean. This powerful deployment underscores America’s commitment to defending its allies and deterring aggression in a region rife with conflict and tension. The USS Dwight D. Eisenhower joins the USS Gerald R. Ford, significantly bolstering the U.S. naval presence in waters that have long been a strategic flashpoint. The Eastern Mediterranean has witnessed increasing friction as Iran continues to exert influence, using groups like Hezbollah to threaten Israel, a key U.S. ally. The U.S. military’s move sends a clear signal of unwavering support for Israel, particularly in its ongoing conflict with Hamas and the broader struggle against terrorism. This show of force is a testament to the United States’ military capabilities and its readiness to act against threats. With both aircraft carriers in close proximity, the message to Tehran is unmistakable: any attempt to open a second front against Israel from Lebanon through proxy forces will be met with formidable resistance. The deployment of these carriers is not only about demonstrating military strength but also serves as a deterrent. Iran’s aspirations for regional dominance have been challenged by U.S. military power, ensuring the security of international waters and maintaining the balance of power in favor of U.S. interests and those of its allies. As the carriers make their way through the Mediterranean, they serve as floating fortresses equipped with advanced fighter jets, including F/A-18F Super Hornets, ready to deliver rapid and decisive action if necessary. This flexing of naval muscle showcases the United States’ commitment to peace through strength, a principle that resonates strongly with conservative audiences. The swift movement of the USS Dwight D. Eisenhower through the Strait of Gibraltar and into the Eastern Mediterranean is also a strategic signal to America’s adversaries. The U.S. is willing to deploy its best assets to maintain stability and counter aggressive maneuvers by states like Iran that support terror activities through groups officially designated as terrorist organizations by the U.S. government. Defense Secretary Lloyd Austin, with the backing of President Joe Biden, has placed additional troops on prepare-to-deploy orders, further highlighting the readiness of the U.S. to support its allies and protect its interests. This move, coupled with the carrier strike group’s presence, affirms the United States’ position as a decisive leader on the world stage. As the world watches, the twin carriers’ presence in the Eastern Mediterranean stands as a bulwark against aggression and a guardian of the values that the United States and its allies hold dear. It is a bold statement that America will steadfastly protect its friends and maintain a vigilant watch over regions critical to global security.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Sinister Healthcare Homicides: Nurse’s ‘Murderous Rage’ Echoes Infamous Serial Killer</title><link href="/news/2023/11/05/Sinister-Healthcare-Homicides/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sinister Healthcare Homicides: Nurse’s ‘Murderous Rage’ Echoes Infamous Serial Killer" /><published>2023-11-05T12:29:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-05T12:29:00-05:00</updated><id>/news/2023/11/05/Sinister-Healthcare-Homicides</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/11/05/Sinister-Healthcare-Homicides/">&lt;p&gt;In a tale almost too grim to be true, Heather Irene Pressdee, a former veterinary technician-turned-nurse, stands accused of multiple counts of murder and attempted murder in what appears to be a horrifying instance of life imitating art. The suspected serial killer nurse’s case bears a disturbing resemblance to the chilling narrative of Charles Cullen, the infamous ‘Angel of Death’, raising the specter of a healthcare professional turned harbinger of death.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The allegations are as serious as they are shocking: Pressdee, implicated in the deaths of 17 patients and the injury of others, reportedly harbored a “murderous rage” that fueled her transition from euthanizing animals to administering lethal doses of insulin to unsuspecting patients. Her actions have not only reopened old wounds for the families affected by Cullen’s reign of terror but have also stirred a national conversation about the vulnerabilities in our healthcare system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pressdee’s arrest throws into sharp relief the stark contrast between the nurturing image of a nurse and the calculated coldness of a budding serial killer. It’s a jarring dichotomy that has been thrust into the public eye, not least because of the staggering body count she’s accused of amassing in her short five-year nursing career.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The narrative is ripped right out of a true-crime thriller, with elements so eerily aligned with Hollywood portrayals that it challenges the boundary between reality and fiction. It is alleged that Pressdee, mirroring the modus operandi of Cullen, injected patients with insulin doses they didn’t need – and in some instances, may have timed these doses to ensure the patients would “expire” before a shift change, minimizing the risk of getting caught.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s perhaps more unsettling is the trail of text messages, including one to her mother about “pillow therapy,” which suggests a premeditated contempt for human life rarely seen outside of cinema or the pages of a crime novel. In this digital age, evidence from a suspect’s cellphone can cast a long and incriminating shadow, one that might just reveal the true extent of Pressdee’s alleged crimes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The question that haunts us now is “why?” Why would someone who has sworn to care and heal turn to such dark and destructive acts? The transformation from caring for animals to taking human lives suggests a deeply troubling journey from compassion to cruelty. This journey, as the criminal complaint suggests, didn’t just happen overnight; it was a gradual, morbid evolution of a “budding serial killer.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the authorities continue to unravel this macabre tapestry of deceit and death, one can’t help but wonder about the vulnerability of the very institutions we trust with our lives. If the allegations prove true, Heather Pressdee’s case will serve as a chilling reminder that sometimes the most dangerous predators wear a mask of benevolence, lurking not in the shadows but in the sanitized corridors of our hospitals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This case underscores the imperative for vigilance and thorough scrutiny within the healthcare sector to protect the innocent and prevent such tragedies from recurring. As we delve into the psyche of a suspected killer nurse, it is a sobering moment to reflect on the fragile line between care and harm that has been breached in the most tragic of ways.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The nurse remains in custody, and as this haunting saga continues to unfold, one thing is painfully clear: the face of evil may sometimes wear the guise of a healer, and uncovering the truth behind such a façade is a task both grim and necessary.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a tale almost too grim to be true, Heather Irene Pressdee, a former veterinary technician-turned-nurse, stands accused of multiple counts of murder and attempted murder in what appears to be a horrifying instance of life imitating art. The suspected serial killer nurse’s case bears a disturbing resemblance to the chilling narrative of Charles Cullen, the infamous ‘Angel of Death’, raising the specter of a healthcare professional turned harbinger of death. The allegations are as serious as they are shocking: Pressdee, implicated in the deaths of 17 patients and the injury of others, reportedly harbored a “murderous rage” that fueled her transition from euthanizing animals to administering lethal doses of insulin to unsuspecting patients. Her actions have not only reopened old wounds for the families affected by Cullen’s reign of terror but have also stirred a national conversation about the vulnerabilities in our healthcare system. Pressdee’s arrest throws into sharp relief the stark contrast between the nurturing image of a nurse and the calculated coldness of a budding serial killer. It’s a jarring dichotomy that has been thrust into the public eye, not least because of the staggering body count she’s accused of amassing in her short five-year nursing career. The narrative is ripped right out of a true-crime thriller, with elements so eerily aligned with Hollywood portrayals that it challenges the boundary between reality and fiction. It is alleged that Pressdee, mirroring the modus operandi of Cullen, injected patients with insulin doses they didn’t need – and in some instances, may have timed these doses to ensure the patients would “expire” before a shift change, minimizing the risk of getting caught. What’s perhaps more unsettling is the trail of text messages, including one to her mother about “pillow therapy,” which suggests a premeditated contempt for human life rarely seen outside of cinema or the pages of a crime novel. In this digital age, evidence from a suspect’s cellphone can cast a long and incriminating shadow, one that might just reveal the true extent of Pressdee’s alleged crimes. The question that haunts us now is “why?” Why would someone who has sworn to care and heal turn to such dark and destructive acts? The transformation from caring for animals to taking human lives suggests a deeply troubling journey from compassion to cruelty. This journey, as the criminal complaint suggests, didn’t just happen overnight; it was a gradual, morbid evolution of a “budding serial killer.” As the authorities continue to unravel this macabre tapestry of deceit and death, one can’t help but wonder about the vulnerability of the very institutions we trust with our lives. If the allegations prove true, Heather Pressdee’s case will serve as a chilling reminder that sometimes the most dangerous predators wear a mask of benevolence, lurking not in the shadows but in the sanitized corridors of our hospitals. This case underscores the imperative for vigilance and thorough scrutiny within the healthcare sector to protect the innocent and prevent such tragedies from recurring. As we delve into the psyche of a suspected killer nurse, it is a sobering moment to reflect on the fragile line between care and harm that has been breached in the most tragic of ways. The nurse remains in custody, and as this haunting saga continues to unfold, one thing is painfully clear: the face of evil may sometimes wear the guise of a healer, and uncovering the truth behind such a façade is a task both grim and necessary.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump Triumphs Over Biden in Key Battleground States, NY Times Poll Reveals</title><link href="/politics/2023/11/05/Trump-Tops-Biden-Swing-States/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump Triumphs Over Biden in Key Battleground States, NY Times Poll Reveals" /><published>2023-11-05T11:20:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-05T11:20:00-05:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/11/05/Trump-Tops-Biden-Swing-States</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/11/05/Trump-Tops-Biden-Swing-States/">&lt;p&gt;Former President Donald Trump has surged ahead of President Joe Biden in five of six pivotal swing states, according to recent polling data from the New York Times. This sudden twist in political winds could signal a major red wave on the horizon as we edge closer to the 2024 presidential election.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The figures speak volumes, with Trump boasting an 11-point lead in Nevada and a comfortable advantage in Arizona, Pennsylvania, Georgia, and Michigan. These states, won by Biden in the previous election, appear to be flipping in favor of Trump, hinting at a seismic shift in the political landscape. Only Wisconsin remains a holdout, with Biden clinging to a narrow lead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The significance of these numbers cannot be overstated, particularly considering these states’ histories of teetering between blue and red. Nevada and Arizona, both affected by the pressing border crisis, show a marked turn in public opinion, presumably due to the influx of unvetted migrants—a policy point that has been heavily criticized by conservative circles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, the polling also unveils a stark contrast in the public’s perception of both candidates’ age and mental fitness for office. A vast majority view Biden as too old, questioning his capability to effectively lead the nation. On the other hand, Trump’s age seems to be a lesser concern among his supporters and the general populace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The economic landscape also plays a significant role in Trump’s favor. With high inflation rates and economic uncertainty plaguing the Biden administration, Trump is seen as the more reliable steward of the economy, enjoying a 22-point lead over Biden on this critical issue. National security and immigration also stand out as areas where Trump outpaces the current administration, resonating with the electorate’s desire for a robust and secure nation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As we approach what may be one of the most consequential elections in recent history, the NY Times poll sheds light on a stark reality: Trump is not only in contention but leading in battleground states that could decide the fate of the presidency. This data, though early, may well be the writing on the wall for a Biden campaign that appears to be struggling to connect with voters on pivotal issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With such early indicators, Republican optimism is palpable, as is the trepidation within Democratic circles. It’s clear that Trump’s political clout remains formidable, and if the current trends hold, we could be witnessing the dawn of a political comeback unlike any in American history.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The battle lines are drawn, and the stakes are high. As the political tides seem to be turning, America watches with bated breath as the countdown to 2024 continues.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Former President Donald Trump has surged ahead of President Joe Biden in five of six pivotal swing states, according to recent polling data from the New York Times. This sudden twist in political winds could signal a major red wave on the horizon as we edge closer to the 2024 presidential election. The figures speak volumes, with Trump boasting an 11-point lead in Nevada and a comfortable advantage in Arizona, Pennsylvania, Georgia, and Michigan. These states, won by Biden in the previous election, appear to be flipping in favor of Trump, hinting at a seismic shift in the political landscape. Only Wisconsin remains a holdout, with Biden clinging to a narrow lead. The significance of these numbers cannot be overstated, particularly considering these states’ histories of teetering between blue and red. Nevada and Arizona, both affected by the pressing border crisis, show a marked turn in public opinion, presumably due to the influx of unvetted migrants—a policy point that has been heavily criticized by conservative circles. Interestingly, the polling also unveils a stark contrast in the public’s perception of both candidates’ age and mental fitness for office. A vast majority view Biden as too old, questioning his capability to effectively lead the nation. On the other hand, Trump’s age seems to be a lesser concern among his supporters and the general populace. The economic landscape also plays a significant role in Trump’s favor. With high inflation rates and economic uncertainty plaguing the Biden administration, Trump is seen as the more reliable steward of the economy, enjoying a 22-point lead over Biden on this critical issue. National security and immigration also stand out as areas where Trump outpaces the current administration, resonating with the electorate’s desire for a robust and secure nation. As we approach what may be one of the most consequential elections in recent history, the NY Times poll sheds light on a stark reality: Trump is not only in contention but leading in battleground states that could decide the fate of the presidency. This data, though early, may well be the writing on the wall for a Biden campaign that appears to be struggling to connect with voters on pivotal issues. With such early indicators, Republican optimism is palpable, as is the trepidation within Democratic circles. It’s clear that Trump’s political clout remains formidable, and if the current trends hold, we could be witnessing the dawn of a political comeback unlike any in American history. The battle lines are drawn, and the stakes are high. As the political tides seem to be turning, America watches with bated breath as the countdown to 2024 continues.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Tony Bobulinski Challenges Biden Family for Joint Public Testimony</title><link href="/politics/2023/11/04/Biden-Family-Testimony/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tony Bobulinski Challenges Biden Family for Joint Public Testimony" /><published>2023-11-04T20:11:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-11-04T20:11:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/11/04/Biden-Family-Testimony</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/11/04/Biden-Family-Testimony/">&lt;p&gt;Hunter Biden’s ex-business associate, Tony Bobulinski, is striking back against allegations of falsehood by proposing a remarkable public testimony before Congress involving members of the Biden family. The backdrop of this saga features accusations and denials swirling around the intricate web of the Biden’s international business dealings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bobulinski, embroiled in controversy following claims from Hunter Biden’s legal counsel that he misled federal authorities, has taken an aggressive stance against the accusations. He vehemently denies the charges that he provided false statements to the FBI concerning his business relationship with Hunter Biden and the Chinese energy company CEFC. This dispute draws the public’s attention not only to the alleged business negotiations but also to the political ramifications they may have.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The invitation extended by Bobulinski for a joint public congressional testimony alongside Hunter, his uncle James Biden, and perhaps even Joe Biden himself, raises the stakes in this political and legal drama. His bold challenge throws down the gauntlet, demanding a space where, under the scrutiny of public gaze and oath-bound truth-telling, the veracity of his and the Biden family’s claims can be weighed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This confrontation is rooted in a detailed 10-page letter penned by Hunter Biden’s attorney, Abbe Lowell, to the U.S. Attorney for the District of Columbia, urging an investigation into Bobulinski’s supposed falsehoods. The document alleges that Bobulinski fabricated stories about his dealings with Hunter Biden to unfairly implicate the Biden family in unethical business practices with the Chinese company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet, the tables are turning as Bobulinski, unshaken by the allegations, is calling their bluff. He insists on revealing the facts transparently, believing that the American people deserve to witness this accountability in action. His statement emphasizes the desperation in the use of Department of Justice as a weapon against him, critiquing what he perceives as an attempt to cover up the truth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Central to this are references to the infamous May 13, 2017, email involving the joint venture with CEFC, which has fueled speculations about Joe Biden’s alleged involvement, referred to cryptically as “the big guy.” These insinuations tie the President himself to the controversy, prompting discussions around the integrity and transparency of the current administration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Republican-led House Oversight Committee has responded with its own accusations of witness intimidation by the Biden legal team, vowing not to be deterred in uncovering the truth. The committee insists that Hunter Biden will soon have the opportunity to address these claims directly, potentially before the congressional investigation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the anticipation builds, the public eagerly awaits the Biden family’s response to Bobulinski’s challenge, and whether this joint testimony will come to fruition. Will it be a pivotal moment of truth in American politics, or another chapter in the ongoing narrative of partisanship and obscured truths? Only time, and perhaps the proposed testimony, will tell.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Hunter Biden’s ex-business associate, Tony Bobulinski, is striking back against allegations of falsehood by proposing a remarkable public testimony before Congress involving members of the Biden family. The backdrop of this saga features accusations and denials swirling around the intricate web of the Biden’s international business dealings. Bobulinski, embroiled in controversy following claims from Hunter Biden’s legal counsel that he misled federal authorities, has taken an aggressive stance against the accusations. He vehemently denies the charges that he provided false statements to the FBI concerning his business relationship with Hunter Biden and the Chinese energy company CEFC. This dispute draws the public’s attention not only to the alleged business negotiations but also to the political ramifications they may have. The invitation extended by Bobulinski for a joint public congressional testimony alongside Hunter, his uncle James Biden, and perhaps even Joe Biden himself, raises the stakes in this political and legal drama. His bold challenge throws down the gauntlet, demanding a space where, under the scrutiny of public gaze and oath-bound truth-telling, the veracity of his and the Biden family’s claims can be weighed. This confrontation is rooted in a detailed 10-page letter penned by Hunter Biden’s attorney, Abbe Lowell, to the U.S. Attorney for the District of Columbia, urging an investigation into Bobulinski’s supposed falsehoods. The document alleges that Bobulinski fabricated stories about his dealings with Hunter Biden to unfairly implicate the Biden family in unethical business practices with the Chinese company. Yet, the tables are turning as Bobulinski, unshaken by the allegations, is calling their bluff. He insists on revealing the facts transparently, believing that the American people deserve to witness this accountability in action. His statement emphasizes the desperation in the use of Department of Justice as a weapon against him, critiquing what he perceives as an attempt to cover up the truth. Central to this are references to the infamous May 13, 2017, email involving the joint venture with CEFC, which has fueled speculations about Joe Biden’s alleged involvement, referred to cryptically as “the big guy.” These insinuations tie the President himself to the controversy, prompting discussions around the integrity and transparency of the current administration. The Republican-led House Oversight Committee has responded with its own accusations of witness intimidation by the Biden legal team, vowing not to be deterred in uncovering the truth. The committee insists that Hunter Biden will soon have the opportunity to address these claims directly, potentially before the congressional investigation. As the anticipation builds, the public eagerly awaits the Biden family’s response to Bobulinski’s challenge, and whether this joint testimony will come to fruition. Will it be a pivotal moment of truth in American politics, or another chapter in the ongoing narrative of partisanship and obscured truths? Only time, and perhaps the proposed testimony, will tell.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">New Legislation Targets Ammo Purchases with Background Checks</title><link href="/news/2023/11/04/Ammo-Background-Checks/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="New Legislation Targets Ammo Purchases with Background Checks" /><published>2023-11-04T18:59:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-11-04T18:59:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/11/04/Ammo-Background-Checks</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/11/04/Ammo-Background-Checks/">&lt;p&gt;Key Democrats are pushing forward a piece of legislation that could significantly change the way Americans buy ammunition. Spearheaded by Rep. Robert Garcia (D-CA) and Sen. Elizabeth Warren (D-MA), the proposed Ammunition Modernization and Monitoring Oversight Act, or AMMO Act, aims to place new restrictions on ammo purchases, which could impact gun owners countrywide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Under the AMMO Act, individuals looking to buy ammunition would be subject to background checks, similar to those currently required for firearm purchases. But the legislation doesn’t stop there. It also proposes a limit on the quantity of rounds that can be bought over a five-day span and calls for ammunition dealers to obtain a specific license, setting them apart from the Federal Firearms License (FFL) needed for gun sales.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This legislation has attracted the attention of conservative circles and Second Amendment advocates who view these measures as potential infringements on gun rights. The conversation is heating up as supporters of the bill, like Rep. Debbie Wasserman Schultz (D-FL), rally behind the idea that regulating ammunition is essential for tackling the gun violence epidemic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Garcia, addressing the urgency of the bill, highlighted that controlling ammo accessibility is a critical step in confronting gun-related violence. Similarly, Sen. Warren echoed these sentiments, labeling the Ammo Act as a “common-sense” approach to curtailing gun violence in America.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The proposed Act also includes a provision that would ban out-of-state ammunition purchases, effectively nationalizing a policy that is currently in place in California. The Golden State, which already boasts some of the strictest gun control laws in the country and is acknowledged by Everytown for Gun Safety for its rigorous regulations, also leads in active shooter incidents, according to 2021 statistics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Critics of the bill argue that such legislation may not address the root causes of gun violence and instead place undue burdens on law-abiding citizens exercising their Second Amendment rights. There’s growing concern among gun owners that these measures may pave the way for more restrictive laws in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the debate rages on Capitol Hill, Americans are watching closely to see if the AMMO Act will gain the momentum necessary to pass into law. With gun rights being a fiercely protected American value, any legislation altering the landscape of gun and ammo ownership is sure to be met with vocal responses from all sides of the political spectrum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The implications of the AMMO Act are far-reaching, and its progress through Congress will be a litmus test for the current administration’s stance on gun control. In a nation that holds the right to bear arms as a fundamental liberty, the outcome of this legislation will be a significant indicator of the direction in which America’s gun laws are headed.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Key Democrats are pushing forward a piece of legislation that could significantly change the way Americans buy ammunition. Spearheaded by Rep. Robert Garcia (D-CA) and Sen. Elizabeth Warren (D-MA), the proposed Ammunition Modernization and Monitoring Oversight Act, or AMMO Act, aims to place new restrictions on ammo purchases, which could impact gun owners countrywide. Under the AMMO Act, individuals looking to buy ammunition would be subject to background checks, similar to those currently required for firearm purchases. But the legislation doesn’t stop there. It also proposes a limit on the quantity of rounds that can be bought over a five-day span and calls for ammunition dealers to obtain a specific license, setting them apart from the Federal Firearms License (FFL) needed for gun sales. This legislation has attracted the attention of conservative circles and Second Amendment advocates who view these measures as potential infringements on gun rights. The conversation is heating up as supporters of the bill, like Rep. Debbie Wasserman Schultz (D-FL), rally behind the idea that regulating ammunition is essential for tackling the gun violence epidemic. Rep. Garcia, addressing the urgency of the bill, highlighted that controlling ammo accessibility is a critical step in confronting gun-related violence. Similarly, Sen. Warren echoed these sentiments, labeling the Ammo Act as a “common-sense” approach to curtailing gun violence in America. The proposed Act also includes a provision that would ban out-of-state ammunition purchases, effectively nationalizing a policy that is currently in place in California. The Golden State, which already boasts some of the strictest gun control laws in the country and is acknowledged by Everytown for Gun Safety for its rigorous regulations, also leads in active shooter incidents, according to 2021 statistics. Critics of the bill argue that such legislation may not address the root causes of gun violence and instead place undue burdens on law-abiding citizens exercising their Second Amendment rights. There’s growing concern among gun owners that these measures may pave the way for more restrictive laws in the future. As the debate rages on Capitol Hill, Americans are watching closely to see if the AMMO Act will gain the momentum necessary to pass into law. With gun rights being a fiercely protected American value, any legislation altering the landscape of gun and ammo ownership is sure to be met with vocal responses from all sides of the political spectrum. The implications of the AMMO Act are far-reaching, and its progress through Congress will be a litmus test for the current administration’s stance on gun control. In a nation that holds the right to bear arms as a fundamental liberty, the outcome of this legislation will be a significant indicator of the direction in which America’s gun laws are headed.</summary></entry></feed>