<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-11-02T12:21:15-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/11/02/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-11-02T12:21:15-04:00</published><updated>2023-11-02T12:21:15-04:00</updated><id>/2023/11/02/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/11/02/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/11/02/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-11-02T12:21:15-04:00</published><updated>2023-11-02T12:21:15-04:00</updated><id>/2023/11/02/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/11/02/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/">&lt;p&gt;Recent surprise attacks by Hamas on Israel has fueled ongoing tensions between staunchly conservative commentators and the progressive “Squad” Democrats known for criticizing Israel. The intensity of the backlash highlights the deep political divide over foreign policy in the Middle East.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Hamas’ shocking attack, several members of the “Squad,” including Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.), called for a “ceasefire and de-escalation,” condemning the violence. The absence of a statement from Rep. Rashida Tlaib (D-Mich.) was notably called out by conservative media outlets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;South Carolina GOP Rep. Nancy Mace quickly labeled Ocasio-Cortez a “Hamas apologist” in response to her call for peace and de-escalation. Rep. Ilhan Omar (D-Minn.), no stranger to controversy surrounding her views on Israel, echoed the call for de-escalation and ceasefire. Omar’s prior statements comparing the US and Israel to terrorist groups like Hamas and the Taliban resurfaced in the debate, fueling more criticisms. Omar’s 2019 tweet, where she opined that “Israel has hypnotized the world,” also continues to haunt her political career, often cited by critics to challenge her stance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conservative commentators have been especially vocal. “FOX &amp;amp; Friends Weekend” co-host Rachel Campos-Duffy took aim at Omar, saying she fails to recognize the peace in the Middle East under Trump’s administration. Conservative pundit John Hasson also called out Omar, claiming she insinuated that attacks on IDF forces were acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Massachusetts Democrat Rep. Ayanna Pressley’s concerns over the “devastating attacks on Israelis” were met with skepticism. A prominent conservative online personality, Comfortably Smug, accused the “Squad” of advising Israel to back down after the nation suffered massive attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Jamaal Bowman’s call for an end to the Gaza blockade, in addition to condemning the Hamas attacks, was met with criticism from conservative radio host Jason Rantz. He accused Bowman of pairing his condemnation of terrorism with unwarranted criticisms of Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Cori Bush emphasized the urgent need for a ceasefire, while pushing for an end to “U.S. support for Israeli military occupation and apartheid.” Defense attorney Marina Medvin criticized Bush, suggesting that she equates the death of Palestinian terrorists to the horrific acts committed against Jewish civilians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amidst the political turmoil and intense debate, the attacks have taken a heavy toll. Israeli media report over 300 dead due to the wide-ranging assault. Gaza health officials note that at least 200 Palestinians have perished in the retaliatory Israeli air strikes following the initial Hamas attack. As the situation remains volatile, both sides continue to count their casualties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This divisive issue showcases the challenge America faces in crafting a unified approach to foreign policy, with deeply entrenched political divides at play. As the situation develops, the debate is bound to intensify, shedding light on the complexities of U.S. politics in the global arena.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Rep. George Santos Dodges Expulsion, Emphasizing Need for Due Process</title><link href="/politics/2023/11/02/Santos-House-Expulsion-Attempt/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rep. George Santos Dodges Expulsion, Emphasizing Need for Due Process" /><published>2023-11-02T11:34:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-11-02T11:34:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/11/02/Santos-House-Expulsion-Attempt</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/11/02/Santos-House-Expulsion-Attempt/">&lt;p&gt;Rep. George Santos (R-N.Y.) managed to stave off expulsion from the House of Representatives. The scene turned chaotic as Santos engaged in a heated exchange with an anti-Israel protester, showcasing the high tensions surrounding the Congressman.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Santos found himself in the eye of the storm, with a faction of his fellow New York Republicans leading the charge to expel him from the House. Despite the pressure, the final vote tallied at 213-179 against expulsion, with 19 lawmakers choosing to vote “present.” It is crucial to note that expelling a member from the House is an exceptional action, requiring a two-thirds majority of all members present.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, the vote saw 24 Republicans favoring expulsion, while 31 Democrats opted to keep Santos in the House. This vote distribution led Santos to comment on the perceived political landscape, stating, “There’s more Democrats in this body that believe in the rule of law than there are Republicans. That’s what you should know.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Santos, under a cloud of legal troubles, stood his ground, asserting his right to due process. “I am fighting to clear my name. I am fighting for due process,” he emphasized, highlighting the significance of these legal principles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The New York Republicans spearheading the expulsion effort included Anthony D’Esposito, Nick LaLota, and Mike Lawler. Santos, defending himself on the House floor, accused them of overstepping their roles, acting as “judge, jury, and executioner.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Santos’s speech underscored his commitment to proving his innocence against the myriad of charges leveled against him. “Efforts taken by other members in this body to act as jury and executioner are unconscionable and reckless to our Republican system of government and to the integrity of this body,” he proclaimed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite being the sole member of Congress to speak in his defense during the debate, Santos’s words resonated with the need for consistency in upholding constitutional values. He questioned the actions of his peers, urging them to reflect on their commitment to the Constitution while challenging their role in this legal process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Santos’s escape from expulsion does not mark the end of his legal battles, as he faces 23 charges, including conspiracy, wire fraud, making false statements, falsification of records, aggravated identity theft, and credit card fraud. The resolution of these charges will be crucial in determining his political future, but for now, Santos remains a member of the House of Representatives, emphasizing the paramount importance of due process in the American legal system.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Rep. George Santos (R-N.Y.) managed to stave off expulsion from the House of Representatives. The scene turned chaotic as Santos engaged in a heated exchange with an anti-Israel protester, showcasing the high tensions surrounding the Congressman. Santos found himself in the eye of the storm, with a faction of his fellow New York Republicans leading the charge to expel him from the House. Despite the pressure, the final vote tallied at 213-179 against expulsion, with 19 lawmakers choosing to vote “present.” It is crucial to note that expelling a member from the House is an exceptional action, requiring a two-thirds majority of all members present. Interestingly, the vote saw 24 Republicans favoring expulsion, while 31 Democrats opted to keep Santos in the House. This vote distribution led Santos to comment on the perceived political landscape, stating, “There’s more Democrats in this body that believe in the rule of law than there are Republicans. That’s what you should know.” Santos, under a cloud of legal troubles, stood his ground, asserting his right to due process. “I am fighting to clear my name. I am fighting for due process,” he emphasized, highlighting the significance of these legal principles. The New York Republicans spearheading the expulsion effort included Anthony D’Esposito, Nick LaLota, and Mike Lawler. Santos, defending himself on the House floor, accused them of overstepping their roles, acting as “judge, jury, and executioner.” Santos’s speech underscored his commitment to proving his innocence against the myriad of charges leveled against him. “Efforts taken by other members in this body to act as jury and executioner are unconscionable and reckless to our Republican system of government and to the integrity of this body,” he proclaimed. Despite being the sole member of Congress to speak in his defense during the debate, Santos’s words resonated with the need for consistency in upholding constitutional values. He questioned the actions of his peers, urging them to reflect on their commitment to the Constitution while challenging their role in this legal process. Santos’s escape from expulsion does not mark the end of his legal battles, as he faces 23 charges, including conspiracy, wire fraud, making false statements, falsification of records, aggravated identity theft, and credit card fraud. The resolution of these charges will be crucial in determining his political future, but for now, Santos remains a member of the House of Representatives, emphasizing the paramount importance of due process in the American legal system.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Rep. Boebert Stands Firm: ‘No Place in Congress for Anti-Israel Sentiments’</title><link href="/politics/2023/11/02/Boebert-Tlaib-Controversy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rep. Boebert Stands Firm: ‘No Place in Congress for Anti-Israel Sentiments’" /><published>2023-11-02T10:26:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-11-02T10:26:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/11/02/Boebert-Tlaib-Controversy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/11/02/Boebert-Tlaib-Controversy/">&lt;p&gt;Rep. Lauren Boebert (R-Colo.) did not mince words as she declared that there is absolutely no room in Congress for individuals who share the same anti-Israel views as Rep. Rashida Tlaib (D-Mich.). Boebert’s statement comes in the aftermath of a terrorist attack on Israel by Hamas on October 7th, which left over 1,400 Israelis dead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The House of Representatives, caught in the midst of political tumult, witnessed a motion last week by Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene (R-Ga.) seeking to censure Tlaib for her vehement criticism of Israel following the attack. However, this motion was tabled with a vote of 222-186, as 23 Republicans joined Democrats in opposition. Boebert, unwavering in her stance, was not among the dissenters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During her appearance on “Eric Bolling The Balance,” Boebert clearly articulated her viewpoint, stating, “There are lines that members of Congress should not cross, and supporting terrorist groups like Hamas is definitely one of those lines.” She continued by expressing that there is simply no place in Congress for individuals who embody ignorance and hatred to the extent that Tlaib does, voicing her support for the censure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since becoming the first Congress member of Palestinian descent in 2018, Tlaib has been vocal in her critique of Israeli policies, calling for sanctions and accusing Israel of perpetuating apartheid in the Gaza Strip. She maintains this stance despite the Palestinians’ self-governing status in Gaza, a result of electing Hamas to power in 2006.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Boebert did not hold back as she addressed this issue, stating, “There are some [in Congress] who are siding with Hamas during this horrible and brutal attack on Israel, this war that is taking place.” She highlighted that while there are members on the opposite side of the aisle expressing support for Israel, it remains uncertain whether it will translate into concrete action against one of their own.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Emphasizing the strength of the U.S.-Israel alliance, Boebert affirmed, “Israel, our nation’s most trusted ally, has every right to defend itself. And we are here standing in solidarity as Republicans with Israel every step of the way.” She condemned Hamas’ actions as utterly repulsive and expressed her heartfelt prayers for the Israelis and all innocent victims caught in the crossfire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Boebert’s strong, unwavering support for Israel and her call for accountability within Congress reflect the conservative values of standing with allies and ensuring that anti-Israel sentiments do not find a foothold in American politics.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Rep. Lauren Boebert (R-Colo.) did not mince words as she declared that there is absolutely no room in Congress for individuals who share the same anti-Israel views as Rep. Rashida Tlaib (D-Mich.). Boebert’s statement comes in the aftermath of a terrorist attack on Israel by Hamas on October 7th, which left over 1,400 Israelis dead. The House of Representatives, caught in the midst of political tumult, witnessed a motion last week by Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene (R-Ga.) seeking to censure Tlaib for her vehement criticism of Israel following the attack. However, this motion was tabled with a vote of 222-186, as 23 Republicans joined Democrats in opposition. Boebert, unwavering in her stance, was not among the dissenters. During her appearance on “Eric Bolling The Balance,” Boebert clearly articulated her viewpoint, stating, “There are lines that members of Congress should not cross, and supporting terrorist groups like Hamas is definitely one of those lines.” She continued by expressing that there is simply no place in Congress for individuals who embody ignorance and hatred to the extent that Tlaib does, voicing her support for the censure. Since becoming the first Congress member of Palestinian descent in 2018, Tlaib has been vocal in her critique of Israeli policies, calling for sanctions and accusing Israel of perpetuating apartheid in the Gaza Strip. She maintains this stance despite the Palestinians’ self-governing status in Gaza, a result of electing Hamas to power in 2006. Boebert did not hold back as she addressed this issue, stating, “There are some [in Congress] who are siding with Hamas during this horrible and brutal attack on Israel, this war that is taking place.” She highlighted that while there are members on the opposite side of the aisle expressing support for Israel, it remains uncertain whether it will translate into concrete action against one of their own. Emphasizing the strength of the U.S.-Israel alliance, Boebert affirmed, “Israel, our nation’s most trusted ally, has every right to defend itself. And we are here standing in solidarity as Republicans with Israel every step of the way.” She condemned Hamas’ actions as utterly repulsive and expressed her heartfelt prayers for the Israelis and all innocent victims caught in the crossfire. Boebert’s strong, unwavering support for Israel and her call for accountability within Congress reflect the conservative values of standing with allies and ensuring that anti-Israel sentiments do not find a foothold in American politics.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A Sinister Surprise: Sewing Needles Found in Halloween Candy</title><link href="/news/2023/11/02/Halloween-Candy-Safety/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Sinister Surprise: Sewing Needles Found in Halloween Candy" /><published>2023-11-02T09:18:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-11-02T09:18:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/11/02/Halloween-Candy-Safety</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/11/02/Halloween-Candy-Safety/">&lt;p&gt;A discerning parent discovered sewing needles hidden inside their child’s Halloween candy. The incident occurred during the much-anticipated trick-or-treat festivities in Cumberland County, and has since spurred a full-blown police investigation, as well as a community-wide call to action for increased vigilance and caution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Silver Spring Township Police Department reported that officers were dispatched to Pine Hill Avenue at 7:03 p.m. on Halloween night, following the parent’s alarming discovery. Authorities confirmed that needles were found in three separate pieces of candy, with one being discovered by a parent who had taken a bite of a piece they picked up off the ground. Thankfully, the quick reflexes of the parent prevented any injuries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The local police chief, Chris Raubenstine, expressed his concern and disbelief at the situation, stating that this was the first time in his 30-year career that he had encountered such a malicious act. The police are currently investigating whether the needle-laden candy was dropped accidentally or was placed intentionally, with malicious intent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Such incidents, while rare, cast a shadow on what should be a fun and festive time for children and families. Halloween is a beloved tradition, filled with costumes, laughter, and of course, plenty of sweet treats. However, the discovery of sewing needles in candy serves as a stark reminder that there are individuals who seek to harm and create chaos, even during times of celebration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The police have since issued an urgent warning to parents and guardians, urging them to meticulously inspect all candy before allowing their children to consume it. They have also requested the public’s assistance in identifying the individual or individuals responsible for this heinous act, providing a hotline for anyone with information to come forward.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The conservative community, known for its values of family, safety, and community, has rallied together in the face of this threat. Parents are sharing warnings and safety tips on social media, ensuring that their neighbors are aware of the potential danger and know how to protect their children.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the investigation is ongoing, the community’s swift response and unwavering commitment to safety highlight the strength and resilience that define conservative values. In times of crisis, the community comes together, united in their dedication to protecting the innocent and bringing those responsible to justice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As Halloween comes to a close, and the candy wrappers are discarded, the lessons learned from this unnerving incident will remain. The community, empowered by knowledge and strengthened by unity, stands ready to face any threat, ensuring a safe and joyful Halloween for all.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">A discerning parent discovered sewing needles hidden inside their child’s Halloween candy. The incident occurred during the much-anticipated trick-or-treat festivities in Cumberland County, and has since spurred a full-blown police investigation, as well as a community-wide call to action for increased vigilance and caution. The Silver Spring Township Police Department reported that officers were dispatched to Pine Hill Avenue at 7:03 p.m. on Halloween night, following the parent’s alarming discovery. Authorities confirmed that needles were found in three separate pieces of candy, with one being discovered by a parent who had taken a bite of a piece they picked up off the ground. Thankfully, the quick reflexes of the parent prevented any injuries. The local police chief, Chris Raubenstine, expressed his concern and disbelief at the situation, stating that this was the first time in his 30-year career that he had encountered such a malicious act. The police are currently investigating whether the needle-laden candy was dropped accidentally or was placed intentionally, with malicious intent. Such incidents, while rare, cast a shadow on what should be a fun and festive time for children and families. Halloween is a beloved tradition, filled with costumes, laughter, and of course, plenty of sweet treats. However, the discovery of sewing needles in candy serves as a stark reminder that there are individuals who seek to harm and create chaos, even during times of celebration. The police have since issued an urgent warning to parents and guardians, urging them to meticulously inspect all candy before allowing their children to consume it. They have also requested the public’s assistance in identifying the individual or individuals responsible for this heinous act, providing a hotline for anyone with information to come forward. The conservative community, known for its values of family, safety, and community, has rallied together in the face of this threat. Parents are sharing warnings and safety tips on social media, ensuring that their neighbors are aware of the potential danger and know how to protect their children. While the investigation is ongoing, the community’s swift response and unwavering commitment to safety highlight the strength and resilience that define conservative values. In times of crisis, the community comes together, united in their dedication to protecting the innocent and bringing those responsible to justice. As Halloween comes to a close, and the candy wrappers are discarded, the lessons learned from this unnerving incident will remain. The community, empowered by knowledge and strengthened by unity, stands ready to face any threat, ensuring a safe and joyful Halloween for all.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump Fights for His Rightful Place on the 2024 Ballot</title><link href="/politics/2023/11/02/Trump-2024-Ballot-Case/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump Fights for His Rightful Place on the 2024 Ballot" /><published>2023-11-02T08:12:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-11-02T08:12:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/11/02/Trump-2024-Ballot-Case</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/11/02/Trump-2024-Ballot-Case/">&lt;p&gt;In a courtroom in Colorado, the battle for justice and fairness rages on as former President Donald Trump takes a stand against attempts to unjustly remove him from the 2024 presidential ballot. A local state judge, Sarah B. Wallace, has denied Trump’s motion to dismiss the case, but the fight is far from over. The Trump legal team remains unshaken, ready to present a robust defense of the 45th President’s right to run for office again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Six Colorado voters, four of whom identify as Republicans, have brought this case forward, attempting to disqualify Trump based on his alleged involvement in the January 6th events at the U.S. Capitol. They accuse the former president of inciting an insurrection, referencing Section 3 of the 14th Amendment in their argument. However, the facts tell a different story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump’s attorneys have ardently argued that his speech on that fateful day was fully protected under the First Amendment, emphasizing his call for peaceful protest. Former Colorado Secretary of State Scott Gessler, representing Trump, stated, “The failure to do something is the opposite of the word ‘engaged.’ President Trump didn’t engage…He gave a speech in which he asked people to peacefully and patriotically go to the Capitol and protest.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This legal battle in Colorado is not an isolated incident. Similar cases are emerging in Minnesota and Michigan, as the left continues its relentless pursuit to silence Trump and his millions of supporters. But the Trump camp remains resilient, standing strong against these unfounded attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For Trump supporters and conservative Republicans, this case represents yet another attempt by the left to undermine the democratic process and stifle the voice of the American people. Trump’s commitment to fighting this legal battle demonstrates his unwavering dedication to preserving the values that make America great.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the hearings continue, all eyes are on Colorado, where the outcome of this case will set a precedent for future battles. The conservative community stands united, confident in Trump’s ability to overcome this challenge and continue his fight for a better, stronger America.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With a legacy of economic prosperity, national security, and unwavering patriotism, Trump’s place on the 2024 ballot is not just a legal matter—it’s a question of upholding the principles that define our nation. The people have spoken before, and they are ready to do so again, standing by a leader who has proven time and again that he puts America first.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the face of adversity, Trump and his supporters remain optimistic, fueled by a deep love for their country and a steadfast belief in the power of the people. The road ahead may be fraught with challenges, but the fight for justice and fairness continues, as the Trump legal team prepares to make their case and secure Trump’s rightful place on the 2024 ballot.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a courtroom in Colorado, the battle for justice and fairness rages on as former President Donald Trump takes a stand against attempts to unjustly remove him from the 2024 presidential ballot. A local state judge, Sarah B. Wallace, has denied Trump’s motion to dismiss the case, but the fight is far from over. The Trump legal team remains unshaken, ready to present a robust defense of the 45th President’s right to run for office again. Six Colorado voters, four of whom identify as Republicans, have brought this case forward, attempting to disqualify Trump based on his alleged involvement in the January 6th events at the U.S. Capitol. They accuse the former president of inciting an insurrection, referencing Section 3 of the 14th Amendment in their argument. However, the facts tell a different story. Trump’s attorneys have ardently argued that his speech on that fateful day was fully protected under the First Amendment, emphasizing his call for peaceful protest. Former Colorado Secretary of State Scott Gessler, representing Trump, stated, “The failure to do something is the opposite of the word ‘engaged.’ President Trump didn’t engage…He gave a speech in which he asked people to peacefully and patriotically go to the Capitol and protest.” This legal battle in Colorado is not an isolated incident. Similar cases are emerging in Minnesota and Michigan, as the left continues its relentless pursuit to silence Trump and his millions of supporters. But the Trump camp remains resilient, standing strong against these unfounded attacks. For Trump supporters and conservative Republicans, this case represents yet another attempt by the left to undermine the democratic process and stifle the voice of the American people. Trump’s commitment to fighting this legal battle demonstrates his unwavering dedication to preserving the values that make America great. As the hearings continue, all eyes are on Colorado, where the outcome of this case will set a precedent for future battles. The conservative community stands united, confident in Trump’s ability to overcome this challenge and continue his fight for a better, stronger America. With a legacy of economic prosperity, national security, and unwavering patriotism, Trump’s place on the 2024 ballot is not just a legal matter—it’s a question of upholding the principles that define our nation. The people have spoken before, and they are ready to do so again, standing by a leader who has proven time and again that he puts America first. In the face of adversity, Trump and his supporters remain optimistic, fueled by a deep love for their country and a steadfast belief in the power of the people. The road ahead may be fraught with challenges, but the fight for justice and fairness continues, as the Trump legal team prepares to make their case and secure Trump’s rightful place on the 2024 ballot.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Decades-Long Sentence for 75-Year-Old Teacher in Shocking Student Assault Case</title><link href="/news/2023/11/02/Wisconsin-Teacher-Sentencing/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Decades-Long Sentence for 75-Year-Old Teacher in Shocking Student Assault Case" /><published>2023-11-02T07:03:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-11-02T07:03:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/11/02/Wisconsin-Teacher-Sentencing</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/11/02/Wisconsin-Teacher-Sentencing/">&lt;p&gt;A 75-year-old former private school teacher, Anne Nelson-Koch, has been sentenced to a 10-year prison term for sexually assaulting a teenage student during the 2016-17 school year. Prosecutors had initially sought a staggering 100-year sentence, highlighting the gravity of the allegations against Nelson-Koch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nelson-Koch, who was 67 at the time of the crimes, engaged in illicit sexual activities with a 14-year-old boy in the school’s basement, subjecting him to repeated acts of sexual assault. The former teacher faced a plethora of charges, including sexual assault of a child, child enticement with sexual contact, and exposing intimate parts to a minor, resulting in her being found guilty on over a dozen counts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the prosecution presented a compelling case, detailing the severe trauma inflicted upon the young victim, the defense managed to shed light on Nelson-Koch’s character through testimonies from her friends. These character references played a pivotal role in the court’s decision, ultimately leading to a reduced sentence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The implications of this case extend far beyond the courtroom, as it has ignited a broader conversation about the safety of children in educational institutions and the need for stringent measures to prevent such horrific incidents. The Monroe County community has been left reeling, as parents grapple with the reality of sexual predators lurking within trusted institutions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the trial, the victim’s father delivered an emotional statement, imploring the court to protect his son and expressing his anguish over feeling helpless during the ordeal. The father’s words left an indelible mark on those present, underscoring the lasting impact of such heinous acts on victims and their families.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Assistant District Attorney Sarah Skiles, representing Monroe County, expressed her commitment to safeguarding children and ensuring that perpetrators of sexual assault face the consequences of their actions. She highlighted the tireless efforts of Investigator Paul Sloan, who played a crucial role in bringing Nelson-Koch to justice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the dust settles on this harrowing case, the community is left to ponder the necessary steps to prevent such incidents in the future. The 10-year sentence handed down to Nelson-Koch serves as a stark reminder that even in our most trusted institutions, vigilance is paramount to protect the most vulnerable among us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This high-profile sentencing will undoubtedly resonate throughout Wisconsin and beyond, as educators, parents, and law enforcement officials reflect on the lessons learned and the actions needed to ensure the safety and well-being of students everywhere.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">A 75-year-old former private school teacher, Anne Nelson-Koch, has been sentenced to a 10-year prison term for sexually assaulting a teenage student during the 2016-17 school year. Prosecutors had initially sought a staggering 100-year sentence, highlighting the gravity of the allegations against Nelson-Koch. Nelson-Koch, who was 67 at the time of the crimes, engaged in illicit sexual activities with a 14-year-old boy in the school’s basement, subjecting him to repeated acts of sexual assault. The former teacher faced a plethora of charges, including sexual assault of a child, child enticement with sexual contact, and exposing intimate parts to a minor, resulting in her being found guilty on over a dozen counts. While the prosecution presented a compelling case, detailing the severe trauma inflicted upon the young victim, the defense managed to shed light on Nelson-Koch’s character through testimonies from her friends. These character references played a pivotal role in the court’s decision, ultimately leading to a reduced sentence. The implications of this case extend far beyond the courtroom, as it has ignited a broader conversation about the safety of children in educational institutions and the need for stringent measures to prevent such horrific incidents. The Monroe County community has been left reeling, as parents grapple with the reality of sexual predators lurking within trusted institutions. During the trial, the victim’s father delivered an emotional statement, imploring the court to protect his son and expressing his anguish over feeling helpless during the ordeal. The father’s words left an indelible mark on those present, underscoring the lasting impact of such heinous acts on victims and their families. Assistant District Attorney Sarah Skiles, representing Monroe County, expressed her commitment to safeguarding children and ensuring that perpetrators of sexual assault face the consequences of their actions. She highlighted the tireless efforts of Investigator Paul Sloan, who played a crucial role in bringing Nelson-Koch to justice. As the dust settles on this harrowing case, the community is left to ponder the necessary steps to prevent such incidents in the future. The 10-year sentence handed down to Nelson-Koch serves as a stark reminder that even in our most trusted institutions, vigilance is paramount to protect the most vulnerable among us. This high-profile sentencing will undoubtedly resonate throughout Wisconsin and beyond, as educators, parents, and law enforcement officials reflect on the lessons learned and the actions needed to ensure the safety and well-being of students everywhere.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Capital Chaos: Surge in Youth Violence Highlights DC’s Failed Crime Policies</title><link href="/news/2023/11/02/DC-Carjacking-Crisis/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Capital Chaos: Surge in Youth Violence Highlights DC’s Failed Crime Policies" /><published>2023-11-02T06:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-11-02T06:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/11/02/DC-Carjacking-Crisis</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/11/02/DC-Carjacking-Crisis/">&lt;p&gt;In yet another glaring example of Washington D.C.’s spiraling crime problem, a 12-year-old has been charged following a botched carjacking that left a 13-year-old dead. This tragic incident is a stark reminder of the surging violence plaguing our nation’s capital, highlighting the dire need for immediate action to protect law-abiding citizens and hold criminals accountable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The attempted carjacking occurred around 10 p.m. Saturday in the 600 block of D Street, NW. A 12-year-old, together with 13-year-old Vernard Toney, Jr., menacingly approached an off-duty federal security officer, demanding he exit his vehicle while intimating possession of a firearm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Faced with what appeared to be a life-threatening situation, the officer, acting in self-defense, discharged his weapon, fatally wounding Toney. The 12-year-old accomplice fled the scene, leaving behind a scenario that is becoming all too common in D.C.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Police were able to track down and arrest the 12-year-old thanks to surveillance footage, and he now awaits his day in court. But this incident is just the tip of the iceberg in a city that has seen a disturbing increase in violent crime, particularly among minors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Critics are pointing fingers at the city’s lenient crime policies, which have created an environment where lawlessness prevails and criminals operate with impunity. The soft-on-crime approach, championed by liberal politicians and activists, has utterly failed the citizens of Washington D.C., leaving them to bear the brunt of escalating violence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The tragic death of a young boy and the criminal involvement of another are clear indicators that the current system is not working. It is a call to action for leaders at all levels of government to step up, reject failed policies, and implement stringent measures to curb crime and ensure public safety.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Washington D.C. residents deserve to live in a city free from the fear of violence. They deserve leaders who prioritize their safety, support law enforcement, and are committed to restoring law and order. The time for talk is over; it’s time for action. We cannot afford to lose another life to the senseless violence that has taken hold of our capital.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our nation’s capital is in crisis, and it’s up to us to demand change, hold our leaders accountable, and work together to reclaim our city from the clutches of crime.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In yet another glaring example of Washington D.C.’s spiraling crime problem, a 12-year-old has been charged following a botched carjacking that left a 13-year-old dead. This tragic incident is a stark reminder of the surging violence plaguing our nation’s capital, highlighting the dire need for immediate action to protect law-abiding citizens and hold criminals accountable. The attempted carjacking occurred around 10 p.m. Saturday in the 600 block of D Street, NW. A 12-year-old, together with 13-year-old Vernard Toney, Jr., menacingly approached an off-duty federal security officer, demanding he exit his vehicle while intimating possession of a firearm. Faced with what appeared to be a life-threatening situation, the officer, acting in self-defense, discharged his weapon, fatally wounding Toney. The 12-year-old accomplice fled the scene, leaving behind a scenario that is becoming all too common in D.C. Police were able to track down and arrest the 12-year-old thanks to surveillance footage, and he now awaits his day in court. But this incident is just the tip of the iceberg in a city that has seen a disturbing increase in violent crime, particularly among minors. Critics are pointing fingers at the city’s lenient crime policies, which have created an environment where lawlessness prevails and criminals operate with impunity. The soft-on-crime approach, championed by liberal politicians and activists, has utterly failed the citizens of Washington D.C., leaving them to bear the brunt of escalating violence. The tragic death of a young boy and the criminal involvement of another are clear indicators that the current system is not working. It is a call to action for leaders at all levels of government to step up, reject failed policies, and implement stringent measures to curb crime and ensure public safety. Washington D.C. residents deserve to live in a city free from the fear of violence. They deserve leaders who prioritize their safety, support law enforcement, and are committed to restoring law and order. The time for talk is over; it’s time for action. We cannot afford to lose another life to the senseless violence that has taken hold of our capital. Our nation’s capital is in crisis, and it’s up to us to demand change, hold our leaders accountable, and work together to reclaim our city from the clutches of crime.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">BLM Organizer Sentenced: A Tale of Deceit and Misused Funds</title><link href="/news/2023/11/01/Activist-Fraud-Exposed/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="BLM Organizer Sentenced: A Tale of Deceit and Misused Funds" /><published>2023-11-01T18:12:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-11-01T18:12:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/11/01/Activist-Fraud-Exposed</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/11/01/Activist-Fraud-Exposed/">&lt;p&gt;Xahra Saleem, a leading figure in the Black Lives Matter (BLM) movement and the 2020 Bristol protests, has been justly sentenced to two and a half years in prison for her fraudulent misappropriation of charity funds. Saleem, who played a pivotal role in orchestrating the protest that led to the dismantling of Sir Edward Colston’s statue, faced the court and was convicted of stealing over £32,000.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saleem, also known under the alias Yvonne Maina and a founder of the All Black Lives Bristol group, deceitfully established fundraising pages, claiming to support a local children’s group, Changing Your Mindset. The supposed intention was to finance a trip to Africa for disadvantaged children. However, she exploited the funds for her own indulgence, splurging on an array of personal items, including an iPhone, a computer, fast food, beauty products, and an exorbitant £5,800 on Uber rides within an 11-month timeframe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The court proceedings laid bare her egregious breach of trust, with the judge emphasizing the severe damage inflicted upon the victims. Saleem attempted to justify her refusal to release the donations with a series of unconvincing excuses, eventually admitting her guilt and expressing remorse for her actions. Nonetheless, her apologies and admission of guilt came too late for the charity, which was forced to shut down as a result of her selfish actions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saleem’s arrest by Avon and Somerset Police in July 2021 marked a pivotal moment, bringing her deceitful practices to an end. However, the fallout from her actions had already caused irreversible damage to the community. The charity’s closure left a void, and tragically, a young individual connected to Saleem and supported by the charity lost his life to violence. Representatives from Changing Your Mindset believe this loss could have been avoided had the charity remained operational.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saleem’s sentencing brings to light the need for greater accountability and transparency within activist movements and charitable organizations. Her actions serve as a stark reminder that not all those who claim to champion social justice are acting in good faith. It underscores the importance of vigilance and due diligence to ensure that funds intended for community betterment are used appropriately. The community, now left to pick up the pieces, must remain vigilant and demand accountability to prevent such egregious breaches of trust in the future.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Xahra Saleem, a leading figure in the Black Lives Matter (BLM) movement and the 2020 Bristol protests, has been justly sentenced to two and a half years in prison for her fraudulent misappropriation of charity funds. Saleem, who played a pivotal role in orchestrating the protest that led to the dismantling of Sir Edward Colston’s statue, faced the court and was convicted of stealing over £32,000. Saleem, also known under the alias Yvonne Maina and a founder of the All Black Lives Bristol group, deceitfully established fundraising pages, claiming to support a local children’s group, Changing Your Mindset. The supposed intention was to finance a trip to Africa for disadvantaged children. However, she exploited the funds for her own indulgence, splurging on an array of personal items, including an iPhone, a computer, fast food, beauty products, and an exorbitant £5,800 on Uber rides within an 11-month timeframe. The court proceedings laid bare her egregious breach of trust, with the judge emphasizing the severe damage inflicted upon the victims. Saleem attempted to justify her refusal to release the donations with a series of unconvincing excuses, eventually admitting her guilt and expressing remorse for her actions. Nonetheless, her apologies and admission of guilt came too late for the charity, which was forced to shut down as a result of her selfish actions. Saleem’s arrest by Avon and Somerset Police in July 2021 marked a pivotal moment, bringing her deceitful practices to an end. However, the fallout from her actions had already caused irreversible damage to the community. The charity’s closure left a void, and tragically, a young individual connected to Saleem and supported by the charity lost his life to violence. Representatives from Changing Your Mindset believe this loss could have been avoided had the charity remained operational. Saleem’s sentencing brings to light the need for greater accountability and transparency within activist movements and charitable organizations. Her actions serve as a stark reminder that not all those who claim to champion social justice are acting in good faith. It underscores the importance of vigilance and due diligence to ensure that funds intended for community betterment are used appropriately. The community, now left to pick up the pieces, must remain vigilant and demand accountability to prevent such egregious breaches of trust in the future.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Tragedy Strikes Kentucky: A Call for Unity and Support in the Wake of Coal Plant Collapse</title><link href="/news/2023/11/01/Kentucky-Coal-Plant-Collapse/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tragedy Strikes Kentucky: A Call for Unity and Support in the Wake of Coal Plant Collapse" /><published>2023-11-01T16:57:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-11-01T16:57:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/11/01/Kentucky-Coal-Plant-Collapse</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/11/01/Kentucky-Coal-Plant-Collapse/">&lt;p&gt;Kentucky has been thrust into the national spotlight following the catastrophic collapse of a coal preparation plant in Martin County, resulting in a tragic loss of life and leaving another worker trapped amidst the rubble. Governor Andy Beshear has declared a state of emergency, mobilizing state resources and shining a light on the gravity of the situation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The collapse, which occurred late Tuesday, has sent shockwaves throughout the community and the state at large. Governor Beshear, taking to social media, urged the people of Kentucky to unite in prayer and support for the victims, their families, and the brave first responders working tirelessly at the scene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“One worker has lost their life, and another remains trapped. We are doing everything we can, and I urge you all to keep them in your thoughts and prayers,” Governor Beshear stated solemnly. This tragedy hits close to home for many in Kentucky, a state with deep roots in the coal industry, and it serves as a stark reminder of the inherent dangers faced by those working in this critical sector of our economy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Martin County Sheriff’s Office and multiple other agencies are on-site, navigating the challenging and dangerous conditions in a race against time to rescue the trapped worker. “This is a complex and delicate operation. We are pouring all of our resources into the rescue efforts, but we need the community’s support and prayers more than ever,” shared Martin County Sheriff John Kirk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The coal preparation plant, which had been out of commission for several years, was in the process of being dismantled when the unthinkable happened. “These workers were doing their job, preparing the structure for demolition when the building collapsed. It’s a tragic accident, and our hearts go out to all those affected,” explained Sheriff Kirk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Governor Beshear’s swift response, declaring a state of emergency, ensures that all necessary resources are made available to aid in the rescue efforts. Kentucky Attorney General Daniel Cameron also took to social media, calling for prayers and support for the trapped workers and the first responders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The tragedy in Martin County serves as a somber reminder of the risks associated with the coal industry, and it highlights the need for continued attention to worker safety and structural integrity. As Kentucky grapples with this disaster, the unity and strength of its people will be paramount.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Governor Beshear’s message is clear: “In these trying times, we must come together as a community, as a state, and support one another. We are Kentucky strong, and we will get through this together.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the rescue operations continue, the eyes of the nation are on Kentucky, hoping and praying for a miracle amidst the devastation. The people of Kentucky, resilient and united, stand ready to support the victims, their families, and the brave men and women on the front lines of this disaster.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Kentucky has been thrust into the national spotlight following the catastrophic collapse of a coal preparation plant in Martin County, resulting in a tragic loss of life and leaving another worker trapped amidst the rubble. Governor Andy Beshear has declared a state of emergency, mobilizing state resources and shining a light on the gravity of the situation. The collapse, which occurred late Tuesday, has sent shockwaves throughout the community and the state at large. Governor Beshear, taking to social media, urged the people of Kentucky to unite in prayer and support for the victims, their families, and the brave first responders working tirelessly at the scene. “One worker has lost their life, and another remains trapped. We are doing everything we can, and I urge you all to keep them in your thoughts and prayers,” Governor Beshear stated solemnly. This tragedy hits close to home for many in Kentucky, a state with deep roots in the coal industry, and it serves as a stark reminder of the inherent dangers faced by those working in this critical sector of our economy. The Martin County Sheriff’s Office and multiple other agencies are on-site, navigating the challenging and dangerous conditions in a race against time to rescue the trapped worker. “This is a complex and delicate operation. We are pouring all of our resources into the rescue efforts, but we need the community’s support and prayers more than ever,” shared Martin County Sheriff John Kirk. The coal preparation plant, which had been out of commission for several years, was in the process of being dismantled when the unthinkable happened. “These workers were doing their job, preparing the structure for demolition when the building collapsed. It’s a tragic accident, and our hearts go out to all those affected,” explained Sheriff Kirk. Governor Beshear’s swift response, declaring a state of emergency, ensures that all necessary resources are made available to aid in the rescue efforts. Kentucky Attorney General Daniel Cameron also took to social media, calling for prayers and support for the trapped workers and the first responders. The tragedy in Martin County serves as a somber reminder of the risks associated with the coal industry, and it highlights the need for continued attention to worker safety and structural integrity. As Kentucky grapples with this disaster, the unity and strength of its people will be paramount. Governor Beshear’s message is clear: “In these trying times, we must come together as a community, as a state, and support one another. We are Kentucky strong, and we will get through this together.” As the rescue operations continue, the eyes of the nation are on Kentucky, hoping and praying for a miracle amidst the devastation. The people of Kentucky, resilient and united, stand ready to support the victims, their families, and the brave men and women on the front lines of this disaster.</summary></entry></feed>