<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-09-14T09:19:49-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/09/14/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-09-14T09:19:49-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-14T09:19:49-04:00</updated><id>/2023/09/14/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/14/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">The Great Escape - Fugitive Killer Cavalcante’s Daring Run Ends in Pennsylvania</title><link href="/news/2023/09/14/Escapee-Recapture/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Great Escape - Fugitive Killer Cavalcante’s Daring Run Ends in Pennsylvania" /><published>2023-09-14T09:08:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-14T09:08:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/14/Escapee-Recapture</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/14/Escapee-Recapture/">&lt;p&gt;Pennsylvania’s Chester County, located approximately 30 miles from Philadelphia, was the epicenter of a two-week-long suspenseful manhunt. The fugitive in question? Danelo Cavalcante, a 34-year-old convicted murderer who managed a Hollywood-esque escape from the local prison.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On August 31st, the audacious escape of Cavalcante was caught on camera, showing him crab-walking up a wall to freedom from the Chester County Prison. He was awaiting a transfer to state prison when he made his daring getaway. This set off a massive manhunt, with authorities using every tool at their disposal - mounted units, SWAT teams, and state and local police - scouring the farmlands and woodlands of the county.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cavalcante, originally from Brazil, was no stranger to crime. Convicted for the 2021 murder of his ex-girlfriend, Deborah Brandao, he is also a prime suspect in another homicide from 2017 back in Brazil. His escape had residents on high alert as reports of home break-ins began to surface. Cavalcante stole supplies, altered his appearance, and in one harrowing instance, exchanged gunfire with a homeowner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Images captured six hours post his arrest show a disheveled Cavalcante, barefoot in a hospital robe, displaying the aftermath of his capture. A K-9 bite wound, courtesy of his attempt to escape the arresting officers, had required medical treatment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lt. Col. George Bivens of the Pennsylvania State Police described the arrest, emphasizing the element of surprise. “They were able to move in very quietly,” he reported. Cavalcante, seemingly unaware, was cornered with stolen goods and a rifle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The community can now breathe a sigh of relief. This man, who once crawled his way to freedom and evoked widespread panic, is now back behind bars, awaiting a life sentence for his crimes.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Pennsylvania’s Chester County, located approximately 30 miles from Philadelphia, was the epicenter of a two-week-long suspenseful manhunt. The fugitive in question? Danelo Cavalcante, a 34-year-old convicted murderer who managed a Hollywood-esque escape from the local prison. On August 31st, the audacious escape of Cavalcante was caught on camera, showing him crab-walking up a wall to freedom from the Chester County Prison. He was awaiting a transfer to state prison when he made his daring getaway. This set off a massive manhunt, with authorities using every tool at their disposal - mounted units, SWAT teams, and state and local police - scouring the farmlands and woodlands of the county. Cavalcante, originally from Brazil, was no stranger to crime. Convicted for the 2021 murder of his ex-girlfriend, Deborah Brandao, he is also a prime suspect in another homicide from 2017 back in Brazil. His escape had residents on high alert as reports of home break-ins began to surface. Cavalcante stole supplies, altered his appearance, and in one harrowing instance, exchanged gunfire with a homeowner. Images captured six hours post his arrest show a disheveled Cavalcante, barefoot in a hospital robe, displaying the aftermath of his capture. A K-9 bite wound, courtesy of his attempt to escape the arresting officers, had required medical treatment. Lt. Col. George Bivens of the Pennsylvania State Police described the arrest, emphasizing the element of surprise. “They were able to move in very quietly,” he reported. Cavalcante, seemingly unaware, was cornered with stolen goods and a rifle. The community can now breathe a sigh of relief. This man, who once crawled his way to freedom and evoked widespread panic, is now back behind bars, awaiting a life sentence for his crimes.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump vs. Soros - Epic Showdown Looms Ahead of 2024 Elections</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/14/Trump-Soros-Battle/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump vs. Soros - Epic Showdown Looms Ahead of 2024 Elections" /><published>2023-09-14T08:10:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-14T08:10:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/14/Trump-Soros-Battle</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/14/Trump-Soros-Battle/">&lt;p&gt;Former President Donald Trump, in a fervent call to his supporters, declared that the billionaire activist George Soros and his family are ardently mobilizing resources to derail his potential 2024 bid for the White House. Trump’s sentiments underscore the mounting tension between the Trump and Soros camps, both significant powerhouses in American politics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Citing a headline from the Post Millenium, Trump referenced: “George Soros’ son shifts priorities, resources to focus on defeating MAGA in 2024,” highlighting Soros’s alleged intensified efforts to stifle the “MAGA” movement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The Soros Dynasty is laser-focused on a single mission for 2024: pouring in whatever it takes to ensure the people are deprived of their voice in their homeland,” Trump’s email to his supporters elucidated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The backdrop to Trump’s assertions traces back to a recent op-ed by Alex Soros, son of George Soros and chairman of the Open Society Foundations (OSF). OSF is globally recognized for its stance against Trump’s ‘America First’ agenda during his presidency. In his piece, Alex expressed concern over the potential consequences of a “MAGA-style” Republican triumph in the upcoming U.S. presidential elections, particularly emphasizing its ramifications for the European Union (EU).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Explaining his organization’s strategic pivot, Alex stated, “Given the looming challenges we currently face and the imminent ones awaiting us, we are re-evaluating our European priorities.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adding to the complexity, Trump accentuated Soros’s massive political financial outlays. “Soros has already splurged $50 million with the aim to seize the White House in 2024. Furthermore, an affiliated Soros Super PAC has dished out $75 million. He reigns as the UNDISPUTED BIGGEST DONOR in American politics,” Trump pointed out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Continuing his appeal, Trump stressed, “His son is gearing up to infuse millions more, all in a bid to obstruct our glorious movement. But united, we hold the power to financially outpace Soros and prevent his dynasty from purchasing the White House in 2024.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rounding off his message, Trump reflected on his presidential tenure, crediting himself with destabilizing the established order. He insinuated that this upheaval cemented his position as a thorn in the side of deep-rooted special interests, branding his movement as their “supreme adversary.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the 2024 election edges closer, the mounting tension between these titans promises to keep the political arena bustling with intrigue and fervor.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Former President Donald Trump, in a fervent call to his supporters, declared that the billionaire activist George Soros and his family are ardently mobilizing resources to derail his potential 2024 bid for the White House. Trump’s sentiments underscore the mounting tension between the Trump and Soros camps, both significant powerhouses in American politics. Citing a headline from the Post Millenium, Trump referenced: “George Soros’ son shifts priorities, resources to focus on defeating MAGA in 2024,” highlighting Soros’s alleged intensified efforts to stifle the “MAGA” movement. “The Soros Dynasty is laser-focused on a single mission for 2024: pouring in whatever it takes to ensure the people are deprived of their voice in their homeland,” Trump’s email to his supporters elucidated. The backdrop to Trump’s assertions traces back to a recent op-ed by Alex Soros, son of George Soros and chairman of the Open Society Foundations (OSF). OSF is globally recognized for its stance against Trump’s ‘America First’ agenda during his presidency. In his piece, Alex expressed concern over the potential consequences of a “MAGA-style” Republican triumph in the upcoming U.S. presidential elections, particularly emphasizing its ramifications for the European Union (EU). Explaining his organization’s strategic pivot, Alex stated, “Given the looming challenges we currently face and the imminent ones awaiting us, we are re-evaluating our European priorities.” Adding to the complexity, Trump accentuated Soros’s massive political financial outlays. “Soros has already splurged $50 million with the aim to seize the White House in 2024. Furthermore, an affiliated Soros Super PAC has dished out $75 million. He reigns as the UNDISPUTED BIGGEST DONOR in American politics,” Trump pointed out. Continuing his appeal, Trump stressed, “His son is gearing up to infuse millions more, all in a bid to obstruct our glorious movement. But united, we hold the power to financially outpace Soros and prevent his dynasty from purchasing the White House in 2024.” Rounding off his message, Trump reflected on his presidential tenure, crediting himself with destabilizing the established order. He insinuated that this upheaval cemented his position as a thorn in the side of deep-rooted special interests, branding his movement as their “supreme adversary.” As the 2024 election edges closer, the mounting tension between these titans promises to keep the political arena bustling with intrigue and fervor.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">New Mexico’s Concealed Carry Clash - Gun Owners Triumph Over Ban</title><link href="/news/2023/09/14/NM-Gun-Rights-Battle/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="New Mexico’s Concealed Carry Clash - Gun Owners Triumph Over Ban" /><published>2023-09-14T07:03:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-14T07:03:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/14/NM-Gun-Rights-Battle</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/14/NM-Gun-Rights-Battle/">&lt;p&gt;Amidst the ongoing national debate on gun rights, New Mexico finds itself at the center of a legal skirmish. On Wednesday, the Gun Owners of America (GOA) scored a significant legal victory, obtaining a temporary restraining order against New Mexico Governor Michelle Lujan Grisham’s recent ban on concealed carry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The action was swift. Only two days after the announcement of the ban, GOA moved forward with a lawsuit in a U.S. District Court, challenging the Governor’s order. Erich Pratt, GOA’s executive vice president, conveyed the organization’s stance vehemently, “Gun Owners of America has filed a federal lawsuit challenging Governor Michelle Lujan Grisham’s gross and egregious violation of the U.S. Constitution.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Governor Grisham’s assertion, suggesting that there are ‘exceptions to the Second Amendment,’ has provoked outrage and concern among gun rights advocates. Pratt argued that this notion not only misses the mark but also “blows open a huge hole in the Bill of Rights.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the dust begins to settle on this initial confrontation, gun rights supporters are bolstered by the fact that, for the moment, the restraining order has put a pin in Grisham’s ban. However, it remains an oral order, indicating that a more detailed legal discourse is on the horizon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This case underscores the ongoing tension between individual rights and governmental regulations, a friction that is particularly pronounced when it comes to the Second Amendment. With New Mexicans’ rights hanging in the balance, all eyes are on how this legal showdown will evolve, potentially setting a precedent for future disputes in this arena.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Amidst the ongoing national debate on gun rights, New Mexico finds itself at the center of a legal skirmish. On Wednesday, the Gun Owners of America (GOA) scored a significant legal victory, obtaining a temporary restraining order against New Mexico Governor Michelle Lujan Grisham’s recent ban on concealed carry. The action was swift. Only two days after the announcement of the ban, GOA moved forward with a lawsuit in a U.S. District Court, challenging the Governor’s order. Erich Pratt, GOA’s executive vice president, conveyed the organization’s stance vehemently, “Gun Owners of America has filed a federal lawsuit challenging Governor Michelle Lujan Grisham’s gross and egregious violation of the U.S. Constitution.” Governor Grisham’s assertion, suggesting that there are ‘exceptions to the Second Amendment,’ has provoked outrage and concern among gun rights advocates. Pratt argued that this notion not only misses the mark but also “blows open a huge hole in the Bill of Rights.” As the dust begins to settle on this initial confrontation, gun rights supporters are bolstered by the fact that, for the moment, the restraining order has put a pin in Grisham’s ban. However, it remains an oral order, indicating that a more detailed legal discourse is on the horizon. This case underscores the ongoing tension between individual rights and governmental regulations, a friction that is particularly pronounced when it comes to the Second Amendment. With New Mexicans’ rights hanging in the balance, all eyes are on how this legal showdown will evolve, potentially setting a precedent for future disputes in this arena.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Deion Sanders Denies NFL Rumors - College’s Rising Mentor?</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/14/Deion-Sanders-Coaching-Decision/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Deion Sanders Denies NFL Rumors - College’s Rising Mentor?" /><published>2023-09-14T06:12:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-14T06:12:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/14/Deion-Sanders-Coaching-Decision</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/14/Deion-Sanders-Coaching-Decision/">&lt;p&gt;Launching the Colorado Buffaloes to a promising 2-0 start this season, Deion Sanders appears to have bigger fish to fry than the glitz and glamour of the NFL.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After his transition from Jackson State, an FCS school, to Colorado in December, Sanders swiftly became a household name in the coaching realm. His leadership has ushered the Buffaloes to national prominence, with both “Big Noon Kickoff” and “College Gameday” gearing up to cover their imminent clash against Colorado State.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2023/09/720/405/GettyImages-colorado-1-copy.jpg?ve=1&amp;amp;tl=1&quot; alt=&quot;Deion Sanders during warm ups&quot; /&gt;(RJ Sangosti/MediaNews Group/The Denver Post via Getty Images)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet, with growing acclaim come rumors. Many speculated if Sanders would soon take his talent to the NFL sidelines. Joel Klatt, in a recent segment, laid such speculations to rest. “He’s not going to the NFL,” Klatt affirmed. Sharing insights from a conversation with Sanders, Klatt conveyed, “Deion doesn’t want to coach in the NFL. He sees his role as more of a mentor.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sanders’ passion lies in shaping young athletes during the pivotal years of college. Klatt highlighted Sanders’ perspective, stating he “believes this is his ministry. To be present for these college kids.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sanders doesn’t just impress on the coaching front. His adeptness as a recruiter is evident. Under the moniker “Coach Prime”, Sanders succeeded in bringing Travis Hunter, 2022’s top recruit, from Jackson State to Colorado. And whispers have it that Bryce Underwood, pegged as the premier quarterback recruit for 2025, has Colorado on his radar, thanks to reports.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2023/09/720/405/deion-sanders-after-win.jpg?ve=1&amp;amp;tl=1&quot; alt=&quot;Deion Sanders runs on the field&quot; /&gt;(Tim Heitman/USA Today Sports)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Addressing his recruitment philosophy, Sanders opined, “Obviously, when you have a coach that played defensive back, you attract skill positions.” He went on to hint at the barrage of inquiries they receive from budding players keen on joining the Colorado ranks, showcasing the burgeoning interest and trust in his leadership.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the foreseeable future, it’s clear: Sanders is on a mission to redefine college football, leaving the NFL’s allure in the rearview.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Launching the Colorado Buffaloes to a promising 2-0 start this season, Deion Sanders appears to have bigger fish to fry than the glitz and glamour of the NFL. After his transition from Jackson State, an FCS school, to Colorado in December, Sanders swiftly became a household name in the coaching realm. His leadership has ushered the Buffaloes to national prominence, with both “Big Noon Kickoff” and “College Gameday” gearing up to cover their imminent clash against Colorado State. (RJ Sangosti/MediaNews Group/The Denver Post via Getty Images) Yet, with growing acclaim come rumors. Many speculated if Sanders would soon take his talent to the NFL sidelines. Joel Klatt, in a recent segment, laid such speculations to rest. “He’s not going to the NFL,” Klatt affirmed. Sharing insights from a conversation with Sanders, Klatt conveyed, “Deion doesn’t want to coach in the NFL. He sees his role as more of a mentor.” Sanders’ passion lies in shaping young athletes during the pivotal years of college. Klatt highlighted Sanders’ perspective, stating he “believes this is his ministry. To be present for these college kids.” Sanders doesn’t just impress on the coaching front. His adeptness as a recruiter is evident. Under the moniker “Coach Prime”, Sanders succeeded in bringing Travis Hunter, 2022’s top recruit, from Jackson State to Colorado. And whispers have it that Bryce Underwood, pegged as the premier quarterback recruit for 2025, has Colorado on his radar, thanks to reports. (Tim Heitman/USA Today Sports) Addressing his recruitment philosophy, Sanders opined, “Obviously, when you have a coach that played defensive back, you attract skill positions.” He went on to hint at the barrage of inquiries they receive from budding players keen on joining the Colorado ranks, showcasing the burgeoning interest and trust in his leadership. For the foreseeable future, it’s clear: Sanders is on a mission to redefine college football, leaving the NFL’s allure in the rearview.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Virginia Candidate’s Web Antics - A Brazen Display of Poor Judgment?</title><link href="/news/2023/09/13/Virginia-Candidate-Scandal/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Virginia Candidate’s Web Antics - A Brazen Display of Poor Judgment?" /><published>2023-09-13T18:43:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-13T18:43:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/13/Virginia-Candidate-Scandal</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/13/Virginia-Candidate-Scandal/">&lt;p&gt;In an era where the line between private and public life is increasingly blurred, revelations regarding the personal choices of individuals seeking public office have emerged once more. Susanna Gibson, a Democratic contender for a pivotal seat in the Virginia House of Delegates, has recently come under scrutiny for her online activities, a series of questionable decisions that cast doubt on her fitness for public service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though Gibson is involved in a tight race for her seat, her online behavior seems to have overshadowed her political aspirations. As reported by reputable sources, including the far-left Associated Press, Gibson engaged in explicit acts alongside her husband, broadcasted live for a global audience. What’s even more startling is her monetization approach – charging viewers for specific requests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One might argue that what someone does in their personal life is their business alone, but Gibson’s actions were far from private. Her online handle, “HotWifeExperience,” reveals a calculated choice to parade these exploits on Chaturbate, a platform that merges the worlds of chat and adult entertainment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gibson’s attempts to rationalize her actions, labeling them as “fundraising” endeavors for her campaign, only magnify the recklessness of her decisions. She went so far as to claim the videos going public as some form of “sex crime.” However, by definition, revenge porn entails the dissemination of private photos or videos out of malice. Gibson’s content was available on a public platform, making it crystal clear that she intended for these videos to be consumed by the masses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The implications of this revelation go beyond just personal indiscretion. It calls into question Gibson’s decision-making capabilities, her vulnerability to potential blackmail, and the ethical boundaries she’s willing to cross.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though her opponent, Republican David Owen, has opted for a compassionate stance, focusing solely on his campaign, the underlying concern remains. Would Gibson’s unchecked actions leave her susceptible to external influence?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In an era that demands transparency and accountability from public officials, Gibson’s actions serve as a reminder that character, integrity, and judgment remain paramount. Voters, now more than ever, need representatives who not only champion their causes but also reflect the values and principles they hold dear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It remains to be seen how this scandal will affect the upcoming elections, but one thing is certain: it’s a stark reminder of the weight of choices and the magnifying lens of public office.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In an era where the line between private and public life is increasingly blurred, revelations regarding the personal choices of individuals seeking public office have emerged once more. Susanna Gibson, a Democratic contender for a pivotal seat in the Virginia House of Delegates, has recently come under scrutiny for her online activities, a series of questionable decisions that cast doubt on her fitness for public service. Though Gibson is involved in a tight race for her seat, her online behavior seems to have overshadowed her political aspirations. As reported by reputable sources, including the far-left Associated Press, Gibson engaged in explicit acts alongside her husband, broadcasted live for a global audience. What’s even more startling is her monetization approach – charging viewers for specific requests. One might argue that what someone does in their personal life is their business alone, but Gibson’s actions were far from private. Her online handle, “HotWifeExperience,” reveals a calculated choice to parade these exploits on Chaturbate, a platform that merges the worlds of chat and adult entertainment. Gibson’s attempts to rationalize her actions, labeling them as “fundraising” endeavors for her campaign, only magnify the recklessness of her decisions. She went so far as to claim the videos going public as some form of “sex crime.” However, by definition, revenge porn entails the dissemination of private photos or videos out of malice. Gibson’s content was available on a public platform, making it crystal clear that she intended for these videos to be consumed by the masses. The implications of this revelation go beyond just personal indiscretion. It calls into question Gibson’s decision-making capabilities, her vulnerability to potential blackmail, and the ethical boundaries she’s willing to cross. Though her opponent, Republican David Owen, has opted for a compassionate stance, focusing solely on his campaign, the underlying concern remains. Would Gibson’s unchecked actions leave her susceptible to external influence? In an era that demands transparency and accountability from public officials, Gibson’s actions serve as a reminder that character, integrity, and judgment remain paramount. Voters, now more than ever, need representatives who not only champion their causes but also reflect the values and principles they hold dear. It remains to be seen how this scandal will affect the upcoming elections, but one thing is certain: it’s a stark reminder of the weight of choices and the magnifying lens of public office.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hunter Biden’s Attorneys Under Fire - Accusations of Intimidating IRS Whistleblowers Emerge</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/13/Biden-Attorneys-Accused/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hunter Biden’s Attorneys Under Fire - Accusations of Intimidating IRS Whistleblowers Emerge" /><published>2023-09-13T17:42:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-13T17:42:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/13/Biden-Attorneys-Accused</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/13/Biden-Attorneys-Accused/">&lt;p&gt;In a rapidly escalating political development, House Republicans have addressed a strongly-worded letter to Attorney General Merrick Garland. This letter, penned by prominent Republican figures, alleges that Hunter Biden’s legal team actively sought to “intimidate and harass” two key whistleblowers from the Internal Revenue Service (IRS) during the ongoing tax investigation into the President’s son.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reps. Jim Jordan (R-OH), Jason Smith (R-MO), and James Comer (R-KY) named the IRS whistleblowers as Gary Shapley and Joseph Ziegler. These individuals recently came forward, suggesting that political machinations interfered with prosecutorial decisions spanning the extensive federal examination of Hunter Biden.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Notably, the letter levels severe accusations at Biden’s attorneys, asserting they “slandered” Shapley and Ziegler, painting them as “disgruntled”. Furthermore, it contends that Biden’s legal team pressured the Department of Justice to seek prosecution against these whistleblowers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Federal law safeguards whistleblowers from undue retaliation. The overt efforts to coerce these whistleblowers spark grave concerns about possible obstructions in our Committees’ inquiry,” the GOP leaders penned in the letter. They subsequently requested details on any endeavors by Hunter Biden’s lawyers to coax the Department into taking punitive action against the mentioned IRS whistleblowers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a revealing highlight, the letter references a New York Times report. According to this article, Biden’s legal team argued with the Justice Department that the whistleblowers “violated the law by sharing investigation details with Congress and should consequently face legal proceedings.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the clock ticking, the Republicans have given the DOJ a deadline until September 26, 5 p.m., to present any correspondences from Hunter Biden’s attorneys that “call for the investigation or prosecution” of the whistleblowers. Additionally, any documented communication between Biden’s lawyers and the DOJ about potential criminal investigations against Shapley or Ziegler is also sought.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the horizon, Attorney General Garland is slated to appear before the House Judiciary Committee on September 20 for a routine oversight hearing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This news coincides with the expectation that House Speaker Kevin McCarthy (R-CA) will soon endorse an impeachment inquiry into President Biden, focusing on allegations tied to his son’s controversial business associations.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a rapidly escalating political development, House Republicans have addressed a strongly-worded letter to Attorney General Merrick Garland. This letter, penned by prominent Republican figures, alleges that Hunter Biden’s legal team actively sought to “intimidate and harass” two key whistleblowers from the Internal Revenue Service (IRS) during the ongoing tax investigation into the President’s son. Reps. Jim Jordan (R-OH), Jason Smith (R-MO), and James Comer (R-KY) named the IRS whistleblowers as Gary Shapley and Joseph Ziegler. These individuals recently came forward, suggesting that political machinations interfered with prosecutorial decisions spanning the extensive federal examination of Hunter Biden. Notably, the letter levels severe accusations at Biden’s attorneys, asserting they “slandered” Shapley and Ziegler, painting them as “disgruntled”. Furthermore, it contends that Biden’s legal team pressured the Department of Justice to seek prosecution against these whistleblowers. “Federal law safeguards whistleblowers from undue retaliation. The overt efforts to coerce these whistleblowers spark grave concerns about possible obstructions in our Committees’ inquiry,” the GOP leaders penned in the letter. They subsequently requested details on any endeavors by Hunter Biden’s lawyers to coax the Department into taking punitive action against the mentioned IRS whistleblowers. In a revealing highlight, the letter references a New York Times report. According to this article, Biden’s legal team argued with the Justice Department that the whistleblowers “violated the law by sharing investigation details with Congress and should consequently face legal proceedings.” With the clock ticking, the Republicans have given the DOJ a deadline until September 26, 5 p.m., to present any correspondences from Hunter Biden’s attorneys that “call for the investigation or prosecution” of the whistleblowers. Additionally, any documented communication between Biden’s lawyers and the DOJ about potential criminal investigations against Shapley or Ziegler is also sought. On the horizon, Attorney General Garland is slated to appear before the House Judiciary Committee on September 20 for a routine oversight hearing. This news coincides with the expectation that House Speaker Kevin McCarthy (R-CA) will soon endorse an impeachment inquiry into President Biden, focusing on allegations tied to his son’s controversial business associations.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Major Blow to Gulf Cartel - Top Enforcer Arrested near Texas Border</title><link href="/news/2023/09/13/Gulf-Cartel-Enforcer/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Major Blow to Gulf Cartel - Top Enforcer Arrested near Texas Border" /><published>2023-09-13T16:50:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-13T16:50:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/13/Gulf-Cartel-Enforcer</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/13/Gulf-Cartel-Enforcer/">&lt;p&gt;Amidst the chaos of the cartel battles brewing near the Texas border, a critical arrest was made. One of the Gulf Cartel’s top enforcers in Reynosa, Roque “Rocky, Metro 58 or Comandante Roque” Cruz Fuentes, known for his leadership in the Metros faction’s security forces, is now behind bars.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On an early Thursday morning, Mexican Navy’s elite force, popularly referred to as Marinos, established strategic perimeters across the Las Fuentes and Olmitos neighborhoods. This was the backdrop for the meticulously executed raids targeting Roque and his operations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Throughout the operation, three helicopters, armed with sharpshooters, blanketed the skies, providing invaluable air support. Simultaneously, a diversionary raid was underway, a strategic move to distract and deter any gunmen attempting to intervene and rescue their leader.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the arrest wasn’t the only significant outcome of this operation. Authorities, during their mission, successfully liberated a woman kidnapped and held by El Roque in his hideout.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Following the arrest, El Roque, along with eight of his armed associates, was swiftly transported to Matamoros. There, at the local Mexico Attorney General’s Office, the processing began. Post-processing, they were then moved to Mexico City, where El Roque is slated to face a federal judge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Breitbart Texas’ law enforcement sources have disclosed that El Roque, as a high-ranking member of Los Metros, was implicated in an extensive list of violent acts. From orchestrating shootouts to commissioning a slew of kidnappings and murders, his actions were part of a larger ongoing feud with the Matamoros faction of the Gulf Cartel, known as Los Escorpiones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This arrest marks a significant step in curbing the violence and dominance of cartel factions in the region. But as history has shown, the ever-resilient cartels often bounce back, potentially escalating the tension in the already volatile borderlands.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Amidst the chaos of the cartel battles brewing near the Texas border, a critical arrest was made. One of the Gulf Cartel’s top enforcers in Reynosa, Roque “Rocky, Metro 58 or Comandante Roque” Cruz Fuentes, known for his leadership in the Metros faction’s security forces, is now behind bars. On an early Thursday morning, Mexican Navy’s elite force, popularly referred to as Marinos, established strategic perimeters across the Las Fuentes and Olmitos neighborhoods. This was the backdrop for the meticulously executed raids targeting Roque and his operations. Throughout the operation, three helicopters, armed with sharpshooters, blanketed the skies, providing invaluable air support. Simultaneously, a diversionary raid was underway, a strategic move to distract and deter any gunmen attempting to intervene and rescue their leader. However, the arrest wasn’t the only significant outcome of this operation. Authorities, during their mission, successfully liberated a woman kidnapped and held by El Roque in his hideout. Following the arrest, El Roque, along with eight of his armed associates, was swiftly transported to Matamoros. There, at the local Mexico Attorney General’s Office, the processing began. Post-processing, they were then moved to Mexico City, where El Roque is slated to face a federal judge. Breitbart Texas’ law enforcement sources have disclosed that El Roque, as a high-ranking member of Los Metros, was implicated in an extensive list of violent acts. From orchestrating shootouts to commissioning a slew of kidnappings and murders, his actions were part of a larger ongoing feud with the Matamoros faction of the Gulf Cartel, known as Los Escorpiones. This arrest marks a significant step in curbing the violence and dominance of cartel factions in the region. But as history has shown, the ever-resilient cartels often bounce back, potentially escalating the tension in the already volatile borderlands.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Amy Schumer’s Online Jest - Triggers Controversy Over Masterson Support</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/13/Amy-Schumer-Controversy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Amy Schumer’s Online Jest - Triggers Controversy Over Masterson Support" /><published>2023-09-13T14:45:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-13T14:45:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/13/Amy-Schumer-Controversy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/13/Amy-Schumer-Controversy/">&lt;p&gt;The unpredictable landscape of celebrity social media took another twist when comedian Amy Schumer found herself in the midst of a storm after jesting about Ashton Kutcher and Mila Kunis’ support for Danny Masterson, recently convicted of rape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The incident began when Schumer, attempting to apologize for a post seen as “cyberbullying” towards actress Nicole Kidman, made a sarcastic reference to Kutcher and Kunis’ letters of support for Masterson. These letters were sent to a judge prior to Masterson’s sentencing hearing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amy’s apology read, “I want to apologize to all the people I hurt posting a photo of Nicole Kidman and alluding to her being an alien. I will be asking the cast of that ’70s show to write letters advocating for my forgiveness.” She appended her message with the hashtag “#takingtimetoheal.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, this joke did not land well with the online audience. Comments poured in from fans and critics alike, denouncing Schumer for making light of such a grave issue. Reactions varied from accusing Schumer of being “tasteless” to questioning her decision to jest about a sensitive matter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adding to the complexity of the situation is the fact that Masterson was recently sentenced to a rigorous 30 years to life in prison, post his conviction on two counts of forcible rape. Kutcher and Kunis’ letters were among nearly 50 submitted to the court in support of Masterson. Astonishingly, in Kutcher’s letter, he praised Masterson as a “role model” and credited him for keeping him away from drugs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both Kutcher and Kunis later took to Instagram, expressing regret for their letters, clarifying that they were not meant to belittle Masterson’s victims in any way. “We support victims,” Kunis asserted, reiterating their dedication to supporting victims through their philanthropic endeavors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Masterson’s legal journey isn’t over yet. His legal team has expressed their intent to appeal the guilty verdict. Shawn Holley, Masterson’s attorney, stated, “Mr. Masterson did not commit the crimes for which he has been convicted… we are confident that these convictions will be overturned.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This tangled web of celebrity opinions, legal ramifications, and public sentiment showcases the ever-blurring lines between personal opinions, public images, and the weight of social media in today’s age.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">The unpredictable landscape of celebrity social media took another twist when comedian Amy Schumer found herself in the midst of a storm after jesting about Ashton Kutcher and Mila Kunis’ support for Danny Masterson, recently convicted of rape. The incident began when Schumer, attempting to apologize for a post seen as “cyberbullying” towards actress Nicole Kidman, made a sarcastic reference to Kutcher and Kunis’ letters of support for Masterson. These letters were sent to a judge prior to Masterson’s sentencing hearing. Amy’s apology read, “I want to apologize to all the people I hurt posting a photo of Nicole Kidman and alluding to her being an alien. I will be asking the cast of that ’70s show to write letters advocating for my forgiveness.” She appended her message with the hashtag “#takingtimetoheal.” However, this joke did not land well with the online audience. Comments poured in from fans and critics alike, denouncing Schumer for making light of such a grave issue. Reactions varied from accusing Schumer of being “tasteless” to questioning her decision to jest about a sensitive matter. Adding to the complexity of the situation is the fact that Masterson was recently sentenced to a rigorous 30 years to life in prison, post his conviction on two counts of forcible rape. Kutcher and Kunis’ letters were among nearly 50 submitted to the court in support of Masterson. Astonishingly, in Kutcher’s letter, he praised Masterson as a “role model” and credited him for keeping him away from drugs. Both Kutcher and Kunis later took to Instagram, expressing regret for their letters, clarifying that they were not meant to belittle Masterson’s victims in any way. “We support victims,” Kunis asserted, reiterating their dedication to supporting victims through their philanthropic endeavors. Masterson’s legal journey isn’t over yet. His legal team has expressed their intent to appeal the guilty verdict. Shawn Holley, Masterson’s attorney, stated, “Mr. Masterson did not commit the crimes for which he has been convicted… we are confident that these convictions will be overturned.” This tangled web of celebrity opinions, legal ramifications, and public sentiment showcases the ever-blurring lines between personal opinions, public images, and the weight of social media in today’s age.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Tennessee Tycoon Under Fire - Allegations, Innocence, and Controversy</title><link href="/news/2023/09/13/Tennessee-Scandal/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tennessee Tycoon Under Fire - Allegations, Innocence, and Controversy" /><published>2023-09-13T13:45:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-13T13:45:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/13/Tennessee-Scandal</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/13/Tennessee-Scandal/">&lt;p&gt;In an unfolding saga rife with accusations, controversy, and vehement declarations of innocence, Sean Williams, a once-renowned Tennessee businessman, finds himself at the heart of a growing firestorm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Allegations and Arrests&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ten women have levelled charges against Williams, accusing him of drugging and sexually assaulting them at high-profile gatherings held in his opulent downtown apartment. Responding to these claims, Williams, in written correspondence from the Laurel County Jail, mocked the notion of him drugging anyone. He emphasized his newfound popularity due to his lavish lifestyle and flashy parties, insisting that many were eager to be part of these soirées.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Williams was on the lam for two years before North Carolina police nabbed him this April, uncovering on his electronic devices videos purportedly showing him sexually assaulting 52 different women. In a startling discovery, a thumb drive in his possession allegedly contained over 5,000 images of child pornography.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Law Enforcement in Question&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further muddying the waters, the Johnson City Police Department (JCPD) has also come under scrutiny. The lawsuit alleges the department grossly mishandled several complaints against Williams, essentially turning a blind eye. Reports suggest that between 2019 and 2020, at least six complaints alleging Williams’ nefarious activities reached the JCPD. Rather than apprehending Williams, officers allegedly regarded him as “untouchable.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Seeking Justice&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kateri Dahl, a former Assistant U.S. Attorney, played a crucial role in shining a light on Williams’ alleged transgressions. Dahl claims she was dismissed from her position after voicing concerns regarding Williams. In a bid to ensure justice, Dahl has now donned the role of a whistleblower, highlighting the JCPD’s purported lapses in handling victims’ cases.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An independent audit commissioned by the city corroborates many of Dahl’s claims, revealing “material deficiencies” in JCPD’s handling of sexual assaults. With such lapses, the ability to gather essential evidence for thorough investigations is severely hampered. The audit found the department’s reporting process to be “inconsistent, ineffective, and incomplete.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Williams’ Rebuttal&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Firm in his denial, Williams accuses law enforcement of fabricating evidence, alleging his money was stolen, and illicit drugs were “planted” on him. He asserts that all the images and videos acquired by the police merely depict consensual interactions with friends. As for the ten women pressing charges, Williams suggests each has a personal vendetta against him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amid this web of allegations, the narrative remains contentious. What seems evident, however, is that this case will continue to dominate headlines as the quest for truth, and justice presses on.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In an unfolding saga rife with accusations, controversy, and vehement declarations of innocence, Sean Williams, a once-renowned Tennessee businessman, finds himself at the heart of a growing firestorm. Allegations and Arrests Ten women have levelled charges against Williams, accusing him of drugging and sexually assaulting them at high-profile gatherings held in his opulent downtown apartment. Responding to these claims, Williams, in written correspondence from the Laurel County Jail, mocked the notion of him drugging anyone. He emphasized his newfound popularity due to his lavish lifestyle and flashy parties, insisting that many were eager to be part of these soirées. Williams was on the lam for two years before North Carolina police nabbed him this April, uncovering on his electronic devices videos purportedly showing him sexually assaulting 52 different women. In a startling discovery, a thumb drive in his possession allegedly contained over 5,000 images of child pornography. Law Enforcement in Question Further muddying the waters, the Johnson City Police Department (JCPD) has also come under scrutiny. The lawsuit alleges the department grossly mishandled several complaints against Williams, essentially turning a blind eye. Reports suggest that between 2019 and 2020, at least six complaints alleging Williams’ nefarious activities reached the JCPD. Rather than apprehending Williams, officers allegedly regarded him as “untouchable.” Seeking Justice Kateri Dahl, a former Assistant U.S. Attorney, played a crucial role in shining a light on Williams’ alleged transgressions. Dahl claims she was dismissed from her position after voicing concerns regarding Williams. In a bid to ensure justice, Dahl has now donned the role of a whistleblower, highlighting the JCPD’s purported lapses in handling victims’ cases. An independent audit commissioned by the city corroborates many of Dahl’s claims, revealing “material deficiencies” in JCPD’s handling of sexual assaults. With such lapses, the ability to gather essential evidence for thorough investigations is severely hampered. The audit found the department’s reporting process to be “inconsistent, ineffective, and incomplete.” Williams’ Rebuttal Firm in his denial, Williams accuses law enforcement of fabricating evidence, alleging his money was stolen, and illicit drugs were “planted” on him. He asserts that all the images and videos acquired by the police merely depict consensual interactions with friends. As for the ten women pressing charges, Williams suggests each has a personal vendetta against him. Amid this web of allegations, the narrative remains contentious. What seems evident, however, is that this case will continue to dominate headlines as the quest for truth, and justice presses on.</summary></entry></feed>