<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-10-26T18:14:17-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/26/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-26T18:14:17-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-26T18:14:17-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/26/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/26/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/26/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-26T18:14:17-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-26T18:14:17-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/26/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/26/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/">&lt;p&gt;Recent surprise attacks by Hamas on Israel has fueled ongoing tensions between staunchly conservative commentators and the progressive “Squad” Democrats known for criticizing Israel. The intensity of the backlash highlights the deep political divide over foreign policy in the Middle East.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Hamas’ shocking attack, several members of the “Squad,” including Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.), called for a “ceasefire and de-escalation,” condemning the violence. The absence of a statement from Rep. Rashida Tlaib (D-Mich.) was notably called out by conservative media outlets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;South Carolina GOP Rep. Nancy Mace quickly labeled Ocasio-Cortez a “Hamas apologist” in response to her call for peace and de-escalation. Rep. Ilhan Omar (D-Minn.), no stranger to controversy surrounding her views on Israel, echoed the call for de-escalation and ceasefire. Omar’s prior statements comparing the US and Israel to terrorist groups like Hamas and the Taliban resurfaced in the debate, fueling more criticisms. Omar’s 2019 tweet, where she opined that “Israel has hypnotized the world,” also continues to haunt her political career, often cited by critics to challenge her stance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conservative commentators have been especially vocal. “FOX &amp;amp; Friends Weekend” co-host Rachel Campos-Duffy took aim at Omar, saying she fails to recognize the peace in the Middle East under Trump’s administration. Conservative pundit John Hasson also called out Omar, claiming she insinuated that attacks on IDF forces were acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Massachusetts Democrat Rep. Ayanna Pressley’s concerns over the “devastating attacks on Israelis” were met with skepticism. A prominent conservative online personality, Comfortably Smug, accused the “Squad” of advising Israel to back down after the nation suffered massive attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Jamaal Bowman’s call for an end to the Gaza blockade, in addition to condemning the Hamas attacks, was met with criticism from conservative radio host Jason Rantz. He accused Bowman of pairing his condemnation of terrorism with unwarranted criticisms of Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Cori Bush emphasized the urgent need for a ceasefire, while pushing for an end to “U.S. support for Israeli military occupation and apartheid.” Defense attorney Marina Medvin criticized Bush, suggesting that she equates the death of Palestinian terrorists to the horrific acts committed against Jewish civilians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amidst the political turmoil and intense debate, the attacks have taken a heavy toll. Israeli media report over 300 dead due to the wide-ranging assault. Gaza health officials note that at least 200 Palestinians have perished in the retaliatory Israeli air strikes following the initial Hamas attack. As the situation remains volatile, both sides continue to count their casualties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This divisive issue showcases the challenge America faces in crafting a unified approach to foreign policy, with deeply entrenched political divides at play. As the situation develops, the debate is bound to intensify, shedding light on the complexities of U.S. politics in the global arena.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Reckless Behavior in the Capitol: Congressman Jamaal Bowman’s Disturbing Misconduct</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/26/Congressman-Fire-Alarm-Incident/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Reckless Behavior in the Capitol: Congressman Jamaal Bowman’s Disturbing Misconduct" /><published>2023-10-26T15:41:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-26T15:41:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/26/Congressman-Fire-Alarm-Incident</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/26/Congressman-Fire-Alarm-Incident/">&lt;p&gt;New York Representative Jamaal Bowman’s recent misconduct in the Capitol has raised eyebrows and drawn criticism from various quarters. In a disappointing turn of events, the Congressman pleaded guilty to a misdemeanor charge for falsely pulling a fire alarm in a congressional office building last month, just as lawmakers were gearing up for a critical vote.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bowman’s actions, which could have led to a six-month jail sentence, were settled with a plea deal requiring him to pay a $1,000 fine, write an apology to the Capitol Police, and serve three months of probation. Following this period, the charge will be withdrawn. Despite these consequences, many are left questioning Bowman’s judgement and the integrity of his actions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Initially, Bowman claimed he pulled the fire alarm in an attempt to open emergency doors to make it to a vote in time. However, this explanation quickly fell apart as Breitbart News exposed that he had discarded emergency warning signs before pulling the alarm and exiting the building from a different floor, blatantly contradicting his story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Facing the media, Bowman admitted to his actions, expressing regret for the confusion and disturbance caused. He acknowledged breaking D.C. law but seemed to downplay the gravity of his actions. “I really regret that this caused so much confusion and that people had to evacuate, and I just caused a disturbance. I hate that. It’s pretty embarrassing,” he stated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, his apology and admission do little to excuse his reckless behavior. Prosecutors were ready to prove that he knowingly pulled the alarm without any emergency and failed to immediately inform Capitol Police of his actions. His admission of guilt has prompted Republican lawmakers to draft a resolution seeking his expulsion from Congress, a move that underscores the severity of his misconduct.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bowman’s attempt to paint his actions as a misunderstanding does not hold water. He continues to claim he did not intend to disrupt congressional proceedings, but the evidence and his admission say otherwise. He broke the law, and now he must face the consequences of his actions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This incident serves as a stark reminder that elected officials are not above the law and must be held accountable for their actions, regardless of their political affiliations or positions. Bowman’s irresponsible behavior has not only damaged his own reputation but has also cast a shadow on the integrity of congressional proceedings, raising concerns about the standards to which our elected officials are held.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">New York Representative Jamaal Bowman’s recent misconduct in the Capitol has raised eyebrows and drawn criticism from various quarters. In a disappointing turn of events, the Congressman pleaded guilty to a misdemeanor charge for falsely pulling a fire alarm in a congressional office building last month, just as lawmakers were gearing up for a critical vote. Bowman’s actions, which could have led to a six-month jail sentence, were settled with a plea deal requiring him to pay a $1,000 fine, write an apology to the Capitol Police, and serve three months of probation. Following this period, the charge will be withdrawn. Despite these consequences, many are left questioning Bowman’s judgement and the integrity of his actions. Initially, Bowman claimed he pulled the fire alarm in an attempt to open emergency doors to make it to a vote in time. However, this explanation quickly fell apart as Breitbart News exposed that he had discarded emergency warning signs before pulling the alarm and exiting the building from a different floor, blatantly contradicting his story. Facing the media, Bowman admitted to his actions, expressing regret for the confusion and disturbance caused. He acknowledged breaking D.C. law but seemed to downplay the gravity of his actions. “I really regret that this caused so much confusion and that people had to evacuate, and I just caused a disturbance. I hate that. It’s pretty embarrassing,” he stated. However, his apology and admission do little to excuse his reckless behavior. Prosecutors were ready to prove that he knowingly pulled the alarm without any emergency and failed to immediately inform Capitol Police of his actions. His admission of guilt has prompted Republican lawmakers to draft a resolution seeking his expulsion from Congress, a move that underscores the severity of his misconduct. Bowman’s attempt to paint his actions as a misunderstanding does not hold water. He continues to claim he did not intend to disrupt congressional proceedings, but the evidence and his admission say otherwise. He broke the law, and now he must face the consequences of his actions. This incident serves as a stark reminder that elected officials are not above the law and must be held accountable for their actions, regardless of their political affiliations or positions. Bowman’s irresponsible behavior has not only damaged his own reputation but has also cast a shadow on the integrity of congressional proceedings, raising concerns about the standards to which our elected officials are held.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Groundbreaking Texas Immigration Bill Advances: Empowering Local Law Enforcement</title><link href="/news/2023/10/26/Texas-Immigration-Bill/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Groundbreaking Texas Immigration Bill Advances: Empowering Local Law Enforcement" /><published>2023-10-26T14:25:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-26T14:25:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/26/Texas-Immigration-Bill</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/26/Texas-Immigration-Bill/">&lt;p&gt;In a move to strengthen border security, the Texas state House of Representatives has successfully passed a series of bills, with one in particular drawing significant attention. House Bill 4, designed to empower local police forces to arrest and deport illegal migrants, has cleared the state house, marking a pivotal moment in the ongoing debate surrounding immigration policy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amidst a turbulent political climate, the Texas legislature has allocated over $1 billion for the construction of border barriers and has taken steps to increase sentences for human trafficking offenses. House Bill 4, however, stands out as it directly challenges federal jurisdiction over immigration matters, granting unprecedented authority to state and local law enforcement agencies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The progression of these bills follows hours of heated debate in the state house, with emotions running high on both sides of the aisle. State Rep. Cody Harris of Palestine played a crucial role in moving the bill forward, calling to block new amendments and subsequently bringing the debate to an end. The bill passed with a majority vote of 84-60, though not without leaving a significant impact on the representatives present.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;State Rep. Armando Lucio Walle of Houston expressed his deep frustration following the bill’s passage, highlighting the personal and emotional toll these political debates have on individuals and communities alike. “It hurts us to our f—ing core,” Walle told Harris, emphasizing the profound disconnect and lack of understanding that he believes exists between the bill’s supporters and those it will affect most directly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As House Bill 4 makes its way to the state Senate, where Republicans hold a majority, it is widely expected to pass and become law. Proponents of the bill, such as State Rep. David Spille from Fort Worth, argue that it represents a “humane, logical, and efficient approach” to addressing illegal immigration. Spille asserts that there is nothing unfair about “ordering someone back from where they came if they arrived here illegally.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While supporters celebrate the bill’s advancement, it is essential to recognize the broader context of this legislative action. The Biden administration recently released new border numbers for September, revealing a record-breaking number of encounters and marking FY 23 as a year of unprecedented immigration challenges. Amidst these challenges, the administration has reiterated its opposition to border walls, even as it takes steps to address urgent needs in South Texas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the nation watches closely, the passage of House Bill 4 in Texas may very well set a precedent for how state and local governments engage with federal immigration policies in the future. The bill’s progress serves as a testament to the complex and often contentious nature of immigration policy in the United States, highlighting the need for comprehensive and thoughtful solutions that address the root causes of migration and ensure the fair and humane treatment of all individuals, regardless of their immigration status.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a move to strengthen border security, the Texas state House of Representatives has successfully passed a series of bills, with one in particular drawing significant attention. House Bill 4, designed to empower local police forces to arrest and deport illegal migrants, has cleared the state house, marking a pivotal moment in the ongoing debate surrounding immigration policy. Amidst a turbulent political climate, the Texas legislature has allocated over $1 billion for the construction of border barriers and has taken steps to increase sentences for human trafficking offenses. House Bill 4, however, stands out as it directly challenges federal jurisdiction over immigration matters, granting unprecedented authority to state and local law enforcement agencies. The progression of these bills follows hours of heated debate in the state house, with emotions running high on both sides of the aisle. State Rep. Cody Harris of Palestine played a crucial role in moving the bill forward, calling to block new amendments and subsequently bringing the debate to an end. The bill passed with a majority vote of 84-60, though not without leaving a significant impact on the representatives present. State Rep. Armando Lucio Walle of Houston expressed his deep frustration following the bill’s passage, highlighting the personal and emotional toll these political debates have on individuals and communities alike. “It hurts us to our f—ing core,” Walle told Harris, emphasizing the profound disconnect and lack of understanding that he believes exists between the bill’s supporters and those it will affect most directly. As House Bill 4 makes its way to the state Senate, where Republicans hold a majority, it is widely expected to pass and become law. Proponents of the bill, such as State Rep. David Spille from Fort Worth, argue that it represents a “humane, logical, and efficient approach” to addressing illegal immigration. Spille asserts that there is nothing unfair about “ordering someone back from where they came if they arrived here illegally.” While supporters celebrate the bill’s advancement, it is essential to recognize the broader context of this legislative action. The Biden administration recently released new border numbers for September, revealing a record-breaking number of encounters and marking FY 23 as a year of unprecedented immigration challenges. Amidst these challenges, the administration has reiterated its opposition to border walls, even as it takes steps to address urgent needs in South Texas. As the nation watches closely, the passage of House Bill 4 in Texas may very well set a precedent for how state and local governments engage with federal immigration policies in the future. The bill’s progress serves as a testament to the complex and often contentious nature of immigration policy in the United States, highlighting the need for comprehensive and thoughtful solutions that address the root causes of migration and ensure the fair and humane treatment of all individuals, regardless of their immigration status.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Caution Advised: Study Links Simultaneous COVID and Flu Vaccines to Stroke Risk in Seniors</title><link href="/news/2023/10/26/Stroke-Risk-Vaccine-Combination/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Caution Advised: Study Links Simultaneous COVID and Flu Vaccines to Stroke Risk in Seniors" /><published>2023-10-26T13:10:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-26T13:10:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/26/Stroke-Risk-Vaccine-Combination</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/26/Stroke-Risk-Vaccine-Combination/">&lt;p&gt;A recent study has raised concerns about the potential risks associated with administering the COVID-19 vaccine and the flu shot simultaneously, particularly for seniors above the age of 85. Health experts from the Food and Drug Administration (FDA) have pinpointed this potential risk while analyzing Medicare claims data, putting a spotlight on the need for careful consideration when it comes to vaccine combinations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The study, which follows a previous report by the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) and the FDA, highlighted a potential risk of strokes caused by blood clots in the brains of older adults receiving both vaccines on the same day. While the overall risk remains low—approximately 3 in 100,000 doses—the study’s findings are significant enough to warrant further investigation and awareness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The serious side effect appears to be triggered specifically by the high-dose or adjuvanted flu shot, which is designed to elicit a stronger immune response. Interestingly, further analysis indicated a slight increased risk even for seniors aged 65 and older who only received the flu shot, correlating to an additional 1-2 strokes per 100,000 doses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dr. Steve Nissen, a respected cardiologist and researcher at the Cleveland Clinic in Ohio, emphasized that “the absolute risk is minuscule,” especially when compared to the grave risks posed by COVID-19 to individuals over the age of 85. However, the findings are still crucial for informed decision-making when it comes to vaccination strategies for older populations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The CDC is actively following up on these preliminary findings with additional studies to understand the full extent of the potential risk. Dr. Tom Shimabukuro, director of the Immunization Safety Office at the CDC, reiterated that the current data does not provide “clear and consistent evidence” of a safety problem, but the investigation is ongoing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Health experts continue to underline the importance of vaccination for older adults, particularly given their increased vulnerability to severe outcomes from both the flu and COVID-19. However, for those concerned about potential risks, spacing out the vaccines by about two weeks could be a viable option to minimize interactions and potential side effects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The FDA’s investigation found no increase in stroke risk for individuals over 65 who received either the Pfizer or Moderna COVID-19 vaccines, though a slight increase in risk was noted for those 85 and older who received the Pfizer shot. Regardless, the findings underscore the need for a nuanced approach to vaccination for older adults, ensuring that the benefits of protection against severe disease are carefully weighed against potential risks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the study awaits peer review, the healthcare community remains vigilant, continuing to explore and understand the complexities of vaccine interactions to ensure the safety and well-being of all individuals, particularly our most vulnerable populations.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">A recent study has raised concerns about the potential risks associated with administering the COVID-19 vaccine and the flu shot simultaneously, particularly for seniors above the age of 85. Health experts from the Food and Drug Administration (FDA) have pinpointed this potential risk while analyzing Medicare claims data, putting a spotlight on the need for careful consideration when it comes to vaccine combinations. The study, which follows a previous report by the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) and the FDA, highlighted a potential risk of strokes caused by blood clots in the brains of older adults receiving both vaccines on the same day. While the overall risk remains low—approximately 3 in 100,000 doses—the study’s findings are significant enough to warrant further investigation and awareness. The serious side effect appears to be triggered specifically by the high-dose or adjuvanted flu shot, which is designed to elicit a stronger immune response. Interestingly, further analysis indicated a slight increased risk even for seniors aged 65 and older who only received the flu shot, correlating to an additional 1-2 strokes per 100,000 doses. Dr. Steve Nissen, a respected cardiologist and researcher at the Cleveland Clinic in Ohio, emphasized that “the absolute risk is minuscule,” especially when compared to the grave risks posed by COVID-19 to individuals over the age of 85. However, the findings are still crucial for informed decision-making when it comes to vaccination strategies for older populations. The CDC is actively following up on these preliminary findings with additional studies to understand the full extent of the potential risk. Dr. Tom Shimabukuro, director of the Immunization Safety Office at the CDC, reiterated that the current data does not provide “clear and consistent evidence” of a safety problem, but the investigation is ongoing. Health experts continue to underline the importance of vaccination for older adults, particularly given their increased vulnerability to severe outcomes from both the flu and COVID-19. However, for those concerned about potential risks, spacing out the vaccines by about two weeks could be a viable option to minimize interactions and potential side effects. The FDA’s investigation found no increase in stroke risk for individuals over 65 who received either the Pfizer or Moderna COVID-19 vaccines, though a slight increase in risk was noted for those 85 and older who received the Pfizer shot. Regardless, the findings underscore the need for a nuanced approach to vaccination for older adults, ensuring that the benefits of protection against severe disease are carefully weighed against potential risks. As the study awaits peer review, the healthcare community remains vigilant, continuing to explore and understand the complexities of vaccine interactions to ensure the safety and well-being of all individuals, particularly our most vulnerable populations.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Examining Rep. Tlaib’s Alleged Hamas Connections: A Deep Dive into Fundraising Ties</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/26/Ties-to-Hamas/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Examining Rep. Tlaib’s Alleged Hamas Connections: A Deep Dive into Fundraising Ties" /><published>2023-10-26T12:06:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-26T12:06:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/26/Ties-to-Hamas</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/26/Ties-to-Hamas/">&lt;p&gt;Canary Mission, a watchdog group, has recently released a report alleging that Rep. Rashida Tlaib, a Democrat representing Michigan, has extensive fundraising ties to supporters of Hamas, a designated terrorist organization. The congresswoman, already a controversial figure due to accusations of antisemitism, is now facing scrutiny for her campaign’s financial connections.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to Canary Mission, Rep. Tlaib hired three activists with links to Hamas to fundraise for her 2018 campaign. One of these individuals reportedly spent eight months in prison due to alleged connections to the terrorist group. The report raises questions about the vetting process for individuals involved in political fundraising and the potential implications of such ties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The congresswoman’s use of a pro-terror Facebook page, PAC-USA, for campaign fundraising is also highlighted in the report. This, combined with her co-founding of Black4Palestine, a Detroit-based group accused of harboring anti-American, anti-Israel, and pro-terror sentiments, adds layers to the allegations against her. The co-founder of Black4Palestine has allegedly used the group to collaborate with members of the Popular Front for the Liberation of Palestine, another organization designated as a terrorist group by Washington in 1997.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adam Kredo, a senior reporter at the Washington Free Beacon, commented on the situation via Twitter, stating, “This is truly wild. Appears to show a direct line from Hamas supporters to Tlaib’s financial channels.” His statement underscores the gravity of the allegations and the potential impact on Rep. Tlaib’s political standing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These claims put Rep. Tlaib in a precarious position, especially considering her history of controversies related to antisemitism and her stance on Israel. Her refusal to remove a social media post blaming Israel for an attack on a hospital in Gaza has only fueled the fire of criticism against her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The report from Canary Mission necessitates a thorough investigation to ascertain the validity of these allegations. If proven true, it could have significant repercussions for Rep. Tlaib’s career and reputation, and raise serious questions about the influence of terrorist-linked individuals in American politics. The situation calls for transparency, accountability, and a commitment to upholding the principles of democracy and national security.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Canary Mission, a watchdog group, has recently released a report alleging that Rep. Rashida Tlaib, a Democrat representing Michigan, has extensive fundraising ties to supporters of Hamas, a designated terrorist organization. The congresswoman, already a controversial figure due to accusations of antisemitism, is now facing scrutiny for her campaign’s financial connections. According to Canary Mission, Rep. Tlaib hired three activists with links to Hamas to fundraise for her 2018 campaign. One of these individuals reportedly spent eight months in prison due to alleged connections to the terrorist group. The report raises questions about the vetting process for individuals involved in political fundraising and the potential implications of such ties. The congresswoman’s use of a pro-terror Facebook page, PAC-USA, for campaign fundraising is also highlighted in the report. This, combined with her co-founding of Black4Palestine, a Detroit-based group accused of harboring anti-American, anti-Israel, and pro-terror sentiments, adds layers to the allegations against her. The co-founder of Black4Palestine has allegedly used the group to collaborate with members of the Popular Front for the Liberation of Palestine, another organization designated as a terrorist group by Washington in 1997. Adam Kredo, a senior reporter at the Washington Free Beacon, commented on the situation via Twitter, stating, “This is truly wild. Appears to show a direct line from Hamas supporters to Tlaib’s financial channels.” His statement underscores the gravity of the allegations and the potential impact on Rep. Tlaib’s political standing. These claims put Rep. Tlaib in a precarious position, especially considering her history of controversies related to antisemitism and her stance on Israel. Her refusal to remove a social media post blaming Israel for an attack on a hospital in Gaza has only fueled the fire of criticism against her. The report from Canary Mission necessitates a thorough investigation to ascertain the validity of these allegations. If proven true, it could have significant repercussions for Rep. Tlaib’s career and reputation, and raise serious questions about the influence of terrorist-linked individuals in American politics. The situation calls for transparency, accountability, and a commitment to upholding the principles of democracy and national security.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump Dominates in Texas: Surges Ahead in Polls Against Biden and GOP Rivals</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/26/Trump-Leads-Texas-Poll/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump Dominates in Texas: Surges Ahead in Polls Against Biden and GOP Rivals" /><published>2023-10-26T10:55:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-26T10:55:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/26/Trump-Leads-Texas-Poll</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/26/Trump-Leads-Texas-Poll/">&lt;p&gt;Former President Donald Trump is making waves in Texas, showing a robust lead in the latest polls over President Joe Biden and other GOP presidential hopefuls. The University of Texas/Texas Politics Project has revealed that Trump is currently 8 points ahead of Biden, capturing 45% of the vote compared to Biden’s 37%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This poll, conducted between October 5th and 17th, surveyed 1,200 self-declared registered Texas voters, boasting a margin of error of plus or minus 2.83%. It has sent ripples across the political landscape, highlighting Trump’s enduring influence and popularity in the Lone Star State.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump’s position as the GOP front-runner is further solidified with a staggering 49-point lead over Florida Governor Ron DeSantis, one of his main rivals for the 2024 GOP presidential nomination. An impressive 62% of respondents expressed their intent to vote for Trump, leaving DeSantis with a mere 13%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Former South Carolina Governor Nikki Haley trails even further behind, with Trump holding a commanding 55-point lead in this potential matchup. Other GOP candidates combined garnered support from just 3% of respondents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With immigration and border security topping the list of concerns for Texas voters, Trump’s tough stance on these issues seems to be resonating well. Over a third of voters, or 35%, identified these issues as the most critical facing Texas today. This sentiment was particularly strong among Republican voters, 60% of whom pinpointed immigration and border security as their top concern.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These poll results highlight the uphill battle Biden faces in Texas, a state where his policies, particularly on immigration, have been met with staunch opposition. Senator Ted Cruz, a prominent Texas Republican, has been vocal in his criticism of Biden’s handling of the migrant crisis at the southern border.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Biden has recently taken steps to bolster border security, including a decision to continue construction of the border wall in South Texas, these moves have been met with mixed reactions. His decision to waive 26 federal laws to expedite the wall’s construction was seen by some as a stunning reversal, drawing ire from both sides of the aisle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the 2024 elections loom closer, Trump’s lead in Texas paints a vivid picture of the political landscape, showcasing his enduring appeal among Republican voters and highlighting the challenges Biden faces in swaying this key demographic. The poll results underscore the significant influence of immigration and border security issues in Texas politics, setting the stage for what promises to be a highly contested and closely watched electoral battle in the Lone Star State.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Former President Donald Trump is making waves in Texas, showing a robust lead in the latest polls over President Joe Biden and other GOP presidential hopefuls. The University of Texas/Texas Politics Project has revealed that Trump is currently 8 points ahead of Biden, capturing 45% of the vote compared to Biden’s 37%. This poll, conducted between October 5th and 17th, surveyed 1,200 self-declared registered Texas voters, boasting a margin of error of plus or minus 2.83%. It has sent ripples across the political landscape, highlighting Trump’s enduring influence and popularity in the Lone Star State. Trump’s position as the GOP front-runner is further solidified with a staggering 49-point lead over Florida Governor Ron DeSantis, one of his main rivals for the 2024 GOP presidential nomination. An impressive 62% of respondents expressed their intent to vote for Trump, leaving DeSantis with a mere 13%. Former South Carolina Governor Nikki Haley trails even further behind, with Trump holding a commanding 55-point lead in this potential matchup. Other GOP candidates combined garnered support from just 3% of respondents. With immigration and border security topping the list of concerns for Texas voters, Trump’s tough stance on these issues seems to be resonating well. Over a third of voters, or 35%, identified these issues as the most critical facing Texas today. This sentiment was particularly strong among Republican voters, 60% of whom pinpointed immigration and border security as their top concern. These poll results highlight the uphill battle Biden faces in Texas, a state where his policies, particularly on immigration, have been met with staunch opposition. Senator Ted Cruz, a prominent Texas Republican, has been vocal in his criticism of Biden’s handling of the migrant crisis at the southern border. While Biden has recently taken steps to bolster border security, including a decision to continue construction of the border wall in South Texas, these moves have been met with mixed reactions. His decision to waive 26 federal laws to expedite the wall’s construction was seen by some as a stunning reversal, drawing ire from both sides of the aisle. As the 2024 elections loom closer, Trump’s lead in Texas paints a vivid picture of the political landscape, showcasing his enduring appeal among Republican voters and highlighting the challenges Biden faces in swaying this key demographic. The poll results underscore the significant influence of immigration and border security issues in Texas politics, setting the stage for what promises to be a highly contested and closely watched electoral battle in the Lone Star State.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Revving Up Resistance: GOP Challenges Biden’s Clampdown on Fossil Fuel Transit</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/26/Fossil-Fuel-Transportation-Showdown/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Revving Up Resistance: GOP Challenges Biden’s Clampdown on Fossil Fuel Transit" /><published>2023-10-26T09:45:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-26T09:45:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/26/Fossil-Fuel-Transportation-Showdown</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/26/Fossil-Fuel-Transportation-Showdown/">&lt;p&gt;Pushing back against the Biden administration’s stringent measures on fossil fuel transportation, 25 Republican lawmakers have unleashed a formidable opposition, challenging the recent prohibition on transporting liquefied natural gas (LNG) via rail. Leading the charge are Sen. Ted Cruz from Texas and Rep. Sam Graves of Missouri, both holding significant roles in their respective chambers’ committees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A Bicameral Battle for Energy Independence:
Cruz, ranking member of the Senate Commerce Committee, and Graves, chairman of the House Transportation and Infrastructure Committee, have co-authored a potent letter to Tristan Brown, Deputy Administrator of the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration (PHMSA). In it, they express their grave concerns over the administration’s latest strike in what they term as the “war on American energy.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unpacking the Administration’s Decision:
This controversial move by the Biden administration took place last month, suspending a 2020 authorization that allowed for the rail transport of LNG. This suspension is set to last until a new permanent rule is established or until June 30, 2025. The 25 Republicans argue that this decision disregards PHMSA’s primary mission of safety, citing data that shows transporting hazardous materials by highway is inherently riskier.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Highlighting the Hypocrisy:
The lawmakers pull no punches, asserting that this move is a smokescreen for a broader attack on domestic fossil fuel production, one that willingly overlooks the detrimental effects on consumers and national security. They accuse the Biden administration of virtue signaling, rather than making tangible progress in emission reduction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PHMSA’s Response and The Road Ahead:
PHMSA has defended its decision, stating that the suspension provides ample time for ongoing testing and the development of mitigation measures for LNG rail transportation. The Republican coalition, however, remains unconvinced, continuing their call for a reversal of this decision, or at the very least, a ruleset that upholds PHMSA’s safety mission while considering the cost-benefit analysis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A Nation at an Energy Crossroads:
This robust challenge from the Republicans highlights the ongoing battle between traditional energy proponents and the green energy agenda of the Biden administration. It remains to be seen how this tug-of-war will play out, but one thing is certain: the Republicans are not backing down without a fight. With their letter, they have made it clear that they stand for energy independence, consumer protection, and a balanced approach to environmental policy. The ball is now in the Biden administration’s court, as the nation watches to see how this critical issue in American energy policy will be resolved.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Pushing back against the Biden administration’s stringent measures on fossil fuel transportation, 25 Republican lawmakers have unleashed a formidable opposition, challenging the recent prohibition on transporting liquefied natural gas (LNG) via rail. Leading the charge are Sen. Ted Cruz from Texas and Rep. Sam Graves of Missouri, both holding significant roles in their respective chambers’ committees. A Bicameral Battle for Energy Independence: Cruz, ranking member of the Senate Commerce Committee, and Graves, chairman of the House Transportation and Infrastructure Committee, have co-authored a potent letter to Tristan Brown, Deputy Administrator of the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration (PHMSA). In it, they express their grave concerns over the administration’s latest strike in what they term as the “war on American energy.” Unpacking the Administration’s Decision: This controversial move by the Biden administration took place last month, suspending a 2020 authorization that allowed for the rail transport of LNG. This suspension is set to last until a new permanent rule is established or until June 30, 2025. The 25 Republicans argue that this decision disregards PHMSA’s primary mission of safety, citing data that shows transporting hazardous materials by highway is inherently riskier. Highlighting the Hypocrisy: The lawmakers pull no punches, asserting that this move is a smokescreen for a broader attack on domestic fossil fuel production, one that willingly overlooks the detrimental effects on consumers and national security. They accuse the Biden administration of virtue signaling, rather than making tangible progress in emission reduction. PHMSA’s Response and The Road Ahead: PHMSA has defended its decision, stating that the suspension provides ample time for ongoing testing and the development of mitigation measures for LNG rail transportation. The Republican coalition, however, remains unconvinced, continuing their call for a reversal of this decision, or at the very least, a ruleset that upholds PHMSA’s safety mission while considering the cost-benefit analysis. A Nation at an Energy Crossroads: This robust challenge from the Republicans highlights the ongoing battle between traditional energy proponents and the green energy agenda of the Biden administration. It remains to be seen how this tug-of-war will play out, but one thing is certain: the Republicans are not backing down without a fight. With their letter, they have made it clear that they stand for energy independence, consumer protection, and a balanced approach to environmental policy. The ball is now in the Biden administration’s court, as the nation watches to see how this critical issue in American energy policy will be resolved.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Over 20 Dead in Lewiston, Maine Mass Shooting</title><link href="/news/2023/10/26/Manhunt-Intensifies-After-Lewiston-Maine-Mass-Shooting/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Over 20 Dead in Lewiston, Maine Mass Shooting" /><published>2023-10-26T08:26:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-26T08:26:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/26/Manhunt-Intensifies-After-Lewiston-Maine-Mass-Shooting</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/26/Manhunt-Intensifies-After-Lewiston-Maine-Mass-Shooting/">&lt;p&gt;The tranquil city of Lewiston, Maine was rocked by a mass shooting that has left at least 22 people dead and dozens more injured. The incident unfolded late Wednesday night, shaking the local community to its core. Maine Department of Public Safety Commissioner Mike Sauschuck addressed the media, confirming the scale of the tragedy, but also emphasizing the “very fluid” nature of the ongoing investigation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Robert R. Card, a 40-year-old Bowdoin resident with military training, has been identified as a person of interest in the case. The Lewiston Police Department has issued a stark warning to the public, labeling Card as “armed and dangerous” and urging anyone with information on his whereabouts to contact law enforcement immediately. This marks one of the deadliest incidents in Maine’s recent history, surpassing the total number of homicides recorded in the state for the entire year of 2022.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The response from law enforcement has been swift and significant. Additional FBI agents, SWAT teams, and other resources have been deployed to assist in the manhunt and ensure community safety. Authorities have expanded the shelter-in-place order to include surrounding areas as the search for Card continues, emphasizing the urgency of the situation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Local hospitals and emergency services are working tirelessly to tend to the injured, with Central Maine Medical Center confirming their response to a “mass casualty, mass shooter event.” The exact number of casualties remains unconfirmed as the situation continues to unfold.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;President Biden has been briefed on the incident, and Maine Governor Janet Mills has urged residents to heed directions from law enforcement. Local schools, colleges, and municipal buildings have closed their doors in response to the tragedy, as the community grapples with the shock and heartache of this unprecedented event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The search for Robert Card and the investigation into this mass shooting are ongoing. Law enforcement is leaving no stone unturned as they work to bring justice to the victims and their families. As the community of Lewiston, Maine, mourns the loss of life and comes to terms with this tragedy, the nation watches, waits, and stands in solidarity with them during this time of crisis.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">The tranquil city of Lewiston, Maine was rocked by a mass shooting that has left at least 22 people dead and dozens more injured. The incident unfolded late Wednesday night, shaking the local community to its core. Maine Department of Public Safety Commissioner Mike Sauschuck addressed the media, confirming the scale of the tragedy, but also emphasizing the “very fluid” nature of the ongoing investigation. Robert R. Card, a 40-year-old Bowdoin resident with military training, has been identified as a person of interest in the case. The Lewiston Police Department has issued a stark warning to the public, labeling Card as “armed and dangerous” and urging anyone with information on his whereabouts to contact law enforcement immediately. This marks one of the deadliest incidents in Maine’s recent history, surpassing the total number of homicides recorded in the state for the entire year of 2022. The response from law enforcement has been swift and significant. Additional FBI agents, SWAT teams, and other resources have been deployed to assist in the manhunt and ensure community safety. Authorities have expanded the shelter-in-place order to include surrounding areas as the search for Card continues, emphasizing the urgency of the situation. Local hospitals and emergency services are working tirelessly to tend to the injured, with Central Maine Medical Center confirming their response to a “mass casualty, mass shooter event.” The exact number of casualties remains unconfirmed as the situation continues to unfold. President Biden has been briefed on the incident, and Maine Governor Janet Mills has urged residents to heed directions from law enforcement. Local schools, colleges, and municipal buildings have closed their doors in response to the tragedy, as the community grapples with the shock and heartache of this unprecedented event. The search for Robert Card and the investigation into this mass shooting are ongoing. Law enforcement is leaving no stone unturned as they work to bring justice to the victims and their families. As the community of Lewiston, Maine, mourns the loss of life and comes to terms with this tragedy, the nation watches, waits, and stands in solidarity with them during this time of crisis.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Apple TV+ Prices Skyrocket: What This Means for Consumers</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/26/Streaming-Inflation-Apple-TV/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Apple TV+ Prices Skyrocket: What This Means for Consumers" /><published>2023-10-26T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-26T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/26/Streaming-Inflation-Apple-TV</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/26/Streaming-Inflation-Apple-TV/">&lt;p&gt;Apple has decided to significantly hike the prices of its popular streaming service, Apple TV+. Subscribers are about to feel the pinch in their wallets as the cost of a monthly subscription jumps from $6.99 to $9.99, and yearly subscriptions increase from $69 to $99. This marks a whopping 40% increase, leaving consumers and industry experts alike grappling with the implications of such a steep rise in costs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just a year ago, Apple implemented a price increase for its streaming service, raising the monthly subscription cost from $4.99 to $6.99. With this latest increase, the price has effectively doubled in a mere 12 months, sending shockwaves through the streaming entertainment industry. Subscribers can expect these new prices to take effect on their next billing date, leaving many to wonder if the service is worth the escalating cost.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apple’s price hikes come on the heels of similar moves by other major players in the streaming world. Disney+, Netflix, and Amazon Prime Video have all recently increased their subscription costs, putting additional financial pressure on consumers. However, unlike its competitors, Apple has yet to unveil an ad-supported option, which could potentially offer a more affordable alternative for budget-conscious viewers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The industry has coined the term “streamflation” to describe the recent trend of rising costs in the streaming entertainment sector. A Wall Street Journal analysis published in August revealed that the average cost of a major ad-free streaming service has surged nearly 25% in a year. Streaming companies are gambling on the willingness of consumers to either shell out more money or switch to less expensive, ad-supported tiers, which tend to be more profitable for the providers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s not just Apple TV+ that’s experiencing a price hike; other services under the Apple umbrella are also getting more expensive. Apple Music’s annual plan is seeing a 10% increase, rising to $109 per year. Additionally, Apple Arcade and Apple News+ monthly subscriptions are going up by $2 and $3 respectively, settling at $6.99 and $12.99.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the streaming entertainment landscape continues to evolve, consumers are left navigating the tricky terrain of rising costs and the quest for value. With no signs of prices plateauing anytime soon, the question on everyone’s mind is: How much are we willing to pay for our entertainment, and what are the alternatives? Apple’s bold move has undoubtedly set a precedent, and only time will tell how the market—and the consumers—will respond.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Apple has decided to significantly hike the prices of its popular streaming service, Apple TV+. Subscribers are about to feel the pinch in their wallets as the cost of a monthly subscription jumps from $6.99 to $9.99, and yearly subscriptions increase from $69 to $99. This marks a whopping 40% increase, leaving consumers and industry experts alike grappling with the implications of such a steep rise in costs. Just a year ago, Apple implemented a price increase for its streaming service, raising the monthly subscription cost from $4.99 to $6.99. With this latest increase, the price has effectively doubled in a mere 12 months, sending shockwaves through the streaming entertainment industry. Subscribers can expect these new prices to take effect on their next billing date, leaving many to wonder if the service is worth the escalating cost. Apple’s price hikes come on the heels of similar moves by other major players in the streaming world. Disney+, Netflix, and Amazon Prime Video have all recently increased their subscription costs, putting additional financial pressure on consumers. However, unlike its competitors, Apple has yet to unveil an ad-supported option, which could potentially offer a more affordable alternative for budget-conscious viewers. The industry has coined the term “streamflation” to describe the recent trend of rising costs in the streaming entertainment sector. A Wall Street Journal analysis published in August revealed that the average cost of a major ad-free streaming service has surged nearly 25% in a year. Streaming companies are gambling on the willingness of consumers to either shell out more money or switch to less expensive, ad-supported tiers, which tend to be more profitable for the providers. It’s not just Apple TV+ that’s experiencing a price hike; other services under the Apple umbrella are also getting more expensive. Apple Music’s annual plan is seeing a 10% increase, rising to $109 per year. Additionally, Apple Arcade and Apple News+ monthly subscriptions are going up by $2 and $3 respectively, settling at $6.99 and $12.99. As the streaming entertainment landscape continues to evolve, consumers are left navigating the tricky terrain of rising costs and the quest for value. With no signs of prices plateauing anytime soon, the question on everyone’s mind is: How much are we willing to pay for our entertainment, and what are the alternatives? Apple’s bold move has undoubtedly set a precedent, and only time will tell how the market—and the consumers—will respond.</summary></entry></feed>