<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-11-07T17:14:35-05:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/11/07/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-11-07T17:14:35-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-07T17:14:35-05:00</updated><id>/2023/11/07/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/11/07/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/11/07/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-11-07T17:14:35-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-07T17:14:35-05:00</updated><id>/2023/11/07/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/11/07/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/">&lt;p&gt;Recent surprise attacks by Hamas on Israel has fueled ongoing tensions between staunchly conservative commentators and the progressive “Squad” Democrats known for criticizing Israel. The intensity of the backlash highlights the deep political divide over foreign policy in the Middle East.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Hamas’ shocking attack, several members of the “Squad,” including Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.), called for a “ceasefire and de-escalation,” condemning the violence. The absence of a statement from Rep. Rashida Tlaib (D-Mich.) was notably called out by conservative media outlets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;South Carolina GOP Rep. Nancy Mace quickly labeled Ocasio-Cortez a “Hamas apologist” in response to her call for peace and de-escalation. Rep. Ilhan Omar (D-Minn.), no stranger to controversy surrounding her views on Israel, echoed the call for de-escalation and ceasefire. Omar’s prior statements comparing the US and Israel to terrorist groups like Hamas and the Taliban resurfaced in the debate, fueling more criticisms. Omar’s 2019 tweet, where she opined that “Israel has hypnotized the world,” also continues to haunt her political career, often cited by critics to challenge her stance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conservative commentators have been especially vocal. “FOX &amp;amp; Friends Weekend” co-host Rachel Campos-Duffy took aim at Omar, saying she fails to recognize the peace in the Middle East under Trump’s administration. Conservative pundit John Hasson also called out Omar, claiming she insinuated that attacks on IDF forces were acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Massachusetts Democrat Rep. Ayanna Pressley’s concerns over the “devastating attacks on Israelis” were met with skepticism. A prominent conservative online personality, Comfortably Smug, accused the “Squad” of advising Israel to back down after the nation suffered massive attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Jamaal Bowman’s call for an end to the Gaza blockade, in addition to condemning the Hamas attacks, was met with criticism from conservative radio host Jason Rantz. He accused Bowman of pairing his condemnation of terrorism with unwarranted criticisms of Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Cori Bush emphasized the urgent need for a ceasefire, while pushing for an end to “U.S. support for Israeli military occupation and apartheid.” Defense attorney Marina Medvin criticized Bush, suggesting that she equates the death of Palestinian terrorists to the horrific acts committed against Jewish civilians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amidst the political turmoil and intense debate, the attacks have taken a heavy toll. Israeli media report over 300 dead due to the wide-ranging assault. Gaza health officials note that at least 200 Palestinians have perished in the retaliatory Israeli air strikes following the initial Hamas attack. As the situation remains volatile, both sides continue to count their casualties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This divisive issue showcases the challenge America faces in crafting a unified approach to foreign policy, with deeply entrenched political divides at play. As the situation develops, the debate is bound to intensify, shedding light on the complexities of U.S. politics in the global arena.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Quick Action by Capitol Police Thwarts Potential Threat Near U.S. Capitol</title><link href="/news/2023/11/07/AR-15-Arrest-Capitol/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Quick Action by Capitol Police Thwarts Potential Threat Near U.S. Capitol" /><published>2023-11-07T17:05:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-07T17:05:00-05:00</updated><id>/news/2023/11/07/AR-15-Arrest-Capitol</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/11/07/AR-15-Arrest-Capitol/">&lt;p&gt;U.S. Capitol Police swiftly arrested a man armed with an AR-15 near the U.S. Capitol on Tuesday afternoon, eliminating any potential threat to public safety. The individual was detained in the park opposite Union Station, a bustling hub adjacent to the Capitol complex.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The arrest came amid heightened alertness as Capitol Police officers responded to reports of a suspicious vehicle parked in the vicinity. The suspect’s swift apprehension speaks to the readiness and efficiency of law enforcement in securing the area, a reminder of the constant surveillance that protects the nation’s legislative center.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Authorities have assured the public that there appears to be no ongoing danger, as initial investigations suggest the individual was acting alone. This incident underscores the importance of continuous security measures and the need for prompt action in the face of potential risks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the Capitol Police worked to gather more information, they issued a cautionary notice, advising staff and visitors to steer clear of the area during the operation. The park was thoroughly searched, and the suspect’s belongings are being examined to ensure no additional threats remain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Capitol Police’s effective management of the situation averted disruptions to the congressional proceedings and maintained the sanctity of the Capitol grounds. The incident, while isolated, serves as a stark reminder of the challenges faced by security forces in today’s unpredictable environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the suspect securely in custody and the area deemed safe, Capitol Police continue their investigation to ascertain the motives behind the suspect’s presence and any potential connections to larger threats. Their proactive approach and transparent communication via social media provided timely updates, keeping the community informed and engaged.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The incident near the Capitol, though resolved without harm, highlights the critical role of law enforcement in maintaining peace and preventing potential crises. It exemplifies the dedication of the Capitol Police to the safety of all who work within and visit this key symbol of American democracy.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">U.S. Capitol Police swiftly arrested a man armed with an AR-15 near the U.S. Capitol on Tuesday afternoon, eliminating any potential threat to public safety. The individual was detained in the park opposite Union Station, a bustling hub adjacent to the Capitol complex. The arrest came amid heightened alertness as Capitol Police officers responded to reports of a suspicious vehicle parked in the vicinity. The suspect’s swift apprehension speaks to the readiness and efficiency of law enforcement in securing the area, a reminder of the constant surveillance that protects the nation’s legislative center. Authorities have assured the public that there appears to be no ongoing danger, as initial investigations suggest the individual was acting alone. This incident underscores the importance of continuous security measures and the need for prompt action in the face of potential risks. As the Capitol Police worked to gather more information, they issued a cautionary notice, advising staff and visitors to steer clear of the area during the operation. The park was thoroughly searched, and the suspect’s belongings are being examined to ensure no additional threats remain. Capitol Police’s effective management of the situation averted disruptions to the congressional proceedings and maintained the sanctity of the Capitol grounds. The incident, while isolated, serves as a stark reminder of the challenges faced by security forces in today’s unpredictable environment. With the suspect securely in custody and the area deemed safe, Capitol Police continue their investigation to ascertain the motives behind the suspect’s presence and any potential connections to larger threats. Their proactive approach and transparent communication via social media provided timely updates, keeping the community informed and engaged. The incident near the Capitol, though resolved without harm, highlights the critical role of law enforcement in maintaining peace and preventing potential crises. It exemplifies the dedication of the Capitol Police to the safety of all who work within and visit this key symbol of American democracy.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump’s Fortune Soars: A $500 Million Surge Since White House Departure</title><link href="/news/2023/11/07/Trump-Fortune-Growth/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump’s Fortune Soars: A $500 Million Surge Since White House Departure" /><published>2023-11-07T15:53:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-07T15:53:00-05:00</updated><id>/news/2023/11/07/Trump-Fortune-Growth</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/11/07/Trump-Fortune-Growth/">&lt;p&gt;In a striking testament to his enduring business savvy, former President Donald Trump’s net worth has seen a significant uptick, swelling by an impressive $500 million since he bid farewell to the Oval Office. According to the Bloomberg Billionaires Index, Trump’s financial clout now stands at a robust $3.1 billion, an ascension attributed largely to the surging real estate market in the Sunshine State.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The value of Trump’s iconic Mar-a-Lago in Palm Beach and the prestigious Doral golf resort in Miami have both benefitted from Florida’s property boom, contributing substantially to his wealth’s upward trajectory. With the sale of his storied Washington hotel and a strategic reduction of liabilities, Trump boasts a stronger cash position and a lighter debt load than he’s held over the past decade.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet, Bloomberg hints that Trump’s wealth could eclipse the current estimate of $3.1 billion. It concedes that factors such as the Trump brand’s influence, the historical significance of his holdings, and potential redevelopment or rezoning opportunities may significantly inflate property valuations. These considerations, in tandem with Trump’s strategic real estate moves, underscore his acumen as a property mogul with an unparalleled understanding of the market’s nuances.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s no secret that estimates of Trump’s wealth have been a point of contention, often diverging between his own assessments and those of external appraisers. While the New York Attorney General’s lawsuit against the former president pegs his wealth at a lower figure, real estate professionals in Palm Beach have voiced surprise at the undervaluation of Mar-a-Lago, suggesting it could command a market price well into the hundreds of millions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The debate extends to the valuation of Trump’s penthouse in Trump Tower, with Trump’s company asserting a value of $131.3 million in contrast to Bloomberg’s $40 million estimate and the lack of an official court assessment. The intricacies of New York real estate law allow for a broader interpretation of square footage, potentially inflating the size and worth of such a unique and iconic property.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adding to the complexity, any potential sale of Trump’s penthouse could fetch a premium, not solely due to its luxury but also the prestige associated with the Trump name. Trump supporters, in particular, might be willing to pay top dollar for a piece of the former president’s legacy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the Bloomberg Billionaires Index grapples with the fluid nature of real estate valuations, influenced by factors like interest rates and market trends, it acknowledges the possibility that Trump’s wealth could indeed align with his own claims — or even surpass them. This financial narrative is not just a reflection of numbers but also of Trump’s indelible mark on the real estate sector, a legacy that began reshaping New York’s skyline as early as the 1970s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the landscape of American entrepreneurship and real estate development, Trump’s increasing fortune is more than a figure — it’s a chapter in the storied history of a businessman who rose to the pinnacle of political power and continues to command a towering presence in both arenas.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a striking testament to his enduring business savvy, former President Donald Trump’s net worth has seen a significant uptick, swelling by an impressive $500 million since he bid farewell to the Oval Office. According to the Bloomberg Billionaires Index, Trump’s financial clout now stands at a robust $3.1 billion, an ascension attributed largely to the surging real estate market in the Sunshine State. The value of Trump’s iconic Mar-a-Lago in Palm Beach and the prestigious Doral golf resort in Miami have both benefitted from Florida’s property boom, contributing substantially to his wealth’s upward trajectory. With the sale of his storied Washington hotel and a strategic reduction of liabilities, Trump boasts a stronger cash position and a lighter debt load than he’s held over the past decade. Yet, Bloomberg hints that Trump’s wealth could eclipse the current estimate of $3.1 billion. It concedes that factors such as the Trump brand’s influence, the historical significance of his holdings, and potential redevelopment or rezoning opportunities may significantly inflate property valuations. These considerations, in tandem with Trump’s strategic real estate moves, underscore his acumen as a property mogul with an unparalleled understanding of the market’s nuances. It’s no secret that estimates of Trump’s wealth have been a point of contention, often diverging between his own assessments and those of external appraisers. While the New York Attorney General’s lawsuit against the former president pegs his wealth at a lower figure, real estate professionals in Palm Beach have voiced surprise at the undervaluation of Mar-a-Lago, suggesting it could command a market price well into the hundreds of millions. The debate extends to the valuation of Trump’s penthouse in Trump Tower, with Trump’s company asserting a value of $131.3 million in contrast to Bloomberg’s $40 million estimate and the lack of an official court assessment. The intricacies of New York real estate law allow for a broader interpretation of square footage, potentially inflating the size and worth of such a unique and iconic property. Adding to the complexity, any potential sale of Trump’s penthouse could fetch a premium, not solely due to its luxury but also the prestige associated with the Trump name. Trump supporters, in particular, might be willing to pay top dollar for a piece of the former president’s legacy. As the Bloomberg Billionaires Index grapples with the fluid nature of real estate valuations, influenced by factors like interest rates and market trends, it acknowledges the possibility that Trump’s wealth could indeed align with his own claims — or even surpass them. This financial narrative is not just a reflection of numbers but also of Trump’s indelible mark on the real estate sector, a legacy that began reshaping New York’s skyline as early as the 1970s. In the landscape of American entrepreneurship and real estate development, Trump’s increasing fortune is more than a figure — it’s a chapter in the storied history of a businessman who rose to the pinnacle of political power and continues to command a towering presence in both arenas.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump Dominates in GOP Polls: A Resounding Lead Over Republican Contenders</title><link href="/politics/2023/11/07/Trump-Lead-Poll/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump Dominates in GOP Polls: A Resounding Lead Over Republican Contenders" /><published>2023-11-07T14:42:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-07T14:42:00-05:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/11/07/Trump-Lead-Poll</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/11/07/Trump-Lead-Poll/">&lt;p&gt;As the clock ticks closer to the first Republican caucus in Iowa next year, a new CBS News poll has cemented former President Donald Trump’s formidable lead among GOP hopefuls. The survey, resonating with the conservative base, shows Trump’s robust standing with more than half of likely GOP primary voters ready to cast their vote in his favor today, should the opportunity arise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump’s staunch lead in the CBS poll underscores the unshakable loyalty and enthusiasm he commands within the Republican Party. With a whopping 61% of likely GOP primary voters backing him, Trump towers over Florida Governor Ron DeSantis, who currently stands at 18%, and former UN Ambassador Nikki Haley, who trails with 9%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The poll not only highlights Trump’s lead in primary preferences but also showcases his perceived electability against President Joe Biden in the 2024 election. A striking 69% of those surveyed believe Trump is the candidate most likely to reclaim the White House for the Republicans, further solidifying his frontrunner status.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The fervor among Trump supporters is palpable, with an overwhelming 81% expressing they would “enthusiastically support” him if he becomes the Republican nominee. This contrasts sharply with the 21% of likely GOP primary voters favoring other candidates who would share the same level of enthusiasm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While reservations and party loyalty always play a role in politics, the CBS poll indicates that Trump’s base remains unyielding. Not a single Trump supporter from the survey stated they would withdraw their support if he secures the nomination. In contrast, 18% of likely GOP voters who support a different candidate are firm on not voting for Trump in the 2024 presidential race even if he were the party’s choice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The CBS News and YouGov poll, conducted from October 31 to November 3, 2023, included a sample of 2,185 adult US residents and specifically honed in on 556 likely Republican primary voters. The margin of error stands at +/- 2.7 percentage points for the full sample and expands to +/- 5.5 percentage points for the subset of likely GOP primary voters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These numbers are a clear testament to the power and influence Trump continues to wield in the political arena. As the conservative community looks toward the upcoming election cycle, it’s evident that Trump’s leadership and vision still resonate deeply with a vast majority of Republican voters who are ready to march to the polls with his banner held high.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">As the clock ticks closer to the first Republican caucus in Iowa next year, a new CBS News poll has cemented former President Donald Trump’s formidable lead among GOP hopefuls. The survey, resonating with the conservative base, shows Trump’s robust standing with more than half of likely GOP primary voters ready to cast their vote in his favor today, should the opportunity arise. Trump’s staunch lead in the CBS poll underscores the unshakable loyalty and enthusiasm he commands within the Republican Party. With a whopping 61% of likely GOP primary voters backing him, Trump towers over Florida Governor Ron DeSantis, who currently stands at 18%, and former UN Ambassador Nikki Haley, who trails with 9%. The poll not only highlights Trump’s lead in primary preferences but also showcases his perceived electability against President Joe Biden in the 2024 election. A striking 69% of those surveyed believe Trump is the candidate most likely to reclaim the White House for the Republicans, further solidifying his frontrunner status. The fervor among Trump supporters is palpable, with an overwhelming 81% expressing they would “enthusiastically support” him if he becomes the Republican nominee. This contrasts sharply with the 21% of likely GOP primary voters favoring other candidates who would share the same level of enthusiasm. While reservations and party loyalty always play a role in politics, the CBS poll indicates that Trump’s base remains unyielding. Not a single Trump supporter from the survey stated they would withdraw their support if he secures the nomination. In contrast, 18% of likely GOP voters who support a different candidate are firm on not voting for Trump in the 2024 presidential race even if he were the party’s choice. The CBS News and YouGov poll, conducted from October 31 to November 3, 2023, included a sample of 2,185 adult US residents and specifically honed in on 556 likely Republican primary voters. The margin of error stands at +/- 2.7 percentage points for the full sample and expands to +/- 5.5 percentage points for the subset of likely GOP primary voters. These numbers are a clear testament to the power and influence Trump continues to wield in the political arena. As the conservative community looks toward the upcoming election cycle, it’s evident that Trump’s leadership and vision still resonate deeply with a vast majority of Republican voters who are ready to march to the polls with his banner held high.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">U.S. Private Payrolls Stumble: Unmasking the Democratic Leadership’s Failure</title><link href="/news/2023/11/07/Payroll-Miss-Due-to-Democratic-Leadership/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="U.S. Private Payrolls Stumble: Unmasking the Democratic Leadership’s Failure" /><published>2023-11-07T09:59:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-07T09:59:00-05:00</updated><id>/news/2023/11/07/Payroll-Miss-Due-to-Democratic-Leadership</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/11/07/Payroll-Miss-Due-to-Democratic-Leadership/">&lt;p&gt;U.S. private payrolls have significantly missed the mark this October, further exposing the ineptitude of the current Democratic leadership. The ADP National Employment Report revealed a paltry addition of 113,000 jobs last month, falling substantially short of the anticipated 150,000. This miss has sent shockwaves through the economy, casting a dark shadow on the Biden administration’s ability to manage our nation’s financial well-being.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For months, the American people have been promised a strong and resilient economy under Democratic leadership. Yet, time and time again, we are met with underperformance and excuses. The labor market, once a beacon of prosperity, is now showing signs of strain. While some may argue that the market remains tight, the consistent failure to meet payroll expectations tells a different story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Federal Reserve’s aggressive interest rate hikes, totaling 525 basis points since March 2022, were intended to bolster the economy. However, the effects have been anything but positive. Consumers’ views on the labor market, despite what the Conference Board may suggest, are dwindling. The Democratic leadership’s inability to navigate these tumultuous waters has left the American workforce in a state of uncertainty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This payroll miss is not just a number; it is a reflection of a larger issue at hand. The Biden administration’s policies and lack of foresight have direct consequences on the livelihoods of American citizens. The ongoing strikes by the United Auto Workers (UAW) union, resulting in at least 30,000 members off the job, are a testament to the unrest and dissatisfaction brewing under Democratic rule.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As we brace ourselves for the Labor Department’s upcoming employment report, it is crucial to remember that these numbers are not just statistics. They represent the lives and well-being of American workers. The anticipated slowdown in private payrolls, especially in manufacturing, is a direct result of the current administration’s failure to adequately address and resolve labor disputes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The time for accountability is now. The American people deserve a government that is committed to their prosperity and well-being. The underwhelming October payroll numbers are a stark reminder that the Democratic leadership is not up to the task. It is imperative that we demand better, hold our leaders accountable, and work towards a future where the American workforce is strong, resilient, and thriving.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the wake of this payroll miss, let us not forget the real victims here: the American workers. They deserve better than broken promises and missed expectations. They deserve a leadership that is committed to their success and a government that works for them. The October payroll numbers are a call to action, a plea for change, and a reminder that the time for Democratic rule must come to an end.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">U.S. private payrolls have significantly missed the mark this October, further exposing the ineptitude of the current Democratic leadership. The ADP National Employment Report revealed a paltry addition of 113,000 jobs last month, falling substantially short of the anticipated 150,000. This miss has sent shockwaves through the economy, casting a dark shadow on the Biden administration’s ability to manage our nation’s financial well-being. For months, the American people have been promised a strong and resilient economy under Democratic leadership. Yet, time and time again, we are met with underperformance and excuses. The labor market, once a beacon of prosperity, is now showing signs of strain. While some may argue that the market remains tight, the consistent failure to meet payroll expectations tells a different story. The Federal Reserve’s aggressive interest rate hikes, totaling 525 basis points since March 2022, were intended to bolster the economy. However, the effects have been anything but positive. Consumers’ views on the labor market, despite what the Conference Board may suggest, are dwindling. The Democratic leadership’s inability to navigate these tumultuous waters has left the American workforce in a state of uncertainty. This payroll miss is not just a number; it is a reflection of a larger issue at hand. The Biden administration’s policies and lack of foresight have direct consequences on the livelihoods of American citizens. The ongoing strikes by the United Auto Workers (UAW) union, resulting in at least 30,000 members off the job, are a testament to the unrest and dissatisfaction brewing under Democratic rule. As we brace ourselves for the Labor Department’s upcoming employment report, it is crucial to remember that these numbers are not just statistics. They represent the lives and well-being of American workers. The anticipated slowdown in private payrolls, especially in manufacturing, is a direct result of the current administration’s failure to adequately address and resolve labor disputes. The time for accountability is now. The American people deserve a government that is committed to their prosperity and well-being. The underwhelming October payroll numbers are a stark reminder that the Democratic leadership is not up to the task. It is imperative that we demand better, hold our leaders accountable, and work towards a future where the American workforce is strong, resilient, and thriving. In the wake of this payroll miss, let us not forget the real victims here: the American workers. They deserve better than broken promises and missed expectations. They deserve a leadership that is committed to their success and a government that works for them. The October payroll numbers are a call to action, a plea for change, and a reminder that the time for Democratic rule must come to an end.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Staggering Destructive Power of Pentagon’s New Gravity Bomb</title><link href="/news/2023/11/07/Gravity-Bomb-Threat/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Staggering Destructive Power of Pentagon’s New Gravity Bomb" /><published>2023-11-07T09:24:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-07T09:24:00-05:00</updated><id>/news/2023/11/07/Gravity-Bomb-Threat</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/11/07/Gravity-Bomb-Threat/">&lt;p&gt;In a world that seems to be on a perpetual edge of conflict, the Pentagon’s recent announcement about developing a new variant of the gravity bomb, the B61-13, sends a shiver down the spine of those who value peace and stability. This bomb isn’t just any addition to America’s military arsenal; it’s a colossal titan of destruction, capable of wiping out millions in a blink with a force 23 times that of the bomb dropped on Hiroshima.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Department of Defense paints this development as a move to “strengthen deterrence of adversaries and assurance of allies.” It’s a message clear as day to anyone paying attention: the United States intends to maintain its status as the apex military power with unmatched capabilities. The Biden administration asserts that such developments provide “additional options against certain harder and large-area military targets.” But the underlying tone is one of severe warning — to adversaries both veiled and overt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The gravity of the B61-13’s destructive capability is not lost on experts. Professor and historian of nuclear technology, Alex Wellerstein, offers a sobering visualization of the potential catastrophe. A theoretical detonation over Manhattan would result in upwards of 3.2 million casualties, decimating the population. Los Angeles, Chicago, Washington D.C.—no major city is spared in these harrowing scenarios. Each model tells a tale of unthinkable horror, with national icons like the White House and Capitol building reduced to dust alongside countless American lives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The stark reality of such weaponry can feel distant, but the implications are deeply personal. These bombs, though developed for deterrence, hold the stories of cities, of communities, of individual lives within their theoretical blast radii. For conservative audiences, the narrative is twofold: a strong national defense is imperative, yet the moral and ethical weight of wielding such power must be handled with the utmost responsibility and discernment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the world watches, questions about global security and the arms race resurface. The gravity bomb’s development may be a strategic move in the chessboard of international politics, but it’s a stark reminder of the devastating potential of nuclear weapons. The United States has always been a champion of strength, yet with strength comes the responsibility to lead with wisdom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The B61-13 gravity bomb symbolizes a crossroads — a choice between further armament and the search for lasting peace. It’s a choice that resonates with every American, conservative or otherwise, as the nation grapples with the role it plays on the global stage. The power to deter is also the power to destroy, and how the United States balances this dichotomy will define the future of international relations for years to come.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a world that seems to be on a perpetual edge of conflict, the Pentagon’s recent announcement about developing a new variant of the gravity bomb, the B61-13, sends a shiver down the spine of those who value peace and stability. This bomb isn’t just any addition to America’s military arsenal; it’s a colossal titan of destruction, capable of wiping out millions in a blink with a force 23 times that of the bomb dropped on Hiroshima. The Department of Defense paints this development as a move to “strengthen deterrence of adversaries and assurance of allies.” It’s a message clear as day to anyone paying attention: the United States intends to maintain its status as the apex military power with unmatched capabilities. The Biden administration asserts that such developments provide “additional options against certain harder and large-area military targets.” But the underlying tone is one of severe warning — to adversaries both veiled and overt. The gravity of the B61-13’s destructive capability is not lost on experts. Professor and historian of nuclear technology, Alex Wellerstein, offers a sobering visualization of the potential catastrophe. A theoretical detonation over Manhattan would result in upwards of 3.2 million casualties, decimating the population. Los Angeles, Chicago, Washington D.C.—no major city is spared in these harrowing scenarios. Each model tells a tale of unthinkable horror, with national icons like the White House and Capitol building reduced to dust alongside countless American lives. The stark reality of such weaponry can feel distant, but the implications are deeply personal. These bombs, though developed for deterrence, hold the stories of cities, of communities, of individual lives within their theoretical blast radii. For conservative audiences, the narrative is twofold: a strong national defense is imperative, yet the moral and ethical weight of wielding such power must be handled with the utmost responsibility and discernment. As the world watches, questions about global security and the arms race resurface. The gravity bomb’s development may be a strategic move in the chessboard of international politics, but it’s a stark reminder of the devastating potential of nuclear weapons. The United States has always been a champion of strength, yet with strength comes the responsibility to lead with wisdom. The B61-13 gravity bomb symbolizes a crossroads — a choice between further armament and the search for lasting peace. It’s a choice that resonates with every American, conservative or otherwise, as the nation grapples with the role it plays on the global stage. The power to deter is also the power to destroy, and how the United States balances this dichotomy will define the future of international relations for years to come.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Sanders Steps Into the Spotlight with Trump Endorsement</title><link href="/politics/2023/11/07/Endorsement-Showdown/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sanders Steps Into the Spotlight with Trump Endorsement" /><published>2023-11-07T08:10:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-07T08:10:00-05:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/11/07/Endorsement-Showdown</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/11/07/Endorsement-Showdown/">&lt;p&gt;As the 2024 presidential race heats up, a high-profile endorsement is making waves across the nation. Arkansas Governor Sarah Huckabee Sanders is set to endorse former President Donald Trump at a pivotal rally in Florida. This strategic move by Sanders aligns one of the GOP’s rising stars with Trump, who remains a dominant figure in Republican politics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sanders, known for her straight-shooting style as Trump’s White House press secretary, has been a key player in the conservative movement since her tenure in the White House. Her endorsement comes as Trump opts to hold a rally in Florida simultaneously with the third GOP presidential primary debate in Miami, sending a clear signal of his influence and drawing attention away from the debate stage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This endorsement is not just a boon for Trump; it also solidifies Sanders’ position within the Republican hierarchy. Her decision to back Trump before a single primary vote is cast illustrates the political calculus in the GOP, where Trump’s endorsement has proven to be gold dust in Republican primaries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sanders’ support could be seen as a snub to other high-profile Republican contenders like Florida Governor Ron DeSantis, who is widely seen as a potential challenger to Trump. DeSantis, despite not having formally announced a presidential bid, has been garnering significant endorsements, including that of Iowa Governor Kim Reynolds. The tussle for endorsements highlights the strategic battleground for the hearts and minds of Republican voters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The timing of Sanders’ endorsement also speaks volumes. Having remained neutral in the early stages of the primary race, her support for Trump at this juncture suggests a tactical play to consolidate the conservative base. Her rhetoric, sharply critical of President Biden’s policies, echoes the sentiment of a significant portion of the GOP base that yearns for a return to Trump-era policies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump, on his part, has welcomed Sanders’ endorsement, emphasizing their past success in the White House and expressing enthusiasm for her presence at the Florida rally. As Trump’s former press secretary, Sanders’ voice carries weight, and her decision to publicly back Trump solidifies her stance within the party’s pro-Trump faction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For conservative voters, Sanders’ endorsement reinforces the narrative of a “normal versus crazy” political landscape, a line often used to contrast Republican policies with those of the Democrats under Biden’s leadership. As the GOP navigates this divisive time, endorsements from prominent figures like Sanders will likely play a significant role in shaping the party’s future and the outcome of the 2024 presidential nomination.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the days to come, the spotlight will be on Sanders as she takes the stage in Florida, marking a defining moment in the 2024 race. Her backing of Trump sends a clear message to the Republican base and her political adversaries alike: the road to the GOP nomination still runs through Trump’s corner, with Sanders now firmly alongside him.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">As the 2024 presidential race heats up, a high-profile endorsement is making waves across the nation. Arkansas Governor Sarah Huckabee Sanders is set to endorse former President Donald Trump at a pivotal rally in Florida. This strategic move by Sanders aligns one of the GOP’s rising stars with Trump, who remains a dominant figure in Republican politics. Sanders, known for her straight-shooting style as Trump’s White House press secretary, has been a key player in the conservative movement since her tenure in the White House. Her endorsement comes as Trump opts to hold a rally in Florida simultaneously with the third GOP presidential primary debate in Miami, sending a clear signal of his influence and drawing attention away from the debate stage. This endorsement is not just a boon for Trump; it also solidifies Sanders’ position within the Republican hierarchy. Her decision to back Trump before a single primary vote is cast illustrates the political calculus in the GOP, where Trump’s endorsement has proven to be gold dust in Republican primaries. Sanders’ support could be seen as a snub to other high-profile Republican contenders like Florida Governor Ron DeSantis, who is widely seen as a potential challenger to Trump. DeSantis, despite not having formally announced a presidential bid, has been garnering significant endorsements, including that of Iowa Governor Kim Reynolds. The tussle for endorsements highlights the strategic battleground for the hearts and minds of Republican voters. The timing of Sanders’ endorsement also speaks volumes. Having remained neutral in the early stages of the primary race, her support for Trump at this juncture suggests a tactical play to consolidate the conservative base. Her rhetoric, sharply critical of President Biden’s policies, echoes the sentiment of a significant portion of the GOP base that yearns for a return to Trump-era policies. Trump, on his part, has welcomed Sanders’ endorsement, emphasizing their past success in the White House and expressing enthusiasm for her presence at the Florida rally. As Trump’s former press secretary, Sanders’ voice carries weight, and her decision to publicly back Trump solidifies her stance within the party’s pro-Trump faction. For conservative voters, Sanders’ endorsement reinforces the narrative of a “normal versus crazy” political landscape, a line often used to contrast Republican policies with those of the Democrats under Biden’s leadership. As the GOP navigates this divisive time, endorsements from prominent figures like Sanders will likely play a significant role in shaping the party’s future and the outcome of the 2024 presidential nomination. In the days to come, the spotlight will be on Sanders as she takes the stage in Florida, marking a defining moment in the 2024 race. Her backing of Trump sends a clear message to the Republican base and her political adversaries alike: the road to the GOP nomination still runs through Trump’s corner, with Sanders now firmly alongside him.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Greene’s Persistent Crusade: Calls for Censuring Tlaib Reignited</title><link href="/politics/2023/11/07/Censure-Call/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Greene’s Persistent Crusade: Calls for Censuring Tlaib Reignited" /><published>2023-11-07T07:01:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-07T07:01:00-05:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/11/07/Censure-Call</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/11/07/Censure-Call/">&lt;p&gt;In a renewed push to hold lawmakers accountable, Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene has reintroduced a fiery resolution to censure Rep. Rashida Tlaib for her statements on Israel. This move reflects a growing concern among conservatives over perceived antisemitism and the defense of free speech in Congress. Greene’s resolution underscores the high-stakes battle over Israel’s security and the implications of Tlaib’s rhetoric for U.S. ally relations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two weeks after her initial attempt, Greene, the Republican representative from Georgia, is not backing down. Her original resolution accused Tlaib, a Democrat from Michigan, of antisemitism and aligning with extremist views, sparking an intense debate in the House. Despite being voted down, Greene’s persistence in reintroducing the censure shows a commitment to addressing what many GOP members consider inflammatory and dangerous narratives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Greene’s resolution draws attention to Tlaib’s commentary following a Capitol sit-in by “Jewish Voice for Peace” activists protesting Israel’s policies. The action is labeled by Greene as an “illegal occupation,” marking a sharp turn from her earlier accusation of an “insurrection.” This language reflects Greene’s strategy to reframe the discourse around the sit-in and heighten the focus on Tlaib’s involvement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The resolution’s revival is a direct challenge to the 23 House Republicans who previously opposed the censure. Greene’s call to action questions their stance on freedom of speech, contrasting it with the decision to censure Rep. Adam Schiff. In a tweet, Greene pressed her GOP colleagues, emphasizing the need to “stand by our great friend and ally Israel” and condemn Tlaib’s actions, which some constituents view as tantamount to endorsing terrorism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Critics of Greene’s resolution, including some within her party, point to the essential American principle of free speech. Kentucky Rep. Thomas Massie articulated this view, defending the right to express dissenting opinions, a foundational element of democratic dialogue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This escalating situation encapsulates a broader conflict within American politics over the boundaries of free speech, the role of Israel in U.S. foreign policy, and the growing polarization between parties. As Greene seeks to navigate these turbulent waters, the outcome of her resolution could set a precedent for how Congress addresses the intersection of free speech and foreign policy criticism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the House prepares to vote, the conservative base is watching closely. The resolution’s success or failure may not only influence Tlaib’s political future but also shape the GOP’s approach to internal disagreements and their united front against antisemitism and perceived threats to national and international security. The implications for GOP unity and the handling of controversial speech in Congress are significant, making this a critical moment for Republican lawmakers and their constituents.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a renewed push to hold lawmakers accountable, Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene has reintroduced a fiery resolution to censure Rep. Rashida Tlaib for her statements on Israel. This move reflects a growing concern among conservatives over perceived antisemitism and the defense of free speech in Congress. Greene’s resolution underscores the high-stakes battle over Israel’s security and the implications of Tlaib’s rhetoric for U.S. ally relations. Two weeks after her initial attempt, Greene, the Republican representative from Georgia, is not backing down. Her original resolution accused Tlaib, a Democrat from Michigan, of antisemitism and aligning with extremist views, sparking an intense debate in the House. Despite being voted down, Greene’s persistence in reintroducing the censure shows a commitment to addressing what many GOP members consider inflammatory and dangerous narratives. Greene’s resolution draws attention to Tlaib’s commentary following a Capitol sit-in by “Jewish Voice for Peace” activists protesting Israel’s policies. The action is labeled by Greene as an “illegal occupation,” marking a sharp turn from her earlier accusation of an “insurrection.” This language reflects Greene’s strategy to reframe the discourse around the sit-in and heighten the focus on Tlaib’s involvement. The resolution’s revival is a direct challenge to the 23 House Republicans who previously opposed the censure. Greene’s call to action questions their stance on freedom of speech, contrasting it with the decision to censure Rep. Adam Schiff. In a tweet, Greene pressed her GOP colleagues, emphasizing the need to “stand by our great friend and ally Israel” and condemn Tlaib’s actions, which some constituents view as tantamount to endorsing terrorism. Critics of Greene’s resolution, including some within her party, point to the essential American principle of free speech. Kentucky Rep. Thomas Massie articulated this view, defending the right to express dissenting opinions, a foundational element of democratic dialogue. This escalating situation encapsulates a broader conflict within American politics over the boundaries of free speech, the role of Israel in U.S. foreign policy, and the growing polarization between parties. As Greene seeks to navigate these turbulent waters, the outcome of her resolution could set a precedent for how Congress addresses the intersection of free speech and foreign policy criticism. As the House prepares to vote, the conservative base is watching closely. The resolution’s success or failure may not only influence Tlaib’s political future but also shape the GOP’s approach to internal disagreements and their united front against antisemitism and perceived threats to national and international security. The implications for GOP unity and the handling of controversial speech in Congress are significant, making this a critical moment for Republican lawmakers and their constituents.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How Big Tech and Government Tag-Teamed to Muzzle Conservative Voices</title><link href="/news/2023/11/07/Censorship-Exposed/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How Big Tech and Government Tag-Teamed to Muzzle Conservative Voices" /><published>2023-11-07T06:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-07T06:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/news/2023/11/07/Censorship-Exposed</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/11/07/Censorship-Exposed/">&lt;p&gt;A bombshell revelation from Capitol Hill has ripped the lid off what many conservative Americans have long suspected: a covert alliance between Big Tech and the federal government to censor free speech ahead of the 2020 presidential election. A new report spearheaded by House Judiciary Committee Chair Jim Jordan pulls back the curtain on these clandestine operations, igniting a firestorm among free speech advocates and right-leaning citizens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This startling expose details how the Department of Homeland Security (DHS) fostered ties with an academic group at Stanford University, known as the Election Integrity Partnership (EIP), to monitor and manipulate the digital conversation. The internal communications and emails between EIP and DHS’s Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) outline a narrative that reads like a digital-age thriller, where powerful forces align to suppress and remove content from online platforms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the heart of this campaign, emails from leading figures in the cybersecurity and academic arenas reveal a strategic endeavor to guide the hand of Big Tech in suppressing certain viewpoints. One notable communication pinpoints how a high-ranking official at the Atlantic Council’s Digital Forensic Research Lab, a partner of the EIP, discussed CISA’s integral role in the censorship initiative.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ramifications of this are not just political — they strike at the very core of America’s cherished First Amendment rights. High-profile conservative figures, including then-President Donald Trump and other Republican politicians, found their social media content unjustly branded as ‘misinformation’. What is most concerning is that the report unveils a systematic approach to labelling conservative political content under the guise of combating ‘disinformation’, while similar content from the other end of the political spectrum remained unchallenged.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The House Judiciary’s interim report does more than just spotlight instances of bias; it underscores a disturbing trend of narrative control, one that sought to shape the political landscape by limiting the free exchange of ideas. The report argues that the disinformation label has been weaponized, frequently targeting conservative communities and opinions that diverge from mainstream narratives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In an era where digital platforms have become the modern public square, the implications of such censorship are vast and deeply troubling. The concerted efforts to silence voices on these platforms reveal a manipulation of public discourse and an affront to democratic principles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the revelations continue to stir controversy, the question of accountability looms large. While the agencies involved have denied overstepping their bounds, the evidence laid out paints a different picture — one where the balance of power tipped alarmingly towards silence and suppression.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For conservative Americans, the fight for free speech online has never been more pressing. The call to action is clear: it’s time to stand against the tides of censorship and champion the cause of liberty in our digital age. This report may have just sparked the beginning of a pivotal chapter in the ongoing battle for the soul of the internet.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">A bombshell revelation from Capitol Hill has ripped the lid off what many conservative Americans have long suspected: a covert alliance between Big Tech and the federal government to censor free speech ahead of the 2020 presidential election. A new report spearheaded by House Judiciary Committee Chair Jim Jordan pulls back the curtain on these clandestine operations, igniting a firestorm among free speech advocates and right-leaning citizens. This startling expose details how the Department of Homeland Security (DHS) fostered ties with an academic group at Stanford University, known as the Election Integrity Partnership (EIP), to monitor and manipulate the digital conversation. The internal communications and emails between EIP and DHS’s Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) outline a narrative that reads like a digital-age thriller, where powerful forces align to suppress and remove content from online platforms. At the heart of this campaign, emails from leading figures in the cybersecurity and academic arenas reveal a strategic endeavor to guide the hand of Big Tech in suppressing certain viewpoints. One notable communication pinpoints how a high-ranking official at the Atlantic Council’s Digital Forensic Research Lab, a partner of the EIP, discussed CISA’s integral role in the censorship initiative. The ramifications of this are not just political — they strike at the very core of America’s cherished First Amendment rights. High-profile conservative figures, including then-President Donald Trump and other Republican politicians, found their social media content unjustly branded as ‘misinformation’. What is most concerning is that the report unveils a systematic approach to labelling conservative political content under the guise of combating ‘disinformation’, while similar content from the other end of the political spectrum remained unchallenged. The House Judiciary’s interim report does more than just spotlight instances of bias; it underscores a disturbing trend of narrative control, one that sought to shape the political landscape by limiting the free exchange of ideas. The report argues that the disinformation label has been weaponized, frequently targeting conservative communities and opinions that diverge from mainstream narratives. In an era where digital platforms have become the modern public square, the implications of such censorship are vast and deeply troubling. The concerted efforts to silence voices on these platforms reveal a manipulation of public discourse and an affront to democratic principles. As the revelations continue to stir controversy, the question of accountability looms large. While the agencies involved have denied overstepping their bounds, the evidence laid out paints a different picture — one where the balance of power tipped alarmingly towards silence and suppression. For conservative Americans, the fight for free speech online has never been more pressing. The call to action is clear: it’s time to stand against the tides of censorship and champion the cause of liberty in our digital age. This report may have just sparked the beginning of a pivotal chapter in the ongoing battle for the soul of the internet.</summary></entry></feed>