<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-09-12T22:20:56-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/09/12/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-09-12T22:20:56-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-12T22:20:56-04:00</updated><id>/2023/09/12/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/12/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">NYPD Under Siege - Mayor Eric Adams Cuts Police Overtime Amid Mounting Challenges</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/12/NYC-Police-Overtime-Cut/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="NYPD Under Siege - Mayor Eric Adams Cuts Police Overtime Amid Mounting Challenges" /><published>2023-09-12T17:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-12T17:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/12/NYC-Police-Overtime-Cut</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/12/NYC-Police-Overtime-Cut/">&lt;p&gt;Under the pretext of addressing New York City’s growing migrant crisis, Mayor Eric Adams has taken a contentious step by slashing overtime pay for essential city departments, most notably for the police. This move comes at a time when the police department is already grappling with understaffing, reflecting a wider trend of miscalculated priorities in city leadership.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;policy-decisions-in-question&quot;&gt;Policy Decisions in Question&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the movement to reallocate police funding has gained some traction, the consequences of such decisions are manifesting on the streets. The NYPD, already under pressure from rising crime rates and budgetary constraints, now faces further challenges with the recent policy changes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“If City Hall wants to save money without jeopardizing public safety, it needs to invest in keeping experienced cops on the job,” states Patrick Hendry of the Police Benevolent Association, echoing the concerns of many.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;juggling-priorities-with-safety-at-stake&quot;&gt;Juggling Priorities with Safety at Stake&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rather than formulating comprehensive solutions to the migrant issue, Adams’ administration seems to have resorted to a short-sighted approach. The vast resources being directed towards migrant housing is starting to overshadow essential city services. While some migrants might express satisfaction with their housing amenities in NYC, it begs the question: at what cost? The balance between fiscal responsibility and maintaining public safety seems to be tipping in an unfavorable direction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moreover, the lack of a coherent strategy in managing the influx is evident in Mayor Adams’ varied descriptions of the situation - from a “financial tsunami” to the potential risks in shelters. The reactive nature of these policies points to a lack of foresight and strategic planning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-call-for-thoughtful-governance&quot;&gt;A Call for Thoughtful Governance&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cities like New York need leadership that places safety, security, and fiscal prudence at the forefront. Addressing the migrant crisis with humane and effective solutions is vital, but not at the expense of public safety.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mayor Adams’ recent decisions underscore the challenges of city governance, where abstract ideals can sometimes overshadow the practical needs of the people. NYC residents deserve well-thought-out policies that prioritize their well-being.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Under the pretext of addressing New York City’s growing migrant crisis, Mayor Eric Adams has taken a contentious step by slashing overtime pay for essential city departments, most notably for the police. This move comes at a time when the police department is already grappling with understaffing, reflecting a wider trend of miscalculated priorities in city leadership. Policy Decisions in Question While the movement to reallocate police funding has gained some traction, the consequences of such decisions are manifesting on the streets. The NYPD, already under pressure from rising crime rates and budgetary constraints, now faces further challenges with the recent policy changes. “If City Hall wants to save money without jeopardizing public safety, it needs to invest in keeping experienced cops on the job,” states Patrick Hendry of the Police Benevolent Association, echoing the concerns of many. Juggling Priorities with Safety at Stake Rather than formulating comprehensive solutions to the migrant issue, Adams’ administration seems to have resorted to a short-sighted approach. The vast resources being directed towards migrant housing is starting to overshadow essential city services. While some migrants might express satisfaction with their housing amenities in NYC, it begs the question: at what cost? The balance between fiscal responsibility and maintaining public safety seems to be tipping in an unfavorable direction. Moreover, the lack of a coherent strategy in managing the influx is evident in Mayor Adams’ varied descriptions of the situation - from a “financial tsunami” to the potential risks in shelters. The reactive nature of these policies points to a lack of foresight and strategic planning. A Call for Thoughtful Governance Cities like New York need leadership that places safety, security, and fiscal prudence at the forefront. Addressing the migrant crisis with humane and effective solutions is vital, but not at the expense of public safety. Mayor Adams’ recent decisions underscore the challenges of city governance, where abstract ideals can sometimes overshadow the practical needs of the people. NYC residents deserve well-thought-out policies that prioritize their well-being.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Desperate Days for Pennsylvania Fugitive</title><link href="/news/2023/09/12/Desperate-Escape/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Desperate Days for Pennsylvania Fugitive" /><published>2023-09-12T16:01:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-12T16:01:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/12/Desperate-Escape</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/12/Desperate-Escape/">&lt;p&gt;As days go by, the desperation seems to grow for Danelo Cavalcante, a fugitive in Pennsylvania who has been evading authorities for almost two weeks. Pennsylvania police indicate that their net might be closing in, but Cavalcante is pulling out all stops to remain a step ahead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cavalcante’s escape from Chester County Prison, near Philadelphia, took place on August 31, following his conviction for the murder of his ex-girlfriend in 2021. The 34-year-old’s tactics to remain hidden seem to grow more daring with each passing day. Not only did he manage to slip past a heavily guarded police perimeter around Longwood Gardens botanical park, but he also took the audacious step of reaching out to former colleagues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2023/09/720/405/Danelo-Cavalcante-clean-shaven-thumb.jpg?ve=1&amp;amp;tl=1&quot; alt=&quot;Manhunt Continues&quot; /&gt;(Pennsylvania State Police / Chester County Prison)
&lt;em&gt;The search intensifies as Cavalcante’s desperation becomes evident.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lt. Col. George Bivens of the Pennsylvania State Police weighed in on the situation. “His actions speak volumes about his desperation,” Bivens said. “It seems there wasn’t much premeditation in his escape. He’s now on the run, possibly without a strong support system, given that he’s reaching out to people he hasn’t been in touch with for a long time.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A recent encounter provides a glimpse into his current situation. Cavalcante altered his appearance, stole a van from a dairy farm, and drove over 20 miles, reaching out to two of his former co-workers in East Pikeland Township and Phoenixville. His changed look, comprising a clean shave, a colored hoodie, green prison pants, and white shoes, was captured on a doorbell camera.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2023/09/720/405/Cavalcante.jpg?ve=1&amp;amp;tl=1&quot; alt=&quot;Surveillance Image&quot; /&gt;(AP Photo/Matt Rourke)
&lt;em&gt;Security footage aids law enforcement in tracking Cavalcante’s movements.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a twist, immigration authorities have detained Eleni Cavalcante, the fugitive’s sister. However, she seems less than inclined to assist in tracking her brother down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cavalcante’s escape has had repercussions for prison staff as well. The guard on duty during Cavalcante’s dramatic exit – seen on surveillance footage as he adeptly crab-walked a wall in the prison yard – has been dismissed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Authorities remain on high alert, given Cavalcante’s history. “Given his background, it’s only prudent to assume he might be armed and dangerous,” Bivens commented.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back in his native Brazil, Cavalcante is no stranger to the law. He’s sought for a “double qualified homicide” over a vehicle repair-related debt that culminated in the death of Válter Júnior Moreira dos Reis in 2017.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the manhunt intensifies, the central message from the authorities remains clear: aiding Cavalcante in any form could have dire consequences, and the desperate fugitive should be approached with utmost caution.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">As days go by, the desperation seems to grow for Danelo Cavalcante, a fugitive in Pennsylvania who has been evading authorities for almost two weeks. Pennsylvania police indicate that their net might be closing in, but Cavalcante is pulling out all stops to remain a step ahead. Cavalcante’s escape from Chester County Prison, near Philadelphia, took place on August 31, following his conviction for the murder of his ex-girlfriend in 2021. The 34-year-old’s tactics to remain hidden seem to grow more daring with each passing day. Not only did he manage to slip past a heavily guarded police perimeter around Longwood Gardens botanical park, but he also took the audacious step of reaching out to former colleagues. (Pennsylvania State Police / Chester County Prison) The search intensifies as Cavalcante’s desperation becomes evident. Lt. Col. George Bivens of the Pennsylvania State Police weighed in on the situation. “His actions speak volumes about his desperation,” Bivens said. “It seems there wasn’t much premeditation in his escape. He’s now on the run, possibly without a strong support system, given that he’s reaching out to people he hasn’t been in touch with for a long time.” A recent encounter provides a glimpse into his current situation. Cavalcante altered his appearance, stole a van from a dairy farm, and drove over 20 miles, reaching out to two of his former co-workers in East Pikeland Township and Phoenixville. His changed look, comprising a clean shave, a colored hoodie, green prison pants, and white shoes, was captured on a doorbell camera. (AP Photo/Matt Rourke) Security footage aids law enforcement in tracking Cavalcante’s movements. In a twist, immigration authorities have detained Eleni Cavalcante, the fugitive’s sister. However, she seems less than inclined to assist in tracking her brother down. Cavalcante’s escape has had repercussions for prison staff as well. The guard on duty during Cavalcante’s dramatic exit – seen on surveillance footage as he adeptly crab-walked a wall in the prison yard – has been dismissed. Authorities remain on high alert, given Cavalcante’s history. “Given his background, it’s only prudent to assume he might be armed and dangerous,” Bivens commented. Back in his native Brazil, Cavalcante is no stranger to the law. He’s sought for a “double qualified homicide” over a vehicle repair-related debt that culminated in the death of Válter Júnior Moreira dos Reis in 2017. While the manhunt intensifies, the central message from the authorities remains clear: aiding Cavalcante in any form could have dire consequences, and the desperate fugitive should be approached with utmost caution.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Fact Check - Did Biden Visit Ground Zero on September 12, 2001?</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/12/Biden-Ground-Zero-Claim/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Fact Check - Did Biden Visit Ground Zero on September 12, 2001?" /><published>2023-09-12T15:02:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-12T15:02:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/12/Biden-Ground-Zero-Claim</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/12/Biden-Ground-Zero-Claim/">&lt;p&gt;President Joe Biden, during a recent address at Joint Base Elmendorf-Richardson in Anchorage, Alaska, made a claim that raised eyebrows. He stated that he was present at Ground Zero in New York City on September 12, 2001, a day after the horrific attacks on the World Trade Centers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I remember standing there the next day and looking at the building,” the President recollected. The vivid description he offered was as if “looking through the gates of hell.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, records and archival material from that time tell a different story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On September 12, 2001, Biden, then a U.S. Senator, was with his Senate colleagues and delivered a 10-minute speech addressing the attacks. He was recorded stating, “Some have said, yesterday and today, that all has changed for America… but I pray that is not true … the one thing we cannot allow to change are the values upon which this country is built, for if that were to occur, then they would be able to declare victory.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Additionally, Biden, in unity with all his Senate colleagues, voted to pass a resolution that officially condemned the acts of terror on that fateful day. It wasn’t until September 20, 2001, that Biden made his first confirmed visit to Ground Zero, joining a group of senators to witness the aftermath of the terror strike.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These inconsistencies have brought Biden’s comments under scrutiny. Furthermore, Biden’s decision to commemorate the 9/11 anniversary in Alaska, instead of at the actual attack sites in New York City, Virginia, or Pennsylvania, has also generated debate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given the sensitive nature and the magnitude of the events surrounding 9/11, it remains essential to maintain the accuracy of accounts related to it. As the nation remembers and pays tribute to the lives lost, ensuring a factual retelling of events honors their memory.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">President Joe Biden, during a recent address at Joint Base Elmendorf-Richardson in Anchorage, Alaska, made a claim that raised eyebrows. He stated that he was present at Ground Zero in New York City on September 12, 2001, a day after the horrific attacks on the World Trade Centers. “I remember standing there the next day and looking at the building,” the President recollected. The vivid description he offered was as if “looking through the gates of hell.” However, records and archival material from that time tell a different story. On September 12, 2001, Biden, then a U.S. Senator, was with his Senate colleagues and delivered a 10-minute speech addressing the attacks. He was recorded stating, “Some have said, yesterday and today, that all has changed for America… but I pray that is not true … the one thing we cannot allow to change are the values upon which this country is built, for if that were to occur, then they would be able to declare victory.” Additionally, Biden, in unity with all his Senate colleagues, voted to pass a resolution that officially condemned the acts of terror on that fateful day. It wasn’t until September 20, 2001, that Biden made his first confirmed visit to Ground Zero, joining a group of senators to witness the aftermath of the terror strike. These inconsistencies have brought Biden’s comments under scrutiny. Furthermore, Biden’s decision to commemorate the 9/11 anniversary in Alaska, instead of at the actual attack sites in New York City, Virginia, or Pennsylvania, has also generated debate. Given the sensitive nature and the magnitude of the events surrounding 9/11, it remains essential to maintain the accuracy of accounts related to it. As the nation remembers and pays tribute to the lives lost, ensuring a factual retelling of events honors their memory.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The AI Detection Dilemma - ChatGPT Developer Spills the Beans</title><link href="/news/2023/09/12/AI-Detection-Fallacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The AI Detection Dilemma - ChatGPT Developer Spills the Beans" /><published>2023-09-12T14:05:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-12T14:05:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/12/AI-Detection-Fallacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/12/AI-Detection-Fallacy/">&lt;p&gt;OpenAI, the genius minds behind the widely-used AI chatbot ChatGPT, recently dropped a truth bomb on the tech community. AI writing detectors, hailed as the tools of the future, aren’t as adept at their jobs as we once believed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to a disclosure in an FAQ section attached to an educational promotional blog, OpenAI confirmed a long-held suspicion within the industry - AI writing detectors are underperformers. “While some organizations, including ours, have rolled out tools claiming to detect AI-generated content, none have consistently demonstrated an ability to distinguish AI-written text from human prose,” stated OpenAI.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This news isn’t entirely a shock. Detectors, earlier labeled as “mostly illusionary solutions,” have been under the scanner for often marking false positives. Their shaky credibility arises from their dependency on untested detection methods. OpenAI’s short-lived experiment, the AI Classifier, intended to spot AI-crafted content, was discarded after a lackluster performance rate of 26%. This debacle draws even more attention when considering that certain educators have failed whole student batches, accusing them of employing ChatGPT for academic essays.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;OpenAI’s FAQ further dispelled a widespread myth: ChatGPT’s capability to recognize AI-generated content. The company clarified, “ChatGPT doesn’t possess the ‘awareness’ to determine if a text is AI-created. Its answers to queries such as ‘did you pen this [paper]?’ or ‘could AI have authored this?’ are whimsical and lack factual grounding.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The firm also advised against exclusively depending on ChatGPT for research-oriented tasks. “ChatGPT may sound persuasive at times, but it can occasionally relay incorrect or misleading data (often termed a ‘hallucination’ in scholarly circles),” OpenAI warned. This advisory emerges after a lawyer cited non-existent legal cases, misled by ChatGPT’s responses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet, all’s not lost. While automated AI sniffers might falter, human discernment remains invaluable. Educators acquainted with a student’s writing flair can frequently spot abrupt shifts. Additionally, certain AI-generated content, especially from ChatGPT, can betray itself with characteristic hints, such as repetitive phrases, hinting at a copy-paste job.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">OpenAI, the genius minds behind the widely-used AI chatbot ChatGPT, recently dropped a truth bomb on the tech community. AI writing detectors, hailed as the tools of the future, aren’t as adept at their jobs as we once believed. According to a disclosure in an FAQ section attached to an educational promotional blog, OpenAI confirmed a long-held suspicion within the industry - AI writing detectors are underperformers. “While some organizations, including ours, have rolled out tools claiming to detect AI-generated content, none have consistently demonstrated an ability to distinguish AI-written text from human prose,” stated OpenAI. This news isn’t entirely a shock. Detectors, earlier labeled as “mostly illusionary solutions,” have been under the scanner for often marking false positives. Their shaky credibility arises from their dependency on untested detection methods. OpenAI’s short-lived experiment, the AI Classifier, intended to spot AI-crafted content, was discarded after a lackluster performance rate of 26%. This debacle draws even more attention when considering that certain educators have failed whole student batches, accusing them of employing ChatGPT for academic essays. OpenAI’s FAQ further dispelled a widespread myth: ChatGPT’s capability to recognize AI-generated content. The company clarified, “ChatGPT doesn’t possess the ‘awareness’ to determine if a text is AI-created. Its answers to queries such as ‘did you pen this [paper]?’ or ‘could AI have authored this?’ are whimsical and lack factual grounding.” The firm also advised against exclusively depending on ChatGPT for research-oriented tasks. “ChatGPT may sound persuasive at times, but it can occasionally relay incorrect or misleading data (often termed a ‘hallucination’ in scholarly circles),” OpenAI warned. This advisory emerges after a lawyer cited non-existent legal cases, misled by ChatGPT’s responses. Yet, all’s not lost. While automated AI sniffers might falter, human discernment remains invaluable. Educators acquainted with a student’s writing flair can frequently spot abrupt shifts. Additionally, certain AI-generated content, especially from ChatGPT, can betray itself with characteristic hints, such as repetitive phrases, hinting at a copy-paste job.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">RFK Jr.’s Warning - Is the DNC Trying to Silence Opposition?</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/12/DNC-RFK-Campaign/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="RFK Jr.’s Warning - Is the DNC Trying to Silence Opposition?" /><published>2023-09-12T13:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-12T13:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/12/DNC-RFK-Campaign</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/12/DNC-RFK-Campaign/">&lt;p&gt;The road to the 2024 presidential nomination is shaping up to be a contentious one for Robert F. Kennedy Jr. His campaign recently sounded the alarm on what they believe to be an overt attempt by the Democratic National Committee (DNC) to stifle his bid against President Joe Biden.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Former Rep. Dennis Kucinich, D-Ohio, who is currently steering the Kennedy campaign, recently pointed out that the DNC seems to have established a class of pledged delegates named Party Leaders and Elected Officials (PLEOs). According to Kucinich, these PLEOs bear a striking resemblance to super delegates, given the influence the party has over them. “The repositioning of these delegates puts the DNC in a spot where it could override the popular vote,” Kucinich stated, emphasizing the gravity of potentially ignoring the voice of the masses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reordering of state primaries by the DNC, aimed at penalizing states that did not cast their votes in Biden’s favor in the 2020 elections, also came under scrutiny. Kennedy’s campaign has cautioned that such a move could discount the votes of millions, making mail-in voting the only option for many more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This isn’t the first time the DNC has been embroiled in such controversies. Observers can’t help but recall 2016 when there were allegations of the DNC favoring Hillary Clinton over Bernie Sanders. Kennedy, sharing his dismay on Fox News, mentioned, “They are even pondering making me foot the bill for the primaries.” He further criticized the DNC’s logic, suggesting they believe there’s no need for a primary when a candidate is already in place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Biden’s recent reshuffling of the 2024 primary schedule, placing South Carolina at the forefront on Feb. 3, is another significant point of contention. The DNC’s strict guidelines dictate that states not adhering to this altered schedule could face penalties, with a deduction of half their delegates at the national convention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kucinich, echoing the sentiments of many, has reached out to DNC Chair Jaime Harrison twice in the past week, seeking a conversation between Kennedy and Harrison. The aim is to emphasize the importance of voter rights and safeguarding the voice of the populace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Discussing the topic further on Fox News’ “Jesse Watters Prime Time,” Kucinich stated, “Mr. Kennedy’s sole objective is to ensure that every single Democrat vote in the primaries holds weight.” Highlighting the questionable tactics of the DNC, Kucinich expressed fears that even if Kennedy received a significant majority of votes, the DNC’s positioning of extra delegates could still sway the result in Biden’s favor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further aggravating the situation, the DNC’s decision to abstain from hosting debates between Democratic candidates has caused alarm. Both Marianne Williamson and Kennedy, the Democrats challenging Biden, have voiced their concerns on this matter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The unfolding situation puts the spotlight on the DNC’s actions and decisions leading up to the 2024 elections. Only time will tell how this will impact the race and, more importantly, the voters’ faith in the democratic process.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">The road to the 2024 presidential nomination is shaping up to be a contentious one for Robert F. Kennedy Jr. His campaign recently sounded the alarm on what they believe to be an overt attempt by the Democratic National Committee (DNC) to stifle his bid against President Joe Biden. Former Rep. Dennis Kucinich, D-Ohio, who is currently steering the Kennedy campaign, recently pointed out that the DNC seems to have established a class of pledged delegates named Party Leaders and Elected Officials (PLEOs). According to Kucinich, these PLEOs bear a striking resemblance to super delegates, given the influence the party has over them. “The repositioning of these delegates puts the DNC in a spot where it could override the popular vote,” Kucinich stated, emphasizing the gravity of potentially ignoring the voice of the masses. The reordering of state primaries by the DNC, aimed at penalizing states that did not cast their votes in Biden’s favor in the 2020 elections, also came under scrutiny. Kennedy’s campaign has cautioned that such a move could discount the votes of millions, making mail-in voting the only option for many more. This isn’t the first time the DNC has been embroiled in such controversies. Observers can’t help but recall 2016 when there were allegations of the DNC favoring Hillary Clinton over Bernie Sanders. Kennedy, sharing his dismay on Fox News, mentioned, “They are even pondering making me foot the bill for the primaries.” He further criticized the DNC’s logic, suggesting they believe there’s no need for a primary when a candidate is already in place. Biden’s recent reshuffling of the 2024 primary schedule, placing South Carolina at the forefront on Feb. 3, is another significant point of contention. The DNC’s strict guidelines dictate that states not adhering to this altered schedule could face penalties, with a deduction of half their delegates at the national convention. Kucinich, echoing the sentiments of many, has reached out to DNC Chair Jaime Harrison twice in the past week, seeking a conversation between Kennedy and Harrison. The aim is to emphasize the importance of voter rights and safeguarding the voice of the populace. Discussing the topic further on Fox News’ “Jesse Watters Prime Time,” Kucinich stated, “Mr. Kennedy’s sole objective is to ensure that every single Democrat vote in the primaries holds weight.” Highlighting the questionable tactics of the DNC, Kucinich expressed fears that even if Kennedy received a significant majority of votes, the DNC’s positioning of extra delegates could still sway the result in Biden’s favor. Further aggravating the situation, the DNC’s decision to abstain from hosting debates between Democratic candidates has caused alarm. Both Marianne Williamson and Kennedy, the Democrats challenging Biden, have voiced their concerns on this matter. The unfolding situation puts the spotlight on the DNC’s actions and decisions leading up to the 2024 elections. Only time will tell how this will impact the race and, more importantly, the voters’ faith in the democratic process.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Iconic ‘Halloween’ Movie House Hits the Market</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/12/Halloween-House-Sale/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Iconic ‘Halloween’ Movie House Hits the Market" /><published>2023-09-12T12:02:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-12T12:02:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/12/Halloween-House-Sale</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/12/Halloween-House-Sale/">&lt;p&gt;For fans of the legendary horror film “Halloween,” a unique opportunity has arisen. The infamous Pasadena home that served as the backdrop for Laurie Strode’s (played by Jamie Lee Curtis) nightmarish encounters with the relentless Michael Meyers is now listed for sale.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This iconic property, which provided the setting for the chilling events of Haddonfield, Illinois, in the 1978 movie, has remained with one family for three generations. Now, according to the New York Daily News, it awaits a new owner with a listed price of $1.799 million.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The realtor’s description emphasizes the home’s cinematic significance, drawing attention to its familiar stoop: “If you watch the film, you’ll recognize the infamous stoop that Jamie Lee Curtis sat on, holding a pumpkin.” But beyond its filmic connections, the house has undergone transformations over the years. Originally portrayed as a single-family residence, it has since been subdivided into three separate units.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The property also boasts a historic fruit-bearing avocado tree, a remnant from the 1940s, planted by the sellers’ grandfather. This detail provides a touch of nostalgia to the otherwise eerie history of the home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jamie Lee Curtis, now 64, has an intimate bond with the Halloween series, crediting it with many positive turns in her life. Reflecting on her connection to Laurie, she told People magazine, “everything good in my life can be traced back to Laurie.” Curtis even recalls spotting her now-husband of 37 years, Christopher Guest, in a 1984 Rolling Stone article while she was with Debra Hill, the writer of the original Halloween. “Life is scary. But Laurie taught me that life can also be beautiful, filled with love and art and life!” Curtis expressed, cherishing her role’s impact on her personal and professional journey.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The so-called “murder house” wasn’t only featured in the original film. It made a return in the 2021 sequel, “Halloween Kills,” where a harrowing scene involving firefighters unfolds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Realtor Heidi Babcock captures the allure of this unique listing, stating, “This exceptional property is a wonderful place to live, work, and play in one of the most desirable communities in greater LA.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For horror aficionados or fans of cinematic history, this property presents a once-in-a-lifetime chance. Who will be the next to claim this piece of Hollywood horror legacy?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">For fans of the legendary horror film “Halloween,” a unique opportunity has arisen. The infamous Pasadena home that served as the backdrop for Laurie Strode’s (played by Jamie Lee Curtis) nightmarish encounters with the relentless Michael Meyers is now listed for sale. This iconic property, which provided the setting for the chilling events of Haddonfield, Illinois, in the 1978 movie, has remained with one family for three generations. Now, according to the New York Daily News, it awaits a new owner with a listed price of $1.799 million. The realtor’s description emphasizes the home’s cinematic significance, drawing attention to its familiar stoop: “If you watch the film, you’ll recognize the infamous stoop that Jamie Lee Curtis sat on, holding a pumpkin.” But beyond its filmic connections, the house has undergone transformations over the years. Originally portrayed as a single-family residence, it has since been subdivided into three separate units. The property also boasts a historic fruit-bearing avocado tree, a remnant from the 1940s, planted by the sellers’ grandfather. This detail provides a touch of nostalgia to the otherwise eerie history of the home. Jamie Lee Curtis, now 64, has an intimate bond with the Halloween series, crediting it with many positive turns in her life. Reflecting on her connection to Laurie, she told People magazine, “everything good in my life can be traced back to Laurie.” Curtis even recalls spotting her now-husband of 37 years, Christopher Guest, in a 1984 Rolling Stone article while she was with Debra Hill, the writer of the original Halloween. “Life is scary. But Laurie taught me that life can also be beautiful, filled with love and art and life!” Curtis expressed, cherishing her role’s impact on her personal and professional journey. The so-called “murder house” wasn’t only featured in the original film. It made a return in the 2021 sequel, “Halloween Kills,” where a harrowing scene involving firefighters unfolds. Realtor Heidi Babcock captures the allure of this unique listing, stating, “This exceptional property is a wonderful place to live, work, and play in one of the most desirable communities in greater LA.” For horror aficionados or fans of cinematic history, this property presents a once-in-a-lifetime chance. Who will be the next to claim this piece of Hollywood horror legacy?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Waltz Warns - The Danger of Iran Prisoner Swaps</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/12/Hostage-Incentive-Iran/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Waltz Warns - The Danger of Iran Prisoner Swaps" /><published>2023-09-12T11:06:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-12T11:06:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/12/Hostage-Incentive-Iran</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/12/Hostage-Incentive-Iran/">&lt;p&gt;In a candid conversation with “Rob Schmitt Tonight,” Rep. Michael Waltz, R-Fla., voiced his concerns regarding the United States’ recent decision to partake in prisoner swaps with Iran. Highlighting the potential repercussions of such moves, Waltz emphasized that this could unintentionally encourage more hostage-taking incidents by hostile entities in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Waltz, expressing his sympathy and heartbreak for the affected families, recounted an earlier incident in 2015 involving the Iran deal. “One of these hostages was left behind back in 2015 with the original Iran deal. John Kerry, [Then-Secretary of State], was promised the hostage’s release. However, even after the hostage remained in captivity, Kerry went ahead and signed the deal.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Drawing parallels with the current scenario, Waltz expressed his concerns: “The problem with this deal is that future Americans are at risk of being taken hostage all over again.” Waltz’s argument is based on a simple yet concerning principle: When nations like the US give in to the demands of hostage-takers, it provides a strong incentive for other hostile actors, whether they are nations like Iran or Russia, or even terrorist groups, to follow suit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He further added, “There’s no downside for these hostage-takers. In most scenarios, they find themselves in advantageous positions, either financially or through swaps.” Drawing attention to a recent swap involving the world’s largest arms dealer for Brittney Griner, Waltz underlined the troubling pattern that seems to be emerging.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adding another layer to his criticism, Waltz voiced his concerns regarding the lack of transparency from the current administration. “This is just a horrific deal. Despite being a member of both the Intelligence Committee and the Foreign Affairs Committee, we are still in the dark about who these Iranians are that Biden’s administration is releasing.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Decisions involving prisoner swaps are always delicate, with multiple facets to consider. Yet, Waltz’s caution serves as a reminder that, while the immediate resolution of a crisis is paramount, it’s equally essential to consider the long-term implications of such decisions. The well-being and safety of future American citizens overseas might very well depend on the choices made today.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a candid conversation with “Rob Schmitt Tonight,” Rep. Michael Waltz, R-Fla., voiced his concerns regarding the United States’ recent decision to partake in prisoner swaps with Iran. Highlighting the potential repercussions of such moves, Waltz emphasized that this could unintentionally encourage more hostage-taking incidents by hostile entities in the future. Waltz, expressing his sympathy and heartbreak for the affected families, recounted an earlier incident in 2015 involving the Iran deal. “One of these hostages was left behind back in 2015 with the original Iran deal. John Kerry, [Then-Secretary of State], was promised the hostage’s release. However, even after the hostage remained in captivity, Kerry went ahead and signed the deal.” Drawing parallels with the current scenario, Waltz expressed his concerns: “The problem with this deal is that future Americans are at risk of being taken hostage all over again.” Waltz’s argument is based on a simple yet concerning principle: When nations like the US give in to the demands of hostage-takers, it provides a strong incentive for other hostile actors, whether they are nations like Iran or Russia, or even terrorist groups, to follow suit. He further added, “There’s no downside for these hostage-takers. In most scenarios, they find themselves in advantageous positions, either financially or through swaps.” Drawing attention to a recent swap involving the world’s largest arms dealer for Brittney Griner, Waltz underlined the troubling pattern that seems to be emerging. Adding another layer to his criticism, Waltz voiced his concerns regarding the lack of transparency from the current administration. “This is just a horrific deal. Despite being a member of both the Intelligence Committee and the Foreign Affairs Committee, we are still in the dark about who these Iranians are that Biden’s administration is releasing.” Decisions involving prisoner swaps are always delicate, with multiple facets to consider. Yet, Waltz’s caution serves as a reminder that, while the immediate resolution of a crisis is paramount, it’s equally essential to consider the long-term implications of such decisions. The well-being and safety of future American citizens overseas might very well depend on the choices made today.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Rising Concerns - 1 in 5 Workers Fear Tech Will Make Their Jobs Extinct</title><link href="/news/2023/09/12/Technology-Job-Obsolescence/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rising Concerns - 1 in 5 Workers Fear Tech Will Make Their Jobs Extinct" /><published>2023-09-12T10:01:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-12T10:01:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/12/Technology-Job-Obsolescence</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/12/Technology-Job-Obsolescence/">&lt;p&gt;A growing number of Americans are apprehensive about the role technology might play in phasing out their employment. A new Gallup poll suggests that over one in five American workers now harbor concerns about their job’s future due to rapid technological advancements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rising Concern Over Time&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Published this Monday, the poll reveals that 22% of Americans worry that technology might render their jobs redundant. These concerns have seen a marked increase over the years since Gallup first started monitoring this sentiment in August 2017. At that time, a mere 13% expressed such fears. The figure showed a modest rise to 15% in 2019 and 17% in 2020, only to dip back to 15% in 2021. An interesting observation tied to this is the increasing prevalence and attention on artificial intelligence since the 2021 poll.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education and Concerns&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gallup’s data shows a significant shift in concerns among the college-educated workforce, with their fears spiking from 8% to 20%. On the other hand, workers without a college degree have maintained a nearly constant worry level at 24%. This indicates that the disparity in technological replacement concerns between the college-educated and non-college-educated workers has narrowed, with both groups now exhibiting parallel anxiety levels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Demographic Differences in Concern&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The poll further underscores the generational difference in apprehension, indicating that younger workers are more concerned about technology making their jobs obsolete than their older counterparts. Additionally, those earning less than $100,000 annually express more anxiety compared to those with higher incomes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other Workplace Fears&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the dread of technology-induced job redundancy, the Gallup poll highlighted other significant worries among American workers. The leading concern is a potential reduction in wages or benefits. While 31% of the respondents fear a cut in their benefits, 24% are anxious about a potential wage decrease. Concurrently, 20% of those polled are concerned about potential layoffs, with 19% fearing a reduction in working hours. Interestingly, only 7% expressed worry over their jobs being outsourced overseas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Survey Details&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For this research, Gallup interviewed 491 part-time or full-time adult workers in the U.S. between August 1 and August 23. The findings have a margin of error of ±5 percentage points.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">A growing number of Americans are apprehensive about the role technology might play in phasing out their employment. A new Gallup poll suggests that over one in five American workers now harbor concerns about their job’s future due to rapid technological advancements. Rising Concern Over Time Published this Monday, the poll reveals that 22% of Americans worry that technology might render their jobs redundant. These concerns have seen a marked increase over the years since Gallup first started monitoring this sentiment in August 2017. At that time, a mere 13% expressed such fears. The figure showed a modest rise to 15% in 2019 and 17% in 2020, only to dip back to 15% in 2021. An interesting observation tied to this is the increasing prevalence and attention on artificial intelligence since the 2021 poll. Education and Concerns Gallup’s data shows a significant shift in concerns among the college-educated workforce, with their fears spiking from 8% to 20%. On the other hand, workers without a college degree have maintained a nearly constant worry level at 24%. This indicates that the disparity in technological replacement concerns between the college-educated and non-college-educated workers has narrowed, with both groups now exhibiting parallel anxiety levels. Demographic Differences in Concern The poll further underscores the generational difference in apprehension, indicating that younger workers are more concerned about technology making their jobs obsolete than their older counterparts. Additionally, those earning less than $100,000 annually express more anxiety compared to those with higher incomes. Other Workplace Fears Beyond the dread of technology-induced job redundancy, the Gallup poll highlighted other significant worries among American workers. The leading concern is a potential reduction in wages or benefits. While 31% of the respondents fear a cut in their benefits, 24% are anxious about a potential wage decrease. Concurrently, 20% of those polled are concerned about potential layoffs, with 19% fearing a reduction in working hours. Interestingly, only 7% expressed worry over their jobs being outsourced overseas. Survey Details For this research, Gallup interviewed 491 part-time or full-time adult workers in the U.S. between August 1 and August 23. The findings have a margin of error of ±5 percentage points.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Aaron Rodgers’ New York Jets Debut Cut Short by Ankle Injury</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/12/Rodgers-Injury-Debut/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Aaron Rodgers’ New York Jets Debut Cut Short by Ankle Injury" /><published>2023-09-12T09:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-12T09:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/12/Rodgers-Injury-Debut</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/12/Rodgers-Injury-Debut/">&lt;p&gt;Monday night’s highly awaited game between the New York Jets and the Buffalo Bills saw an unexpected turn as Aaron Rodgers, the newly acquired Jets quarterback, had to exit early. After being on the field for only a few minutes into his debut with the Jets, Rodgers suffered an ankle injury, putting a damper on the night for Jets fans.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The injury occurred when Buffalo Bills linebacker Leonard Floyd managed to sack Rodgers. Although Rodgers initially attempted to brush off the setback, he soon needed assistance to leave the field. This was a sight no sports fan ever wishes to see – a prominent player being escorted off the field, especially during a debut.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Subsequent broadcasts from ESPN showed Rodgers, with evident difficulty, making his way onto a cart that transported him towards the stadium’s tunnel. He was then spotted limping towards the locker room, and later, with a protective boot on his injured ankle. Before this unfortunate turn of events, Rodgers had yet to complete a pass, with a record of 0-for-1.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With Rodgers out of the picture, the Jets had to rely on Zach Wilson, their former starting quarterback. Wilson, who started for the Jets during his first two seasons, was supposed to be the backup to Rodgers after losing his primary spot towards the end of 2022.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For Rodgers, this game was meant to be an exhilarating first with the Jets, having recently showcased his prowess in a preseason match against the New York Giants where he threw an impressive touchdown pass to Garrett Wilson. Pre-game, he had spoken about the “butterflies” he felt during that preseason match.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a light-hearted moment before the game, when asked about his feelings on stepping onto the field for his Jets’ debut, Rodgers had humorously remarked that he’d probably be “sobbing.” He had further added that he looked forward to the experience and the energy of the crowd.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately for Rodgers and the Jets, the night didn’t go as planned. The extent of Rodgers’ injury remains to be seen, and fans across the nation are hoping for a swift recovery for the renowned quarterback.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Monday night’s highly awaited game between the New York Jets and the Buffalo Bills saw an unexpected turn as Aaron Rodgers, the newly acquired Jets quarterback, had to exit early. After being on the field for only a few minutes into his debut with the Jets, Rodgers suffered an ankle injury, putting a damper on the night for Jets fans. The injury occurred when Buffalo Bills linebacker Leonard Floyd managed to sack Rodgers. Although Rodgers initially attempted to brush off the setback, he soon needed assistance to leave the field. This was a sight no sports fan ever wishes to see – a prominent player being escorted off the field, especially during a debut. Subsequent broadcasts from ESPN showed Rodgers, with evident difficulty, making his way onto a cart that transported him towards the stadium’s tunnel. He was then spotted limping towards the locker room, and later, with a protective boot on his injured ankle. Before this unfortunate turn of events, Rodgers had yet to complete a pass, with a record of 0-for-1. With Rodgers out of the picture, the Jets had to rely on Zach Wilson, their former starting quarterback. Wilson, who started for the Jets during his first two seasons, was supposed to be the backup to Rodgers after losing his primary spot towards the end of 2022. For Rodgers, this game was meant to be an exhilarating first with the Jets, having recently showcased his prowess in a preseason match against the New York Giants where he threw an impressive touchdown pass to Garrett Wilson. Pre-game, he had spoken about the “butterflies” he felt during that preseason match. In a light-hearted moment before the game, when asked about his feelings on stepping onto the field for his Jets’ debut, Rodgers had humorously remarked that he’d probably be “sobbing.” He had further added that he looked forward to the experience and the energy of the crowd. Unfortunately for Rodgers and the Jets, the night didn’t go as planned. The extent of Rodgers’ injury remains to be seen, and fans across the nation are hoping for a swift recovery for the renowned quarterback.</summary></entry></feed>