<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-09-19T03:14:26-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/09/19/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-09-19T03:14:26-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-19T03:14:26-04:00</updated><id>/2023/09/19/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/19/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Shock in Shawnee - Pastor Accused of Attempted Family Murder and Arson</title><link href="/news/2023/09/18/Pastor-Fire-Incident/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Shock in Shawnee - Pastor Accused of Attempted Family Murder and Arson" /><published>2023-09-18T18:02:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-18T18:02:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/18/Pastor-Fire-Incident</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/18/Pastor-Fire-Incident/">&lt;p&gt;Shawnee, a tranquil suburb in Kansas, was rattled by shocking news involving a local youth pastor’s alleged violent actions against his family. Matthew Richards, 41, stands accused of attempting to kill his wife and five children in their home. Following the alleged attack, he is also charged with attempting to set the residence on fire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;disturbing-details&quot;&gt;Disturbing Details&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The harrowing incident occurred on September 16, when emergency services responded to alerts of a disturbance and fire around 3:47 a.m. Upon arriving, firefighters tackled a blaze in the basement of the family home located on Goode Drive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Richards and all the victims were rushed to the hospital. According to the Shawnee Police Department’s press release, the five children and the wife sustained “laceration injuries of varying degrees.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The aftermath has left Richards with five counts of attempted premeditated first-degree murder and one count of aggravated arson with a risk of bodily harm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;an-unexpected-turn&quot;&gt;An Unexpected Turn&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Crossroads Christian Church, where Richards was employed, showcases a heartwarming biography of him on their website. He is described as “a big kid who loves teaching little kids about Jesus.” The biography paints a contrasting picture, highlighting his marriage to Stephanie since 2003, their five children, and the family’s three rules – emphasizing love for God, people, and sports.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In light of the shocking incident, the Senior Pastor of Crossroads Church, Kurt Witten, issued a statement requesting respect for the ongoing investigation and urging prayers for the Richards family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;investigation-and-legal-proceedings&quot;&gt;Investigation and Legal Proceedings&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As investigations proceed, the community struggles to come to terms with the shocking event involving a figure once revered by many. Richards is currently being held on a staggering $5 million bond. The outcome of this situation will be closely watched by many, awaiting to see how justice unfolds.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Shawnee, a tranquil suburb in Kansas, was rattled by shocking news involving a local youth pastor’s alleged violent actions against his family. Matthew Richards, 41, stands accused of attempting to kill his wife and five children in their home. Following the alleged attack, he is also charged with attempting to set the residence on fire. Disturbing Details The harrowing incident occurred on September 16, when emergency services responded to alerts of a disturbance and fire around 3:47 a.m. Upon arriving, firefighters tackled a blaze in the basement of the family home located on Goode Drive. Richards and all the victims were rushed to the hospital. According to the Shawnee Police Department’s press release, the five children and the wife sustained “laceration injuries of varying degrees.” The aftermath has left Richards with five counts of attempted premeditated first-degree murder and one count of aggravated arson with a risk of bodily harm. An Unexpected Turn The Crossroads Christian Church, where Richards was employed, showcases a heartwarming biography of him on their website. He is described as “a big kid who loves teaching little kids about Jesus.” The biography paints a contrasting picture, highlighting his marriage to Stephanie since 2003, their five children, and the family’s three rules – emphasizing love for God, people, and sports. In light of the shocking incident, the Senior Pastor of Crossroads Church, Kurt Witten, issued a statement requesting respect for the ongoing investigation and urging prayers for the Richards family. Investigation and Legal Proceedings As investigations proceed, the community struggles to come to terms with the shocking event involving a figure once revered by many. Richards is currently being held on a staggering $5 million bond. The outcome of this situation will be closely watched by many, awaiting to see how justice unfolds.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump’s Fiery Rebuke - Biden’s $6 Billion ‘Hostage Deal’ with Iran</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/18/Trump-Biden-Iran-Deal/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump’s Fiery Rebuke - Biden’s $6 Billion ‘Hostage Deal’ with Iran" /><published>2023-09-18T17:10:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-18T17:10:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/18/Trump-Biden-Iran-Deal</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/18/Trump-Biden-Iran-Deal/">&lt;p&gt;Former President Donald Trump, known for his candid expressions and unfiltered opinions, blasted President Joe Biden’s recent deal with Iran. Labeled by Trump as a “6 Billion Dollar Hostage Deal,” this agreement has drawn attention and criticism from several corners.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-lopsided-deal&quot;&gt;A Lopsided Deal?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a candid post on Truth Social, Trump declared that this Iran deal has established a “terrible PRECEDENT for the future.” Expressing his concerns, he warned his followers and the general public to “buckle up” for the potential aftermath of such a deal. Highlighting the past reputation of the United States, he remarked that the once “highly respected USA” has now turned into a “laughingstock” globally.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His comments were in light of the recent event where five U.S. citizens were freed from Iranian custody. In exchange, the U.S. released five Iranian prisoners and unfroze $6 billion in Iranian assets that were under U.S. sanctions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;trumps-perspective&quot;&gt;Trump’s Perspective&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Trump did commend the release of the American hostages, he heavily criticized the price at which their freedom came. Comparing this situation with his tenure as President, he boasted of bringing home 58 hostages from various countries, including North Korea, without any ransom payments. He implied that his strong stance made countries rethink their hostage negotiation strategies. “Toward the end, it got so that countries didn’t even start the conversation asking for money, because they knew they would not get it,” Trump stated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Continuing his critique, Trump expressed his apprehension that such deals might pave the way for what he calls “hostage inflation.” According to him, if countries see that the U.S. is willing to pay billions for the safe return of its citizens, more Americans could potentially be taken hostage in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;whats-the-future-hold&quot;&gt;What’s the Future Hold?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The implication of Trump’s statements is clear. He firmly believes that once a precedent of payment is set, the demands will only increase, leading to more Americans at risk overseas. In his signature style, he concluded by labelling President Biden as “Dumb as a ROCK!” and blaming him for this deal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Only time will tell whether Trump’s fears are realized or if this deal will pave the way for smoother international relations. However, his concerns serve as a reminder to always tread cautiously on the international stage.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Former President Donald Trump, known for his candid expressions and unfiltered opinions, blasted President Joe Biden’s recent deal with Iran. Labeled by Trump as a “6 Billion Dollar Hostage Deal,” this agreement has drawn attention and criticism from several corners. A Lopsided Deal? In a candid post on Truth Social, Trump declared that this Iran deal has established a “terrible PRECEDENT for the future.” Expressing his concerns, he warned his followers and the general public to “buckle up” for the potential aftermath of such a deal. Highlighting the past reputation of the United States, he remarked that the once “highly respected USA” has now turned into a “laughingstock” globally. His comments were in light of the recent event where five U.S. citizens were freed from Iranian custody. In exchange, the U.S. released five Iranian prisoners and unfroze $6 billion in Iranian assets that were under U.S. sanctions. Trump’s Perspective While Trump did commend the release of the American hostages, he heavily criticized the price at which their freedom came. Comparing this situation with his tenure as President, he boasted of bringing home 58 hostages from various countries, including North Korea, without any ransom payments. He implied that his strong stance made countries rethink their hostage negotiation strategies. “Toward the end, it got so that countries didn’t even start the conversation asking for money, because they knew they would not get it,” Trump stated. Continuing his critique, Trump expressed his apprehension that such deals might pave the way for what he calls “hostage inflation.” According to him, if countries see that the U.S. is willing to pay billions for the safe return of its citizens, more Americans could potentially be taken hostage in the future. What’s the Future Hold? The implication of Trump’s statements is clear. He firmly believes that once a precedent of payment is set, the demands will only increase, leading to more Americans at risk overseas. In his signature style, he concluded by labelling President Biden as “Dumb as a ROCK!” and blaming him for this deal. Only time will tell whether Trump’s fears are realized or if this deal will pave the way for smoother international relations. However, his concerns serve as a reminder to always tread cautiously on the international stage.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Breaking Point - Eagle Pass Overwhelmed by Migrant Influx</title><link href="/news/2023/09/18/Unsustainable-Border-Crisis/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Breaking Point - Eagle Pass Overwhelmed by Migrant Influx" /><published>2023-09-18T16:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-18T16:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/18/Unsustainable-Border-Crisis</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/18/Unsustainable-Border-Crisis/">&lt;p&gt;EAGLE PASS, Texas — A small town on the border of Texas is facing a dire situation as over 1,500 migrants crossed into Eagle Pass from Mexico in just six hours. This recent influx surpasses the previous record established merely days ago, where 1,300 migrants crossed within a day. A reality check is in order as these numbers raise alarming concerns about the sustainability and effectiveness of U.S. border and immigration policies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Multiple reports have revealed that the local migrant processing center in Eagle Pass, initially designed to hold approximately 1,000 individuals, had to be shut down as it had already tripled its capacity. Officials are now scrambling to make accommodations, resulting in migrants being held outdoors. The rapid increase in numbers only underscores the pressing need for an overhaul in the current system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“This system is broken,” a source within the Customs and Border Protection (CBP) commented.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the weekend, astonishingly, in a single eight-hour shift, over 700 migrants were taken into custody. With the current infrastructure already stretched thin, the ability of border agents to handle the influx efficiently and humanely is called into question. Sadly, as temperatures are projected to soar to the mid-90s, many of these migrants find themselves awaiting processing outdoors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further south, reports from Piedras Negras, Coahuila, noted that Mexican military officials halted another 1,200 migrants from crossing. But it’s only a matter of time before they attempt again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With processing facilities already bursting at the seams, the situation is becoming untenable. By mid-morning, every Border Patrol agent with a commercial driver’s license in the region had been summoned to transport migrants. Yet hundreds still remained by midday, requiring attention from EMT-trained agents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eagle Pass recently witnessed a massive release of migrants into the community due to these constraints. With the processing center running well over its limits, it’s plausible that this trend of mass releases will continue, if not amplify.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sadly, the release isn’t the end of the challenge. Many migrants find themselves stranded in Eagle Pass without funds, relying on the kindness of residents for rides, money, or meals. Some have reported that shelters, such as Mission Border Hope, will only assist those migrants who have the means to buy a bus ticket out of the town. This leaves many to navigate the over 150 miles to cities like San Antonio on their own.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The plight of these migrants underscores the broader issue – a pressing need to address the evident shortcomings in U.S. border and immigration policies. As the streets of Eagle Pass become flooded with hopeful migrants, the sustainability of the current approach is clearly in jeopardy.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">EAGLE PASS, Texas — A small town on the border of Texas is facing a dire situation as over 1,500 migrants crossed into Eagle Pass from Mexico in just six hours. This recent influx surpasses the previous record established merely days ago, where 1,300 migrants crossed within a day. A reality check is in order as these numbers raise alarming concerns about the sustainability and effectiveness of U.S. border and immigration policies. Multiple reports have revealed that the local migrant processing center in Eagle Pass, initially designed to hold approximately 1,000 individuals, had to be shut down as it had already tripled its capacity. Officials are now scrambling to make accommodations, resulting in migrants being held outdoors. The rapid increase in numbers only underscores the pressing need for an overhaul in the current system. “This system is broken,” a source within the Customs and Border Protection (CBP) commented. Over the weekend, astonishingly, in a single eight-hour shift, over 700 migrants were taken into custody. With the current infrastructure already stretched thin, the ability of border agents to handle the influx efficiently and humanely is called into question. Sadly, as temperatures are projected to soar to the mid-90s, many of these migrants find themselves awaiting processing outdoors. Further south, reports from Piedras Negras, Coahuila, noted that Mexican military officials halted another 1,200 migrants from crossing. But it’s only a matter of time before they attempt again. With processing facilities already bursting at the seams, the situation is becoming untenable. By mid-morning, every Border Patrol agent with a commercial driver’s license in the region had been summoned to transport migrants. Yet hundreds still remained by midday, requiring attention from EMT-trained agents. Eagle Pass recently witnessed a massive release of migrants into the community due to these constraints. With the processing center running well over its limits, it’s plausible that this trend of mass releases will continue, if not amplify. Sadly, the release isn’t the end of the challenge. Many migrants find themselves stranded in Eagle Pass without funds, relying on the kindness of residents for rides, money, or meals. Some have reported that shelters, such as Mission Border Hope, will only assist those migrants who have the means to buy a bus ticket out of the town. This leaves many to navigate the over 150 miles to cities like San Antonio on their own. The plight of these migrants underscores the broader issue – a pressing need to address the evident shortcomings in U.S. border and immigration policies. As the streets of Eagle Pass become flooded with hopeful migrants, the sustainability of the current approach is clearly in jeopardy.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Sheryl Crow on Tennessee Move - How Leaving LA ‘Saved My Life’</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/18/Tennessee-Life-Saver/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sheryl Crow on Tennessee Move - How Leaving LA ‘Saved My Life’" /><published>2023-09-18T15:07:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-18T15:07:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/18/Tennessee-Life-Saver</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/18/Tennessee-Life-Saver/">&lt;p&gt;Sheryl Crow, the musician behind hits like “If It Makes You Happy,” recently spoke candidly about how her move from Los Angeles to Nashville, Tennessee, became a lifesaving decision.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-breath-of-fresh-air&quot;&gt;A Breath of Fresh Air&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the 2023 Sea.Hear.Now Music Festival in New Jersey, Crow connected with her audience, many of whom might be navigating through their own challenges. “I know how hard it is for especially young people… but these are some tricky waters to navigate now,” she voiced.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2023/09/720/405/sheryl-crow_04.jpg?ve=1&amp;amp;tl=1&quot; alt=&quot;Sheryl Crow with her guitar&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Sheryl Crow on stage, embracing her love for music. Photo by Astrida Valigorsky/Getty Images.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Revealing a deeply personal insight, she shared, “I’ll just tell you that, for me, getting out in nature really saved my life.” This shift towards a more natural environment led her to buy a farm in Nashville, where she’d sit among the trees, seeking solace and inspiration. It was in this setting that she wrote “Cross Creek Road.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;finding-her-roots&quot;&gt;Finding Her Roots&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sheryl’s relocation to Nashville wasn’t a mere whim. In 2003, she told Rolling Stone that she felt a deep connection to the city, not just because of her friends in the music business, but because of the warmth and simplicity of the people there. The hustle of cities like New York and L.A. paled in comparison to the serenity she felt in Nashville.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moreover, a significant turning point in her life was her breast cancer diagnosis. She revealed to the New York Times that she bought her farm just two weeks post-diagnosis. “I didn’t feel like I had roots anywhere,” Crow reminisced about the time leading up to her move.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2023/09/720/405/sheryl-crow_03.jpg?ve=1&amp;amp;tl=1&quot; alt=&quot;Sheryl Crow in a stylish outfit&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Sheryl Crow at a fashion event. Photo by Gilbert Flores/WWD via Getty Images.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-mother-first&quot;&gt;A Mother First&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apart from finding personal tranquility, Tennessee also provided an ideal environment for raising her two adopted sons, Wyatt and Levi. Living there, Crow shared the benefits of a community-centric upbringing for her kids. It’s a place where they can grow without the constant flash of cameras, where they can understand the value of helping others, and where they won’t be hounded by paparazzi.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In an industry often filled with fleeting glamour, Sheryl Crow’s story is a testament to the healing power of nature, the comfort of community, and the enduring bond of family.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Sheryl Crow, the musician behind hits like “If It Makes You Happy,” recently spoke candidly about how her move from Los Angeles to Nashville, Tennessee, became a lifesaving decision. A Breath of Fresh Air At the 2023 Sea.Hear.Now Music Festival in New Jersey, Crow connected with her audience, many of whom might be navigating through their own challenges. “I know how hard it is for especially young people… but these are some tricky waters to navigate now,” she voiced. Sheryl Crow on stage, embracing her love for music. Photo by Astrida Valigorsky/Getty Images. Revealing a deeply personal insight, she shared, “I’ll just tell you that, for me, getting out in nature really saved my life.” This shift towards a more natural environment led her to buy a farm in Nashville, where she’d sit among the trees, seeking solace and inspiration. It was in this setting that she wrote “Cross Creek Road.” Finding Her Roots Sheryl’s relocation to Nashville wasn’t a mere whim. In 2003, she told Rolling Stone that she felt a deep connection to the city, not just because of her friends in the music business, but because of the warmth and simplicity of the people there. The hustle of cities like New York and L.A. paled in comparison to the serenity she felt in Nashville. Moreover, a significant turning point in her life was her breast cancer diagnosis. She revealed to the New York Times that she bought her farm just two weeks post-diagnosis. “I didn’t feel like I had roots anywhere,” Crow reminisced about the time leading up to her move. Sheryl Crow at a fashion event. Photo by Gilbert Flores/WWD via Getty Images. A Mother First Apart from finding personal tranquility, Tennessee also provided an ideal environment for raising her two adopted sons, Wyatt and Levi. Living there, Crow shared the benefits of a community-centric upbringing for her kids. It’s a place where they can grow without the constant flash of cameras, where they can understand the value of helping others, and where they won’t be hounded by paparazzi. In an industry often filled with fleeting glamour, Sheryl Crow’s story is a testament to the healing power of nature, the comfort of community, and the enduring bond of family.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Soros Funds Biden’s TikTok Strategy - America’s Teens Under Influence?</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/18/Soros-Biden-TikTok-Influence/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Soros Funds Biden’s TikTok Strategy - America’s Teens Under Influence?" /><published>2023-09-18T14:11:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-18T14:11:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/18/Soros-Biden-TikTok-Influence</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/18/Soros-Biden-TikTok-Influence/">&lt;p&gt;George Soros, the billionaire Democrat donor infamous for championing far-left causes, is now funding an initiative to bolster the image of President Joe Biden on TikTok. But why would Soros show interest in a platform popular among American teenagers?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-tiktok-army-and-soros-agenda&quot;&gt;The TikTok Army and Soros’ Agenda&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Documents brought to light by the New York Post indicate that Soros is bankrolling a “TikTok army” composed of Gen-Z social media enthusiasts. Their main task? To disseminate pro-Biden messages and attack conservative views. The platform of choice? TikTok, which already hosts a vast population of American teens, making them a prime target for political influencing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tax filings unveil that Soros’ Open Society Foundation funneled a staggering $5.5 million to Accelerate Action Inc. over 2020 and 2021. Following this, at least $300,000 was directed in 2022 to Gen Z for Change, an organization that flaunts a vast network of “activists, organizers, and creators.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;bidens-social-media-aides&quot;&gt;Biden’s Social Media Aides&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While President Biden occupies the highest office in the land, he’s actively leaning on Gen Z for Change to amplify his policy messages on social media. Not only has Gen Z for Change met with Biden in the famed Oval Office, but they’ve also received briefings from top White House officials, including sessions on the U.S. involvement in Ukraine and discussions with Surgeon General Vivek Murthy on the pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gen Z for Change influencers are not shy about their views. They’ve used their platform to advocate for controversial policies such as abolishing border enforcement, defunding the police, and ending cash bail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;wheres-the-money-flowing&quot;&gt;Where’s the Money Flowing?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A burning question remains: How is Soros’ money being used by these young TikTok influencers? There’s no clarity on how Gen Z for Change allocates the Soros funds among its TikTok squad. What we do know, however, is that their content seems eerily in line with the White House’s talking points.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aidan Kohn-Murphy, the founder of the group, openly advocates for progressive policies such as Medicare for all, the Green New Deal, and Palestinian liberation. With these talking points and a massive platform, he and others are shaping the opinions of countless Gen Z followers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;soros-the-puppet-master&quot;&gt;Soros: The Puppet Master?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s worth noting that Soros isn’t a novice in the world of influencing public opinion. For years, he’s poured funds into left-leaning causes globally via his Open Society Foundation. The recent strategy to tap into TikTok to promote left-wing ideals seems like another feather in his cap of trying to mould public opinion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, is it fair for teens, many of whom are not yet eligible to vote, to be the target of such heavy political messaging? As America’s future voters, they deserve balanced viewpoints rather than a single-sided narrative bankrolled by billionaire agendas.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">George Soros, the billionaire Democrat donor infamous for championing far-left causes, is now funding an initiative to bolster the image of President Joe Biden on TikTok. But why would Soros show interest in a platform popular among American teenagers? The TikTok Army and Soros’ Agenda Documents brought to light by the New York Post indicate that Soros is bankrolling a “TikTok army” composed of Gen-Z social media enthusiasts. Their main task? To disseminate pro-Biden messages and attack conservative views. The platform of choice? TikTok, which already hosts a vast population of American teens, making them a prime target for political influencing. Tax filings unveil that Soros’ Open Society Foundation funneled a staggering $5.5 million to Accelerate Action Inc. over 2020 and 2021. Following this, at least $300,000 was directed in 2022 to Gen Z for Change, an organization that flaunts a vast network of “activists, organizers, and creators.” Biden’s Social Media Aides While President Biden occupies the highest office in the land, he’s actively leaning on Gen Z for Change to amplify his policy messages on social media. Not only has Gen Z for Change met with Biden in the famed Oval Office, but they’ve also received briefings from top White House officials, including sessions on the U.S. involvement in Ukraine and discussions with Surgeon General Vivek Murthy on the pandemic. Gen Z for Change influencers are not shy about their views. They’ve used their platform to advocate for controversial policies such as abolishing border enforcement, defunding the police, and ending cash bail. Where’s the Money Flowing? A burning question remains: How is Soros’ money being used by these young TikTok influencers? There’s no clarity on how Gen Z for Change allocates the Soros funds among its TikTok squad. What we do know, however, is that their content seems eerily in line with the White House’s talking points. Aidan Kohn-Murphy, the founder of the group, openly advocates for progressive policies such as Medicare for all, the Green New Deal, and Palestinian liberation. With these talking points and a massive platform, he and others are shaping the opinions of countless Gen Z followers. Soros: The Puppet Master? It’s worth noting that Soros isn’t a novice in the world of influencing public opinion. For years, he’s poured funds into left-leaning causes globally via his Open Society Foundation. The recent strategy to tap into TikTok to promote left-wing ideals seems like another feather in his cap of trying to mould public opinion. However, is it fair for teens, many of whom are not yet eligible to vote, to be the target of such heavy political messaging? As America’s future voters, they deserve balanced viewpoints rather than a single-sided narrative bankrolled by billionaire agendas.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ambush Attack on LA Sheriff’s Deputy Ends in Arrest</title><link href="/news/2023/09/18/Arrest-in-LA-Deputy-Ambush/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ambush Attack on LA Sheriff’s Deputy Ends in Arrest" /><published>2023-09-18T13:04:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-18T13:04:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/18/Arrest-in-LA-Deputy-Ambush</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/18/Arrest-in-LA-Deputy-Ambush/">&lt;p&gt;Los Angeles Sheriff’s Deputy Ryan Clinkunbroomer was tragically shot and killed while on duty in Palmdale, California. Now, sources have confirmed to Fox News that an arrest has been made in connection with this horrific incident.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Swift Break in the Case&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Investigators received a pivotal tip which led them to a residence in Palmdale - the same location where Clinkunbroomer was ambushed in his patrol vehicle on Saturday, Sept. 16. A relative of the suspect offered crucial information about the case. As a result, the male suspect was detained without any disruptions, with officers using gas to ensure a peaceful arrest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Reward for Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the wake of the shooting, a significant $250,000 reward was publicized for any leads that would result in an arrest. Surveillance footage showing the moments leading up to the unfortunate event was released. The clip showcased a suspicious black car positioning itself next to Clinkunbroomer’s cruiser, right before the fatal shooting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even though the surveillance video doesn’t reveal the shooting itself, it captures the black vehicle speeding away while the deputy’s cruiser rolls forward slowly, eventually stopping. An observant citizen noticed Clinkunbroomer unresponsive in his car and promptly alerted fellow deputies at the Palmdale Sheriff’s Station.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heading to the Hospital&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With no time to lose, Clinkunbroomer was rushed to the hospital in his cruiser. Midway, an ambulance reached the cruiser, took over the transportation, and another deputy drove his vehicle to a medical center in Lancaster.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While authorities have made progress in the case, the motive behind the shooting remains uncertain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Life of Service&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remembered fondly by his peers and superiors, Clinkunbroomer had served the Palmdale and Antelope Valley communities for eight years. Sheriff Robert Luna remarked about the deputy’s dedication and service, noting that both Clinkunbroomer’s father and grandfather had served in the sheriff’s department as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sheriff Luna voiced his grief on X (formerly known as Twitter), highlighting the sacrifice Ryan Clinkunbroomer made for his community. “He laid everything on the line to serve us,” Luna expressed, underscoring the deputy’s commitment&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Los Angeles Sheriff’s Deputy Ryan Clinkunbroomer was tragically shot and killed while on duty in Palmdale, California. Now, sources have confirmed to Fox News that an arrest has been made in connection with this horrific incident. A Swift Break in the Case Investigators received a pivotal tip which led them to a residence in Palmdale - the same location where Clinkunbroomer was ambushed in his patrol vehicle on Saturday, Sept. 16. A relative of the suspect offered crucial information about the case. As a result, the male suspect was detained without any disruptions, with officers using gas to ensure a peaceful arrest. A Reward for Information In the wake of the shooting, a significant $250,000 reward was publicized for any leads that would result in an arrest. Surveillance footage showing the moments leading up to the unfortunate event was released. The clip showcased a suspicious black car positioning itself next to Clinkunbroomer’s cruiser, right before the fatal shooting. Even though the surveillance video doesn’t reveal the shooting itself, it captures the black vehicle speeding away while the deputy’s cruiser rolls forward slowly, eventually stopping. An observant citizen noticed Clinkunbroomer unresponsive in his car and promptly alerted fellow deputies at the Palmdale Sheriff’s Station. Heading to the Hospital With no time to lose, Clinkunbroomer was rushed to the hospital in his cruiser. Midway, an ambulance reached the cruiser, took over the transportation, and another deputy drove his vehicle to a medical center in Lancaster. While authorities have made progress in the case, the motive behind the shooting remains uncertain. A Life of Service Remembered fondly by his peers and superiors, Clinkunbroomer had served the Palmdale and Antelope Valley communities for eight years. Sheriff Robert Luna remarked about the deputy’s dedication and service, noting that both Clinkunbroomer’s father and grandfather had served in the sheriff’s department as well. Sheriff Luna voiced his grief on X (formerly known as Twitter), highlighting the sacrifice Ryan Clinkunbroomer made for his community. “He laid everything on the line to serve us,” Luna expressed, underscoring the deputy’s commitment</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Impersonator with Guns Crashes RFK Jr Event - A Startling Encounter</title><link href="/news/2023/09/18/Imposing-Impersonator/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Impersonator with Guns Crashes RFK Jr Event - A Startling Encounter" /><published>2023-09-18T11:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-18T11:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/18/Imposing-Impersonator</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/18/Imposing-Impersonator/">&lt;p&gt;In a startling incident, a man was detained at a campaign event for Democratic presidential candidate Robert F. Kennedy Jr. in Los Angeles. Why? He was impersonating a U.S. Marshal, complete with shoulder holsters holding loaded pistols and spare ammo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Los Angeles Police Department identified this man as 44-year-old Adrian Paul Aispuro. Shortly after the incident, Kennedy expressed his gratitude on X, which was once known as Twitter. He thanked the security guards for their fast action.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kennedy wrote, “I’m very grateful that alert and fast-acting protectors from Gavin de Becker and Associates (GDBA) spotted and detained an armed man who attempted to approach me at my Hispanic Heritage speech at the Wilshire Ebell Theatre in Los Angeles tonight.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, the impersonator had not just any badge, but a U.S. Marshal badge. He introduced himself as part of Kennedy’s security detail. Thankfully, the GDBA team was on their toes. They detained him till the LAPD could arrive and make an arrest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kennedy, who is challenging President Biden, also mentioned he has yet to get protection from the Secret Service. He said, “I’m still hoping President Biden will grant me Secret Service protection. I am the first presidential candidate in history to whom the White House has denied a request for protection.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This denial comes even though, back in 1968, Robert F. Kennedy was tragically shot and killed in LA, not far from where this recent event took place. Kennedy Jr.’s uncle, former President John F. Kennedy, was also assassinated in 1963.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Photos of Aispuro from the event have been circulating online. He was caught wearing a black shirt stamped with “Emergency Medical Services.” As of now, he remains in custody with a bail set at $35,000.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This incident is a sobering reminder of the potential threats political figures face, even in modern-day campaigns. It underscores the importance of security and protection for those in the public eye.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a startling incident, a man was detained at a campaign event for Democratic presidential candidate Robert F. Kennedy Jr. in Los Angeles. Why? He was impersonating a U.S. Marshal, complete with shoulder holsters holding loaded pistols and spare ammo. The Los Angeles Police Department identified this man as 44-year-old Adrian Paul Aispuro. Shortly after the incident, Kennedy expressed his gratitude on X, which was once known as Twitter. He thanked the security guards for their fast action. Kennedy wrote, “I’m very grateful that alert and fast-acting protectors from Gavin de Becker and Associates (GDBA) spotted and detained an armed man who attempted to approach me at my Hispanic Heritage speech at the Wilshire Ebell Theatre in Los Angeles tonight.” Interestingly, the impersonator had not just any badge, but a U.S. Marshal badge. He introduced himself as part of Kennedy’s security detail. Thankfully, the GDBA team was on their toes. They detained him till the LAPD could arrive and make an arrest. Kennedy, who is challenging President Biden, also mentioned he has yet to get protection from the Secret Service. He said, “I’m still hoping President Biden will grant me Secret Service protection. I am the first presidential candidate in history to whom the White House has denied a request for protection.” This denial comes even though, back in 1968, Robert F. Kennedy was tragically shot and killed in LA, not far from where this recent event took place. Kennedy Jr.’s uncle, former President John F. Kennedy, was also assassinated in 1963. Photos of Aispuro from the event have been circulating online. He was caught wearing a black shirt stamped with “Emergency Medical Services.” As of now, he remains in custody with a bail set at $35,000. This incident is a sobering reminder of the potential threats political figures face, even in modern-day campaigns. It underscores the importance of security and protection for those in the public eye.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">NKorea’s Kim Strengthens Ties - Returns with Russian Drones and More</title><link href="/news/2023/09/18/NKorea-Russia-Ties/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="NKorea’s Kim Strengthens Ties - Returns with Russian Drones and More" /><published>2023-09-18T10:09:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-18T10:09:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/18/NKorea-Russia-Ties</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/18/NKorea-Russia-Ties/">&lt;p&gt;In a move that’s garnered international attention, North Korean leader Kim Jong Un recently wrapped up a noteworthy six-day visit to Russia. This trip, Kim’s first outside North Korea since the onset of the coronavirus pandemic, had a significant focus on military cooperation between the two nations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;strengthened-relations-amidst-western-concerns&quot;&gt;Strengthened Relations Amidst Western Concerns&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kim’s visit signals a deepening bond between Russia and North Korea, much to the West’s alarm. Observers are anxious about the implications of strengthened ties, especially given Russia’s ongoing conflict in Ukraine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Throughout his visit, Kim engaged in various activities signifying the military unity between the two nations, including a symbolic rifle exchange with Russian President Vladimir Putin and close inspections of advanced Russian weaponry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;defying-international-sanctions&quot;&gt;Defying International Sanctions?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Russia’s Foreign Minister, Sergei Lavrov, during a national television broadcast, underscored Russia’s intention to bolster its alliance with North Korea, irrespective of UN sanctions. “We will be developing equal, fair interaction with the DPRK,” Lavrov noted, referring to North Korea by its official name.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of the many gestures that highlighted the trip, Kim’s reception of drones and a bulletproof vest from the governor of Russia’s Primorye region, which neighbors North Korea, was particularly significant. This gift, comprising five explosive drones and a reconnaissance drone, marked a symbolic end to Kim’s stay in Vladivostok, the Pacific port city just beyond the North Korean border.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond military discussions, the two nations have also deliberated on reviving certain infrastructure projects, escalating grain supplies, and resuming routine air travel. An upcoming official meeting between the two countries is slated for November in Pyongyang.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;an-era-of-renewed-cooperation&quot;&gt;An Era of Renewed Cooperation?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Historical allies, Russia and North Korea, both subjected to global sanctions, have shown signs of renewed camaraderie. Their respective sanctions are due to Moscow’s Ukraine interventions and Pyongyang’s nuclear weapon trials.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During their meeting, Putin and Kim deliberated on the potential for enhanced cooperation and military ties. While Moscow might be eyeing North Korean ammunition for its Ukraine operations, Pyongyang seeks Russia’s expertise in propelling its missile program. Notably, no official agreement has been confirmed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The North Korean state news agency, KCNA, portrayed Kim’s trip as the beginning of a “new era of friendship, solidarity, and cooperation” between the two nations. As a testament to their deepening ties, Putin has accepted an invitation to visit North Korea and even proposed sending a North Korean astronaut to space, a historical first.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the world watches, the evolving alliance between Russia and North Korea will undoubtedly influence the geopolitical landscape in the days to come.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a move that’s garnered international attention, North Korean leader Kim Jong Un recently wrapped up a noteworthy six-day visit to Russia. This trip, Kim’s first outside North Korea since the onset of the coronavirus pandemic, had a significant focus on military cooperation between the two nations. Strengthened Relations Amidst Western Concerns Kim’s visit signals a deepening bond between Russia and North Korea, much to the West’s alarm. Observers are anxious about the implications of strengthened ties, especially given Russia’s ongoing conflict in Ukraine. Throughout his visit, Kim engaged in various activities signifying the military unity between the two nations, including a symbolic rifle exchange with Russian President Vladimir Putin and close inspections of advanced Russian weaponry. Defying International Sanctions? Russia’s Foreign Minister, Sergei Lavrov, during a national television broadcast, underscored Russia’s intention to bolster its alliance with North Korea, irrespective of UN sanctions. “We will be developing equal, fair interaction with the DPRK,” Lavrov noted, referring to North Korea by its official name. Of the many gestures that highlighted the trip, Kim’s reception of drones and a bulletproof vest from the governor of Russia’s Primorye region, which neighbors North Korea, was particularly significant. This gift, comprising five explosive drones and a reconnaissance drone, marked a symbolic end to Kim’s stay in Vladivostok, the Pacific port city just beyond the North Korean border. Beyond military discussions, the two nations have also deliberated on reviving certain infrastructure projects, escalating grain supplies, and resuming routine air travel. An upcoming official meeting between the two countries is slated for November in Pyongyang. An Era of Renewed Cooperation? Historical allies, Russia and North Korea, both subjected to global sanctions, have shown signs of renewed camaraderie. Their respective sanctions are due to Moscow’s Ukraine interventions and Pyongyang’s nuclear weapon trials. During their meeting, Putin and Kim deliberated on the potential for enhanced cooperation and military ties. While Moscow might be eyeing North Korean ammunition for its Ukraine operations, Pyongyang seeks Russia’s expertise in propelling its missile program. Notably, no official agreement has been confirmed. The North Korean state news agency, KCNA, portrayed Kim’s trip as the beginning of a “new era of friendship, solidarity, and cooperation” between the two nations. As a testament to their deepening ties, Putin has accepted an invitation to visit North Korea and even proposed sending a North Korean astronaut to space, a historical first. As the world watches, the evolving alliance between Russia and North Korea will undoubtedly influence the geopolitical landscape in the days to come.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump vs. Biden - A Michigan Showdown on the Horizon?</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/18/Trump-Biden-Michigan-Showdown/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump vs. Biden - A Michigan Showdown on the Horizon?" /><published>2023-09-18T09:15:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-18T09:15:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/18/Trump-Biden-Michigan-Showdown</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/18/Trump-Biden-Michigan-Showdown/">&lt;p&gt;Michigan, often regarded as the heartbeat of America’s political battlegrounds, has once again captured national attention. A recent poll by Susquehanna Polling and Research suggests that if a presidential election were to take place today between Former President Donald Trump and President Joe Biden, the outcome would be too close to call.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;trump-and-biden-the-michigan-standoff&quot;&gt;Trump and Biden: The Michigan Standoff&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The poll, initially shared with the Hill, indicates that 46% of probable Michigander voters would rally behind Biden, with Trump trailing close at 43%. Surprisingly, a considerable 11% remain undecided. With a margin of error standing at 3.7%, it’s clear: these political heavyweights are virtually tied in the Wolverine State.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump’s strong grip on the GOP is evident, with a commendable 90% support from his party base. Comparatively, Biden garners support from 87% of Democrat respondents. Jim Lee, the president of Susquehanna Polling and Research, pointed out a significant tidbit: Biden’s support among Democrats in Michigan has seen a slight dip from 97% in 2020. On the other hand, Trump’s GOP support remains consistent, witnessing only a minor dip from 94% in the previous election.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;independents--the-national-trend&quot;&gt;Independents &amp;amp; the National Trend&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although Biden seems to have a modest lead with independent voters in Michigan (44% vs. Trump’s 37%), national trends are slightly leaning in Trump’s favor. Both Harvard-Harris and CBS News/YouGov polls depict Trump holding an edge among the independent voters at the national level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;michigan-a-legacy-of-close-calls&quot;&gt;Michigan: A Legacy of Close Calls&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Historically, Michigan has been a decisive battleground. Trump’s 2016 victory over Hillary Clinton by a mere one-third of a percentage point is a testament to that. Comparatively, Biden’s win over Trump in 2020 was by a little less than three percentage points. A shift of a few votes can change the course of history in Michigan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;trump-leads-the-gop-desantis-trails&quot;&gt;Trump Leads the GOP, DeSantis Trails&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the Trump vs. Biden matchup is drawing significant attention, there’s also a buzz around other potential contenders. If Governor Ron DeSantis of Florida were to be pitted against Biden, he’d fare slightly worse than Trump, lagging behind by three more points. However, within the GOP, Trump remains the alpha, garnering a massive 65% support, leaving DeSantis trailing significantly at 18%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;wrapping-up&quot;&gt;Wrapping Up&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While these polls provide a sneak peek into the current political sentiment, they’re merely snapshots in time. Michigan’s political landscape has always been dynamic, and only time will reveal the true sentiments of its voters. One thing remains certain: Michigan will be a state to watch in any upcoming elections.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Michigan, often regarded as the heartbeat of America’s political battlegrounds, has once again captured national attention. A recent poll by Susquehanna Polling and Research suggests that if a presidential election were to take place today between Former President Donald Trump and President Joe Biden, the outcome would be too close to call. Trump and Biden: The Michigan Standoff The poll, initially shared with the Hill, indicates that 46% of probable Michigander voters would rally behind Biden, with Trump trailing close at 43%. Surprisingly, a considerable 11% remain undecided. With a margin of error standing at 3.7%, it’s clear: these political heavyweights are virtually tied in the Wolverine State. Trump’s strong grip on the GOP is evident, with a commendable 90% support from his party base. Comparatively, Biden garners support from 87% of Democrat respondents. Jim Lee, the president of Susquehanna Polling and Research, pointed out a significant tidbit: Biden’s support among Democrats in Michigan has seen a slight dip from 97% in 2020. On the other hand, Trump’s GOP support remains consistent, witnessing only a minor dip from 94% in the previous election. Independents &amp;amp; the National Trend Although Biden seems to have a modest lead with independent voters in Michigan (44% vs. Trump’s 37%), national trends are slightly leaning in Trump’s favor. Both Harvard-Harris and CBS News/YouGov polls depict Trump holding an edge among the independent voters at the national level. Michigan: A Legacy of Close Calls Historically, Michigan has been a decisive battleground. Trump’s 2016 victory over Hillary Clinton by a mere one-third of a percentage point is a testament to that. Comparatively, Biden’s win over Trump in 2020 was by a little less than three percentage points. A shift of a few votes can change the course of history in Michigan. Trump Leads the GOP, DeSantis Trails While the Trump vs. Biden matchup is drawing significant attention, there’s also a buzz around other potential contenders. If Governor Ron DeSantis of Florida were to be pitted against Biden, he’d fare slightly worse than Trump, lagging behind by three more points. However, within the GOP, Trump remains the alpha, garnering a massive 65% support, leaving DeSantis trailing significantly at 18%. Wrapping Up While these polls provide a sneak peek into the current political sentiment, they’re merely snapshots in time. Michigan’s political landscape has always been dynamic, and only time will reveal the true sentiments of its voters. One thing remains certain: Michigan will be a state to watch in any upcoming elections.</summary></entry></feed>