<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-09-22T02:20:40-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/09/22/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-09-22T02:20:40-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-22T02:20:40-04:00</updated><id>/2023/09/22/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/22/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">The Connection Between Trident DMG and Democrats Takes Center Stage</title><link href="/news/2023/09/21/Democrat-Linked-PR-Firm/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Connection Between Trident DMG and Democrats Takes Center Stage" /><published>2023-09-21T17:21:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-21T17:21:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/21/Democrat-Linked-PR-Firm</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/21/Democrat-Linked-PR-Firm/">&lt;p&gt;Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu’s recent encounters with protestors in cities like California and New York over his proposed judicial reforms have raised eyebrows. The protests, although seemingly grassroots, might have more intricate ties, namely to Trident DMG, a PR firm based in Washington with known affiliations to the Democratic Party.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trident DMG’s connections to the Democratic Party are no secret in the corridors of power in Washington. And now, with reports suggesting their potential role in organizing opposition against Netanyahu on U.S. soil, these ties are receiving greater scrutiny. Their association with Blue and White Future, an organization from Israel that stands against Netanyahu, has only fueled these speculations. Reports highlight a three-month contract worth $75,000 between Trident DMG and the Israeli organization, putting the PR firm’s Democrat links under the spotlight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eleanor McManus, co-founder and partner of Trident DMG, while emphasizing the company’s role in promoting awareness about the so-called “democracy crisis” in Israel, stopped short of confirming or denying their direct involvement in the U.S. protests against Netanyahu. However, her statement did little to dissuade discussions about the firm’s connections to Democratic power players and their possible influence in international political issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The growing concerns in the Jewish community, fearing an amplification of anti-Israel narratives due to these protests, adds another layer to this unfolding drama. With Trident DMG at the crosshairs, and their Democratic links being examined closely, the tale of foreign influences shaping domestic protests gains yet another chapter.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu’s recent encounters with protestors in cities like California and New York over his proposed judicial reforms have raised eyebrows. The protests, although seemingly grassroots, might have more intricate ties, namely to Trident DMG, a PR firm based in Washington with known affiliations to the Democratic Party. Trident DMG’s connections to the Democratic Party are no secret in the corridors of power in Washington. And now, with reports suggesting their potential role in organizing opposition against Netanyahu on U.S. soil, these ties are receiving greater scrutiny. Their association with Blue and White Future, an organization from Israel that stands against Netanyahu, has only fueled these speculations. Reports highlight a three-month contract worth $75,000 between Trident DMG and the Israeli organization, putting the PR firm’s Democrat links under the spotlight. Eleanor McManus, co-founder and partner of Trident DMG, while emphasizing the company’s role in promoting awareness about the so-called “democracy crisis” in Israel, stopped short of confirming or denying their direct involvement in the U.S. protests against Netanyahu. However, her statement did little to dissuade discussions about the firm’s connections to Democratic power players and their possible influence in international political issues. The growing concerns in the Jewish community, fearing an amplification of anti-Israel narratives due to these protests, adds another layer to this unfolding drama. With Trident DMG at the crosshairs, and their Democratic links being examined closely, the tale of foreign influences shaping domestic protests gains yet another chapter.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Serious Felony Charges - Hunter Biden’s Virtual Court Appearance Disputed</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/21/Hunter-Biden-Felony-Charges/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Serious Felony Charges - Hunter Biden’s Virtual Court Appearance Disputed" /><published>2023-09-21T16:10:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-21T16:10:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/21/Hunter-Biden-Felony-Charges</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/21/Hunter-Biden-Felony-Charges/">&lt;p&gt;In an unfolding legal saga, Special Counsel David Weiss is contesting Hunter Biden’s wish to make his court appearance virtually regarding the significant felony gun charges he faces.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-virtual-tug-of-war&quot;&gt;A Virtual Tug-of-War&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hunter Biden, the son of President Joe Biden, has found himself in hot water with the law. He has been slapped with charges, including making false statements during a firearm purchase and possessing a gun while being an unlawful user or addicted to controlled substances. These accusations have come to the limelight amidst the broader controversies surrounding his past actions and decisions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Biden’s legal team, led by attorney Abbe Lowell, sent out a request for the preliminary court appearance to be held virtually. However, this request isn’t sitting well with some, notably Special Counsel David Weiss.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-grounds-of-opposition&quot;&gt;The Grounds of Opposition&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Weiss has made his stance clear by objecting to this request. His reasoning? The charges are of a “serious” nature, and it’s essential for the court to assess Hunter in person, especially when determining conditions of release. The emphasis here is on the gravity of the charges and the need for the court to make accurate evaluations without the limitations of a video call.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The counter-argument from Biden’s legal team is that they’re not asking for any special treatment. Lowell argues that Hunter is trying to minimize unnecessary strains on government resources, given the logistical challenges of a Secret Service-protected individual traveling cross-country and the subsequent disruptions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-backstory&quot;&gt;The Backstory&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This isn’t the first time Hunter Biden’s activities have made the news. Fox News highlighted an incident from 2018 where a firearm owned by him was discarded in a trash bin near a school in Delaware. This event adds another layer of complexity to the current charges and the surrounding narrative.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, Hunter Biden’s past has been brought to light with his discharge from the Navy in 2014, following a positive cocaine test.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-challenge-to-the-system&quot;&gt;A Challenge to the System?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Abbe Lowell is not backing down without a fight. He’s raised concerns over the nature of the charges and argues that they may be influenced by political pressure. Lowell believes that Hunter’s brief possession of an unloaded gun did not pose a public safety risk. In contrast, a prosecutor succumbing to political influences could threaten the justice system’s integrity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the case progresses, many await to see how this chapter in Hunter Biden’s tumultuous life will conclude. Whether the court appearance will be virtual or in-person remains undecided, but one thing is clear: this legal battle has only just begun.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In an unfolding legal saga, Special Counsel David Weiss is contesting Hunter Biden’s wish to make his court appearance virtually regarding the significant felony gun charges he faces. A Virtual Tug-of-War Hunter Biden, the son of President Joe Biden, has found himself in hot water with the law. He has been slapped with charges, including making false statements during a firearm purchase and possessing a gun while being an unlawful user or addicted to controlled substances. These accusations have come to the limelight amidst the broader controversies surrounding his past actions and decisions. Biden’s legal team, led by attorney Abbe Lowell, sent out a request for the preliminary court appearance to be held virtually. However, this request isn’t sitting well with some, notably Special Counsel David Weiss. The Grounds of Opposition Weiss has made his stance clear by objecting to this request. His reasoning? The charges are of a “serious” nature, and it’s essential for the court to assess Hunter in person, especially when determining conditions of release. The emphasis here is on the gravity of the charges and the need for the court to make accurate evaluations without the limitations of a video call. The counter-argument from Biden’s legal team is that they’re not asking for any special treatment. Lowell argues that Hunter is trying to minimize unnecessary strains on government resources, given the logistical challenges of a Secret Service-protected individual traveling cross-country and the subsequent disruptions. The Backstory This isn’t the first time Hunter Biden’s activities have made the news. Fox News highlighted an incident from 2018 where a firearm owned by him was discarded in a trash bin near a school in Delaware. This event adds another layer of complexity to the current charges and the surrounding narrative. Furthermore, Hunter Biden’s past has been brought to light with his discharge from the Navy in 2014, following a positive cocaine test. A Challenge to the System? Abbe Lowell is not backing down without a fight. He’s raised concerns over the nature of the charges and argues that they may be influenced by political pressure. Lowell believes that Hunter’s brief possession of an unloaded gun did not pose a public safety risk. In contrast, a prosecutor succumbing to political influences could threaten the justice system’s integrity. As the case progresses, many await to see how this chapter in Hunter Biden’s tumultuous life will conclude. Whether the court appearance will be virtual or in-person remains undecided, but one thing is clear: this legal battle has only just begun.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Jared Leto Reveals Past As ‘Professional Drug User’</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/21/Jared-Leto-Drug-Revelations/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Jared Leto Reveals Past As ‘Professional Drug User’" /><published>2023-09-21T15:08:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-21T15:08:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/21/Jared-Leto-Drug-Revelations</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/21/Jared-Leto-Drug-Revelations/">&lt;p&gt;The talented actor and singer, Jared Leto, recently peeled back the curtain on a darker chapter in his life, revealing that he was once “a professional drug user.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During a candid chat with Zane Lowe on Apple Music 1, the 51-year-old “30 Seconds to Mars” frontman reminisced about his time in art school. Surrounded by artists, this environment nurtured both his creative passions and a penchant for drug experimentation. “I grew up in an environment where there were drugs around. I knew what the smell of weed is as a very, very young kid,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As Leto matured, his curiosity grew. He spoke openly about being drawn to drugs and risk-taking, seeking novel experiences. However, this journey was not without its pitfalls. While honing his craft as a painter, he admitted to not just using drugs, but dealing them too. “My experience was certainly one that I took it for a ride and then it took me for a ride, for sure,” he reflected.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet, every dark tale has its turning point. For Leto, it was an “epiphany.” This moment of profound realization made him reconsider his life’s direction. Faced with two diverging paths, Leto chose one filled with aspirations and accomplishments he’d be proud of. Recalling close friends who didn’t make the same choice, Leto remarked somberly, “And they’re not here anymore.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This isn’t the first time Leto has spoken out about his past. In a 2016 interview with Rolling Stone, he delved into his experiences with drugs, sharing some light moments and the inevitable serious ones. “I guess at some point, too, there’s a decision: Is this going to be my life? I made a choice to pursue other dreams.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Leto’s candid revelations serve as a potent reminder of the challenges many face and the resilience required to overcome them. It’s not just about the choices made but the strength to change course when needed.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">The talented actor and singer, Jared Leto, recently peeled back the curtain on a darker chapter in his life, revealing that he was once “a professional drug user.” During a candid chat with Zane Lowe on Apple Music 1, the 51-year-old “30 Seconds to Mars” frontman reminisced about his time in art school. Surrounded by artists, this environment nurtured both his creative passions and a penchant for drug experimentation. “I grew up in an environment where there were drugs around. I knew what the smell of weed is as a very, very young kid,” he shared. As Leto matured, his curiosity grew. He spoke openly about being drawn to drugs and risk-taking, seeking novel experiences. However, this journey was not without its pitfalls. While honing his craft as a painter, he admitted to not just using drugs, but dealing them too. “My experience was certainly one that I took it for a ride and then it took me for a ride, for sure,” he reflected. Yet, every dark tale has its turning point. For Leto, it was an “epiphany.” This moment of profound realization made him reconsider his life’s direction. Faced with two diverging paths, Leto chose one filled with aspirations and accomplishments he’d be proud of. Recalling close friends who didn’t make the same choice, Leto remarked somberly, “And they’re not here anymore.” This isn’t the first time Leto has spoken out about his past. In a 2016 interview with Rolling Stone, he delved into his experiences with drugs, sharing some light moments and the inevitable serious ones. “I guess at some point, too, there’s a decision: Is this going to be my life? I made a choice to pursue other dreams.” Leto’s candid revelations serve as a potent reminder of the challenges many face and the resilience required to overcome them. It’s not just about the choices made but the strength to change course when needed.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">56% of Virginians Say Drop Out - Gibson’s Tumultuous Campaign Journey</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/21/Gibson-Controversy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="56% of Virginians Say Drop Out - Gibson’s Tumultuous Campaign Journey" /><published>2023-09-21T14:12:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-21T14:12:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/21/Gibson-Controversy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/21/Gibson-Controversy/">&lt;p&gt;In an era where privacy lines blur and personal choices become political tools, Susanna Gibson, Virginia House of Delegates candidate for District 57, finds herself at the center of a public scandal that many argue she brought upon herself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A recently surfaced poll from Founders Insight Public Policy Institute, initially reported by the Daily Wire, reveals that a staggering 56% of likely Virginia voters believe Susanna Gibson should exit the political race. To make matters worse for Gibson, only 30% expressed that she should continue her campaign.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-damaging-past-exposed&quot;&gt;A Damaging Past Exposed&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gibson’s fall from grace began with the revelation of her past indulgence in explicit online performances for monetary gains. As a 40-year-old nurse practitioner, wife to an attorney, and mother of two young boys, the explicit actions for which she once collected “tokens” or payments have now resurfaced to haunt her political aspirations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In an attempt to manage the fallout, Gibson posited herself as a victim of revenge porn. However, this stance was debunked swiftly, as several sources confirmed that the content in question was publicly produced and wasn’t “leaked” as she claimed. This has been particularly damaging, considering notable media outlets like the New York Times championed her “victim” narrative without verifying the information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-questionable-response&quot;&gt;A Questionable Response&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One could argue that every individual has the right to their private choices. However, what is concerning to many is Gibson’s handling of the situation. Instead of addressing the issue head-on, she has essentially disappeared from the public eye, leaving many to speculate on her motivations and question her integrity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This disappearing act might be a strategic move on Gibson’s part, waiting for the story to simmer down and for public attention to shift. However, this approach might be too optimistic, given that early voting starts this week and public sentiment is still largely against her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-matter-of-judgment&quot;&gt;A Matter of Judgment&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While it’s reasonable to assert that everyone makes mistakes, especially in their youth, Gibson’s scenario is different. She wasn’t a naive teenager but a mature professional making choices that could impact her family’s future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The subject of one’s past influencing their political career isn’t new. However, Gibson’s situation is particularly unique. It’s not just about her choices but also her seeming lack of foresight and responsibility, especially concerning her two young children. As the controversy continues to unfold, the looming question is whether Virginians can trust Gibson’s judgment in political matters when her personal decisions have been so questionable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the coming weeks, Gibson’s fate will unfold as Virginians decide if they can look past her questionable past and her recent behavior to support her bid for the House of Delegates.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In an era where privacy lines blur and personal choices become political tools, Susanna Gibson, Virginia House of Delegates candidate for District 57, finds herself at the center of a public scandal that many argue she brought upon herself. A recently surfaced poll from Founders Insight Public Policy Institute, initially reported by the Daily Wire, reveals that a staggering 56% of likely Virginia voters believe Susanna Gibson should exit the political race. To make matters worse for Gibson, only 30% expressed that she should continue her campaign. A Damaging Past Exposed Gibson’s fall from grace began with the revelation of her past indulgence in explicit online performances for monetary gains. As a 40-year-old nurse practitioner, wife to an attorney, and mother of two young boys, the explicit actions for which she once collected “tokens” or payments have now resurfaced to haunt her political aspirations. In an attempt to manage the fallout, Gibson posited herself as a victim of revenge porn. However, this stance was debunked swiftly, as several sources confirmed that the content in question was publicly produced and wasn’t “leaked” as she claimed. This has been particularly damaging, considering notable media outlets like the New York Times championed her “victim” narrative without verifying the information. A Questionable Response One could argue that every individual has the right to their private choices. However, what is concerning to many is Gibson’s handling of the situation. Instead of addressing the issue head-on, she has essentially disappeared from the public eye, leaving many to speculate on her motivations and question her integrity. This disappearing act might be a strategic move on Gibson’s part, waiting for the story to simmer down and for public attention to shift. However, this approach might be too optimistic, given that early voting starts this week and public sentiment is still largely against her. A Matter of Judgment While it’s reasonable to assert that everyone makes mistakes, especially in their youth, Gibson’s scenario is different. She wasn’t a naive teenager but a mature professional making choices that could impact her family’s future. The subject of one’s past influencing their political career isn’t new. However, Gibson’s situation is particularly unique. It’s not just about her choices but also her seeming lack of foresight and responsibility, especially concerning her two young children. As the controversy continues to unfold, the looming question is whether Virginians can trust Gibson’s judgment in political matters when her personal decisions have been so questionable. In the coming weeks, Gibson’s fate will unfold as Virginians decide if they can look past her questionable past and her recent behavior to support her bid for the House of Delegates.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A Cry for Help - Sacramento’s Growing Homeless Struggle</title><link href="/news/2023/09/21/Sacramento-Crisis/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Cry for Help - Sacramento’s Growing Homeless Struggle" /><published>2023-09-21T13:02:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-21T13:02:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/21/Sacramento-Crisis</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/21/Sacramento-Crisis/">&lt;p&gt;Sacramento, California’s capital, is often bustling with politicians and city leaders. But recently, it’s the growing number of tents and makeshift shelters that are stealing headlines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;from-the-golden-state-to-a-homeless-crisis&quot;&gt;From the Golden State to a Homeless Crisis&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Democratic District Attorney Thien Ho of Sacramento County is up in arms against his city. Why? It’s over the homeless conditions which, according to him, resemble those of a “Third World country.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Tuesday, Ho announced a civil lawsuit against Sacramento. The lawsuit accuses the city of allowing a public safety crisis concerning its homeless population. And the numbers back his claim: In just seven years, the unhoused population in Sacramento has skyrocketed by over 250%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Our community is on the edge,” the lawsuit reads. “We have homeless folks living in conditions you’d find in severely underdeveloped countries. Meanwhile, the rest of us are caught between wanting to help and dealing with the chaos.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-tipping-point&quot;&gt;The Tipping Point&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ho lamented the repetitive cycle the city seems to be stuck in. “It’s like Groundhog’s Day,” he said, “where the situation remains grim, and nothing improves.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Problems stemming from the increasing homelessness are becoming hard to ignore. Both Judge Michael Bowman and District Attorney Ho have voiced concerns about growing homeless encampments near the courthouse. These settlements are not just an eyesore but also pose genuine threats. Reports include instances of assault, public misconduct, and other disturbances which, according to Ho, compromise the safety of jurors, victims, and witnesses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-plea-for-change&quot;&gt;A Plea for Change&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The city’s response to this escalating crisis has been, to many, unsatisfactory. Mayor Darrell Steinberg promised the initiation of the “Miller Park Safe Camping” to alleviate the situation, but three months on, conditions appear to have only deteriorated. Instances of assault and harassment linked to the homeless population have surged, further deepening the divide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A survey conducted by Ho’s office in July asked locals how the 16 main homeless encampments across Sacramento affected their lives. Out of nearly 3,000 responses, many recounted harrowing experiences. Residents reported assaults, disruptions to community events, and continuous harassment by homeless individuals. Some even stated that their pleas for help from City Hall either went unanswered or were met with dismissive remarks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, in response to the lawsuit, City Attorney Susana Alcala Wood expressed disappointment, stating the DA seems more keen on laying blame than seeking solutions. Mayor Steinberg termed Ho’s actions a “performative distraction,” yet acknowledged the frustrations faced by residents due to the ongoing crisis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sacramento’s struggle highlights the broader challenges many California cities face with their growing homeless populations. While solutions may be complex and multifaceted, the need for actionable change is evident.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Sacramento, California’s capital, is often bustling with politicians and city leaders. But recently, it’s the growing number of tents and makeshift shelters that are stealing headlines. From the Golden State to a Homeless Crisis Democratic District Attorney Thien Ho of Sacramento County is up in arms against his city. Why? It’s over the homeless conditions which, according to him, resemble those of a “Third World country.” On Tuesday, Ho announced a civil lawsuit against Sacramento. The lawsuit accuses the city of allowing a public safety crisis concerning its homeless population. And the numbers back his claim: In just seven years, the unhoused population in Sacramento has skyrocketed by over 250%. “Our community is on the edge,” the lawsuit reads. “We have homeless folks living in conditions you’d find in severely underdeveloped countries. Meanwhile, the rest of us are caught between wanting to help and dealing with the chaos.” The Tipping Point Ho lamented the repetitive cycle the city seems to be stuck in. “It’s like Groundhog’s Day,” he said, “where the situation remains grim, and nothing improves.” Problems stemming from the increasing homelessness are becoming hard to ignore. Both Judge Michael Bowman and District Attorney Ho have voiced concerns about growing homeless encampments near the courthouse. These settlements are not just an eyesore but also pose genuine threats. Reports include instances of assault, public misconduct, and other disturbances which, according to Ho, compromise the safety of jurors, victims, and witnesses. A Plea for Change The city’s response to this escalating crisis has been, to many, unsatisfactory. Mayor Darrell Steinberg promised the initiation of the “Miller Park Safe Camping” to alleviate the situation, but three months on, conditions appear to have only deteriorated. Instances of assault and harassment linked to the homeless population have surged, further deepening the divide. A survey conducted by Ho’s office in July asked locals how the 16 main homeless encampments across Sacramento affected their lives. Out of nearly 3,000 responses, many recounted harrowing experiences. Residents reported assaults, disruptions to community events, and continuous harassment by homeless individuals. Some even stated that their pleas for help from City Hall either went unanswered or were met with dismissive remarks. However, in response to the lawsuit, City Attorney Susana Alcala Wood expressed disappointment, stating the DA seems more keen on laying blame than seeking solutions. Mayor Steinberg termed Ho’s actions a “performative distraction,” yet acknowledged the frustrations faced by residents due to the ongoing crisis. Sacramento’s struggle highlights the broader challenges many California cities face with their growing homeless populations. While solutions may be complex and multifaceted, the need for actionable change is evident.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">McConaughey and Harrelson’s DNA Test Drama - Maury Povich Steps In!</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/21/DNA-Test-Proposal/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="McConaughey and Harrelson’s DNA Test Drama - Maury Povich Steps In!" /><published>2023-09-21T12:09:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-21T12:09:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/21/DNA-Test-Proposal</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/21/DNA-Test-Proposal/">&lt;p&gt;It’s a storyline that sounds like it’s straight out of Hollywood: two leading men, Matthew McConaughey and Woody Harrelson, discovering that they might be half-brothers. But it’s not a movie – it’s real life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The buzz around this surprising possibility grew louder after McConaughey shared some revelations about his family’s past. During a podcast interview, he disclosed that Harrelson’s father might have had a connection with his mother during her divorce. This set off waves of speculation – are the two superstar actors related by blood?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enter Maury Povich, a retired television host, best known for his dramatic on-screen DNA test reveals. In a light-hearted twist, Povich offered to step in and conduct a DNA test for the two stars, even proposing a prime-time TV special. “I would come out of retirement. We could do primetime, ‘DNA, Maury’s back with Woody and Matthew,’” Povich said in a video to E! News.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Harrelson seemed intrigued by the idea when he appeared on “The Late Show with Stephen Colbert,” musing about the implications of such a test. “For [McConaughey], it’s a big deal. He feels like he’s losing a father. But I’m like, no, you’re gaining a different father and a brother.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The two have been friends for over two decades, showcasing their camaraderie in projects such as “True Detective.” Fans are eagerly awaiting their reunion onscreen in the upcoming series, “Brother From Another Mother,” which, given the current rumors, holds an uncanny relevance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, will they take the test? The world waits with bated breath. Whatever the outcome, it’s clear that the bond between McConaughey and Harrelson is stronger than ever. The story of their potential shared heritage adds another layer of intrigue to their already storied friendship.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">It’s a storyline that sounds like it’s straight out of Hollywood: two leading men, Matthew McConaughey and Woody Harrelson, discovering that they might be half-brothers. But it’s not a movie – it’s real life. The buzz around this surprising possibility grew louder after McConaughey shared some revelations about his family’s past. During a podcast interview, he disclosed that Harrelson’s father might have had a connection with his mother during her divorce. This set off waves of speculation – are the two superstar actors related by blood? Enter Maury Povich, a retired television host, best known for his dramatic on-screen DNA test reveals. In a light-hearted twist, Povich offered to step in and conduct a DNA test for the two stars, even proposing a prime-time TV special. “I would come out of retirement. We could do primetime, ‘DNA, Maury’s back with Woody and Matthew,’” Povich said in a video to E! News. Harrelson seemed intrigued by the idea when he appeared on “The Late Show with Stephen Colbert,” musing about the implications of such a test. “For [McConaughey], it’s a big deal. He feels like he’s losing a father. But I’m like, no, you’re gaining a different father and a brother.” The two have been friends for over two decades, showcasing their camaraderie in projects such as “True Detective.” Fans are eagerly awaiting their reunion onscreen in the upcoming series, “Brother From Another Mother,” which, given the current rumors, holds an uncanny relevance. So, will they take the test? The world waits with bated breath. Whatever the outcome, it’s clear that the bond between McConaughey and Harrelson is stronger than ever. The story of their potential shared heritage adds another layer of intrigue to their already storied friendship.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Train Travels - Migrants’ New Path to Texas</title><link href="/news/2023/09/21/Migrant-Journey/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Train Travels - Migrants’ New Path to Texas" /><published>2023-09-21T11:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-21T11:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/21/Migrant-Journey</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/21/Migrant-Journey/">&lt;p&gt;The path to a new life can be hard. For thousands of migrants from Venezuela and Caribbean countries, it’s now taking them on a train journey towards the US border.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;all-aboard-the-migrant-express&quot;&gt;All Aboard the Migrant Express&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Migrants, in search of a brighter future, have turned to trains as their way into Piedras Negras, Coahuila. This city shares its borders with Texas. From here, many hope to enter the US.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Starting their trip in the bustling industrial city of Monterrey, Nuevo Leon, these determined individuals rode in and on the rail cars, moving towards their destination.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But things didn’t always go as planned. Mexican authorities caught wind of their journey and brought their train to a halt. Despite this hiccup, these migrants pressed on, eventually making their way to Piedras Negras.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;piedras-negras---a-gateway-city&quot;&gt;Piedras Negras - A Gateway City&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why Piedras Negras? This city has become a significant spot for migrants. Nearly 4,000 migrants began their crossing into Texas just this past Wednesday. The city’s appeal? The area lacks the extensive border barriers and fencing seen in other regions, making it an attractive point of entry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://media.breitbart.com/media/2023/09/Migrant-Trains-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Migrants at Piedras Negras&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;A crowd of migrants gather at Piedras Negras, looking for an opportunity to cross into Texas.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-bigger-picture&quot;&gt;The Bigger Picture&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The train-riding migrants shared stories of their long journey. Many mentioned that they began in Mexico City with travel permits in hand. But the path wasn’t easy. Along the way, these migrants faced challenges from Mexican immigration agents (known as INM) and police forces. Some even claimed they were extorted by these officials.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the story of these migrants is just one of many, it highlights the lengths people will go to for a chance at a better life. As the situation at the border evolves, the world watches, waiting to see how both sides will respond.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">The path to a new life can be hard. For thousands of migrants from Venezuela and Caribbean countries, it’s now taking them on a train journey towards the US border. All Aboard the Migrant Express Migrants, in search of a brighter future, have turned to trains as their way into Piedras Negras, Coahuila. This city shares its borders with Texas. From here, many hope to enter the US. Starting their trip in the bustling industrial city of Monterrey, Nuevo Leon, these determined individuals rode in and on the rail cars, moving towards their destination. But things didn’t always go as planned. Mexican authorities caught wind of their journey and brought their train to a halt. Despite this hiccup, these migrants pressed on, eventually making their way to Piedras Negras. Piedras Negras - A Gateway City Why Piedras Negras? This city has become a significant spot for migrants. Nearly 4,000 migrants began their crossing into Texas just this past Wednesday. The city’s appeal? The area lacks the extensive border barriers and fencing seen in other regions, making it an attractive point of entry. A crowd of migrants gather at Piedras Negras, looking for an opportunity to cross into Texas. The Bigger Picture The train-riding migrants shared stories of their long journey. Many mentioned that they began in Mexico City with travel permits in hand. But the path wasn’t easy. Along the way, these migrants faced challenges from Mexican immigration agents (known as INM) and police forces. Some even claimed they were extorted by these officials. While the story of these migrants is just one of many, it highlights the lengths people will go to for a chance at a better life. As the situation at the border evolves, the world watches, waiting to see how both sides will respond.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hunter Biden’s Unusual DOJ Treatment Raises Eyebrows</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/21/Hunter-Biden-Justice-Treatment/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hunter Biden’s Unusual DOJ Treatment Raises Eyebrows" /><published>2023-09-21T10:06:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-21T10:06:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/21/Hunter-Biden-Justice-Treatment</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/21/Hunter-Biden-Justice-Treatment/">&lt;p&gt;Hunter Biden’s recent indictment has taken the nation by storm. However, what’s capturing even more attention is the seemingly lenient approach the Department of Justice (DOJ) is taking toward his case, especially when considering its historical hard stance on similar matters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-surprising-treatment-of-a-presidents-son&quot;&gt;The Surprising Treatment of a President’s Son&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hunter Biden’s case isn’t just any case. He’s the first son of a sitting U.S. president to face criminal indictment. While it’s big news, insiders suggest that there’s more to come in this unfolding saga.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A former federal prosecutor has expressed deep concern over how the DOJ has been conducting a five-year investigation into Hunter Biden’s case. The evidence pointing toward corruption and severe criminal actions appears evident.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;comparing-hunters-case-to-traditional-doj-action&quot;&gt;Comparing Hunter’s Case to Traditional DOJ Action&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Historically, the DOJ has been strict, particularly when dealing with firearms offenses. This approach is in line with the Project Safe Neighborhoods (PSN), an initiative established over two decades ago to address such offenses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The program has seen every attorney general’s support, even the current one, Merrick Garland. Through this initiative, countless Americans have been sentenced to an average of 40 months in federal prison for similar gun charges. However, Hunter Biden’s treatment seems to diverge from these typical outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In his role, the former federal prosecutor has dealt with numerous firearms cases. Never has he seen a case with such compelling evidence being settled without charges. After sifting through data of over 189,000 illegal firearms possession cases, not one was found to be given an offer of diversion by the DOJ.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-controversial-sweetheart-deal&quot;&gt;The Controversial Sweetheart Deal&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It caused quite a stir when the DOJ tried to settle Hunter Biden’s case without bringing any charges and even proposed immunity for unrelated charges. But, thanks to a vigilant federal judge, that deal was stopped in its tracks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, weeks later, three indictments were filed against Hunter. These were for allegedly making false statements when buying a gun and for possessing a gun while being addicted to drugs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;more-evidence-awaiting-in-the-wings&quot;&gt;More Evidence Awaiting in the Wings?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There seems to be a treasure trove of evidence against Hunter Biden. An abandoned laptop, containing compromising emails, pictures, and videos, seems to point toward serious criminal activity. This, combined with testimony from a former business associate and revelations from House committee investigations, paints a grim picture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The available evidence seems to indicate the creation of fake companies, collaboration of co-conspirators, and a grand scheme to earn millions from foreign entities. Yet, the DOJ’s investigation seems to overlook these potential charges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-big-question&quot;&gt;The Big Question&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the evidence is as compelling as it appears, why aren’t Hunter and Joe Biden facing the level of scrutiny that others in similar situations have encountered? Many feel that there’s a false sense of security that they will never face serious consequences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Only time will tell if justice will prevail in its true form, or if a different set of rules applies to those in power.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Hunter Biden’s recent indictment has taken the nation by storm. However, what’s capturing even more attention is the seemingly lenient approach the Department of Justice (DOJ) is taking toward his case, especially when considering its historical hard stance on similar matters. The Surprising Treatment of a President’s Son Hunter Biden’s case isn’t just any case. He’s the first son of a sitting U.S. president to face criminal indictment. While it’s big news, insiders suggest that there’s more to come in this unfolding saga. A former federal prosecutor has expressed deep concern over how the DOJ has been conducting a five-year investigation into Hunter Biden’s case. The evidence pointing toward corruption and severe criminal actions appears evident. Comparing Hunter’s Case to Traditional DOJ Action Historically, the DOJ has been strict, particularly when dealing with firearms offenses. This approach is in line with the Project Safe Neighborhoods (PSN), an initiative established over two decades ago to address such offenses. The program has seen every attorney general’s support, even the current one, Merrick Garland. Through this initiative, countless Americans have been sentenced to an average of 40 months in federal prison for similar gun charges. However, Hunter Biden’s treatment seems to diverge from these typical outcomes. In his role, the former federal prosecutor has dealt with numerous firearms cases. Never has he seen a case with such compelling evidence being settled without charges. After sifting through data of over 189,000 illegal firearms possession cases, not one was found to be given an offer of diversion by the DOJ. The Controversial Sweetheart Deal It caused quite a stir when the DOJ tried to settle Hunter Biden’s case without bringing any charges and even proposed immunity for unrelated charges. But, thanks to a vigilant federal judge, that deal was stopped in its tracks. However, weeks later, three indictments were filed against Hunter. These were for allegedly making false statements when buying a gun and for possessing a gun while being addicted to drugs. More Evidence Awaiting in the Wings? There seems to be a treasure trove of evidence against Hunter Biden. An abandoned laptop, containing compromising emails, pictures, and videos, seems to point toward serious criminal activity. This, combined with testimony from a former business associate and revelations from House committee investigations, paints a grim picture. The available evidence seems to indicate the creation of fake companies, collaboration of co-conspirators, and a grand scheme to earn millions from foreign entities. Yet, the DOJ’s investigation seems to overlook these potential charges. The Big Question If the evidence is as compelling as it appears, why aren’t Hunter and Joe Biden facing the level of scrutiny that others in similar situations have encountered? Many feel that there’s a false sense of security that they will never face serious consequences. Only time will tell if justice will prevail in its true form, or if a different set of rules applies to those in power.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump Dominates New Hampshire, DeSantis Drops to Fifth</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/21/Trump-Leads-NH/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump Dominates New Hampshire, DeSantis Drops to Fifth" /><published>2023-09-21T09:07:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-21T09:07:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/21/Trump-Leads-NH</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/21/Trump-Leads-NH/">&lt;p&gt;In a twist of political fate, Former President Donald Trump has taken a strong lead in New Hampshire, while Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis has dramatically fallen to fifth place. This surprising turn was found in a recent CNN New Hampshire Primary Poll.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;trump-towers-in-the-granite-state&quot;&gt;Trump Towers in the Granite State&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to the poll, Trump leads the GOP primary race with an impressive 39% support. This places him a whopping 26 points ahead of the second contender, businessman Vivek Ramaswamy, who gathered 13% of the votes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nikki Haley, the former South Carolina Governor, wasn’t far behind Ramaswamy with 12% support. Former New Jersey Governor Chris Christie was next in line with 11%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;desantis-faces-a-setback&quot;&gt;DeSantis Faces a Setback&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perhaps the biggest news from the poll was DeSantis’s decline. After announcing earlier this summer that his campaign would focus on the first three states, including New Hampshire, the latest poll reveals he has only managed to garner 10% support, placing him fifth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This represents a significant 13-point dip from a survey conducted in July, where DeSantis was shown to have 23% support in New Hampshire. Changes in his campaign strategy, staff layoffs, and a change in campaign management may have contributed to this sharp decline.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-deeper-dive-into-voter-sentiments&quot;&gt;A Deeper Dive into Voter Sentiments&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The survey also shed light on the commitment of the voter base. A substantial 69% of Trump supporters stated they’re sure about supporting him, while only 18% of DeSantis supporters felt the same conviction for their candidate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When participants were questioned about which candidate they felt had the best chance to win the 2024 presidential general election, over half (51%) vouched for Trump. DeSantis lagged far behind with only 16% believing in his chances.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;in-conclusion&quot;&gt;In Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the political landscape can be unpredictable, this recent survey clearly indicates a shift in the wind. With DeSantis’s position dwindling in both national and state-wide polls, and Trump’s strong presence in New Hampshire, the 2024 GOP primary race is shaping up to be an intriguing one.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a twist of political fate, Former President Donald Trump has taken a strong lead in New Hampshire, while Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis has dramatically fallen to fifth place. This surprising turn was found in a recent CNN New Hampshire Primary Poll. Trump Towers in the Granite State According to the poll, Trump leads the GOP primary race with an impressive 39% support. This places him a whopping 26 points ahead of the second contender, businessman Vivek Ramaswamy, who gathered 13% of the votes. Nikki Haley, the former South Carolina Governor, wasn’t far behind Ramaswamy with 12% support. Former New Jersey Governor Chris Christie was next in line with 11%. DeSantis Faces a Setback Perhaps the biggest news from the poll was DeSantis’s decline. After announcing earlier this summer that his campaign would focus on the first three states, including New Hampshire, the latest poll reveals he has only managed to garner 10% support, placing him fifth. This represents a significant 13-point dip from a survey conducted in July, where DeSantis was shown to have 23% support in New Hampshire. Changes in his campaign strategy, staff layoffs, and a change in campaign management may have contributed to this sharp decline. A Deeper Dive into Voter Sentiments The survey also shed light on the commitment of the voter base. A substantial 69% of Trump supporters stated they’re sure about supporting him, while only 18% of DeSantis supporters felt the same conviction for their candidate. When participants were questioned about which candidate they felt had the best chance to win the 2024 presidential general election, over half (51%) vouched for Trump. DeSantis lagged far behind with only 16% believing in his chances. In Conclusion While the political landscape can be unpredictable, this recent survey clearly indicates a shift in the wind. With DeSantis’s position dwindling in both national and state-wide polls, and Trump’s strong presence in New Hampshire, the 2024 GOP primary race is shaping up to be an intriguing one.</summary></entry></feed>