<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-10-12T05:15:47-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/12/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-12T05:15:47-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-12T05:15:47-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/12/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/12/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/12/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-12T05:15:47-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-12T05:15:47-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/12/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/12/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/">&lt;p&gt;Recent surprise attacks by Hamas on Israel has fueled ongoing tensions between staunchly conservative commentators and the progressive “Squad” Democrats known for criticizing Israel. The intensity of the backlash highlights the deep political divide over foreign policy in the Middle East.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Hamas’ shocking attack, several members of the “Squad,” including Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.), called for a “ceasefire and de-escalation,” condemning the violence. The absence of a statement from Rep. Rashida Tlaib (D-Mich.) was notably called out by conservative media outlets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;South Carolina GOP Rep. Nancy Mace quickly labeled Ocasio-Cortez a “Hamas apologist” in response to her call for peace and de-escalation. Rep. Ilhan Omar (D-Minn.), no stranger to controversy surrounding her views on Israel, echoed the call for de-escalation and ceasefire. Omar’s prior statements comparing the US and Israel to terrorist groups like Hamas and the Taliban resurfaced in the debate, fueling more criticisms. Omar’s 2019 tweet, where she opined that “Israel has hypnotized the world,” also continues to haunt her political career, often cited by critics to challenge her stance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conservative commentators have been especially vocal. “FOX &amp;amp; Friends Weekend” co-host Rachel Campos-Duffy took aim at Omar, saying she fails to recognize the peace in the Middle East under Trump’s administration. Conservative pundit John Hasson also called out Omar, claiming she insinuated that attacks on IDF forces were acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Massachusetts Democrat Rep. Ayanna Pressley’s concerns over the “devastating attacks on Israelis” were met with skepticism. A prominent conservative online personality, Comfortably Smug, accused the “Squad” of advising Israel to back down after the nation suffered massive attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Jamaal Bowman’s call for an end to the Gaza blockade, in addition to condemning the Hamas attacks, was met with criticism from conservative radio host Jason Rantz. He accused Bowman of pairing his condemnation of terrorism with unwarranted criticisms of Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Cori Bush emphasized the urgent need for a ceasefire, while pushing for an end to “U.S. support for Israeli military occupation and apartheid.” Defense attorney Marina Medvin criticized Bush, suggesting that she equates the death of Palestinian terrorists to the horrific acts committed against Jewish civilians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amidst the political turmoil and intense debate, the attacks have taken a heavy toll. Israeli media report over 300 dead due to the wide-ranging assault. Gaza health officials note that at least 200 Palestinians have perished in the retaliatory Israeli air strikes following the initial Hamas attack. As the situation remains volatile, both sides continue to count their casualties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This divisive issue showcases the challenge America faces in crafting a unified approach to foreign policy, with deeply entrenched political divides at play. As the situation develops, the debate is bound to intensify, shedding light on the complexities of U.S. politics in the global arena.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Playboy Cuts Ties with Mia Khalifa Over Controversial Hamas Comments</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/11/Playboy-Hamas-Statement/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Playboy Cuts Ties with Mia Khalifa Over Controversial Hamas Comments" /><published>2023-10-11T15:45:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-11T15:45:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/11/Playboy-Hamas-Statement</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/11/Playboy-Hamas-Statement/">&lt;p&gt;In an unexpected twist in the entertainment world, Playboy Magazine has issued a robust statement condemning former porn star Mia Khalifa for her controversial remarks in support of Hamas terrorists. This move is starkly different from Harvard University’s rather subdued response to a similar issue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The magazine’s decision to sever ties with Khalifa came after she took to social media, making polarizing comments about the ongoing conflict in Israel. In her posts, she referred to terrorists as “freedom fighters” and went as far as suggesting they should improve their videography by capturing their horrific actions in a “wider camera shot.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Playboy responded swiftly to Khalifa’s remarks. In their statement, they expressed, “Over the past few days, Mia has made disgusting and reprehensible comments celebrating Hamas’ attacks on Israel and the murder of innocent men, women, and children.” Taking decisive action, Playboy announced the termination of their association with Khalifa, including the removal of her channel from their creator platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Juxtaposed with Playboy’s decisive action, Harvard University’s response to a similar situation seems muted. After more than 30 of its student organizations expressed support for terrorists, the Ivy League institution simply expressed its heartbreak over the violence in Israel. However, they remained silent on the collective endorsement of the Palestinian terror group Hamas by their student bodies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This stark contrast between an entertainment giant and a prestigious educational institution underscores the different stances entities can take in response to politically charged events. Playboy’s assertive stance might reflect a growing trend in the entertainment industry, where brands and influencers are expected to take firm stands on global issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a heartbreaking twist to the Israel conflict, reports surfaced about Itai and Hadar Berdichevsky. The couple were reportedly murdered during the Hamas attack after safeguarding their ten-month-old twins. In another shocking incident, Noa Argamani was attending a peace music festival when she was kidnapped by Hamas terrorists.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prominent figures like Harvard Law School Professor Emeritus Alan Dershowitz have criticized Harvard for its lack of acknowledgment concerning student group statements, especially in the aftermath of the severe attacks in Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The recent events in Israel and the subsequent reactions by global entities like Playboy and Harvard highlight the complexities surrounding political events and the varied responses they elicit.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">In an unexpected twist in the entertainment world, Playboy Magazine has issued a robust statement condemning former porn star Mia Khalifa for her controversial remarks in support of Hamas terrorists. This move is starkly different from Harvard University’s rather subdued response to a similar issue. The magazine’s decision to sever ties with Khalifa came after she took to social media, making polarizing comments about the ongoing conflict in Israel. In her posts, she referred to terrorists as “freedom fighters” and went as far as suggesting they should improve their videography by capturing their horrific actions in a “wider camera shot.” Playboy responded swiftly to Khalifa’s remarks. In their statement, they expressed, “Over the past few days, Mia has made disgusting and reprehensible comments celebrating Hamas’ attacks on Israel and the murder of innocent men, women, and children.” Taking decisive action, Playboy announced the termination of their association with Khalifa, including the removal of her channel from their creator platform. Juxtaposed with Playboy’s decisive action, Harvard University’s response to a similar situation seems muted. After more than 30 of its student organizations expressed support for terrorists, the Ivy League institution simply expressed its heartbreak over the violence in Israel. However, they remained silent on the collective endorsement of the Palestinian terror group Hamas by their student bodies. This stark contrast between an entertainment giant and a prestigious educational institution underscores the different stances entities can take in response to politically charged events. Playboy’s assertive stance might reflect a growing trend in the entertainment industry, where brands and influencers are expected to take firm stands on global issues. In a heartbreaking twist to the Israel conflict, reports surfaced about Itai and Hadar Berdichevsky. The couple were reportedly murdered during the Hamas attack after safeguarding their ten-month-old twins. In another shocking incident, Noa Argamani was attending a peace music festival when she was kidnapped by Hamas terrorists. Prominent figures like Harvard Law School Professor Emeritus Alan Dershowitz have criticized Harvard for its lack of acknowledgment concerning student group statements, especially in the aftermath of the severe attacks in Israel. The recent events in Israel and the subsequent reactions by global entities like Playboy and Harvard highlight the complexities surrounding political events and the varied responses they elicit.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Bipartisan Pressure Rises on Biden Over $6 Billion Iranian Release</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/11/Biden-Iranian-Funds/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bipartisan Pressure Rises on Biden Over $6 Billion Iranian Release" /><published>2023-10-11T14:36:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-11T14:36:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/11/Biden-Iranian-Funds</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/11/Biden-Iranian-Funds/">&lt;p&gt;In a mounting wave of bipartisan concern, key Democrat Senators are urging President Joe Biden to freeze the slated $6 billion in funds intended for Iran, spotlighting a significant divergence within the Democratic party itself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Senators Jon Tester of Montana and Joe Manchin of West Virginia, two leading moderate Democrats, voiced their concerns on Tuesday. Their apprehensions stem from the devastating terrorist onslaught on Israel, an act of aggression that has tentative links to the Iranian government. The attack, executed by Hamas, resulted in the tragic loss of numerous lives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tester, who heads the Senate Defense Appropriations Subcommittee, voiced his stance decisively. He asserted that while the probe into Iran’s potential involvement continues, the U.S. must contemplate freezing the $6 billion Iranian assets. Furthermore, he underscored the need to equip Israel with necessary defenses against such harrowing attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Manchin, known for his influential role as the chairman of the Senate Energy and Natural Resources Committee, echoed similar sentiments. Not only did he express his sustained skepticism regarding the initial fund transfer to Iran, but he also highlighted the imperative of imposing stringent sanctions on nations found to be backing Hamas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amplifying the call to action, a coalition of 20 Republican senators has penned a letter to President Biden, emphatically demanding the suspension of Iranian funds currently held in South Korea. The letter elucidates the urgency to reinforce Israel’s position by restricting Iranian financial access.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nevertheless, the White House remains unyielding in its stance. Responding to inquiries about potential reconsiderations regarding the fund release, National Security Advisor Jake Sullivan emphasized that the aforementioned funds remain untouched.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The confluence of political voices, transcending party lines, underscores the gravity of the situation. With Israel reeling from a catastrophic terrorist act and Iran’s potential role under scrutiny, Biden’s $6 billion decision is undeniably under the magnifying glass.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a mounting wave of bipartisan concern, key Democrat Senators are urging President Joe Biden to freeze the slated $6 billion in funds intended for Iran, spotlighting a significant divergence within the Democratic party itself. Senators Jon Tester of Montana and Joe Manchin of West Virginia, two leading moderate Democrats, voiced their concerns on Tuesday. Their apprehensions stem from the devastating terrorist onslaught on Israel, an act of aggression that has tentative links to the Iranian government. The attack, executed by Hamas, resulted in the tragic loss of numerous lives. Tester, who heads the Senate Defense Appropriations Subcommittee, voiced his stance decisively. He asserted that while the probe into Iran’s potential involvement continues, the U.S. must contemplate freezing the $6 billion Iranian assets. Furthermore, he underscored the need to equip Israel with necessary defenses against such harrowing attacks. Manchin, known for his influential role as the chairman of the Senate Energy and Natural Resources Committee, echoed similar sentiments. Not only did he express his sustained skepticism regarding the initial fund transfer to Iran, but he also highlighted the imperative of imposing stringent sanctions on nations found to be backing Hamas. Amplifying the call to action, a coalition of 20 Republican senators has penned a letter to President Biden, emphatically demanding the suspension of Iranian funds currently held in South Korea. The letter elucidates the urgency to reinforce Israel’s position by restricting Iranian financial access. Nevertheless, the White House remains unyielding in its stance. Responding to inquiries about potential reconsiderations regarding the fund release, National Security Advisor Jake Sullivan emphasized that the aforementioned funds remain untouched. The confluence of political voices, transcending party lines, underscores the gravity of the situation. With Israel reeling from a catastrophic terrorist act and Iran’s potential role under scrutiny, Biden’s $6 billion decision is undeniably under the magnifying glass.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Urgent Search for Suspects in Baltimore University Shooting</title><link href="/news/2023/10/11/Baltimore-University-Shooting/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Urgent Search for Suspects in Baltimore University Shooting" /><published>2023-10-11T13:28:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-11T13:28:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/11/Baltimore-University-Shooting</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/11/Baltimore-University-Shooting/">&lt;p&gt;The Baltimore community remains on edge following a shocking shooting at Morgan State University (MSU). Now, Baltimore police are intensifying their search, releasing distinct images of suspects wanted for questioning regarding the incident.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The unsettling event occurred on October 3, amid homecoming festivities at MSU. A sudden burst of gunfire interrupted the joyous celebrations, wounding five individuals between the ages of 18 and 22. Four of these victims were enrolled as students at the university. Fortunately, all five were swiftly taken to a local hospital, treated for non-critical injuries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Baltimore Police Department, demonstrating their commitment to swiftly resolve this case, shared several images on Tuesday of two men believed to be involved. These photos, now widely circulating on social media platforms, portray two Black men, donned in black hoodies and shoes. One distinctively wears ripped blue jeans, while the other is seen in darker jeans, accessorized with a shoulder bag.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The public’s assistance is crucial. The police have sought the community’s help to identify the individuals in the images. Metro Crime Stoppers, in collaboration with the Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, Firearms and Explosives (ATF), has put forth a reward. They are offering up to $9,000 for information that directly leads to an arrest and subsequent charges in the case.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The night of the shooting was marked by heightened tension and fear. Described as an “active shooter situation,” police raced to the scene, discovering multiple shattered windows, evident signs of the violence that had just taken place. MSU authorities, prioritizing the safety of their students, issued a shelter-in-place order which lasted for over two hours. It was lifted only when the police confirmed the situation had stabilized.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Morgan State University stands as a symbol of educational excellence and historical significance. Recognized as a Historically Black College and University (HBCU), it boasts an impressive student body of roughly 9,000. MSU’s roots trace back to 1867, founded as the Centenary Biblical Institute, with the primary purpose of preparing men for ministry roles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The recent shooting has undoubtedly shaken this academic community. Yet, with combined efforts from the police, the university, and the public, there’s hope for justice and continued safety for all students and staff.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">The Baltimore community remains on edge following a shocking shooting at Morgan State University (MSU). Now, Baltimore police are intensifying their search, releasing distinct images of suspects wanted for questioning regarding the incident. The unsettling event occurred on October 3, amid homecoming festivities at MSU. A sudden burst of gunfire interrupted the joyous celebrations, wounding five individuals between the ages of 18 and 22. Four of these victims were enrolled as students at the university. Fortunately, all five were swiftly taken to a local hospital, treated for non-critical injuries. The Baltimore Police Department, demonstrating their commitment to swiftly resolve this case, shared several images on Tuesday of two men believed to be involved. These photos, now widely circulating on social media platforms, portray two Black men, donned in black hoodies and shoes. One distinctively wears ripped blue jeans, while the other is seen in darker jeans, accessorized with a shoulder bag. The public’s assistance is crucial. The police have sought the community’s help to identify the individuals in the images. Metro Crime Stoppers, in collaboration with the Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, Firearms and Explosives (ATF), has put forth a reward. They are offering up to $9,000 for information that directly leads to an arrest and subsequent charges in the case. The night of the shooting was marked by heightened tension and fear. Described as an “active shooter situation,” police raced to the scene, discovering multiple shattered windows, evident signs of the violence that had just taken place. MSU authorities, prioritizing the safety of their students, issued a shelter-in-place order which lasted for over two hours. It was lifted only when the police confirmed the situation had stabilized. Morgan State University stands as a symbol of educational excellence and historical significance. Recognized as a Historically Black College and University (HBCU), it boasts an impressive student body of roughly 9,000. MSU’s roots trace back to 1867, founded as the Centenary Biblical Institute, with the primary purpose of preparing men for ministry roles. The recent shooting has undoubtedly shaken this academic community. Yet, with combined efforts from the police, the university, and the public, there’s hope for justice and continued safety for all students and staff.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump’s Unprecedented Momentum: Wins Over Democrats!</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/11/Trump-Surges-in-Polls/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump’s Unprecedented Momentum: Wins Over Democrats!" /><published>2023-10-11T12:36:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-11T12:36:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/11/Trump-Surges-in-Polls</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/11/Trump-Surges-in-Polls/">&lt;p&gt;The 2024 general election dynamics are gearing up to be quite unexpected. According to the latest Rasmussen poll, Donald Trump, the former President and Republican front-runner, is not only solidifying his strong base but also making unprecedented inroads into the Democratic electorate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A compelling revelation from the poll is that over half of American voters have expressed their intention to cast their vote for Trump. What’s even more intriguing is that 30% of these votes come from Democrats. These numbers are emblematic of Trump’s expanding popularity and his ability to bridge traditional political divides.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump’s overall support from the likely voters surveyed stands strong at 53%. Within this segment, a noteworthy 38% are affirmatively “very likely” to vote for him. This contrasts with the 43% who lean “unlikely” to vote for Trump, and even among them, only 34% have ruled out voting for him completely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump’s outreach has extended beyond the Democrats. He has secured a significant 50% of Black voters and continues to hold the unwavering loyalty of 80% of Republicans. The unaffiliated or independent voters too seem captivated, with 50% leaning towards voting for Trump.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The precision of the Rasmussen poll adds further credence to these figures. Conducted over three days, from October 2nd to 4th, the poll reached out to 1,032 likely voters. The results come with a reassuring 95% confidence level and a manageable margin of error of +/- 3 percentage points.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adding to the positive sentiment around Trump, the poll indicates that the choice of a vice-presidential candidate may not play a pivotal role in influencing Trump’s support base this time around. A staggering 57% asserted they would continue to support Trump regardless of his choice for a running mate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further buoying Trump’s electoral prospects are other polls echoing this favorable sentiment. The Messenger/HarrisX poll reveals Trump leading current President Joe Biden by a margin of 4 points. Conversely, the Morning Consult poll suggests a tighter race with Biden just a point ahead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the run-up to the 2024 elections intensifies, one thing is certain: Trump’s appeal remains formidable, and he continues to challenge conventional political narratives.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">The 2024 general election dynamics are gearing up to be quite unexpected. According to the latest Rasmussen poll, Donald Trump, the former President and Republican front-runner, is not only solidifying his strong base but also making unprecedented inroads into the Democratic electorate. A compelling revelation from the poll is that over half of American voters have expressed their intention to cast their vote for Trump. What’s even more intriguing is that 30% of these votes come from Democrats. These numbers are emblematic of Trump’s expanding popularity and his ability to bridge traditional political divides. Trump’s overall support from the likely voters surveyed stands strong at 53%. Within this segment, a noteworthy 38% are affirmatively “very likely” to vote for him. This contrasts with the 43% who lean “unlikely” to vote for Trump, and even among them, only 34% have ruled out voting for him completely. Trump’s outreach has extended beyond the Democrats. He has secured a significant 50% of Black voters and continues to hold the unwavering loyalty of 80% of Republicans. The unaffiliated or independent voters too seem captivated, with 50% leaning towards voting for Trump. The precision of the Rasmussen poll adds further credence to these figures. Conducted over three days, from October 2nd to 4th, the poll reached out to 1,032 likely voters. The results come with a reassuring 95% confidence level and a manageable margin of error of +/- 3 percentage points. Adding to the positive sentiment around Trump, the poll indicates that the choice of a vice-presidential candidate may not play a pivotal role in influencing Trump’s support base this time around. A staggering 57% asserted they would continue to support Trump regardless of his choice for a running mate. Further buoying Trump’s electoral prospects are other polls echoing this favorable sentiment. The Messenger/HarrisX poll reveals Trump leading current President Joe Biden by a margin of 4 points. Conversely, the Morning Consult poll suggests a tighter race with Biden just a point ahead. As the run-up to the 2024 elections intensifies, one thing is certain: Trump’s appeal remains formidable, and he continues to challenge conventional political narratives.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Traffic Stop Reveals Terrifying Plans for Mass Violence</title><link href="/news/2023/10/11/Man-Stopped-With-Disturbing-Plans/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Traffic Stop Reveals Terrifying Plans for Mass Violence" /><published>2023-10-11T11:25:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-11T11:25:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/11/Man-Stopped-With-Disturbing-Plans</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/11/Man-Stopped-With-Disturbing-Plans/">&lt;p&gt;In a startling turn of events in Palm Beach County, Florida, a routine traffic stop for a broken headlight led to the unearthing of a harrowing plot for mass violence. Authorities have since detained Henry Horton IV, a 19-year-old, who allegedly had detailed plans for mass shootings and stabbing sprees at multiple locations in Florida.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Jupiter police officer responsible for the initial stop found handwritten notes within Horton’s vehicle that highlighted his sinister intentions. The notes explicitly mentioned an objective to “purchase firearms” and “kill everyone at OHS,” which is an abbreviation for Okeechobee High School.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further discussion with Horton uncovered that he aimed to execute these plans on his 22nd birthday. His manifesto included plans for a stabbing spree at the ‘El Rey Jesus’ church in Miami, aiming to harm at least 10 individuals. Tragically, this wasn’t the end of Horton’s alleged violent aspirations. He admitted to conducting reconnaissance at Marjory Stoneman Douglas High School, which experienced a horrific shooting in 2018 that claimed 17 lives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When inquired about his motivation, Horton chillingly stated he sought “attention or fame.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, technology played a role in this case. With Horton’s consent, officers searched his iPhone, uncovering further plans for mass violence. Notes found in his device included alarming statements like, “I want to mass murder 50 people in a single event.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Additionally, he detailed a widespread plan termed “operation MM,” wherein he expressed a wish to rally “112 other people” with a mindset similar to his to commit mass shootings across all Southern states, targeting a total of “1120 people.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Horton’s notes not only displayed his disturbed intentions but also shed light on his personal life. One note read, “I want some of my family dead,” and continued with distressing threats towards his father, stepmother, and boyfriend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Authorities have since arrested Horton based on his statements and the discovered documents, charging him with written threats of violence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The discovery of Horton’s plans serves as a chilling reminder of the hidden threats that may exist within our communities. It also underscores the importance of alert and diligent law enforcement agencies that can help preempt and prevent potential tragedies.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a startling turn of events in Palm Beach County, Florida, a routine traffic stop for a broken headlight led to the unearthing of a harrowing plot for mass violence. Authorities have since detained Henry Horton IV, a 19-year-old, who allegedly had detailed plans for mass shootings and stabbing sprees at multiple locations in Florida. The Jupiter police officer responsible for the initial stop found handwritten notes within Horton’s vehicle that highlighted his sinister intentions. The notes explicitly mentioned an objective to “purchase firearms” and “kill everyone at OHS,” which is an abbreviation for Okeechobee High School. Further discussion with Horton uncovered that he aimed to execute these plans on his 22nd birthday. His manifesto included plans for a stabbing spree at the ‘El Rey Jesus’ church in Miami, aiming to harm at least 10 individuals. Tragically, this wasn’t the end of Horton’s alleged violent aspirations. He admitted to conducting reconnaissance at Marjory Stoneman Douglas High School, which experienced a horrific shooting in 2018 that claimed 17 lives. When inquired about his motivation, Horton chillingly stated he sought “attention or fame.” Interestingly, technology played a role in this case. With Horton’s consent, officers searched his iPhone, uncovering further plans for mass violence. Notes found in his device included alarming statements like, “I want to mass murder 50 people in a single event.” Additionally, he detailed a widespread plan termed “operation MM,” wherein he expressed a wish to rally “112 other people” with a mindset similar to his to commit mass shootings across all Southern states, targeting a total of “1120 people.” Horton’s notes not only displayed his disturbed intentions but also shed light on his personal life. One note read, “I want some of my family dead,” and continued with distressing threats towards his father, stepmother, and boyfriend. Authorities have since arrested Horton based on his statements and the discovered documents, charging him with written threats of violence. The discovery of Horton’s plans serves as a chilling reminder of the hidden threats that may exist within our communities. It also underscores the importance of alert and diligent law enforcement agencies that can help preempt and prevent potential tragedies.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Sen. Tim Scott Holds Biden Accountable for Hamas Attacks</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/11/Biden-Hamas-Criticism/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sen. Tim Scott Holds Biden Accountable for Hamas Attacks" /><published>2023-10-11T10:34:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-11T10:34:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/11/Biden-Hamas-Criticism</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/11/Biden-Hamas-Criticism/">&lt;p&gt;At a recent event hosted by the Hudson Institute, Sen. Tim Scott (R-SC), a 2024 Republican presidential candidate, did not mince words when addressing President Joe Biden’s handling of the recent Hamas terrorist attacks in Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Scott expressed grave concerns, stating that the Biden administration has made “foolish policy choices” which have had detrimental consequences for the U.S. and its allies. Notably, he criticized Biden for the administration’s actions toward Iran, hinting at a lax approach towards a nation notorious for its association with terrorist groups, like Hamas and Hezbollah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Among the actions scrutinized, Scott shed light on the previous administration’s decision to send “pallets of cash to Iran,” despite several warnings that this could empower terrorist factions. Additionally, he criticized the recent move by the Biden administration to release $6 billion to Iran, which was ostensibly for humanitarian purposes. Scott, echoing concerns from many conservatives, questioned the naiveté of such a move, especially given Iran’s track record.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Highlighting the depth of Iran’s involvement with terrorist activities, reports from The Wall Street Journal suggest that Iranian security officials played a pivotal role in planning Hamas’s recent assault on Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Scott’s criticism extended beyond the topic of Iran. He also chided the Biden administration for what he perceives as a diminishing relationship between the U.S. and Israel. In particular, he pointed out perceived slights against Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu, emphasizing that Biden’s actions might have weakened Israel’s position on the global stage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Concluding his critique, Scott made the bold claim that “Biden has blood on his hands,” suggesting that the administration’s policies inadvertently funded terrorism, weakened alliances, and prompted a series of violent events in Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While President Biden, Vice President Kamala Harris, and Secretary of State Antony Blinken have reiterated America’s unwavering support for Israel, Scott remains skeptical, emphasizing the need for a more proactive and loyal approach to U.S. allies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthering his remarks, Scott also took aim at some of his GOP counterparts, including Gov. Ron DeSantis (R-FL) and Vivek Ramaswamy. He expressed concerns over certain views that could be detrimental to U.S. foreign policies, hinting at the need for a unified front against threats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the presidential race intensifies, candidates like Scott are keen on addressing the pressing issues facing the nation. With foreign policy at the forefront, the nation waits to see how these critiques shape the next phase of political discourse and potential policy changes.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">At a recent event hosted by the Hudson Institute, Sen. Tim Scott (R-SC), a 2024 Republican presidential candidate, did not mince words when addressing President Joe Biden’s handling of the recent Hamas terrorist attacks in Israel. Scott expressed grave concerns, stating that the Biden administration has made “foolish policy choices” which have had detrimental consequences for the U.S. and its allies. Notably, he criticized Biden for the administration’s actions toward Iran, hinting at a lax approach towards a nation notorious for its association with terrorist groups, like Hamas and Hezbollah. Among the actions scrutinized, Scott shed light on the previous administration’s decision to send “pallets of cash to Iran,” despite several warnings that this could empower terrorist factions. Additionally, he criticized the recent move by the Biden administration to release $6 billion to Iran, which was ostensibly for humanitarian purposes. Scott, echoing concerns from many conservatives, questioned the naiveté of such a move, especially given Iran’s track record. Highlighting the depth of Iran’s involvement with terrorist activities, reports from The Wall Street Journal suggest that Iranian security officials played a pivotal role in planning Hamas’s recent assault on Israel. Scott’s criticism extended beyond the topic of Iran. He also chided the Biden administration for what he perceives as a diminishing relationship between the U.S. and Israel. In particular, he pointed out perceived slights against Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu, emphasizing that Biden’s actions might have weakened Israel’s position on the global stage. Concluding his critique, Scott made the bold claim that “Biden has blood on his hands,” suggesting that the administration’s policies inadvertently funded terrorism, weakened alliances, and prompted a series of violent events in Israel. While President Biden, Vice President Kamala Harris, and Secretary of State Antony Blinken have reiterated America’s unwavering support for Israel, Scott remains skeptical, emphasizing the need for a more proactive and loyal approach to U.S. allies. Furthering his remarks, Scott also took aim at some of his GOP counterparts, including Gov. Ron DeSantis (R-FL) and Vivek Ramaswamy. He expressed concerns over certain views that could be detrimental to U.S. foreign policies, hinting at the need for a unified front against threats. As the presidential race intensifies, candidates like Scott are keen on addressing the pressing issues facing the nation. With foreign policy at the forefront, the nation waits to see how these critiques shape the next phase of political discourse and potential policy changes.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Utah Takes on TikTok: State Sues Over Child Addiction Concerns</title><link href="/news/2023/10/11/TikTok-Lawsuit-Utah/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Utah Takes on TikTok: State Sues Over Child Addiction Concerns" /><published>2023-10-11T09:20:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-11T09:20:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/11/TikTok-Lawsuit-Utah</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/11/TikTok-Lawsuit-Utah/">&lt;p&gt;In a bold move against social media titan TikTok, the state of Utah has launched a lawsuit, accusing the platform of creating and promoting addictive behaviors among its younger users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Highlighting the significant role social media plays in the lives of the youth, the lawsuit, announced on Tuesday, asserts that TikTok is deliberately “baiting” children into unhealthy, prolonged usage habits. These alleged deceptive strategies not only encompass content delivery but also misrepresentation about the app’s affiliation with its parent company, ByteDance, based in China.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Utah Governor Spencer Cox emphasized the state’s commitment to safeguarding its children from potentially harmful social media practices, stating, “We will not stand by while these companies fail to take adequate, meaningful action to protect our children.” This lawsuit, filed in Salt Lake City’s state court, builds on similar legal actions initiated by Arkansas and Indiana. Meanwhile, the broader implications of state-driven social media regulations are slated for consideration by the U.S. Supreme Court.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Key elements of the Utah lawsuit revolve around public health concerns. The suit references various studies, pointing out that children dedicating more than three hours daily to social media platforms are more susceptible to mental health issues, such as anxiety and depression.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sean Reyes, Utah’s Attorney General, likened TikTok’s algorithm to a “cruel slot machine,” purposefully designed to capture and retain children’s attention. The main objective of this lawsuit is not only to drive TikTok towards more responsible behavior but also to secure penalties and fines. These funds would be directed towards educational initiatives and other mechanisms that could address the alleged harm caused to Utah’s younger demographic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TikTok’s response to this lawsuit is yet awaited, with spokesperson Hilary McQuaide not immediately providing any comment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, Utah has been at the forefront of driving regulations around children’s social media usage. Earlier in the year, the state passed pioneering laws to curtail children and teen engagement with apps like TikTok. These new regulations, set to be effective from next year, entail a digital curfew for individuals under 18. Further, they enforce parental consent requirements for minor sign-ups and age verification for all Utah-based users. Additionally, tech firms would be mandated to grant parents access to their children’s private accounts, a move which has stirred concerns about infringing on children’s privacy rights, especially for those in the LGBTQ+ community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the battle lines are drawn between state authorities and tech giants, the focal point remains the welfare and protection of young users in an increasingly digital age.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a bold move against social media titan TikTok, the state of Utah has launched a lawsuit, accusing the platform of creating and promoting addictive behaviors among its younger users. Highlighting the significant role social media plays in the lives of the youth, the lawsuit, announced on Tuesday, asserts that TikTok is deliberately “baiting” children into unhealthy, prolonged usage habits. These alleged deceptive strategies not only encompass content delivery but also misrepresentation about the app’s affiliation with its parent company, ByteDance, based in China. Utah Governor Spencer Cox emphasized the state’s commitment to safeguarding its children from potentially harmful social media practices, stating, “We will not stand by while these companies fail to take adequate, meaningful action to protect our children.” This lawsuit, filed in Salt Lake City’s state court, builds on similar legal actions initiated by Arkansas and Indiana. Meanwhile, the broader implications of state-driven social media regulations are slated for consideration by the U.S. Supreme Court. Key elements of the Utah lawsuit revolve around public health concerns. The suit references various studies, pointing out that children dedicating more than three hours daily to social media platforms are more susceptible to mental health issues, such as anxiety and depression. Sean Reyes, Utah’s Attorney General, likened TikTok’s algorithm to a “cruel slot machine,” purposefully designed to capture and retain children’s attention. The main objective of this lawsuit is not only to drive TikTok towards more responsible behavior but also to secure penalties and fines. These funds would be directed towards educational initiatives and other mechanisms that could address the alleged harm caused to Utah’s younger demographic. TikTok’s response to this lawsuit is yet awaited, with spokesperson Hilary McQuaide not immediately providing any comment. Interestingly, Utah has been at the forefront of driving regulations around children’s social media usage. Earlier in the year, the state passed pioneering laws to curtail children and teen engagement with apps like TikTok. These new regulations, set to be effective from next year, entail a digital curfew for individuals under 18. Further, they enforce parental consent requirements for minor sign-ups and age verification for all Utah-based users. Additionally, tech firms would be mandated to grant parents access to their children’s private accounts, a move which has stirred concerns about infringing on children’s privacy rights, especially for those in the LGBTQ+ community. As the battle lines are drawn between state authorities and tech giants, the focal point remains the welfare and protection of young users in an increasingly digital age.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Bomb Threat Shuts Down Santa Monica Pier: Ferris Wheel Drama Ends Peacefully</title><link href="/news/2023/10/11/Bomb-Threat-Santa-Monica/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bomb Threat Shuts Down Santa Monica Pier: Ferris Wheel Drama Ends Peacefully" /><published>2023-10-11T08:17:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-11T08:17:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/11/Bomb-Threat-Santa-Monica</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/11/Bomb-Threat-Santa-Monica/">&lt;p&gt;In a shocking turn of events, a man scaled the Ferris wheel at Santa Monica Pier on Monday, causing a major scare by claiming he possessed a bomb. The iconic tourist destination was swiftly evacuated amidst the growing alarm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Early in the afternoon, onlookers watched in a mix of horror and curiosity as the man climbed the famed Ferris wheel. Witnesses reported overhearing the man’s bomb claims, prompting immediate action by local authorities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Santa Monica Police Department’s Crisis Negotiation Team was promptly dispatched to the scene. As a precaution, both the pier and its adjoining amusement park were cleared of all visitors. Police took to social media to confirm the incident, underscoring the serious nature of the threat and the immediate actions taken.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The standoff reached its conclusion around 4:15 p.m., with police taking the man into custody. Authorities thoroughly inspected the scene and, much to everyone’s relief, announced that no bomb or other explosive device was discovered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Several bystanders captured the event on their mobile devices, and footage revealed officers tackling the man as he descended from the Ferris wheel. These visuals quickly made their way to social media platforms and news outlets, amplifying the tension and drama of the situation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adding to the tension, dozens of visitors were left stranded on the Ferris wheel during the crisis. Their prolonged wait in the gondolas only added to the palpable anxiety of the situation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This incident, while thankfully resolved without any injuries or actual threats, underscores the vulnerabilities of public spaces and the challenges law enforcement agencies face. Vigilance and quick response from both the public and authorities were critical in ensuring that the situation didn’t escalate further.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Santa Monica Pier, a symbol of joy and recreation for many, became the center of a tense showdown, reminding all of the unpredictabilities of public spaces and the importance of safety protocols.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a shocking turn of events, a man scaled the Ferris wheel at Santa Monica Pier on Monday, causing a major scare by claiming he possessed a bomb. The iconic tourist destination was swiftly evacuated amidst the growing alarm. Early in the afternoon, onlookers watched in a mix of horror and curiosity as the man climbed the famed Ferris wheel. Witnesses reported overhearing the man’s bomb claims, prompting immediate action by local authorities. The Santa Monica Police Department’s Crisis Negotiation Team was promptly dispatched to the scene. As a precaution, both the pier and its adjoining amusement park were cleared of all visitors. Police took to social media to confirm the incident, underscoring the serious nature of the threat and the immediate actions taken. The standoff reached its conclusion around 4:15 p.m., with police taking the man into custody. Authorities thoroughly inspected the scene and, much to everyone’s relief, announced that no bomb or other explosive device was discovered. Several bystanders captured the event on their mobile devices, and footage revealed officers tackling the man as he descended from the Ferris wheel. These visuals quickly made their way to social media platforms and news outlets, amplifying the tension and drama of the situation. Adding to the tension, dozens of visitors were left stranded on the Ferris wheel during the crisis. Their prolonged wait in the gondolas only added to the palpable anxiety of the situation. This incident, while thankfully resolved without any injuries or actual threats, underscores the vulnerabilities of public spaces and the challenges law enforcement agencies face. Vigilance and quick response from both the public and authorities were critical in ensuring that the situation didn’t escalate further. The Santa Monica Pier, a symbol of joy and recreation for many, became the center of a tense showdown, reminding all of the unpredictabilities of public spaces and the importance of safety protocols.</summary></entry></feed>