<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-10-21T12:18:45-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/21/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-21T12:18:45-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-21T12:18:45-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/21/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/21/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/21/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-21T12:18:45-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-21T12:18:45-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/21/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/21/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/">&lt;p&gt;Recent surprise attacks by Hamas on Israel has fueled ongoing tensions between staunchly conservative commentators and the progressive “Squad” Democrats known for criticizing Israel. The intensity of the backlash highlights the deep political divide over foreign policy in the Middle East.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Hamas’ shocking attack, several members of the “Squad,” including Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.), called for a “ceasefire and de-escalation,” condemning the violence. The absence of a statement from Rep. Rashida Tlaib (D-Mich.) was notably called out by conservative media outlets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;South Carolina GOP Rep. Nancy Mace quickly labeled Ocasio-Cortez a “Hamas apologist” in response to her call for peace and de-escalation. Rep. Ilhan Omar (D-Minn.), no stranger to controversy surrounding her views on Israel, echoed the call for de-escalation and ceasefire. Omar’s prior statements comparing the US and Israel to terrorist groups like Hamas and the Taliban resurfaced in the debate, fueling more criticisms. Omar’s 2019 tweet, where she opined that “Israel has hypnotized the world,” also continues to haunt her political career, often cited by critics to challenge her stance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conservative commentators have been especially vocal. “FOX &amp;amp; Friends Weekend” co-host Rachel Campos-Duffy took aim at Omar, saying she fails to recognize the peace in the Middle East under Trump’s administration. Conservative pundit John Hasson also called out Omar, claiming she insinuated that attacks on IDF forces were acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Massachusetts Democrat Rep. Ayanna Pressley’s concerns over the “devastating attacks on Israelis” were met with skepticism. A prominent conservative online personality, Comfortably Smug, accused the “Squad” of advising Israel to back down after the nation suffered massive attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Jamaal Bowman’s call for an end to the Gaza blockade, in addition to condemning the Hamas attacks, was met with criticism from conservative radio host Jason Rantz. He accused Bowman of pairing his condemnation of terrorism with unwarranted criticisms of Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Cori Bush emphasized the urgent need for a ceasefire, while pushing for an end to “U.S. support for Israeli military occupation and apartheid.” Defense attorney Marina Medvin criticized Bush, suggesting that she equates the death of Palestinian terrorists to the horrific acts committed against Jewish civilians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amidst the political turmoil and intense debate, the attacks have taken a heavy toll. Israeli media report over 300 dead due to the wide-ranging assault. Gaza health officials note that at least 200 Palestinians have perished in the retaliatory Israeli air strikes following the initial Hamas attack. As the situation remains volatile, both sides continue to count their casualties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This divisive issue showcases the challenge America faces in crafting a unified approach to foreign policy, with deeply entrenched political divides at play. As the situation develops, the debate is bound to intensify, shedding light on the complexities of U.S. politics in the global arena.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Unraveling the Biden Financial Web: $200K Transaction Under Scrutiny</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/21/Biden-Family-Financial-Dealings/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Unraveling the Biden Financial Web: $200K Transaction Under Scrutiny" /><published>2023-10-21T08:12:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-21T08:12:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/21/Biden-Family-Financial-Dealings</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/21/Biden-Family-Financial-Dealings/">&lt;p&gt;A recent revelation suggests that President Joe Biden may have been entangled in his family’s controversial financial dealings. House Oversight Committee Chair, James Comer (R-Ky.), announced on Friday that bank records indicate James and Sara Biden, Joe Biden’s brother and sister-in-law respectively, paid him a hefty sum of $200,000 via a personal check in March 2018.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This financial transaction has ignited debates, with critics suggesting that it offers proof of the Biden family’s alleged influence-peddling operations. “This is more than just a personal transaction; it hints at how President Biden could have potentially benefited from his family’s questionable use of his name and their access to him,” Comer commented in a video statement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Digging deeper into the financial trail, James Biden, in 2018, secured loans amounting to $600,000 from Americore, a company known for its financial struggles as a rural hospital operator. Bankruptcy court records imply that James Biden leveraged his familial ties, asserting that his surname “Biden” had the power to “open doors” and that he could fetch a substantial investment from the Middle East, banking on his political affiliations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Intriguingly, on March 1, 2018, Americore transferred a $200,000 loan to James and Sara Biden’s personal bank account. The same day, James Biden funneled the exact amount to Joe Biden, labeling it as a “loan repayment.” Comer emphasized the dubious nature of this transaction, saying, “Even if it’s categorized as a personal loan repayment, the fact remains that Joe Biden’s reimbursement from his brother hinged on the success of questionable financial arrangements.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Joe Biden is now under pressure to shed light on these findings. Comer is demanding clarity on several fronts: Is there concrete evidence that Joe Biden had indeed loaned $200,000 to his brother? What were the terms of this financial agreement?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, Comer raises the possibility of other similar financial agreements with family members. “Could there be other family members who have made similar substantial payments to him?” Comer posits in the video.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, while the nature of family financial entanglements isn’t uncommon, when it concerns the first family of the nation, transparency and clarity become paramount. The coming days will undoubtedly see heightened scrutiny and demand for answers from the President and his family regarding these allegations.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">A recent revelation suggests that President Joe Biden may have been entangled in his family’s controversial financial dealings. House Oversight Committee Chair, James Comer (R-Ky.), announced on Friday that bank records indicate James and Sara Biden, Joe Biden’s brother and sister-in-law respectively, paid him a hefty sum of $200,000 via a personal check in March 2018. This financial transaction has ignited debates, with critics suggesting that it offers proof of the Biden family’s alleged influence-peddling operations. “This is more than just a personal transaction; it hints at how President Biden could have potentially benefited from his family’s questionable use of his name and their access to him,” Comer commented in a video statement. Digging deeper into the financial trail, James Biden, in 2018, secured loans amounting to $600,000 from Americore, a company known for its financial struggles as a rural hospital operator. Bankruptcy court records imply that James Biden leveraged his familial ties, asserting that his surname “Biden” had the power to “open doors” and that he could fetch a substantial investment from the Middle East, banking on his political affiliations. Intriguingly, on March 1, 2018, Americore transferred a $200,000 loan to James and Sara Biden’s personal bank account. The same day, James Biden funneled the exact amount to Joe Biden, labeling it as a “loan repayment.” Comer emphasized the dubious nature of this transaction, saying, “Even if it’s categorized as a personal loan repayment, the fact remains that Joe Biden’s reimbursement from his brother hinged on the success of questionable financial arrangements.” Joe Biden is now under pressure to shed light on these findings. Comer is demanding clarity on several fronts: Is there concrete evidence that Joe Biden had indeed loaned $200,000 to his brother? What were the terms of this financial agreement? Furthermore, Comer raises the possibility of other similar financial agreements with family members. “Could there be other family members who have made similar substantial payments to him?” Comer posits in the video. In conclusion, while the nature of family financial entanglements isn’t uncommon, when it concerns the first family of the nation, transparency and clarity become paramount. The coming days will undoubtedly see heightened scrutiny and demand for answers from the President and his family regarding these allegations.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Maryland Judge Assassinated Following Divorce Ruling</title><link href="/news/2023/10/21/Maryland-Judge-Targeted-Attack/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Maryland Judge Assassinated Following Divorce Ruling" /><published>2023-10-21T07:01:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-21T07:01:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/21/Maryland-Judge-Targeted-Attack</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/21/Maryland-Judge-Targeted-Attack/">&lt;p&gt;Maryland’s Circuit Court Judge Andrew Wilkinson from Hagerstown was brutally gunned down outside his home on Thursday evening. This tragic incident is believed to be a retaliatory act following a judgment in a divorce hearing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Authorities from the Washington County Sheriff’s Office quickly identified the prime suspect, Pedro Argote, who had a direct link to the judgment. Earlier that day, Judge Wilkinson had granted child custody to a woman amidst Argote’s divorce proceedings. Interestingly, Argote was absent during the hearing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“This wasn’t random. It was a targeted attack on Judge Wilkinson,” declared Washington County Sheriff Brian K. Albert in a press briefing on Friday. The sheriff’s office has warned the public that Argote, 49, is still on the loose, armed, and could be dangerous. Notably, he is a legal owner of a firearm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2023/10/720/405/394512179_711778497658852_1440711396504505403_n-1.jpg?ve=1&amp;amp;tl=1&quot; alt=&quot;Pedro Argote&apos;s vehicle&quot; /&gt;(Washington County Sheriff)
&lt;em&gt;Authorities have identified Pedro Argote’s car as a silver 2009 Mercedes GL450 with Maryland registration plates reading 4EH0408.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The violent episode took place post 8 p.m. on Olde Waterford Road in Hagerstown. Judge Wilkinson, 52 at the time of his death, was ambushed in his driveway while his wife and son were inside the house. He was rushed to Meritus Medical Center but was pronounced dead on arrival.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Records revealed that authorities had been previously called to Argote’s residence on two separate occasions in response to “verbal domestic assaults.” However, Pedro Argote had managed to maintain a clean slate, with no prior criminal record in Washington County.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wilkinson’s association with the 4th Judicial Circuit began in 2020. Born in Guam in 1971, the judge earned his credentials from the prestigious University of North Carolina and later, the Emory University School of Law.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2023/10/720/405/394013405_711778427658859_1493866060322353593_n-1.jpg?ve=1&amp;amp;tl=1&quot; alt=&quot;Pedro Argote&quot; /&gt;(Washington County Sheriff)
&lt;em&gt;Washington County Sheriff’s Office on Friday named Pedro Argote as a suspect.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the hunt for Argote intensifies, Washington County court records have provided an intriguing insight: Judge Wilkinson had been overseeing Argote’s divorce case since 2022. The next scheduled hearing was set for October 31st.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The alarming nature of the assassination raises concerns over the security of judiciary officials. However, the sheriff’s office has clarified that there seems to be no ongoing threat to other judges in the vicinity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This incident serves as a brutal reminder of the dangers public servants might face, emphasizing the need for heightened security measures and precautions.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Maryland’s Circuit Court Judge Andrew Wilkinson from Hagerstown was brutally gunned down outside his home on Thursday evening. This tragic incident is believed to be a retaliatory act following a judgment in a divorce hearing. Authorities from the Washington County Sheriff’s Office quickly identified the prime suspect, Pedro Argote, who had a direct link to the judgment. Earlier that day, Judge Wilkinson had granted child custody to a woman amidst Argote’s divorce proceedings. Interestingly, Argote was absent during the hearing. “This wasn’t random. It was a targeted attack on Judge Wilkinson,” declared Washington County Sheriff Brian K. Albert in a press briefing on Friday. The sheriff’s office has warned the public that Argote, 49, is still on the loose, armed, and could be dangerous. Notably, he is a legal owner of a firearm. (Washington County Sheriff) Authorities have identified Pedro Argote’s car as a silver 2009 Mercedes GL450 with Maryland registration plates reading 4EH0408. The violent episode took place post 8 p.m. on Olde Waterford Road in Hagerstown. Judge Wilkinson, 52 at the time of his death, was ambushed in his driveway while his wife and son were inside the house. He was rushed to Meritus Medical Center but was pronounced dead on arrival. Records revealed that authorities had been previously called to Argote’s residence on two separate occasions in response to “verbal domestic assaults.” However, Pedro Argote had managed to maintain a clean slate, with no prior criminal record in Washington County. Wilkinson’s association with the 4th Judicial Circuit began in 2020. Born in Guam in 1971, the judge earned his credentials from the prestigious University of North Carolina and later, the Emory University School of Law. (Washington County Sheriff) Washington County Sheriff’s Office on Friday named Pedro Argote as a suspect. While the hunt for Argote intensifies, Washington County court records have provided an intriguing insight: Judge Wilkinson had been overseeing Argote’s divorce case since 2022. The next scheduled hearing was set for October 31st. The alarming nature of the assassination raises concerns over the security of judiciary officials. However, the sheriff’s office has clarified that there seems to be no ongoing threat to other judges in the vicinity. This incident serves as a brutal reminder of the dangers public servants might face, emphasizing the need for heightened security measures and precautions.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Wokeness Takes a Toll: ESPN’s Profits Plunge by 20%</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/21/Wokeness-Hits-ESPN-Profit/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Wokeness Takes a Toll: ESPN’s Profits Plunge by 20%" /><published>2023-10-21T06:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-21T06:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/21/Wokeness-Hits-ESPN-Profit</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/21/Wokeness-Hits-ESPN-Profit/">&lt;p&gt;In a surprising revelation, Disney disclosed that the profits for its sports division, ESPN, have plummeted by a staggering 20% in the first nine months of the year. While the decline in profits is attributable to multiple factors, the increasingly ‘woke’ content strategy adopted by ESPN appears to be a significant contributor to this downturn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite a series of massive layoffs which included big names like Keyshawn Johnson, Max Kellerman, Steve Young, Suzy Kolber, and others, the sports network’s finances show no signs of revival. Revenues for ESPN were at $13.2 billion over the first nine months of 2023, which marks a 1.3% drop compared to the same period in the previous fiscal year, as per a report by Front Office Sports.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the global shift from cable to streaming services is undoubtedly affecting all traditional broadcasters, with cable viewership slipping below 50% of total TV usage in the U.S. for the first time in decades, the extent of ESPN’s woes can’t be attributed to this transition alone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ESPN, historically known for its sports-centric content, seems to be diving deep into the realm of ‘wokeness’ — a decision that hasn’t resonated well with its core audience. The channel’s latest venture into a show exploring “racism” in sports, fronted by the controversial figure Ibram X. Kendi, is a prime example. Kendi, known for his so-called “Center for Antiracist Research”, has faced multiple accusations and has recently laid off more than half the staff from his organization after being accused of squandering $43 million in donations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sports broadcasting fees, especially for prime content, are surging as well. ESPN is now shelling out a whopping $2.7 billion every year to the NFL for rights that include Monday Night Football and the Super Bowl. These rising costs, coupled with declining revenues, are squeezing the channel’s profit margins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the financial decline and backlash from segments of their viewership, it seems like ESPN, under Disney’s ownership, continues to drift further into left-leaning political agendas and content strategies. This shift appears to be alienating a significant portion of their traditional audience who are looking for pure sports content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, while the changing landscape of TV viewership is a challenge that all broadcasters need to navigate, ESPN’s current profit loss seems to be amplified by its insistence on integrating ‘wokeness’ into its programming. If they aim to revive their fortunes, a return to sports-centric content without the overlay of heavy political commentary might be the way forward.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">In a surprising revelation, Disney disclosed that the profits for its sports division, ESPN, have plummeted by a staggering 20% in the first nine months of the year. While the decline in profits is attributable to multiple factors, the increasingly ‘woke’ content strategy adopted by ESPN appears to be a significant contributor to this downturn. Despite a series of massive layoffs which included big names like Keyshawn Johnson, Max Kellerman, Steve Young, Suzy Kolber, and others, the sports network’s finances show no signs of revival. Revenues for ESPN were at $13.2 billion over the first nine months of 2023, which marks a 1.3% drop compared to the same period in the previous fiscal year, as per a report by Front Office Sports. While the global shift from cable to streaming services is undoubtedly affecting all traditional broadcasters, with cable viewership slipping below 50% of total TV usage in the U.S. for the first time in decades, the extent of ESPN’s woes can’t be attributed to this transition alone. ESPN, historically known for its sports-centric content, seems to be diving deep into the realm of ‘wokeness’ — a decision that hasn’t resonated well with its core audience. The channel’s latest venture into a show exploring “racism” in sports, fronted by the controversial figure Ibram X. Kendi, is a prime example. Kendi, known for his so-called “Center for Antiracist Research”, has faced multiple accusations and has recently laid off more than half the staff from his organization after being accused of squandering $43 million in donations. Sports broadcasting fees, especially for prime content, are surging as well. ESPN is now shelling out a whopping $2.7 billion every year to the NFL for rights that include Monday Night Football and the Super Bowl. These rising costs, coupled with declining revenues, are squeezing the channel’s profit margins. Despite the financial decline and backlash from segments of their viewership, it seems like ESPN, under Disney’s ownership, continues to drift further into left-leaning political agendas and content strategies. This shift appears to be alienating a significant portion of their traditional audience who are looking for pure sports content. In conclusion, while the changing landscape of TV viewership is a challenge that all broadcasters need to navigate, ESPN’s current profit loss seems to be amplified by its insistence on integrating ‘wokeness’ into its programming. If they aim to revive their fortunes, a return to sports-centric content without the overlay of heavy political commentary might be the way forward.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Cory Booker Cowers from Rockets He Helped Give Iran In Deal</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/20/Corey-Booker-Israel-Stance/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Cory Booker Cowers from Rockets He Helped Give Iran In Deal" /><published>2023-10-20T15:25:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-20T15:25:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/20/Corey-Booker-Israel-Stance</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/20/Corey-Booker-Israel-Stance/">&lt;p&gt;The recent attacks in Israel and the ongoing geopolitical tensions in the Middle East have brought renewed focus on U.S. political leaders and their positions concerning the region. Among those under the lens is Senator Cory Booker, a notable figure who has, in the past, shown a special connection to Israel. But his controversial decision regarding the Iran Nuclear Deal has raised eyebrows and led to questions about his real stance on the U.S.-Israel relationship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2015, Cory Booker supported the Joint Comprehensive Plan of Action (JCPOA), more commonly referred to as the Iran Deal. This move, which provided Iran with access to $150 billion and legitimized their nuclear program, was seen by many as a significant risk, with fears that the funds could indirectly support groups antagonistic to Israel. Critics argue that the deal, rather than ensuring peace, could inadvertently bolster enemies of Israel, such as the militant group, Hamas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Booker’s decision to support the JCPOA came as a surprise to many who saw him as a staunch supporter of Israel. His bond with the nation was evident during numerous visits, including his initial trip, arranged by Rabbi Shmuley Boteach in 1994. The Rabbi recalls their close relationship, forged over decades, with a shared love for Israel at its center.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet, the choice to back the JCPOA seemed to eclipse this connection, leading to a public fallout between Booker and Rabbi Boteach. The Rabbi even held a press conference alongside then-Governor Chris Christie, decrying Booker’s decision as aiding global terror.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recent events in Israel, particularly the horrors of the October 7th massacre, have intensified the scrutiny on Booker. While President Joe Biden and other U.S. officials traveled to Israel in a show of solidarity, Booker’s hasty departure from the country during this crisis further fueled criticisms of his commitment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contrasting Booker’s reaction to the events in Israel with the responses of other U.S. officials, such as Senator Joni Ernst and Senate Majority Leader Chuck Schumer, underscores the dichotomy. While these leaders showed solidarity by visiting the nation during its time of need, Booker’s abrupt exit left many questioning his allegiance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This episode has also unearthed older political decisions, like Booker’s relationship with Senator Robert Menendez. Despite once testifying to Menendez’s character during a corruption trial, Booker later called for his resignation upon Menendez’s indictment by the FBI on other charges. Critics argue that Booker’s political decisions often seem influenced more by personal ambition than moral conviction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, Senator Cory Booker’s actions concerning Israel and the JCPOA continue to spark debates. While his history with Israel is deeply rooted, his more recent decisions paint a complex picture, leaving many to ponder the true nature of his stance on U.S.-Israel relations.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">The recent attacks in Israel and the ongoing geopolitical tensions in the Middle East have brought renewed focus on U.S. political leaders and their positions concerning the region. Among those under the lens is Senator Cory Booker, a notable figure who has, in the past, shown a special connection to Israel. But his controversial decision regarding the Iran Nuclear Deal has raised eyebrows and led to questions about his real stance on the U.S.-Israel relationship. In 2015, Cory Booker supported the Joint Comprehensive Plan of Action (JCPOA), more commonly referred to as the Iran Deal. This move, which provided Iran with access to $150 billion and legitimized their nuclear program, was seen by many as a significant risk, with fears that the funds could indirectly support groups antagonistic to Israel. Critics argue that the deal, rather than ensuring peace, could inadvertently bolster enemies of Israel, such as the militant group, Hamas. Booker’s decision to support the JCPOA came as a surprise to many who saw him as a staunch supporter of Israel. His bond with the nation was evident during numerous visits, including his initial trip, arranged by Rabbi Shmuley Boteach in 1994. The Rabbi recalls their close relationship, forged over decades, with a shared love for Israel at its center. Yet, the choice to back the JCPOA seemed to eclipse this connection, leading to a public fallout between Booker and Rabbi Boteach. The Rabbi even held a press conference alongside then-Governor Chris Christie, decrying Booker’s decision as aiding global terror. Recent events in Israel, particularly the horrors of the October 7th massacre, have intensified the scrutiny on Booker. While President Joe Biden and other U.S. officials traveled to Israel in a show of solidarity, Booker’s hasty departure from the country during this crisis further fueled criticisms of his commitment. Contrasting Booker’s reaction to the events in Israel with the responses of other U.S. officials, such as Senator Joni Ernst and Senate Majority Leader Chuck Schumer, underscores the dichotomy. While these leaders showed solidarity by visiting the nation during its time of need, Booker’s abrupt exit left many questioning his allegiance. This episode has also unearthed older political decisions, like Booker’s relationship with Senator Robert Menendez. Despite once testifying to Menendez’s character during a corruption trial, Booker later called for his resignation upon Menendez’s indictment by the FBI on other charges. Critics argue that Booker’s political decisions often seem influenced more by personal ambition than moral conviction. In conclusion, Senator Cory Booker’s actions concerning Israel and the JCPOA continue to spark debates. While his history with Israel is deeply rooted, his more recent decisions paint a complex picture, leaving many to ponder the true nature of his stance on U.S.-Israel relations.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Inspector Sounds Alarm on Biden’s $400 Billion Green Energy Program</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/20/Green-Energy-Loan-Concerns/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Inspector Sounds Alarm on Biden’s $400 Billion Green Energy Program" /><published>2023-10-20T14:12:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-20T14:12:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/20/Green-Energy-Loan-Concerns</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/20/Green-Energy-Loan-Concerns/">&lt;p&gt;Amidst the rush towards green energy, U.S. Department of Energy (DOE) Inspector General Teri Donaldson has fired a warning shot, suggesting the Biden administration’s colossal $400 billion green energy loan initiative could be susceptible to abuse. This potential mishandling of taxpayer money raises valid concerns over the government’s capacity to effectively manage such a gargantuan sum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During her testimony to the Senate Energy and Natural Resources Committee, Donaldson pointed out that the sheer magnitude of the funds, coupled with the speed at which they are to be distributed, creates a “level of risk that may be unprecedented.” She cited concerns over possible foreign entanglements that could slip through without detection, highlighting that vast sums of money moving so swiftly across a complicated landscape is a perfect storm for oversight challenges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To give a clearer perspective on the scope of this program, Donaldson compared the green energy loan size to that of Wells Fargo’s domestic commercial and industrial loan balance, which stood at $292 billion at the end of 2022. It’s worth noting that many of the projects funded are so innovative that they aren’t deemed acceptable by private equity investors—projects the market views as risky.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, Donaldson’s concerns don’t stop there. She also highlighted issues with the DOE’s vetting center, which, despite being a positive step towards transparency and accountability, still lacks adequate staffing and clear procedures. This is alarming, especially when considering that decisions about which projects will be vetted and the criteria for those vettings remain unclear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Topping it off, a joint report from Sen. John Barrasso and Rep. Cathy McMorris Rodgers stressed “multiple levels of failure” in the creation and execution of the Inflation Reduction Act (IRA). The report underscored potential conflicts of interest and even the possibility of indirectly benefiting Chinese industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While it’s undeniable that pushing for green energy is a step in the right direction for a sustainable future, it’s essential that taxpayer money is handled with the utmost care and transparency. As the nation grapples with this enormous expenditure, it’s crucial that officials take heed of these warnings and ensure that the green energy loan program is not only effective but also free from potential abuses.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Amidst the rush towards green energy, U.S. Department of Energy (DOE) Inspector General Teri Donaldson has fired a warning shot, suggesting the Biden administration’s colossal $400 billion green energy loan initiative could be susceptible to abuse. This potential mishandling of taxpayer money raises valid concerns over the government’s capacity to effectively manage such a gargantuan sum. During her testimony to the Senate Energy and Natural Resources Committee, Donaldson pointed out that the sheer magnitude of the funds, coupled with the speed at which they are to be distributed, creates a “level of risk that may be unprecedented.” She cited concerns over possible foreign entanglements that could slip through without detection, highlighting that vast sums of money moving so swiftly across a complicated landscape is a perfect storm for oversight challenges. To give a clearer perspective on the scope of this program, Donaldson compared the green energy loan size to that of Wells Fargo’s domestic commercial and industrial loan balance, which stood at $292 billion at the end of 2022. It’s worth noting that many of the projects funded are so innovative that they aren’t deemed acceptable by private equity investors—projects the market views as risky. However, Donaldson’s concerns don’t stop there. She also highlighted issues with the DOE’s vetting center, which, despite being a positive step towards transparency and accountability, still lacks adequate staffing and clear procedures. This is alarming, especially when considering that decisions about which projects will be vetted and the criteria for those vettings remain unclear. Topping it off, a joint report from Sen. John Barrasso and Rep. Cathy McMorris Rodgers stressed “multiple levels of failure” in the creation and execution of the Inflation Reduction Act (IRA). The report underscored potential conflicts of interest and even the possibility of indirectly benefiting Chinese industry. While it’s undeniable that pushing for green energy is a step in the right direction for a sustainable future, it’s essential that taxpayer money is handled with the utmost care and transparency. As the nation grapples with this enormous expenditure, it’s crucial that officials take heed of these warnings and ensure that the green energy loan program is not only effective but also free from potential abuses.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Biden’s Alarming Silence: US Forces Under Attack</title><link href="/news/2023/10/20/Biden-Silence-Attacks/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Biden’s Alarming Silence: US Forces Under Attack" /><published>2023-10-20T13:04:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-20T13:04:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/20/Biden-Silence-Attacks</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/20/Biden-Silence-Attacks/">&lt;p&gt;In a shocking display of seeming negligence, President Joe Biden has failed to publicly address a series of attacks on U.S. forces in Iraq and Syria. Within the past 48 hours, our troops have faced at least seven targeted aggressions, and the nation’s Commander in Chief has been eerily silent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reports confirm that U.S. officials have been aware of the continued attacks in the region, particularly with the ongoing tensions sparked by the Israel-Hamas conflict. A drone strike resulted in minor injuries for U.S. forces stationed in Syria. Another alarming incident involved a false alarm at the Al-Asad airbase in Iraq, during which a civilian contractor tragically succumbed to a cardiac arrest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite dispatching naval reinforcements to the Middle East, including two aircraft carriers, warships, and approximately 2,000 Marines, Biden has yet to comment on the situation or offer a strategic response. The pressing question is: Why the conspicuous silence?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Ain al-Asad airbase, hosting U.S. and other international forces, has been at the epicenter of these attacks. The base experienced a barrage of drones and rockets, with multiple explosions reported within its confines. Another U.S. military base near Baghdad’s international airport has also been targeted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pentagon spokesperson, Brigadier General Patrick Ryder, refrained from speculating about potential reactions to these onslaughts. However, he assured that the U.S. would take all necessary steps to protect its forces and coalition allies. Ryder emphasized that any potential response would occur “at a time in a manner of our choosing.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As tensions flare in the region, it’s essential to underscore the considerable civilian casualties. Since Hamas’s assault on southern Israel, approximately 1,400 individuals, primarily civilians, have lost their lives. The Palestinian enclave of the Gaza Strip has faced nonstop bombardments, resulting in significant Palestinian casualties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Ryder has stated that there isn’t a direct connection between the increase in attacks on U.S. troops and the Israel-Hamas conflict, the correlation is hard to ignore. Tensions in Iraq regarding the war in Gaza have notably surged, with influential figures condemning Israel’s actions and calling for global intervention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Iranian-backed militias, known for targeting U.S. forces in Iraq and the U.S. embassy in Baghdad in the past, might be behind these recent drone strikes. Such militias had previously adhered to a truce, allowing Iraq to experience a period of relative calm. But the current circumstances and heightened sentiments could easily disrupt this fragile peace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With U.S. forces enduring consistent attacks and mounting regional tensions, President Biden’s silence is concerning. The nation looks to its leader for reassurance, strategy, and action during times of crisis. But as our brave soldiers stand their ground overseas, they await a word from their Commander in Chief.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a shocking display of seeming negligence, President Joe Biden has failed to publicly address a series of attacks on U.S. forces in Iraq and Syria. Within the past 48 hours, our troops have faced at least seven targeted aggressions, and the nation’s Commander in Chief has been eerily silent. Reports confirm that U.S. officials have been aware of the continued attacks in the region, particularly with the ongoing tensions sparked by the Israel-Hamas conflict. A drone strike resulted in minor injuries for U.S. forces stationed in Syria. Another alarming incident involved a false alarm at the Al-Asad airbase in Iraq, during which a civilian contractor tragically succumbed to a cardiac arrest. Despite dispatching naval reinforcements to the Middle East, including two aircraft carriers, warships, and approximately 2,000 Marines, Biden has yet to comment on the situation or offer a strategic response. The pressing question is: Why the conspicuous silence? The Ain al-Asad airbase, hosting U.S. and other international forces, has been at the epicenter of these attacks. The base experienced a barrage of drones and rockets, with multiple explosions reported within its confines. Another U.S. military base near Baghdad’s international airport has also been targeted. Pentagon spokesperson, Brigadier General Patrick Ryder, refrained from speculating about potential reactions to these onslaughts. However, he assured that the U.S. would take all necessary steps to protect its forces and coalition allies. Ryder emphasized that any potential response would occur “at a time in a manner of our choosing.” As tensions flare in the region, it’s essential to underscore the considerable civilian casualties. Since Hamas’s assault on southern Israel, approximately 1,400 individuals, primarily civilians, have lost their lives. The Palestinian enclave of the Gaza Strip has faced nonstop bombardments, resulting in significant Palestinian casualties. While Ryder has stated that there isn’t a direct connection between the increase in attacks on U.S. troops and the Israel-Hamas conflict, the correlation is hard to ignore. Tensions in Iraq regarding the war in Gaza have notably surged, with influential figures condemning Israel’s actions and calling for global intervention. Iranian-backed militias, known for targeting U.S. forces in Iraq and the U.S. embassy in Baghdad in the past, might be behind these recent drone strikes. Such militias had previously adhered to a truce, allowing Iraq to experience a period of relative calm. But the current circumstances and heightened sentiments could easily disrupt this fragile peace. With U.S. forces enduring consistent attacks and mounting regional tensions, President Biden’s silence is concerning. The nation looks to its leader for reassurance, strategy, and action during times of crisis. But as our brave soldiers stand their ground overseas, they await a word from their Commander in Chief.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Governor Sanders’ Bold Move Against ‘Woke’ Language</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/20/Sanders-Woke-Language/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Governor Sanders’ Bold Move Against ‘Woke’ Language" /><published>2023-10-20T11:57:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-20T11:57:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/20/Sanders-Woke-Language</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/20/Sanders-Woke-Language/">&lt;p&gt;In a decisive move against what many term as “woke” language, Gov. Sarah Huckabee Sanders of Arkansas is introducing an executive order that mandates the use of gender-specific language, specifically when addressing women. This act emerges as a strong stand against the increasing trend of adopting gender-neutral terms in governmental communication.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The science is clear and real; There are things only women can do, like perform the miracle of birth,” Sanders expressed in the executive order. She emphasized that government documentation should “celebrate gender distinctions between men and women — not erase them.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This order is primarily a reaction to the nation-wide effort to adopt what is dubbed as “culturally conscious” or “inclusive” language. Such changes frequently attempt to remove traditional gender associations from words. One specific instance this spring showcased the Arkansas Department of Health describing potential negative effects on “pregnant people.” Sanders’ order will now necessitate the usage of the terms “pregnant women” or “pregnant mom.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The executive order further clarifies the preferred language for other scenarios:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Instead of “menstruating person” or “menstruating people”, use “woman” or “women.”&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Rather than “birthing person”, the term should be “birth mom.”&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;“Chestfeeding” should be replaced with “breastfeeding.”&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Instead of “laboring person,” use “birth mom,” and “woman” in place of “birth-giver.”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sanders, who holds the distinction of being the first female governor of Arkansas, has been consistently vocal against the removal of feminine associations from terms traditionally used for women. She notably criticized President Biden, stating that he became “the first man to surrender his presidency to a woke mob that can’t tell you what a woman is.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The trend of adjusting gender-specific terms is not unique to Arkansas. For instance, Portland, Oregon, recently encouraged its city staff to embrace a more “culturally conscious” vocabulary. This adjustment included avoiding the use of words like “women,” “Caucasian,” and “citizen.” Similarly, educational institutions across the nation are adapting their curriculums to mirror this trend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sanders, however, is determined to push back against these changes, voicing her concerns at the executive order’s signing ceremony. She is expected to state, “Enough trying to erase women and girls. Enough denying our biological differences from men.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This bold step by Gov. Sanders is sure to spark extensive debate both in Arkansas and across the nation. With tensions rising over the balance between tradition and inclusivity, this executive order may serve as a tipping point in the ongoing discourse about “woke” language in America.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a decisive move against what many term as “woke” language, Gov. Sarah Huckabee Sanders of Arkansas is introducing an executive order that mandates the use of gender-specific language, specifically when addressing women. This act emerges as a strong stand against the increasing trend of adopting gender-neutral terms in governmental communication. “The science is clear and real; There are things only women can do, like perform the miracle of birth,” Sanders expressed in the executive order. She emphasized that government documentation should “celebrate gender distinctions between men and women — not erase them.” This order is primarily a reaction to the nation-wide effort to adopt what is dubbed as “culturally conscious” or “inclusive” language. Such changes frequently attempt to remove traditional gender associations from words. One specific instance this spring showcased the Arkansas Department of Health describing potential negative effects on “pregnant people.” Sanders’ order will now necessitate the usage of the terms “pregnant women” or “pregnant mom.” The executive order further clarifies the preferred language for other scenarios: Instead of “menstruating person” or “menstruating people”, use “woman” or “women.” Rather than “birthing person”, the term should be “birth mom.” “Chestfeeding” should be replaced with “breastfeeding.” Instead of “laboring person,” use “birth mom,” and “woman” in place of “birth-giver.” Sanders, who holds the distinction of being the first female governor of Arkansas, has been consistently vocal against the removal of feminine associations from terms traditionally used for women. She notably criticized President Biden, stating that he became “the first man to surrender his presidency to a woke mob that can’t tell you what a woman is.” The trend of adjusting gender-specific terms is not unique to Arkansas. For instance, Portland, Oregon, recently encouraged its city staff to embrace a more “culturally conscious” vocabulary. This adjustment included avoiding the use of words like “women,” “Caucasian,” and “citizen.” Similarly, educational institutions across the nation are adapting their curriculums to mirror this trend. Sanders, however, is determined to push back against these changes, voicing her concerns at the executive order’s signing ceremony. She is expected to state, “Enough trying to erase women and girls. Enough denying our biological differences from men.” This bold step by Gov. Sanders is sure to spark extensive debate both in Arkansas and across the nation. With tensions rising over the balance between tradition and inclusivity, this executive order may serve as a tipping point in the ongoing discourse about “woke” language in America.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Biden’s Incoherence: Spotlight on the Israel Press Conference</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/20/Biden-Israel-Conference/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Biden’s Incoherence: Spotlight on the Israel Press Conference" /><published>2023-10-20T10:34:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-20T10:34:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/20/Biden-Israel-Conference</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/20/Biden-Israel-Conference/">&lt;p&gt;In a recent press conference held in Tel Aviv, President Joe Biden’s cognitive abilities have been brought into sharp focus. Critics, including Oscar-nominated actor James Woods, voiced significant concerns regarding Biden’s apparent inability to maintain coherence during his speech.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While seated next to Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu, Biden, despite relying on prepared notecards, seemed to drift off-topic, ultimately appearing to lose his way entirely. Such instances intensify worries surrounding his mental fitness, with Woods even pointing to Biden’s “obvious dementia”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Woods, who has never been one to mince his words, labeled Biden as a “crooked hack” following this event. He further criticized Biden for his ambiguous terminology, particularly his use of the term “other team” in lieu of directly addressing the terrorists affecting Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond these remarks, the conference’s content itself was newsworthy. Biden announced a whopping $100 million in humanitarian aid for Gaza and the West Bank. This move is seen by some as further evidence of Biden’s shifting stance on Israel. Recent works, such as Alex Marlow’s book “Breaking Biden”, highlight alleged harm the current US President has directed towards Israel, including efforts to rejuvenate the Iran Nuclear Deal. Moreover, claims have been made of Biden staffing the Pentagon with so-called “experts” who were later revealed to have ties to Iran.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Critics argue that this is not merely an isolated event, but rather a continued pattern of Biden’s inadequacy to govern effectively, with Woods even suggesting that “the fate of mankind is at stake” with Biden at the helm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s imperative to stay informed, critically assess our leaders, and ensure transparency and efficacy in governance. Only through scrutiny and holding our leaders accountable can we hope to pave a path forward that aligns with the best interests of the people.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">In a recent press conference held in Tel Aviv, President Joe Biden’s cognitive abilities have been brought into sharp focus. Critics, including Oscar-nominated actor James Woods, voiced significant concerns regarding Biden’s apparent inability to maintain coherence during his speech. While seated next to Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu, Biden, despite relying on prepared notecards, seemed to drift off-topic, ultimately appearing to lose his way entirely. Such instances intensify worries surrounding his mental fitness, with Woods even pointing to Biden’s “obvious dementia”. Woods, who has never been one to mince his words, labeled Biden as a “crooked hack” following this event. He further criticized Biden for his ambiguous terminology, particularly his use of the term “other team” in lieu of directly addressing the terrorists affecting Israel. Beyond these remarks, the conference’s content itself was newsworthy. Biden announced a whopping $100 million in humanitarian aid for Gaza and the West Bank. This move is seen by some as further evidence of Biden’s shifting stance on Israel. Recent works, such as Alex Marlow’s book “Breaking Biden”, highlight alleged harm the current US President has directed towards Israel, including efforts to rejuvenate the Iran Nuclear Deal. Moreover, claims have been made of Biden staffing the Pentagon with so-called “experts” who were later revealed to have ties to Iran. Critics argue that this is not merely an isolated event, but rather a continued pattern of Biden’s inadequacy to govern effectively, with Woods even suggesting that “the fate of mankind is at stake” with Biden at the helm. It’s imperative to stay informed, critically assess our leaders, and ensure transparency and efficacy in governance. Only through scrutiny and holding our leaders accountable can we hope to pave a path forward that aligns with the best interests of the people.</summary></entry></feed>