<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-10-22T02:19:16-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/22/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-22T02:19:16-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-22T02:19:16-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/22/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/22/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/22/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-22T02:19:16-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-22T02:19:16-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/22/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/22/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/">&lt;p&gt;Recent surprise attacks by Hamas on Israel has fueled ongoing tensions between staunchly conservative commentators and the progressive “Squad” Democrats known for criticizing Israel. The intensity of the backlash highlights the deep political divide over foreign policy in the Middle East.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Hamas’ shocking attack, several members of the “Squad,” including Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.), called for a “ceasefire and de-escalation,” condemning the violence. The absence of a statement from Rep. Rashida Tlaib (D-Mich.) was notably called out by conservative media outlets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;South Carolina GOP Rep. Nancy Mace quickly labeled Ocasio-Cortez a “Hamas apologist” in response to her call for peace and de-escalation. Rep. Ilhan Omar (D-Minn.), no stranger to controversy surrounding her views on Israel, echoed the call for de-escalation and ceasefire. Omar’s prior statements comparing the US and Israel to terrorist groups like Hamas and the Taliban resurfaced in the debate, fueling more criticisms. Omar’s 2019 tweet, where she opined that “Israel has hypnotized the world,” also continues to haunt her political career, often cited by critics to challenge her stance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conservative commentators have been especially vocal. “FOX &amp;amp; Friends Weekend” co-host Rachel Campos-Duffy took aim at Omar, saying she fails to recognize the peace in the Middle East under Trump’s administration. Conservative pundit John Hasson also called out Omar, claiming she insinuated that attacks on IDF forces were acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Massachusetts Democrat Rep. Ayanna Pressley’s concerns over the “devastating attacks on Israelis” were met with skepticism. A prominent conservative online personality, Comfortably Smug, accused the “Squad” of advising Israel to back down after the nation suffered massive attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Jamaal Bowman’s call for an end to the Gaza blockade, in addition to condemning the Hamas attacks, was met with criticism from conservative radio host Jason Rantz. He accused Bowman of pairing his condemnation of terrorism with unwarranted criticisms of Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Cori Bush emphasized the urgent need for a ceasefire, while pushing for an end to “U.S. support for Israeli military occupation and apartheid.” Defense attorney Marina Medvin criticized Bush, suggesting that she equates the death of Palestinian terrorists to the horrific acts committed against Jewish civilians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amidst the political turmoil and intense debate, the attacks have taken a heavy toll. Israeli media report over 300 dead due to the wide-ranging assault. Gaza health officials note that at least 200 Palestinians have perished in the retaliatory Israeli air strikes following the initial Hamas attack. As the situation remains volatile, both sides continue to count their casualties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This divisive issue showcases the challenge America faces in crafting a unified approach to foreign policy, with deeply entrenched political divides at play. As the situation develops, the debate is bound to intensify, shedding light on the complexities of U.S. politics in the global arena.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump’s Email Blast: ‘Crooked Joe’ and the $200,000 Mystery</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/21/Trump-Biden-Fundraising/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump’s Email Blast: ‘Crooked Joe’ and the $200,000 Mystery" /><published>2023-10-21T17:15:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-21T17:15:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/21/Trump-Biden-Fundraising</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/21/Trump-Biden-Fundraising/">&lt;p&gt;In a recent fundraising email, former President Donald Trump intensified his attack on President Joe Biden, alleging financial missteps and a possible money trail connecting Biden to his family’s business dealings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The email surfaced after James Comer, the House Oversight Committee Chair and Republican representative from Kentucky, revealed evidence of a $200,000 check transaction. This check, from Biden’s brother, James Biden, was directed to “Joseph R. Biden Jr.” This discovery follows Biden’s earlier response to bribery allegations, where he quipped, “Where’s the money?” A question that the GOP, backed by Trump, now claims to have answered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, this isn’t where the money trail ends. Trump’s email also highlighted James Biden’s loan history from Americore, a rural hospital operator. Bankruptcy court documents unveiled that in 2018, James acquired a substantial $600,000 loan from Americore. The reasoning? Allegedly, it was based on James’ surname “Biden” which would purportedly “open doors” and secure significant investments from the Middle East due to his political affiliations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a striking sequence of events, $200,000 was wired to James and Sara Biden from Americore in March of 2018. And astonishingly, on that same day, a check of $200,000 was penned to Joe Biden from his brother, James.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In response to these revelations, Trump’s campaign rekindled the moniker, “Crooked Joe Biden.” This branding is a pivot from the once-popular “Sleepy Joe” label, primarily due to the mounting allegations of deception in Biden’s acknowledgment of his family’s financial affairs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Concluding his fundraising email, Trump stated, “The coincidences just keep piling up.” Making it clear, he, along with many others, sees more than mere coincidence in these monetary exchanges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chair James Comer has assured the public that this isn’t the last they’ll hear about these findings. While the House Oversight Committee zeroes in on the mysterious $200,000 “loan repayment,” they have listed immediate questions that President Biden must address. These queries revolve around Biden’s financial exchanges with family members, particularly regarding the astounding sum transferred from James Biden.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amid these evolving political dramas, the American public awaits clarity. As allegations mount and political tensions rise, it’s evident that the financial dealings of the Biden family will remain a topic of national discussion for some time to come.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a recent fundraising email, former President Donald Trump intensified his attack on President Joe Biden, alleging financial missteps and a possible money trail connecting Biden to his family’s business dealings. The email surfaced after James Comer, the House Oversight Committee Chair and Republican representative from Kentucky, revealed evidence of a $200,000 check transaction. This check, from Biden’s brother, James Biden, was directed to “Joseph R. Biden Jr.” This discovery follows Biden’s earlier response to bribery allegations, where he quipped, “Where’s the money?” A question that the GOP, backed by Trump, now claims to have answered. However, this isn’t where the money trail ends. Trump’s email also highlighted James Biden’s loan history from Americore, a rural hospital operator. Bankruptcy court documents unveiled that in 2018, James acquired a substantial $600,000 loan from Americore. The reasoning? Allegedly, it was based on James’ surname “Biden” which would purportedly “open doors” and secure significant investments from the Middle East due to his political affiliations. In a striking sequence of events, $200,000 was wired to James and Sara Biden from Americore in March of 2018. And astonishingly, on that same day, a check of $200,000 was penned to Joe Biden from his brother, James. In response to these revelations, Trump’s campaign rekindled the moniker, “Crooked Joe Biden.” This branding is a pivot from the once-popular “Sleepy Joe” label, primarily due to the mounting allegations of deception in Biden’s acknowledgment of his family’s financial affairs. Concluding his fundraising email, Trump stated, “The coincidences just keep piling up.” Making it clear, he, along with many others, sees more than mere coincidence in these monetary exchanges. Chair James Comer has assured the public that this isn’t the last they’ll hear about these findings. While the House Oversight Committee zeroes in on the mysterious $200,000 “loan repayment,” they have listed immediate questions that President Biden must address. These queries revolve around Biden’s financial exchanges with family members, particularly regarding the astounding sum transferred from James Biden. Amid these evolving political dramas, the American public awaits clarity. As allegations mount and political tensions rise, it’s evident that the financial dealings of the Biden family will remain a topic of national discussion for some time to come.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Maher’s Take: Elite Colleges - A Breeding Ground for Ignorance?</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/21/Elite-Colleges-Criticism/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Maher’s Take: Elite Colleges - A Breeding Ground for Ignorance?" /><published>2023-10-21T16:01:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-21T16:01:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/21/Elite-Colleges-Criticism</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/21/Elite-Colleges-Criticism/">&lt;p&gt;In a bold and controversial stance, HBO’s “Real Time” host Bill Maher has urged America’s youth to reconsider their dreams of attending elite colleges. According to Maher, an Ivy League graduate himself, these prestigious institutions are nothing short of “North Korean re-education camps” that foster ignorance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maher’s critique of elite colleges comes as a fresh wave of concern over the state of higher education in America. He claims these institutions have evolved into hotbeds of indoctrination where “bad ideas” take root, and the nuances of global politics are reduced to oversimplified binaries of “oppressors” and “oppressed.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Diving into the Israel-Palestinian conflict as an example, Maher highlighted the disturbing trend of uninformed students supporting radical ideas without understanding the intricate historical and political background. He quipped about students labeling words as violence while simultaneously endorsing extreme actions against the state of Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Elaborating on his point, Maher expressed dismay at the widespread ignorance among elite college students. “They don’t know much of anything, actually. But it doesn’t deter them from having an opinion,” Maher said. He criticized the modern college curriculum for its lack of historical depth, suggesting that students are more interested in surfing TikTok than delving deep into academic pursuits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Drawing parallels between college life and “North Korean re-education camps,” Maher took a swipe at the perceived power dynamics within universities. He painted a grim picture of institutions where student whims dictate institutional decisions, rendering college presidents voiceless.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adding to his barrage of criticisms, Maher called out elite institutions for promoting segregation under the guise of inclusion and diversity. He raised concerns about all-black dorms, segregated graduation ceremonies, and orientation programs. Moreover, Maher didn’t shy away from addressing the controversial topic of racial bias against Asian applicants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a closing salvo, Maher remarked on the irony of elite institutions producing right-wing figures who publicly decry elitism. In his eyes, this performance of anti-elitism by Ivy League graduates is nothing short of “repulsive.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a world where college prestige often dictates career trajectories, Maher’s words serve as a cautionary tale. They beckon young aspirants to look beyond the ivy-covered walls and question whether the education they’re receiving genuinely broadens their horizons or narrows them.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">In a bold and controversial stance, HBO’s “Real Time” host Bill Maher has urged America’s youth to reconsider their dreams of attending elite colleges. According to Maher, an Ivy League graduate himself, these prestigious institutions are nothing short of “North Korean re-education camps” that foster ignorance. Maher’s critique of elite colleges comes as a fresh wave of concern over the state of higher education in America. He claims these institutions have evolved into hotbeds of indoctrination where “bad ideas” take root, and the nuances of global politics are reduced to oversimplified binaries of “oppressors” and “oppressed.” Diving into the Israel-Palestinian conflict as an example, Maher highlighted the disturbing trend of uninformed students supporting radical ideas without understanding the intricate historical and political background. He quipped about students labeling words as violence while simultaneously endorsing extreme actions against the state of Israel. Elaborating on his point, Maher expressed dismay at the widespread ignorance among elite college students. “They don’t know much of anything, actually. But it doesn’t deter them from having an opinion,” Maher said. He criticized the modern college curriculum for its lack of historical depth, suggesting that students are more interested in surfing TikTok than delving deep into academic pursuits. Drawing parallels between college life and “North Korean re-education camps,” Maher took a swipe at the perceived power dynamics within universities. He painted a grim picture of institutions where student whims dictate institutional decisions, rendering college presidents voiceless. Adding to his barrage of criticisms, Maher called out elite institutions for promoting segregation under the guise of inclusion and diversity. He raised concerns about all-black dorms, segregated graduation ceremonies, and orientation programs. Moreover, Maher didn’t shy away from addressing the controversial topic of racial bias against Asian applicants. As a closing salvo, Maher remarked on the irony of elite institutions producing right-wing figures who publicly decry elitism. In his eyes, this performance of anti-elitism by Ivy League graduates is nothing short of “repulsive.” In a world where college prestige often dictates career trajectories, Maher’s words serve as a cautionary tale. They beckon young aspirants to look beyond the ivy-covered walls and question whether the education they’re receiving genuinely broadens their horizons or narrows them.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A Grave Mistake: White House Accidentally Exposes Special Forces in Biden Photo-Op</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/21/Special-Forces-Doxxing-Incident/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Grave Mistake: White House Accidentally Exposes Special Forces in Biden Photo-Op" /><published>2023-10-21T16:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-21T16:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/21/Special-Forces-Doxxing-Incident</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/21/Special-Forces-Doxxing-Incident/">&lt;p&gt;In an alarming incident this week, the White House admitted to accidentally revealing the identities of American Special Forces in Israel during President Joe Biden’s visit. The blunder occurred when a photo, featuring the President with the Special Forces, was posted on the White House’s Instagram account, which boasts a following of 7.6 million. The photo inadvertently exposed the faces of these highly confidential operatives, placing their safety, as well as that of their families, in jeopardy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The White House’s failure to blur or conceal the identities of the Special Forces has drawn widespread criticism and concern. Visible in the photo were also unique identifiers such as tattoos, further jeopardizing the anonymity of the personnel. The caption of the now-removed photo read, “In Israel, President Biden met with first responders to thank them for their bravery and the work they’re doing in response to the Hamas terrorist attacks.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After retired Army Chief Warrant Officer 2 Samuel Shoemate brought this severe oversight to public attention, and after the photo had already reached hundreds of thousands of viewers, the White House acted swiftly to remove the image and issued an apology. “As soon as this was brought to our attention, we immediately deleted the photo. We regret the error and any issues this may have caused,” the White House stated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, accountability for this blunder remains unclear, as the White House has not disclosed who was responsible for the error. When the Pentagon was approached for comments, they redirected inquiries back to the White House. “I’d have to refer you to the White House on that. I just don’t have any information to provide,” was the response from Pentagon press secretary Brig. Gen. Pat Ryder during a press conference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This incident raises questions about the integrity of Biden’s promise to never use troops for political purposes, a pledge he made during his first visit to the Pentagon as President, stating, “I will never dishonor you. I will never disrespect you. I will never politicize the work you do.” This promise seems to be contradicted by his actions, as this is not the first instance where Biden has utilized troops as political props. In September 2022, Biden delivered a highly charged political speech, positioning two Marine sentries directly behind him, drawing sharp criticism from various quarters including Republican officials, conservative commentators, Marine veterans, military spouses, and even corporate news journalists.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This latest incident, therefore, not only jeopardizes the safety of the exposed Special Forces but also brings to light the ongoing issue of the politicization of the military, a matter that requires immediate attention and rectification.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In an alarming incident this week, the White House admitted to accidentally revealing the identities of American Special Forces in Israel during President Joe Biden’s visit. The blunder occurred when a photo, featuring the President with the Special Forces, was posted on the White House’s Instagram account, which boasts a following of 7.6 million. The photo inadvertently exposed the faces of these highly confidential operatives, placing their safety, as well as that of their families, in jeopardy. The White House’s failure to blur or conceal the identities of the Special Forces has drawn widespread criticism and concern. Visible in the photo were also unique identifiers such as tattoos, further jeopardizing the anonymity of the personnel. The caption of the now-removed photo read, “In Israel, President Biden met with first responders to thank them for their bravery and the work they’re doing in response to the Hamas terrorist attacks.” After retired Army Chief Warrant Officer 2 Samuel Shoemate brought this severe oversight to public attention, and after the photo had already reached hundreds of thousands of viewers, the White House acted swiftly to remove the image and issued an apology. “As soon as this was brought to our attention, we immediately deleted the photo. We regret the error and any issues this may have caused,” the White House stated. However, accountability for this blunder remains unclear, as the White House has not disclosed who was responsible for the error. When the Pentagon was approached for comments, they redirected inquiries back to the White House. “I’d have to refer you to the White House on that. I just don’t have any information to provide,” was the response from Pentagon press secretary Brig. Gen. Pat Ryder during a press conference. This incident raises questions about the integrity of Biden’s promise to never use troops for political purposes, a pledge he made during his first visit to the Pentagon as President, stating, “I will never dishonor you. I will never disrespect you. I will never politicize the work you do.” This promise seems to be contradicted by his actions, as this is not the first instance where Biden has utilized troops as political props. In September 2022, Biden delivered a highly charged political speech, positioning two Marine sentries directly behind him, drawing sharp criticism from various quarters including Republican officials, conservative commentators, Marine veterans, military spouses, and even corporate news journalists. This latest incident, therefore, not only jeopardizes the safety of the exposed Special Forces but also brings to light the ongoing issue of the politicization of the military, a matter that requires immediate attention and rectification.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A New Arena for Political Rivalry: Truth Social Welcomes Biden</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/21/Truth-Social-Political-Platform/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A New Arena for Political Rivalry: Truth Social Welcomes Biden" /><published>2023-10-21T14:54:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-21T14:54:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/21/Truth-Social-Political-Platform</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/21/Truth-Social-Political-Platform/">&lt;p&gt;In an unexpected twist of digital diplomacy, Truth Social, the brainchild of former President Donald Trump, has rolled out the welcome mat for none other than its founder’s 2024 rival, President Joe Biden. The Biden-Harris HQ campaign account made its debut on the platform with a cheeky post: “Well. Let’s see how this goes. Converts welcome!”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This embrace of the platform by Biden’s reelection campaign has caught the eyes of political enthusiasts and analysts alike. It raises questions about the balance of power in the digital realm, as political heavyweights look to engage and influence potential voters on varying platforms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Devin Nunes, former Rep. and now CEO of Trump Media and Technology Group, voiced his perspective on Newsmax’s “The Chris Salcedo Show”. “We’re a free speech platform,” Nunes declared, distinguishing Truth Social from social media giants like Twitter, Facebook, and Instagram. “We welcome anyone and everyone. Contrary to perhaps popular belief, we aren’t looking to ban or kick off the Biden campaign.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By the end of the week, Biden-Harris HQ’s follower count stood at an impressive 33,600 - surpassing even the follower count of the Team Trump account. However, Trump’s primary account remains a juggernaut with a whopping 6.45 million followers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nunes took a jibe at media outlets, calling them out for spinning narratives about Biden’s follower count. He mused over the idea of Biden potentially overtaking Trump on Truth Social, remarking, “If that happens, great for him. But most of those following Biden are likely doing so to engage with his campaign, often critically.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nunes alluded to the swathes of comments under Biden’s posts that seem to be real-time fact-checking the president’s campaign, a testament to the interactive and unfiltered nature of the platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the 2024 election season heats up, the use of platforms like Truth Social offers an uncharted territory for campaigns to navigate. With both major parties marking their territory on the platform, it’s clear that the battle for the White House will be fought as fiercely online as off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In today’s digital age, where a tweet can sway public opinion and a post can ignite a debate, platforms like Truth Social are more than just social networks. They are political battlegrounds, and the game has just begun.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In an unexpected twist of digital diplomacy, Truth Social, the brainchild of former President Donald Trump, has rolled out the welcome mat for none other than its founder’s 2024 rival, President Joe Biden. The Biden-Harris HQ campaign account made its debut on the platform with a cheeky post: “Well. Let’s see how this goes. Converts welcome!”. This embrace of the platform by Biden’s reelection campaign has caught the eyes of political enthusiasts and analysts alike. It raises questions about the balance of power in the digital realm, as political heavyweights look to engage and influence potential voters on varying platforms. Devin Nunes, former Rep. and now CEO of Trump Media and Technology Group, voiced his perspective on Newsmax’s “The Chris Salcedo Show”. “We’re a free speech platform,” Nunes declared, distinguishing Truth Social from social media giants like Twitter, Facebook, and Instagram. “We welcome anyone and everyone. Contrary to perhaps popular belief, we aren’t looking to ban or kick off the Biden campaign.” By the end of the week, Biden-Harris HQ’s follower count stood at an impressive 33,600 - surpassing even the follower count of the Team Trump account. However, Trump’s primary account remains a juggernaut with a whopping 6.45 million followers. Nunes took a jibe at media outlets, calling them out for spinning narratives about Biden’s follower count. He mused over the idea of Biden potentially overtaking Trump on Truth Social, remarking, “If that happens, great for him. But most of those following Biden are likely doing so to engage with his campaign, often critically.” Nunes alluded to the swathes of comments under Biden’s posts that seem to be real-time fact-checking the president’s campaign, a testament to the interactive and unfiltered nature of the platform. As the 2024 election season heats up, the use of platforms like Truth Social offers an uncharted territory for campaigns to navigate. With both major parties marking their territory on the platform, it’s clear that the battle for the White House will be fought as fiercely online as off. In today’s digital age, where a tweet can sway public opinion and a post can ignite a debate, platforms like Truth Social are more than just social networks. They are political battlegrounds, and the game has just begun.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Sky-High Tensions: US-Chinese Aerial Confrontations on the Rise</title><link href="/news/2023/10/21/US-China-Aerial-Tensions/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sky-High Tensions: US-Chinese Aerial Confrontations on the Rise" /><published>2023-10-21T13:47:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-21T13:47:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/21/US-China-Aerial-Tensions</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/21/US-China-Aerial-Tensions/">&lt;p&gt;Recent data from the U.S. Department of Defense (DOD) signals an alarming increase in dangerous encounters between American and Chinese aircraft. The DOD voiced concerns about the “coercive and risky” behaviors demonstrated by Chinese planes in their interactions with U.S. aircraft.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During a press briefing on Tuesday, DOD officials showcased newly declassified images and footage illustrating these precarious situations. Ely Ratner, the Assistant Defense Secretary for Indo-Pacific Security Affairs, articulated the gravity of the situation. “From 2021 onward, over 180 incidents involving risky behaviors from People’s Liberation Army (PLA) operators have been reported, more than what we saw in the preceding decade,” Ratner stated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These behaviors include aggressive maneuvers, rapid approaches, and even the firing of flares dangerously close to U.S. aircraft. Such actions are perceived as attempts by the PLA to challenge and obstruct U.S. military operations within regions internationally recognized as global commons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ratner emphasized that the People’s Liberation Army (PLA) doesn’t limit its disruptive antics to U.S. aircraft. When factoring in similar confrontations against aircraft belonging to U.S. allies and partners, the number jumps to almost 300 incidents in the same timeframe. Such statistics underline a broader trend of hostility and provocation in east Asian territories.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Images released by the DOD paint a concerning picture of these interactions. One particularly distressing image displays a PLA fighter jet, mere feet away from a U.S. aircraft, maneuvering in a way that could compromise the safety of both planes. Another document captures a PLA pilot resorting to crude language after being radioed by the U.S. operator.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Admiral John Aquilino, the Indo-Pacom Commander, offered a perspective on these incidents. “While aerial intercepts occur frequently worldwide, they predominantly transpire without mishaps. There’s no reason for the interactions in the Indo-Pacific with the PRC to deviate from this norm,” he stated. Aquilino highlighted the paramount importance of the safety of U.S. servicemembers, asserting the need to spotlight and mitigate these hazardous behaviors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though the DOD has shed light on the rising aerial confrontations, they did not provide a concise delineation between what they termed as “coercive” and “risky” versus more commonly used descriptors like “unsafe” or “unprofessional.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With tensions escalating in the skies, it remains imperative for both nations to find avenues of communication and collaboration, ensuring the safety and security of all involved.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Recent data from the U.S. Department of Defense (DOD) signals an alarming increase in dangerous encounters between American and Chinese aircraft. The DOD voiced concerns about the “coercive and risky” behaviors demonstrated by Chinese planes in their interactions with U.S. aircraft. During a press briefing on Tuesday, DOD officials showcased newly declassified images and footage illustrating these precarious situations. Ely Ratner, the Assistant Defense Secretary for Indo-Pacific Security Affairs, articulated the gravity of the situation. “From 2021 onward, over 180 incidents involving risky behaviors from People’s Liberation Army (PLA) operators have been reported, more than what we saw in the preceding decade,” Ratner stated. These behaviors include aggressive maneuvers, rapid approaches, and even the firing of flares dangerously close to U.S. aircraft. Such actions are perceived as attempts by the PLA to challenge and obstruct U.S. military operations within regions internationally recognized as global commons. Ratner emphasized that the People’s Liberation Army (PLA) doesn’t limit its disruptive antics to U.S. aircraft. When factoring in similar confrontations against aircraft belonging to U.S. allies and partners, the number jumps to almost 300 incidents in the same timeframe. Such statistics underline a broader trend of hostility and provocation in east Asian territories. Images released by the DOD paint a concerning picture of these interactions. One particularly distressing image displays a PLA fighter jet, mere feet away from a U.S. aircraft, maneuvering in a way that could compromise the safety of both planes. Another document captures a PLA pilot resorting to crude language after being radioed by the U.S. operator. Admiral John Aquilino, the Indo-Pacom Commander, offered a perspective on these incidents. “While aerial intercepts occur frequently worldwide, they predominantly transpire without mishaps. There’s no reason for the interactions in the Indo-Pacific with the PRC to deviate from this norm,” he stated. Aquilino highlighted the paramount importance of the safety of U.S. servicemembers, asserting the need to spotlight and mitigate these hazardous behaviors. Though the DOD has shed light on the rising aerial confrontations, they did not provide a concise delineation between what they termed as “coercive” and “risky” versus more commonly used descriptors like “unsafe” or “unprofessional.” With tensions escalating in the skies, it remains imperative for both nations to find avenues of communication and collaboration, ensuring the safety and security of all involved.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Unraveling the Biden Financial Web: $200K Transaction Under Scrutiny</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/21/Biden-Family-Financial-Dealings/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Unraveling the Biden Financial Web: $200K Transaction Under Scrutiny" /><published>2023-10-21T08:12:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-21T08:12:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/21/Biden-Family-Financial-Dealings</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/21/Biden-Family-Financial-Dealings/">&lt;p&gt;A recent revelation suggests that President Joe Biden may have been entangled in his family’s controversial financial dealings. House Oversight Committee Chair, James Comer (R-Ky.), announced on Friday that bank records indicate James and Sara Biden, Joe Biden’s brother and sister-in-law respectively, paid him a hefty sum of $200,000 via a personal check in March 2018.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This financial transaction has ignited debates, with critics suggesting that it offers proof of the Biden family’s alleged influence-peddling operations. “This is more than just a personal transaction; it hints at how President Biden could have potentially benefited from his family’s questionable use of his name and their access to him,” Comer commented in a video statement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Digging deeper into the financial trail, James Biden, in 2018, secured loans amounting to $600,000 from Americore, a company known for its financial struggles as a rural hospital operator. Bankruptcy court records imply that James Biden leveraged his familial ties, asserting that his surname “Biden” had the power to “open doors” and that he could fetch a substantial investment from the Middle East, banking on his political affiliations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Intriguingly, on March 1, 2018, Americore transferred a $200,000 loan to James and Sara Biden’s personal bank account. The same day, James Biden funneled the exact amount to Joe Biden, labeling it as a “loan repayment.” Comer emphasized the dubious nature of this transaction, saying, “Even if it’s categorized as a personal loan repayment, the fact remains that Joe Biden’s reimbursement from his brother hinged on the success of questionable financial arrangements.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Joe Biden is now under pressure to shed light on these findings. Comer is demanding clarity on several fronts: Is there concrete evidence that Joe Biden had indeed loaned $200,000 to his brother? What were the terms of this financial agreement?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, Comer raises the possibility of other similar financial agreements with family members. “Could there be other family members who have made similar substantial payments to him?” Comer posits in the video.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, while the nature of family financial entanglements isn’t uncommon, when it concerns the first family of the nation, transparency and clarity become paramount. The coming days will undoubtedly see heightened scrutiny and demand for answers from the President and his family regarding these allegations.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">A recent revelation suggests that President Joe Biden may have been entangled in his family’s controversial financial dealings. House Oversight Committee Chair, James Comer (R-Ky.), announced on Friday that bank records indicate James and Sara Biden, Joe Biden’s brother and sister-in-law respectively, paid him a hefty sum of $200,000 via a personal check in March 2018. This financial transaction has ignited debates, with critics suggesting that it offers proof of the Biden family’s alleged influence-peddling operations. “This is more than just a personal transaction; it hints at how President Biden could have potentially benefited from his family’s questionable use of his name and their access to him,” Comer commented in a video statement. Digging deeper into the financial trail, James Biden, in 2018, secured loans amounting to $600,000 from Americore, a company known for its financial struggles as a rural hospital operator. Bankruptcy court records imply that James Biden leveraged his familial ties, asserting that his surname “Biden” had the power to “open doors” and that he could fetch a substantial investment from the Middle East, banking on his political affiliations. Intriguingly, on March 1, 2018, Americore transferred a $200,000 loan to James and Sara Biden’s personal bank account. The same day, James Biden funneled the exact amount to Joe Biden, labeling it as a “loan repayment.” Comer emphasized the dubious nature of this transaction, saying, “Even if it’s categorized as a personal loan repayment, the fact remains that Joe Biden’s reimbursement from his brother hinged on the success of questionable financial arrangements.” Joe Biden is now under pressure to shed light on these findings. Comer is demanding clarity on several fronts: Is there concrete evidence that Joe Biden had indeed loaned $200,000 to his brother? What were the terms of this financial agreement? Furthermore, Comer raises the possibility of other similar financial agreements with family members. “Could there be other family members who have made similar substantial payments to him?” Comer posits in the video. In conclusion, while the nature of family financial entanglements isn’t uncommon, when it concerns the first family of the nation, transparency and clarity become paramount. The coming days will undoubtedly see heightened scrutiny and demand for answers from the President and his family regarding these allegations.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Maryland Judge Assassinated Following Divorce Ruling</title><link href="/news/2023/10/21/Maryland-Judge-Targeted-Attack/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Maryland Judge Assassinated Following Divorce Ruling" /><published>2023-10-21T07:01:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-21T07:01:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/21/Maryland-Judge-Targeted-Attack</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/21/Maryland-Judge-Targeted-Attack/">&lt;p&gt;Maryland’s Circuit Court Judge Andrew Wilkinson from Hagerstown was brutally gunned down outside his home on Thursday evening. This tragic incident is believed to be a retaliatory act following a judgment in a divorce hearing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Authorities from the Washington County Sheriff’s Office quickly identified the prime suspect, Pedro Argote, who had a direct link to the judgment. Earlier that day, Judge Wilkinson had granted child custody to a woman amidst Argote’s divorce proceedings. Interestingly, Argote was absent during the hearing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“This wasn’t random. It was a targeted attack on Judge Wilkinson,” declared Washington County Sheriff Brian K. Albert in a press briefing on Friday. The sheriff’s office has warned the public that Argote, 49, is still on the loose, armed, and could be dangerous. Notably, he is a legal owner of a firearm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2023/10/720/405/394512179_711778497658852_1440711396504505403_n-1.jpg?ve=1&amp;amp;tl=1&quot; alt=&quot;Pedro Argote&apos;s vehicle&quot; /&gt;(Washington County Sheriff)
&lt;em&gt;Authorities have identified Pedro Argote’s car as a silver 2009 Mercedes GL450 with Maryland registration plates reading 4EH0408.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The violent episode took place post 8 p.m. on Olde Waterford Road in Hagerstown. Judge Wilkinson, 52 at the time of his death, was ambushed in his driveway while his wife and son were inside the house. He was rushed to Meritus Medical Center but was pronounced dead on arrival.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Records revealed that authorities had been previously called to Argote’s residence on two separate occasions in response to “verbal domestic assaults.” However, Pedro Argote had managed to maintain a clean slate, with no prior criminal record in Washington County.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wilkinson’s association with the 4th Judicial Circuit began in 2020. Born in Guam in 1971, the judge earned his credentials from the prestigious University of North Carolina and later, the Emory University School of Law.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2023/10/720/405/394013405_711778427658859_1493866060322353593_n-1.jpg?ve=1&amp;amp;tl=1&quot; alt=&quot;Pedro Argote&quot; /&gt;(Washington County Sheriff)
&lt;em&gt;Washington County Sheriff’s Office on Friday named Pedro Argote as a suspect.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the hunt for Argote intensifies, Washington County court records have provided an intriguing insight: Judge Wilkinson had been overseeing Argote’s divorce case since 2022. The next scheduled hearing was set for October 31st.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The alarming nature of the assassination raises concerns over the security of judiciary officials. However, the sheriff’s office has clarified that there seems to be no ongoing threat to other judges in the vicinity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This incident serves as a brutal reminder of the dangers public servants might face, emphasizing the need for heightened security measures and precautions.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Maryland’s Circuit Court Judge Andrew Wilkinson from Hagerstown was brutally gunned down outside his home on Thursday evening. This tragic incident is believed to be a retaliatory act following a judgment in a divorce hearing. Authorities from the Washington County Sheriff’s Office quickly identified the prime suspect, Pedro Argote, who had a direct link to the judgment. Earlier that day, Judge Wilkinson had granted child custody to a woman amidst Argote’s divorce proceedings. Interestingly, Argote was absent during the hearing. “This wasn’t random. It was a targeted attack on Judge Wilkinson,” declared Washington County Sheriff Brian K. Albert in a press briefing on Friday. The sheriff’s office has warned the public that Argote, 49, is still on the loose, armed, and could be dangerous. Notably, he is a legal owner of a firearm. (Washington County Sheriff) Authorities have identified Pedro Argote’s car as a silver 2009 Mercedes GL450 with Maryland registration plates reading 4EH0408. The violent episode took place post 8 p.m. on Olde Waterford Road in Hagerstown. Judge Wilkinson, 52 at the time of his death, was ambushed in his driveway while his wife and son were inside the house. He was rushed to Meritus Medical Center but was pronounced dead on arrival. Records revealed that authorities had been previously called to Argote’s residence on two separate occasions in response to “verbal domestic assaults.” However, Pedro Argote had managed to maintain a clean slate, with no prior criminal record in Washington County. Wilkinson’s association with the 4th Judicial Circuit began in 2020. Born in Guam in 1971, the judge earned his credentials from the prestigious University of North Carolina and later, the Emory University School of Law. (Washington County Sheriff) Washington County Sheriff’s Office on Friday named Pedro Argote as a suspect. While the hunt for Argote intensifies, Washington County court records have provided an intriguing insight: Judge Wilkinson had been overseeing Argote’s divorce case since 2022. The next scheduled hearing was set for October 31st. The alarming nature of the assassination raises concerns over the security of judiciary officials. However, the sheriff’s office has clarified that there seems to be no ongoing threat to other judges in the vicinity. This incident serves as a brutal reminder of the dangers public servants might face, emphasizing the need for heightened security measures and precautions.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Wokeness Takes a Toll: ESPN’s Profits Plunge by 20%</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/21/Wokeness-Hits-ESPN-Profit/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Wokeness Takes a Toll: ESPN’s Profits Plunge by 20%" /><published>2023-10-21T06:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-21T06:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/21/Wokeness-Hits-ESPN-Profit</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/21/Wokeness-Hits-ESPN-Profit/">&lt;p&gt;In a surprising revelation, Disney disclosed that the profits for its sports division, ESPN, have plummeted by a staggering 20% in the first nine months of the year. While the decline in profits is attributable to multiple factors, the increasingly ‘woke’ content strategy adopted by ESPN appears to be a significant contributor to this downturn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite a series of massive layoffs which included big names like Keyshawn Johnson, Max Kellerman, Steve Young, Suzy Kolber, and others, the sports network’s finances show no signs of revival. Revenues for ESPN were at $13.2 billion over the first nine months of 2023, which marks a 1.3% drop compared to the same period in the previous fiscal year, as per a report by Front Office Sports.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the global shift from cable to streaming services is undoubtedly affecting all traditional broadcasters, with cable viewership slipping below 50% of total TV usage in the U.S. for the first time in decades, the extent of ESPN’s woes can’t be attributed to this transition alone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ESPN, historically known for its sports-centric content, seems to be diving deep into the realm of ‘wokeness’ — a decision that hasn’t resonated well with its core audience. The channel’s latest venture into a show exploring “racism” in sports, fronted by the controversial figure Ibram X. Kendi, is a prime example. Kendi, known for his so-called “Center for Antiracist Research”, has faced multiple accusations and has recently laid off more than half the staff from his organization after being accused of squandering $43 million in donations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sports broadcasting fees, especially for prime content, are surging as well. ESPN is now shelling out a whopping $2.7 billion every year to the NFL for rights that include Monday Night Football and the Super Bowl. These rising costs, coupled with declining revenues, are squeezing the channel’s profit margins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the financial decline and backlash from segments of their viewership, it seems like ESPN, under Disney’s ownership, continues to drift further into left-leaning political agendas and content strategies. This shift appears to be alienating a significant portion of their traditional audience who are looking for pure sports content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, while the changing landscape of TV viewership is a challenge that all broadcasters need to navigate, ESPN’s current profit loss seems to be amplified by its insistence on integrating ‘wokeness’ into its programming. If they aim to revive their fortunes, a return to sports-centric content without the overlay of heavy political commentary might be the way forward.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">In a surprising revelation, Disney disclosed that the profits for its sports division, ESPN, have plummeted by a staggering 20% in the first nine months of the year. While the decline in profits is attributable to multiple factors, the increasingly ‘woke’ content strategy adopted by ESPN appears to be a significant contributor to this downturn. Despite a series of massive layoffs which included big names like Keyshawn Johnson, Max Kellerman, Steve Young, Suzy Kolber, and others, the sports network’s finances show no signs of revival. Revenues for ESPN were at $13.2 billion over the first nine months of 2023, which marks a 1.3% drop compared to the same period in the previous fiscal year, as per a report by Front Office Sports. While the global shift from cable to streaming services is undoubtedly affecting all traditional broadcasters, with cable viewership slipping below 50% of total TV usage in the U.S. for the first time in decades, the extent of ESPN’s woes can’t be attributed to this transition alone. ESPN, historically known for its sports-centric content, seems to be diving deep into the realm of ‘wokeness’ — a decision that hasn’t resonated well with its core audience. The channel’s latest venture into a show exploring “racism” in sports, fronted by the controversial figure Ibram X. Kendi, is a prime example. Kendi, known for his so-called “Center for Antiracist Research”, has faced multiple accusations and has recently laid off more than half the staff from his organization after being accused of squandering $43 million in donations. Sports broadcasting fees, especially for prime content, are surging as well. ESPN is now shelling out a whopping $2.7 billion every year to the NFL for rights that include Monday Night Football and the Super Bowl. These rising costs, coupled with declining revenues, are squeezing the channel’s profit margins. Despite the financial decline and backlash from segments of their viewership, it seems like ESPN, under Disney’s ownership, continues to drift further into left-leaning political agendas and content strategies. This shift appears to be alienating a significant portion of their traditional audience who are looking for pure sports content. In conclusion, while the changing landscape of TV viewership is a challenge that all broadcasters need to navigate, ESPN’s current profit loss seems to be amplified by its insistence on integrating ‘wokeness’ into its programming. If they aim to revive their fortunes, a return to sports-centric content without the overlay of heavy political commentary might be the way forward.</summary></entry></feed>