<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-10-04T04:20:15-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/04/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-04T04:20:15-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-04T04:20:15-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/04/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/04/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Streaming Showdown - The Dim Future of Hollywood’s Digital Ventures?</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/03/Streaming-Service-Economics/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Streaming Showdown - The Dim Future of Hollywood’s Digital Ventures?" /><published>2023-10-03T17:02:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-03T17:02:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/03/Streaming-Service-Economics</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/03/Streaming-Service-Economics/">&lt;p&gt;The bustling digital age has not been kind to Hollywood’s big-ticket streaming platforms. Wall Street’s investors, as cited by The Wall Street Journal, are casting a skeptical eye, pointing to what they describe as “hopeless economics” for these services. But what does this mean for the average consumer?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;an-oversaturated-market&quot;&gt;An Oversaturated Market&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Streaming services might be today’s trend, but there’s a glaring problem: overproduction. Hollywood pumps out over 300 new TV shows annually. Surprisingly, around 290 of them don’t resonate with viewers, leading to enormous monetary losses on content that’s left unseen. With the latest writer’s contract in play, insiders predict that the number of scripted shows could potentially drop by a third in the coming years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;keeping-viewership-numbers-close-to-the-chest&quot;&gt;Keeping Viewership Numbers Close to the Chest&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In an industry that thrives on numbers, streaming services have surprisingly resisted revealing their viewership data. Despite writers pushing for transparency, streaming giants have decided against publicizing these figures, sharing only aggregate data with the Writers’ Guild. The reluctance to disclose such information could be attributed to a fear that poor viewership numbers might adversely impact stock prices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;consolidation---the-next-step&quot;&gt;Consolidation - The Next Step?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With a multitude of streaming services vying for attention, the market’s future might lie in “consolidation.” Think of it as a streaming package deal, where for a fixed fee, consumers get access to multiple platforms like Disney+, Netflix, and ESPN. It might sound familiar; this strategy reflects the model that cable TV followed, where viewers paid for a bunch of channels, many of which they rarely watched.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, critics argue that this consolidation is just a ruse to recreate the old Cable TV model, where content merit took a backseat. In the golden era of cable TV, viewers paid for multiple channels, leading to a content glut filled with ads, repetitive shows, and often biased programming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-need-for-merit-based-content&quot;&gt;The Need for Merit-Based Content&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the glaring differences between cable TV and streaming services is the need for content merit in the latter. Consumers choose their subscriptions based on the quality and appeal of the content. Streaming platforms can’t afford to rest on their laurels, unlike the old cable TV days. If these platforms opt for bundled packages, it might allow them to slip back into the old content production patterns, leading to more generic, less engaging programming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;exploring-free-alternatives&quot;&gt;Exploring Free Alternatives&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For viewers tired of paying for content they don’t enjoy, there are alternatives like PlutoTV, FreeVee, and Tubi. These platforms offer a plethora of shows and movies, ensuring that viewers don’t need to dig into their pockets for quality entertainment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;final-thoughts&quot;&gt;Final Thoughts&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The world of streaming is at a crossroads. As Hollywood grapples with the challenges of producing engaging content and staying profitable, viewers should be cautious. After all, it’s about value for money and getting the quality entertainment that viewers deserve. As the industry evolves, it’s up to consumers to vote with their wallets and ensure they’re getting the best bang for their buck.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">The bustling digital age has not been kind to Hollywood’s big-ticket streaming platforms. Wall Street’s investors, as cited by The Wall Street Journal, are casting a skeptical eye, pointing to what they describe as “hopeless economics” for these services. But what does this mean for the average consumer? An Oversaturated Market Streaming services might be today’s trend, but there’s a glaring problem: overproduction. Hollywood pumps out over 300 new TV shows annually. Surprisingly, around 290 of them don’t resonate with viewers, leading to enormous monetary losses on content that’s left unseen. With the latest writer’s contract in play, insiders predict that the number of scripted shows could potentially drop by a third in the coming years. Keeping Viewership Numbers Close to the Chest In an industry that thrives on numbers, streaming services have surprisingly resisted revealing their viewership data. Despite writers pushing for transparency, streaming giants have decided against publicizing these figures, sharing only aggregate data with the Writers’ Guild. The reluctance to disclose such information could be attributed to a fear that poor viewership numbers might adversely impact stock prices. Consolidation - The Next Step? With a multitude of streaming services vying for attention, the market’s future might lie in “consolidation.” Think of it as a streaming package deal, where for a fixed fee, consumers get access to multiple platforms like Disney+, Netflix, and ESPN. It might sound familiar; this strategy reflects the model that cable TV followed, where viewers paid for a bunch of channels, many of which they rarely watched. However, critics argue that this consolidation is just a ruse to recreate the old Cable TV model, where content merit took a backseat. In the golden era of cable TV, viewers paid for multiple channels, leading to a content glut filled with ads, repetitive shows, and often biased programming. The Need for Merit-Based Content One of the glaring differences between cable TV and streaming services is the need for content merit in the latter. Consumers choose their subscriptions based on the quality and appeal of the content. Streaming platforms can’t afford to rest on their laurels, unlike the old cable TV days. If these platforms opt for bundled packages, it might allow them to slip back into the old content production patterns, leading to more generic, less engaging programming. Exploring Free Alternatives For viewers tired of paying for content they don’t enjoy, there are alternatives like PlutoTV, FreeVee, and Tubi. These platforms offer a plethora of shows and movies, ensuring that viewers don’t need to dig into their pockets for quality entertainment. Final Thoughts The world of streaming is at a crossroads. As Hollywood grapples with the challenges of producing engaging content and staying profitable, viewers should be cautious. After all, it’s about value for money and getting the quality entertainment that viewers deserve. As the industry evolves, it’s up to consumers to vote with their wallets and ensure they’re getting the best bang for their buck.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Baton Rouge Police Under Fire - Inside the Controversial ‘Brave Cave’</title><link href="/news/2023/10/03/Baton-Rouge-Torture-Warehouse/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Baton Rouge Police Under Fire - Inside the Controversial ‘Brave Cave’" /><published>2023-10-03T16:12:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-03T16:12:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/03/Baton-Rouge-Torture-Warehouse</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/03/Baton-Rouge-Torture-Warehouse/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Baton Rouge Faces a Tumultuous Turn&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Baton Rouge Police Department (BRPD) is currently mired in controversy after several alarming allegations of misconduct inside a facility colloquially known as the “Brave Cave.” The disturbing events reportedly occurring inside this so-called ‘torture warehouse’ are the subject of numerous lawsuits, one of which has been filed by a grandmother alleging “sexual humiliation” after a routine traffic stop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deeper into the “Brave Cave” Allegations&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BRPD is enduring increasing public scrutiny following the FBI’s decision to open a civil rights investigation into the “Brave Cave.” Ternell Brown and Jeremy Lee, two of the plaintiffs, have spotlighted the notorious warehouse in their respective lawsuits filed earlier this year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Brown claims that she experienced “sexual humiliation” after enduring unnecessary strip and body cavity searches at the facility. Lee’s case is equally harrowing. After his arrest and subsequent detention at the “Brave Cave”, he was reportedly so severely beaten that the local jail refused him entry until he received hospital treatment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2023/09/720/405/Ternell-Brown-3.jpg?ve=1&amp;amp;tl=1&quot; alt=&quot;Jeremy Lee Body Camera Footage&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Jeremy Lee as captured on body-worn camera footage during his alleged detainment and assault in the ‘Brave Cave’ facility. Image Credit: Thompson Justice Institute.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ryan Thompson, representing Brown, mentioned to media outlets that more allegations of abuse from the “Brave Cave” continue to surface. He anticipates filing another lawsuit soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Responding to the uproar, BRPD Public Information Officer L’Jean McKneely stated that the department is taking the accusations seriously and has initiated both administrative and criminal investigations. The contentious “Brave Cave” facility has been closed, and the officers associated with it have been reassigned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The History and Fallout&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many are now asking: What was the “Brave Cave?” According to multiple sources, it served as a sort of “home base” where BRPD officers would take suspects for intensive interrogation, with the intent to gather intelligence and potentially turn them into informants. The location, which processed “thousands of suspects” over two decades, has now been shut down by Baton Rouge officials.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The investigations have exposed disturbing instances of alleged misconduct by officers, including using excessive force and conspiring to hide incriminating body camera footage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Right to Justice&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every individual, regardless of their situation, has rights, including the right to legal representation and a fair trial. The allegations emerging from Baton Rouge are deeply troubling and raise pressing questions about the violation of these rights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The office of East Baton Rouge Parish Attorney Anderson Dotson and the Baton Rouge Union of Police have refrained from commenting due to the ongoing legal battles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the legal proceedings unfold, the Baton Rouge community and the nation will be closely watching. The hope is that justice will prevail, trust will be restored, and measures will be put in place to prevent any future misconduct.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Baton Rouge Faces a Tumultuous Turn The Baton Rouge Police Department (BRPD) is currently mired in controversy after several alarming allegations of misconduct inside a facility colloquially known as the “Brave Cave.” The disturbing events reportedly occurring inside this so-called ‘torture warehouse’ are the subject of numerous lawsuits, one of which has been filed by a grandmother alleging “sexual humiliation” after a routine traffic stop. Deeper into the “Brave Cave” Allegations BRPD is enduring increasing public scrutiny following the FBI’s decision to open a civil rights investigation into the “Brave Cave.” Ternell Brown and Jeremy Lee, two of the plaintiffs, have spotlighted the notorious warehouse in their respective lawsuits filed earlier this year. Brown claims that she experienced “sexual humiliation” after enduring unnecessary strip and body cavity searches at the facility. Lee’s case is equally harrowing. After his arrest and subsequent detention at the “Brave Cave”, he was reportedly so severely beaten that the local jail refused him entry until he received hospital treatment. Jeremy Lee as captured on body-worn camera footage during his alleged detainment and assault in the ‘Brave Cave’ facility. Image Credit: Thompson Justice Institute. Ryan Thompson, representing Brown, mentioned to media outlets that more allegations of abuse from the “Brave Cave” continue to surface. He anticipates filing another lawsuit soon. Responding to the uproar, BRPD Public Information Officer L’Jean McKneely stated that the department is taking the accusations seriously and has initiated both administrative and criminal investigations. The contentious “Brave Cave” facility has been closed, and the officers associated with it have been reassigned. The History and Fallout Many are now asking: What was the “Brave Cave?” According to multiple sources, it served as a sort of “home base” where BRPD officers would take suspects for intensive interrogation, with the intent to gather intelligence and potentially turn them into informants. The location, which processed “thousands of suspects” over two decades, has now been shut down by Baton Rouge officials. The investigations have exposed disturbing instances of alleged misconduct by officers, including using excessive force and conspiring to hide incriminating body camera footage. The Right to Justice Every individual, regardless of their situation, has rights, including the right to legal representation and a fair trial. The allegations emerging from Baton Rouge are deeply troubling and raise pressing questions about the violation of these rights. The office of East Baton Rouge Parish Attorney Anderson Dotson and the Baton Rouge Union of Police have refrained from commenting due to the ongoing legal battles. While the legal proceedings unfold, the Baton Rouge community and the nation will be closely watching. The hope is that justice will prevail, trust will be restored, and measures will be put in place to prevent any future misconduct.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump Slams AG James - Claims Businesses Exiting New York</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/03/Trump-Business-Exodus-NY/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump Slams AG James - Claims Businesses Exiting New York" /><published>2023-10-03T15:17:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-03T15:17:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/03/Trump-Business-Exodus-NY</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/03/Trump-Business-Exodus-NY/">&lt;p&gt;The courtroom drama enveloping former President Donald Trump took a heated turn when he criticized New York Attorney General Letitia James. Trump alleges that businesses are leaving the state due to the Attorney General’s aggressive actions and said that “anybody that does business in New York State is crazy.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;trump-vs-the-big-apple&quot;&gt;Trump vs. The Big Apple&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first day of Attorney General Letitia James’ civil fraud case against Trump was marked by the former president’s scathing remarks against her and the judicial process in New York. Trump’s main argument is that the state, under James, is hostile to businesses. He remarked:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“And you ought to go after this attorney general because she’s turning off everybody from coming in. Businesses are fleeing New York because of horrible, horrible attorney generals and judges like we have.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;election-campaigns--personal-agendas&quot;&gt;Election Campaigns &amp;amp; Personal Agendas&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trump emphasized that James had used her intent to prosecute him as a selling point during her election campaign. He said:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“When you have a radical left attorney general like Letitia James…she got elected on the fact that she’s going to ‘take down President Trump.’”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This allegation isn’t baseless. As Breitbart News reported, James had indeed promised punitive measures against Trump during her 2018 campaign, a fact noted by several publications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;accusations-of-racism--election-interference&quot;&gt;Accusations of Racism &amp;amp; Election Interference&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trump didn’t shy away from calling James a “racist attorney general”, reiterating his belief that the ongoing trial is part of a “witch hunt.” His frustrations also pointed toward the broader political scenario. Trump said:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“This is a continuation of the single greatest witch hunt of all time. We have a racist attorney general who’s a horror show.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The former president believes the case against him is an attempt at “election interference” by parties threatened by his political presence. He underscored:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“This has to do with election interference, plain and simple. They’re trying to damage me so that I don’t do as well as I’m doing in the election.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-glimpse-of-the-political-landscape&quot;&gt;A Glimpse of the Political Landscape&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These comments shed light on the tense political climate leading up to the 2024 presidential elections. Trump’s accusations against AG James, the judiciary, and the broader Democratic agenda hint at the deep divisions within the country’s political landscape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the trial continues, it’s crucial for observers to separate the legal matters from the political rhetoric. However, with Trump expected to be present for the coming hearings, one can anticipate further fiery exchanges in and out of the courtroom.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">The courtroom drama enveloping former President Donald Trump took a heated turn when he criticized New York Attorney General Letitia James. Trump alleges that businesses are leaving the state due to the Attorney General’s aggressive actions and said that “anybody that does business in New York State is crazy.” Trump vs. The Big Apple The first day of Attorney General Letitia James’ civil fraud case against Trump was marked by the former president’s scathing remarks against her and the judicial process in New York. Trump’s main argument is that the state, under James, is hostile to businesses. He remarked: “And you ought to go after this attorney general because she’s turning off everybody from coming in. Businesses are fleeing New York because of horrible, horrible attorney generals and judges like we have.” Election Campaigns &amp;amp; Personal Agendas Trump emphasized that James had used her intent to prosecute him as a selling point during her election campaign. He said: “When you have a radical left attorney general like Letitia James…she got elected on the fact that she’s going to ‘take down President Trump.’” This allegation isn’t baseless. As Breitbart News reported, James had indeed promised punitive measures against Trump during her 2018 campaign, a fact noted by several publications. Accusations of Racism &amp;amp; Election Interference Trump didn’t shy away from calling James a “racist attorney general”, reiterating his belief that the ongoing trial is part of a “witch hunt.” His frustrations also pointed toward the broader political scenario. Trump said: “This is a continuation of the single greatest witch hunt of all time. We have a racist attorney general who’s a horror show.” The former president believes the case against him is an attempt at “election interference” by parties threatened by his political presence. He underscored: “This has to do with election interference, plain and simple. They’re trying to damage me so that I don’t do as well as I’m doing in the election.” A Glimpse of the Political Landscape These comments shed light on the tense political climate leading up to the 2024 presidential elections. Trump’s accusations against AG James, the judiciary, and the broader Democratic agenda hint at the deep divisions within the country’s political landscape. As the trial continues, it’s crucial for observers to separate the legal matters from the political rhetoric. However, with Trump expected to be present for the coming hearings, one can anticipate further fiery exchanges in and out of the courtroom.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Kidnapped Woman in Washington - A Disturbing Fantasy Act</title><link href="/news/2023/10/03/Kidnapping-Fantasy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Kidnapped Woman in Washington - A Disturbing Fantasy Act" /><published>2023-10-03T14:21:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-03T14:21:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/03/Kidnapping-Fantasy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/03/Kidnapping-Fantasy/">&lt;p&gt;In a harrowing case emerging from Tacoma, Washington, a repeat offender is facing life imprisonment after the court found him guilty of holding a woman hostage in his garage for several weeks, “acting out a fantasy.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Henry Hauser, a 56-year-old with a history of heinous crimes, was convicted last week on kidnapping and sexual assault charges. With his sentencing set for Friday, the community anticipates a potential life sentence without parole.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-predatory-offer&quot;&gt;A Predatory Offer&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The female victim, who was homeless at the time, shared that on Nov. 10, 2021, Hauser had lured her with the promise of shelter in his garage. However, the initial friendly demeanor soon took a dark turn. The victim recounts that after spending some time in the garage, upon sensing discomfort and attempting to depart, she was forcefully restrained by Hauser. He bound her to his truck with a chain, leading to a weeks-long nightmare.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Throughout her captivity, the woman stated that Hauser drugged her repeatedly, resulting in significant “memory issues.” She detailed the disturbing statements Hauser made, suggesting he was living out a sinister fantasy. “He would ask her if she wanted to be hurt… say he was going to kill her slowly, but other times would say he wanted to ‘keep’ her,” the court affidavit reveals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This terrifying ordeal finally came to an end on Nov. 28, 2021, when the victim managed to free herself due to Hauser’s carelessness, allowing her to escape and find help.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-long-trail-of-crimes&quot;&gt;A Long Trail of Crimes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tacoma police apprehended Hauser on Dec. 2, 2021, after he was spotted on Walmart surveillance footage using the victim’s food stamps. His criminal history further exacerbates the alarming nature of his recent conviction. Hauser, labeled a level 3 sex offender, had previously severed his ankle monitor ties. He was also convicted in 2014 for kidnapping a minor at knifepoint, where he then administered drugs and assaulted her. Earlier in 2007, his rap sheet expanded with convictions for second-degree kidnapping involving a deadly weapon and felony harassment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The community and the broader public eagerly await his sentencing, hoping for justice for the victim and to ensure a repeat offender like Hauser stays behind bars, preventing any more heinous acts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyone with additional information on the case is urged to get in touch with the local police. The importance of community vigilance and timely reporting can’t be overstated to ensure safety for all.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a harrowing case emerging from Tacoma, Washington, a repeat offender is facing life imprisonment after the court found him guilty of holding a woman hostage in his garage for several weeks, “acting out a fantasy.” Henry Hauser, a 56-year-old with a history of heinous crimes, was convicted last week on kidnapping and sexual assault charges. With his sentencing set for Friday, the community anticipates a potential life sentence without parole. A Predatory Offer The female victim, who was homeless at the time, shared that on Nov. 10, 2021, Hauser had lured her with the promise of shelter in his garage. However, the initial friendly demeanor soon took a dark turn. The victim recounts that after spending some time in the garage, upon sensing discomfort and attempting to depart, she was forcefully restrained by Hauser. He bound her to his truck with a chain, leading to a weeks-long nightmare. Throughout her captivity, the woman stated that Hauser drugged her repeatedly, resulting in significant “memory issues.” She detailed the disturbing statements Hauser made, suggesting he was living out a sinister fantasy. “He would ask her if she wanted to be hurt… say he was going to kill her slowly, but other times would say he wanted to ‘keep’ her,” the court affidavit reveals. This terrifying ordeal finally came to an end on Nov. 28, 2021, when the victim managed to free herself due to Hauser’s carelessness, allowing her to escape and find help. A Long Trail of Crimes Tacoma police apprehended Hauser on Dec. 2, 2021, after he was spotted on Walmart surveillance footage using the victim’s food stamps. His criminal history further exacerbates the alarming nature of his recent conviction. Hauser, labeled a level 3 sex offender, had previously severed his ankle monitor ties. He was also convicted in 2014 for kidnapping a minor at knifepoint, where he then administered drugs and assaulted her. Earlier in 2007, his rap sheet expanded with convictions for second-degree kidnapping involving a deadly weapon and felony harassment. The community and the broader public eagerly await his sentencing, hoping for justice for the victim and to ensure a repeat offender like Hauser stays behind bars, preventing any more heinous acts. Anyone with additional information on the case is urged to get in touch with the local police. The importance of community vigilance and timely reporting can’t be overstated to ensure safety for all.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Graham Stands Up - Accuses NY of Trying to Destroy Trump</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/03/Graham-Defends-Trump/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Graham Stands Up - Accuses NY of Trying to Destroy Trump" /><published>2023-10-03T13:01:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-03T13:01:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/03/Graham-Defends-Trump</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/03/Graham-Defends-Trump/">&lt;p&gt;In a world where politics and personal vendettas often merge, Senator Lindsey Graham (R-SC) voices his robust defense of former President Donald Trump. On Monday, appearing on FNC’s “Hannity”, Graham made a bold claim regarding New York State Attorney General Letitia James’ civil suit against Trump, painting it as part of a calculated assault against the former president.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-deliberate-strategy-against-trump&quot;&gt;A Deliberate Strategy Against Trump?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Graham pulled no punches, labeling the legal actions as “a systematic effort to destroy Donald Trump as a political person.” He emphasized Trump’s crime in the eyes of his adversaries: “His crime was he was a good conservative president.” Graham’s sentiments hint at an escalating animosity within the political arena, where he states, “I’ve never seen hatred toward a political figure like I see against President Trump.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;banks-insurance-and-fiscal-valuations&quot;&gt;Banks, Insurance, and Fiscal Valuations&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sean Hannity, the anchor of the show, brought forward a valid point to the discussion. He said, “The banks got paid, the insurance companies got paid,” questioning the actual premise of the fraud case. Hannity’s sharp observation highlights the obligation of banks and insurance companies to carry out their fiduciary duties. These institutions, when entering into multi-million dollar agreements, should not solely rely on external valuations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;grahams-call-to-action&quot;&gt;Graham’s Call to Action&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Graham’s spirited defense continued, taking aim at the judicial decision itself. He expressed his incredulity regarding the valuation of Trump’s Mar-a-Lago, remarking, “The judge believes that Mar-a-Lago’s worth $18 million. What a friggin’ joke.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a stirring appeal to the audience and potential voters in key states, Graham said, “President Trump can’t be in Iowa and South Carolina and New Hampshire. But if you live in these states, you can help him by making sure that liberals do not get away with this. Vote for President Trump.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-rallying-cry-for-conservatives&quot;&gt;A Rallying Cry for Conservatives&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In these tumultuous times, where political battles are increasingly fought in courts rather than ballot boxes, Graham’s words serve as a rallying cry for conservatives. The Senator’s fervent defense of Trump underscores the broader theme of political bias, framing the NY lawsuit as a targeted move against the former president.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the political climate continues to heat up with the approach of the 2024 elections, such defenses and accusations will likely play a significant role in shaping public opinion. It remains to be seen how this will influence voter sentiments, but one thing is clear: the battle lines are drawn.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a world where politics and personal vendettas often merge, Senator Lindsey Graham (R-SC) voices his robust defense of former President Donald Trump. On Monday, appearing on FNC’s “Hannity”, Graham made a bold claim regarding New York State Attorney General Letitia James’ civil suit against Trump, painting it as part of a calculated assault against the former president. A Deliberate Strategy Against Trump? Graham pulled no punches, labeling the legal actions as “a systematic effort to destroy Donald Trump as a political person.” He emphasized Trump’s crime in the eyes of his adversaries: “His crime was he was a good conservative president.” Graham’s sentiments hint at an escalating animosity within the political arena, where he states, “I’ve never seen hatred toward a political figure like I see against President Trump.” Banks, Insurance, and Fiscal Valuations Sean Hannity, the anchor of the show, brought forward a valid point to the discussion. He said, “The banks got paid, the insurance companies got paid,” questioning the actual premise of the fraud case. Hannity’s sharp observation highlights the obligation of banks and insurance companies to carry out their fiduciary duties. These institutions, when entering into multi-million dollar agreements, should not solely rely on external valuations. Graham’s Call to Action Graham’s spirited defense continued, taking aim at the judicial decision itself. He expressed his incredulity regarding the valuation of Trump’s Mar-a-Lago, remarking, “The judge believes that Mar-a-Lago’s worth $18 million. What a friggin’ joke.” In a stirring appeal to the audience and potential voters in key states, Graham said, “President Trump can’t be in Iowa and South Carolina and New Hampshire. But if you live in these states, you can help him by making sure that liberals do not get away with this. Vote for President Trump.” A Rallying Cry for Conservatives In these tumultuous times, where political battles are increasingly fought in courts rather than ballot boxes, Graham’s words serve as a rallying cry for conservatives. The Senator’s fervent defense of Trump underscores the broader theme of political bias, framing the NY lawsuit as a targeted move against the former president. As the political climate continues to heat up with the approach of the 2024 elections, such defenses and accusations will likely play a significant role in shaping public opinion. It remains to be seen how this will influence voter sentiments, but one thing is clear: the battle lines are drawn.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Dramatic Rescue - 9-Year-Old Charlotte Sena Found After Kidnapping</title><link href="/news/2023/10/03/Charlotte-Sena-Rescue/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dramatic Rescue - 9-Year-Old Charlotte Sena Found After Kidnapping" /><published>2023-10-03T12:06:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-03T12:06:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/03/Charlotte-Sena-Rescue</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/03/Charlotte-Sena-Rescue/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MOREAU, N.Y.&lt;/strong&gt; — Joyful tears were shed as missing 9-year-old Charlotte Sena was found safe and sound after a distressing disappearance from Moreau Lake State Park in New York over the weekend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The determined efforts of the New York State Police culminated in the arrest of a suspect, identified as 47-year-old Craig Nelson Ross Jr. The arrest followed after police, in a twist straight out of a crime drama, witnessed Ross drop a ransom note in the Sena family mailbox.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Charlotte, described as a “bright and adventurous girl”, went missing during a seemingly peaceful bike ride in the park. Her family was sent into a panic, and her disappearance triggered an immediate search and subsequent Amber Alert. The alert described the urgency and potential danger of the situation, pushing for Charlotte’s swift return.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet, even as hope started to dwindle among the public, close family friends like Patrick Kane remained steadfast in their optimism. “God’s going to bring her back home,” he asserted even before the good news was announced.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And indeed, hope wasn’t misplaced. State and federal tactical teams pinpointed Ross’s location, descending on a camper tucked behind his mother’s residence in Milton. Inside, a brief standoff ensued, after which Ross was apprehended. More importantly, Charlotte was found — scared but unharmed, hidden inside a camper cabinet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Governor Kathy Hochul couldn’t hide her relief and gratitude during a press briefing, lauding the efforts of the police forces involved. “It is because of their efforts that Charlotte will be able to return home safe to her family,” she expressed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Charlotte’s story serves as a somber reminder of the dangers that can lurk even in the most unsuspecting places. However, it also highlights the power of community, resilience, and the unyielding hope that binds families and entire states together during trying times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ongoing investigation means that many questions remain unanswered. Authorities continue to encourage anyone with pertinent information to come forward.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For now, the Sena family, their friends, and countless well-wishers take a moment to breathe, thankful for Charlotte’s safe return.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">MOREAU, N.Y. — Joyful tears were shed as missing 9-year-old Charlotte Sena was found safe and sound after a distressing disappearance from Moreau Lake State Park in New York over the weekend. The determined efforts of the New York State Police culminated in the arrest of a suspect, identified as 47-year-old Craig Nelson Ross Jr. The arrest followed after police, in a twist straight out of a crime drama, witnessed Ross drop a ransom note in the Sena family mailbox. Charlotte, described as a “bright and adventurous girl”, went missing during a seemingly peaceful bike ride in the park. Her family was sent into a panic, and her disappearance triggered an immediate search and subsequent Amber Alert. The alert described the urgency and potential danger of the situation, pushing for Charlotte’s swift return. Yet, even as hope started to dwindle among the public, close family friends like Patrick Kane remained steadfast in their optimism. “God’s going to bring her back home,” he asserted even before the good news was announced. And indeed, hope wasn’t misplaced. State and federal tactical teams pinpointed Ross’s location, descending on a camper tucked behind his mother’s residence in Milton. Inside, a brief standoff ensued, after which Ross was apprehended. More importantly, Charlotte was found — scared but unharmed, hidden inside a camper cabinet. Governor Kathy Hochul couldn’t hide her relief and gratitude during a press briefing, lauding the efforts of the police forces involved. “It is because of their efforts that Charlotte will be able to return home safe to her family,” she expressed. Charlotte’s story serves as a somber reminder of the dangers that can lurk even in the most unsuspecting places. However, it also highlights the power of community, resilience, and the unyielding hope that binds families and entire states together during trying times. The ongoing investigation means that many questions remain unanswered. Authorities continue to encourage anyone with pertinent information to come forward. For now, the Sena family, their friends, and countless well-wishers take a moment to breathe, thankful for Charlotte’s safe return.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Freedom of Speech Under Fire - Trudeau’s New Mandate on Podcast Platforms</title><link href="/news/2023/10/03/Canadian-Podcast-Regulation/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Freedom of Speech Under Fire - Trudeau’s New Mandate on Podcast Platforms" /><published>2023-10-03T11:18:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-03T11:18:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/03/Canadian-Podcast-Regulation</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/03/Canadian-Podcast-Regulation/">&lt;p&gt;Canada’s Prime Minister, Justin Trudeau, has implemented stringent new mandates, requiring podcast platforms and streaming services to register with the Canadian Radio-television and Telecommunications Commission (CRTC), sparking concerns amongst free speech advocates over the authoritarian approach to independent media.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-stranglehold-on-streaming-services&quot;&gt;A Stranglehold on Streaming Services?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The regulation mandates that platforms operating in Canada with annual revenues of $10 million or more must register with the CRTC by November 28th. The proclaimed intention is to modernize Canada’s broadcasting framework and promote meaningful contributions to Canadian and Indigenous content. The move potentially equates online content to the restrictions traditionally placed on broadcasting mediums like television and radio.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;who-is-affected&quot;&gt;Who is Affected?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This decree affects online service providers of podcasts but exempts individuals who produce or share podcasts online. Also, the framework does not apply to services exclusively featuring video games or audiobooks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;freedom-of-speech---a-diminishing-right&quot;&gt;Freedom of Speech - A Diminishing Right?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The overhaul has caused alarm, with renowned voices such as independent journalist Glenn Greenwald and tech magnate Elon Musk, criticizing Trudeau’s regime as being repressive and aiming to stifle free speech. The development comes as a reaction to the perceived amplification of censorship and control by Trudeau’s government, with multiple instances of citizens facing punitive measures for expressing divergent views on gender and other subjects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;international-backlash&quot;&gt;International Backlash&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The backlash is not only domestic. Observers and critics worldwide are voicing their concerns, with some drawing extreme parallels, labeling Trudeau’s actions as analogous to authoritarian regimes. The critics argue that such regulations can suppress the dissident voices and independent media, depriving the citizens of Canada of their right to be informed and to express their views freely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-wake-up-call-for-podcasters&quot;&gt;A Wake-up Call for Podcasters&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The new regulations have ignited debates around the limits of free speech and the role of government in controlling media. While the government asserts its stance as a means to adapt to changing circumstances and ensure diversity of perspectives, detractors view it as a means of enforcing conformity and silencing dissenting opinions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The implementation of new regulations by Prime Minister Justin Trudeau has highlighted the delicate balance between maintaining order and preserving individual freedoms in the realm of digital media and broadcasting. The outcry from international and domestic observers underscores the global implications of such mandates, raising urgent questions about the preservation of free speech and democratic values in a rapidly evolving digital landscape.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Canada’s Prime Minister, Justin Trudeau, has implemented stringent new mandates, requiring podcast platforms and streaming services to register with the Canadian Radio-television and Telecommunications Commission (CRTC), sparking concerns amongst free speech advocates over the authoritarian approach to independent media. A Stranglehold on Streaming Services? The regulation mandates that platforms operating in Canada with annual revenues of $10 million or more must register with the CRTC by November 28th. The proclaimed intention is to modernize Canada’s broadcasting framework and promote meaningful contributions to Canadian and Indigenous content. The move potentially equates online content to the restrictions traditionally placed on broadcasting mediums like television and radio. Who is Affected? This decree affects online service providers of podcasts but exempts individuals who produce or share podcasts online. Also, the framework does not apply to services exclusively featuring video games or audiobooks. Freedom of Speech - A Diminishing Right? The overhaul has caused alarm, with renowned voices such as independent journalist Glenn Greenwald and tech magnate Elon Musk, criticizing Trudeau’s regime as being repressive and aiming to stifle free speech. The development comes as a reaction to the perceived amplification of censorship and control by Trudeau’s government, with multiple instances of citizens facing punitive measures for expressing divergent views on gender and other subjects. International Backlash The backlash is not only domestic. Observers and critics worldwide are voicing their concerns, with some drawing extreme parallels, labeling Trudeau’s actions as analogous to authoritarian regimes. The critics argue that such regulations can suppress the dissident voices and independent media, depriving the citizens of Canada of their right to be informed and to express their views freely. A Wake-up Call for Podcasters The new regulations have ignited debates around the limits of free speech and the role of government in controlling media. While the government asserts its stance as a means to adapt to changing circumstances and ensure diversity of perspectives, detractors view it as a means of enforcing conformity and silencing dissenting opinions. Conclusion The implementation of new regulations by Prime Minister Justin Trudeau has highlighted the delicate balance between maintaining order and preserving individual freedoms in the realm of digital media and broadcasting. The outcry from international and domestic observers underscores the global implications of such mandates, raising urgent questions about the preservation of free speech and democratic values in a rapidly evolving digital landscape.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump Stands Strong in ‘Sham’ NY Trial</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/03/Trump-Trial-Defense/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump Stands Strong in ‘Sham’ NY Trial" /><published>2023-10-03T10:03:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-03T10:03:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/03/Trump-Trial-Defense</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/03/Trump-Trial-Defense/">&lt;p&gt;In a society where legal cases have become weapons of political destruction, former President Donald Trump, a pivotal figure in modern American politics, makes a rare, voluntary trip to court to confront a civil trial stemming from a lawsuit by New York Attorney General Letitia James. The trial has been labeled by Trump and his supporters as a blatant and disgraceful ‘witch hunt,’ aimed at tarnishing his illustrious name and reputation ahead of the upcoming 2024 presidential election, in which he currently leads the Republican primary field by a significant margin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-fight-against-corrupt-proceedings&quot;&gt;A Fight against ‘Corrupt’ Proceedings&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trump stepped into the courthouse in Lower Manhattan, standing tall, exhibiting characteristic resilience and resolve. With the world watching, he robustly defended his financial statements as ‘phenomenal,’ condemning the trial as a continuation of a relentless pursuit spearheaded by individuals with ulterior motives. His powerful remarks highlighted the ongoing corrosion of legal proceedings by political intent, showcasing his enduring fight against corrupt systems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;trumps-unwavering-assertions&quot;&gt;Trump’s Unwavering Assertions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Just so you know, my financial statements are phenomenal,” Trump asserted, emphasizing his innocence and the groundlessness of the charges against him. He questioned the involvement of banks, highlighting their satisfaction with him as a ‘perfect client,’ having been paid back on time, with no defaults or any other complications. Trump’s strong and clear-cut assertions underscored his commitment to truth and transparency, reinforcing his stand against the allegations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;rogue-elements-and-scams&quot;&gt;‘Rogue’ Elements and Scams&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trump unhesitatingly blasted both the presiding judge, Arthur Engoron, and Attorney General Letitia James, labeling them as ‘rogue’ and ‘racist’ respectively. He criticized James for her obsession with targeting him, citing it as a political tool to gain traction for her gubernatorial run, which ultimately failed. His statements accentuated the severity of the biased and unfair treatment meted out to him, portraying the extensive manipulation within the trial.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-real-issues&quot;&gt;The Real Issues&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While Trump’s business dealings and family have been the focus of the AG’s probe, he highlighted the rising crime and violence on the streets of New York, pointing out the misplaced priorities of the state’s legal enforcers. “People are being murdered all over the sidewalks of New York,” Trump remarked, bringing to light the pressing issues being overshadowed by political vendettas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-symbol-of-resilience&quot;&gt;A Symbol of Resilience&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite the ongoing onslaught, Trump remains a symbol of resilience and unwavering strength in the face of adversity, echoing the sentiments of millions who believe in his vision and leadership. His staunch defense against politically motivated trials exemplifies his steadfast dedication to his values and the American people, continually fueling the flame of hope for a balanced and just political environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In an era marked by politically charged legal battles, Trump’s vigorous defense and steadfast resolve stand out, reinforcing his position as a pivotal leader, tirelessly fighting against corruption and for the truth. His commitment to facing and addressing issues head-on continues to resonate with many, elevating his status as a symbol of enduring strength and integrity in turbulent times.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a society where legal cases have become weapons of political destruction, former President Donald Trump, a pivotal figure in modern American politics, makes a rare, voluntary trip to court to confront a civil trial stemming from a lawsuit by New York Attorney General Letitia James. The trial has been labeled by Trump and his supporters as a blatant and disgraceful ‘witch hunt,’ aimed at tarnishing his illustrious name and reputation ahead of the upcoming 2024 presidential election, in which he currently leads the Republican primary field by a significant margin. A Fight against ‘Corrupt’ Proceedings Trump stepped into the courthouse in Lower Manhattan, standing tall, exhibiting characteristic resilience and resolve. With the world watching, he robustly defended his financial statements as ‘phenomenal,’ condemning the trial as a continuation of a relentless pursuit spearheaded by individuals with ulterior motives. His powerful remarks highlighted the ongoing corrosion of legal proceedings by political intent, showcasing his enduring fight against corrupt systems. Trump’s Unwavering Assertions “Just so you know, my financial statements are phenomenal,” Trump asserted, emphasizing his innocence and the groundlessness of the charges against him. He questioned the involvement of banks, highlighting their satisfaction with him as a ‘perfect client,’ having been paid back on time, with no defaults or any other complications. Trump’s strong and clear-cut assertions underscored his commitment to truth and transparency, reinforcing his stand against the allegations. ‘Rogue’ Elements and Scams Trump unhesitatingly blasted both the presiding judge, Arthur Engoron, and Attorney General Letitia James, labeling them as ‘rogue’ and ‘racist’ respectively. He criticized James for her obsession with targeting him, citing it as a political tool to gain traction for her gubernatorial run, which ultimately failed. His statements accentuated the severity of the biased and unfair treatment meted out to him, portraying the extensive manipulation within the trial. The Real Issues While Trump’s business dealings and family have been the focus of the AG’s probe, he highlighted the rising crime and violence on the streets of New York, pointing out the misplaced priorities of the state’s legal enforcers. “People are being murdered all over the sidewalks of New York,” Trump remarked, bringing to light the pressing issues being overshadowed by political vendettas. A Symbol of Resilience Despite the ongoing onslaught, Trump remains a symbol of resilience and unwavering strength in the face of adversity, echoing the sentiments of millions who believe in his vision and leadership. His staunch defense against politically motivated trials exemplifies his steadfast dedication to his values and the American people, continually fueling the flame of hope for a balanced and just political environment. In an era marked by politically charged legal battles, Trump’s vigorous defense and steadfast resolve stand out, reinforcing his position as a pivotal leader, tirelessly fighting against corruption and for the truth. His commitment to facing and addressing issues head-on continues to resonate with many, elevating his status as a symbol of enduring strength and integrity in turbulent times.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">AI Doppelganger Alert - Tom Hanks Denies Involvement in Dental Insurance Ad</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/03/Tom-Hanks-AI-Imposter/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="AI Doppelganger Alert - Tom Hanks Denies Involvement in Dental Insurance Ad" /><published>2023-10-03T09:15:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-03T09:15:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/03/Tom-Hanks-AI-Imposter</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/03/Tom-Hanks-AI-Imposter/">&lt;p&gt;Hollywood’s beloved actor, Tom Hanks, known for his myriad of memorable roles, is warning fans about a deceptive video circulating the web. The video in question, purporting to feature Hanks endorsing a dental insurance plan, is not just an example of false advertising—it’s completely fabricated through artificial intelligence (AI). The actor made it emphatically clear that he has no connection with the product, nor the company behind it, and alerted his 9.5 million Instagram followers to the hoax.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;ai-driven-deception&quot;&gt;AI-Driven Deception&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The AI-rendered video displays a youthful Tom Hanks persuasively selling dental insurance. It showcases how advanced and convincing deepfake technologies have become. Hanks took to Instagram to sound the alarm, urging caution among his followers about the deceptive representation, labeling it as “fakery.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-glimpse-into-deepfake-technology&quot;&gt;A Glimpse into Deepfake Technology&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Deepfake technology utilizes AI to create hyper-realistic but entirely fake content. In this instance, it fabricated a version of Tom Hanks to endorse a product he has never associated with. It raises serious concerns about the ethical implications and potential harm these convincing fabrications could cause.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;hollywoods-battle-with-ai&quot;&gt;Hollywood’s Battle with AI&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The creation of deceptive AI representations is not a singular occurrence in Hollywood. The industry is actively engaged in a battle against the imposition of AI in the creative process. A recent settlement amidst a writer’s strike highlighted the tension, as it stressed that studios cannot compel writers to use AI, and AI products must only complement human writers, not replace them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-continuing-struggle-for-authenticity&quot;&gt;The Continuing Struggle for Authenticity&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This incident illustrates the continual struggle between technology and authenticity within the entertainment industry. The impact of generative AI not only affects writers but also visual artists and actors, reshaping the understanding of “fair use” in the process. Industry executive, Barry Diller, argued that the protections in place are not sufficient, stressing the necessity for clear boundaries between AI-generated and genuine content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-warning-and-a-precedent&quot;&gt;A Warning and a Precedent&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tom Hanks’ revelation serves as both a warning and a precedent. The actor, discussing the challenges AI poses, emphasized the artistic and legal complications arising from such technologies. “Outside the understanding of AI and deepfake, there’ll be nothing to tell you that it’s not me and me alone,” he said. This incident underscores the crucial need for audiences to remain vigilant and discerning, in a world where seeing is not always believing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The startling revelation by Tom Hanks sheds light on the advancing field of AI and its escalating presence in our lives. The warning issued by the esteemed actor calls for increased awareness and critical evaluation of content, reinforcing the need for stringent measures to prevent the proliferation of deceptive AI-generated representations. In a world inundated with information and imagery, discerning the real from the fabricated becomes paramount, and the revelation from Hanks is a stark reminder of this new reality.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Hollywood’s beloved actor, Tom Hanks, known for his myriad of memorable roles, is warning fans about a deceptive video circulating the web. The video in question, purporting to feature Hanks endorsing a dental insurance plan, is not just an example of false advertising—it’s completely fabricated through artificial intelligence (AI). The actor made it emphatically clear that he has no connection with the product, nor the company behind it, and alerted his 9.5 million Instagram followers to the hoax. AI-Driven Deception The AI-rendered video displays a youthful Tom Hanks persuasively selling dental insurance. It showcases how advanced and convincing deepfake technologies have become. Hanks took to Instagram to sound the alarm, urging caution among his followers about the deceptive representation, labeling it as “fakery.” A Glimpse into Deepfake Technology Deepfake technology utilizes AI to create hyper-realistic but entirely fake content. In this instance, it fabricated a version of Tom Hanks to endorse a product he has never associated with. It raises serious concerns about the ethical implications and potential harm these convincing fabrications could cause. Hollywood’s Battle with AI The creation of deceptive AI representations is not a singular occurrence in Hollywood. The industry is actively engaged in a battle against the imposition of AI in the creative process. A recent settlement amidst a writer’s strike highlighted the tension, as it stressed that studios cannot compel writers to use AI, and AI products must only complement human writers, not replace them. The Continuing Struggle for Authenticity This incident illustrates the continual struggle between technology and authenticity within the entertainment industry. The impact of generative AI not only affects writers but also visual artists and actors, reshaping the understanding of “fair use” in the process. Industry executive, Barry Diller, argued that the protections in place are not sufficient, stressing the necessity for clear boundaries between AI-generated and genuine content. A Warning and a Precedent Tom Hanks’ revelation serves as both a warning and a precedent. The actor, discussing the challenges AI poses, emphasized the artistic and legal complications arising from such technologies. “Outside the understanding of AI and deepfake, there’ll be nothing to tell you that it’s not me and me alone,” he said. This incident underscores the crucial need for audiences to remain vigilant and discerning, in a world where seeing is not always believing. Conclusion The startling revelation by Tom Hanks sheds light on the advancing field of AI and its escalating presence in our lives. The warning issued by the esteemed actor calls for increased awareness and critical evaluation of content, reinforcing the need for stringent measures to prevent the proliferation of deceptive AI-generated representations. In a world inundated with information and imagery, discerning the real from the fabricated becomes paramount, and the revelation from Hanks is a stark reminder of this new reality.</summary></entry></feed>