<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-10-26T07:12:41-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/26/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-26T07:12:41-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-26T07:12:41-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/26/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/26/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/26/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-26T07:12:41-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-26T07:12:41-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/26/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/26/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/">&lt;p&gt;Recent surprise attacks by Hamas on Israel has fueled ongoing tensions between staunchly conservative commentators and the progressive “Squad” Democrats known for criticizing Israel. The intensity of the backlash highlights the deep political divide over foreign policy in the Middle East.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Hamas’ shocking attack, several members of the “Squad,” including Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.), called for a “ceasefire and de-escalation,” condemning the violence. The absence of a statement from Rep. Rashida Tlaib (D-Mich.) was notably called out by conservative media outlets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;South Carolina GOP Rep. Nancy Mace quickly labeled Ocasio-Cortez a “Hamas apologist” in response to her call for peace and de-escalation. Rep. Ilhan Omar (D-Minn.), no stranger to controversy surrounding her views on Israel, echoed the call for de-escalation and ceasefire. Omar’s prior statements comparing the US and Israel to terrorist groups like Hamas and the Taliban resurfaced in the debate, fueling more criticisms. Omar’s 2019 tweet, where she opined that “Israel has hypnotized the world,” also continues to haunt her political career, often cited by critics to challenge her stance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conservative commentators have been especially vocal. “FOX &amp;amp; Friends Weekend” co-host Rachel Campos-Duffy took aim at Omar, saying she fails to recognize the peace in the Middle East under Trump’s administration. Conservative pundit John Hasson also called out Omar, claiming she insinuated that attacks on IDF forces were acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Massachusetts Democrat Rep. Ayanna Pressley’s concerns over the “devastating attacks on Israelis” were met with skepticism. A prominent conservative online personality, Comfortably Smug, accused the “Squad” of advising Israel to back down after the nation suffered massive attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Jamaal Bowman’s call for an end to the Gaza blockade, in addition to condemning the Hamas attacks, was met with criticism from conservative radio host Jason Rantz. He accused Bowman of pairing his condemnation of terrorism with unwarranted criticisms of Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Cori Bush emphasized the urgent need for a ceasefire, while pushing for an end to “U.S. support for Israeli military occupation and apartheid.” Defense attorney Marina Medvin criticized Bush, suggesting that she equates the death of Palestinian terrorists to the horrific acts committed against Jewish civilians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amidst the political turmoil and intense debate, the attacks have taken a heavy toll. Israeli media report over 300 dead due to the wide-ranging assault. Gaza health officials note that at least 200 Palestinians have perished in the retaliatory Israeli air strikes following the initial Hamas attack. As the situation remains volatile, both sides continue to count their casualties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This divisive issue showcases the challenge America faces in crafting a unified approach to foreign policy, with deeply entrenched political divides at play. As the situation develops, the debate is bound to intensify, shedding light on the complexities of U.S. politics in the global arena.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Miraculous Rescue: Eight Abducted Children Found Safe in California</title><link href="/news/2023/10/25/Abducted-Children-Rescued/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Miraculous Rescue: Eight Abducted Children Found Safe in California" /><published>2023-10-25T15:21:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-25T15:21:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/25/Abducted-Children-Rescued</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/25/Abducted-Children-Rescued/">&lt;p&gt;Police in California have successfully located and rescued eight children who were abducted from Arkansas. The children’s biological mother, Trista Fullerton, is now in custody, thanks to an alert citizen who noticed her bizarre behavior and contacted the authorities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Late Saturday night, the Anderson Police Department responded to a tip about a woman acting strangely in the parking lot of a local convenience store. Upon arrival, they discovered Fullerton, aged 36, along with six of the eight missing children. Fullerton, who had lost custodial rights to her children, was promptly taken into custody.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further investigation led to the recovery of the remaining two children, ensuring that all eight were safe and accounted for. The children have since been reunited with their foster families, providing relief and closure to a case that could have ended much differently.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trista Fullerton had a previous history of domestic violence, with a record that includes charges of domestic battery and violating a no-contact order. This pattern of behavior adds a layer of complexity to the case, highlighting the importance of vigilance and community awareness in safeguarding the wellbeing of children.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Anderson Police Department has expressed their gratitude to the Shasta County Sheriff’s Office for their assistance, as well as to the citizen who made the crucial call. The community played a vital role in bringing this incident to a swift and safe resolution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the specifics of Fullerton’s bizarre behavior have not been disclosed, the police’s prompt response and the cooperation of alert community members were key in locating and rescuing the abducted children. This case serves as a powerful reminder of the impact that vigilant citizens can have in ensuring the safety of the most vulnerable among us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trista Fullerton is currently being held without bail at the Shasta County Jail, facing charges on a fugitive from justice warrant. As the legal proceedings unfold, the focus remains on the wellbeing of the eight children, who have been given a second chance at safety and stability thanks to the concerted efforts of law enforcement and the community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the wake of this harrowing incident, parents and guardians are urged to remain vigilant and to report any suspicious behavior. The safety of our children is a communal responsibility, and this case underscores the power of collective awareness and action in protecting the vulnerable.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Police in California have successfully located and rescued eight children who were abducted from Arkansas. The children’s biological mother, Trista Fullerton, is now in custody, thanks to an alert citizen who noticed her bizarre behavior and contacted the authorities. Late Saturday night, the Anderson Police Department responded to a tip about a woman acting strangely in the parking lot of a local convenience store. Upon arrival, they discovered Fullerton, aged 36, along with six of the eight missing children. Fullerton, who had lost custodial rights to her children, was promptly taken into custody. Further investigation led to the recovery of the remaining two children, ensuring that all eight were safe and accounted for. The children have since been reunited with their foster families, providing relief and closure to a case that could have ended much differently. Trista Fullerton had a previous history of domestic violence, with a record that includes charges of domestic battery and violating a no-contact order. This pattern of behavior adds a layer of complexity to the case, highlighting the importance of vigilance and community awareness in safeguarding the wellbeing of children. The Anderson Police Department has expressed their gratitude to the Shasta County Sheriff’s Office for their assistance, as well as to the citizen who made the crucial call. The community played a vital role in bringing this incident to a swift and safe resolution. While the specifics of Fullerton’s bizarre behavior have not been disclosed, the police’s prompt response and the cooperation of alert community members were key in locating and rescuing the abducted children. This case serves as a powerful reminder of the impact that vigilant citizens can have in ensuring the safety of the most vulnerable among us. Trista Fullerton is currently being held without bail at the Shasta County Jail, facing charges on a fugitive from justice warrant. As the legal proceedings unfold, the focus remains on the wellbeing of the eight children, who have been given a second chance at safety and stability thanks to the concerted efforts of law enforcement and the community. In the wake of this harrowing incident, parents and guardians are urged to remain vigilant and to report any suspicious behavior. The safety of our children is a communal responsibility, and this case underscores the power of collective awareness and action in protecting the vulnerable.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Post-Roe Landscape: A Surge in Abortions Across Legal States</title><link href="/news/2023/10/25/Abortion-Rates-Increase/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Post-Roe Landscape: A Surge in Abortions Across Legal States" /><published>2023-10-25T14:08:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-25T14:08:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/25/Abortion-Rates-Increase</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/25/Abortion-Rates-Increase/">&lt;p&gt;In the year since the Supreme Court’s pivotal decision to overturn Roe v. Wade, the United States has witnessed a paradoxical shift in abortion statistics. While legal abortions have plummeted in states with bans or restrictions, the national tally of abortions has surprisingly increased.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A recent report by the Society of Family Planning, a group advocating for abortion access, reveals that state bans and restrictions haven’t translated into a decrease in overall abortion numbers. Instead, they have redirected the flow of abortion seekers to states where the procedure remains legal after six weeks of pregnancy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Drawing comparisons with baseline data from April and May 2022, the report highlights a nearly 117,000 increase in abortions in permissive states from July 2022 to June 2023. Conversely, restrictive states saw a reduction of around 115,000 procedures. The juxtaposition of these figures underscores the complex and nuanced landscape of abortion access in post-Roe America.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Illinois, Florida, North Carolina, California, and New Mexico are at the forefront of this increase, collectively facilitating tens of thousands of additional abortions. On the flip side, Texas, Georgia, Tennessee, Louisiana, and Alabama experienced the steepest declines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The report emphasizes the strategic geographical positioning of states like Illinois and North Carolina, which have become vital access points for individuals traveling from states with stringent abortion laws. The data paints a picture of an America divided, with access to abortion increasingly dependent on one’s zip code.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking forward, new restrictions looming in states that currently serve as abortion havens could significantly alter this landscape. North Carolina and Florida, in particular, are on the precipice of potential legislative changes that could curtail access.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Guttmacher Institute’s recent findings reinforce this narrative, noting a 31% drop in abortions in North Carolina following the implementation of a 12-week ban in July. Florida finds itself in a precarious position as well, with its Supreme Court currently deliberating a case that could usher in a six-week abortion ban.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As America grapples with the aftermath of the Supreme Court’s decision, the fluctuating abortion rates across states paint a picture of a nation at a crossroads. The report from the Society of Family Planning not only highlights the shifting dynamics of abortion access but also emphasizes the crucial role that state borders play in shaping the choices available to individuals across the nation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As we look to the future, the landscape of abortion access remains uncertain, with the potential for further shifts and changes as states continue to navigate this complex and contentious issue.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In the year since the Supreme Court’s pivotal decision to overturn Roe v. Wade, the United States has witnessed a paradoxical shift in abortion statistics. While legal abortions have plummeted in states with bans or restrictions, the national tally of abortions has surprisingly increased. A recent report by the Society of Family Planning, a group advocating for abortion access, reveals that state bans and restrictions haven’t translated into a decrease in overall abortion numbers. Instead, they have redirected the flow of abortion seekers to states where the procedure remains legal after six weeks of pregnancy. Drawing comparisons with baseline data from April and May 2022, the report highlights a nearly 117,000 increase in abortions in permissive states from July 2022 to June 2023. Conversely, restrictive states saw a reduction of around 115,000 procedures. The juxtaposition of these figures underscores the complex and nuanced landscape of abortion access in post-Roe America. Illinois, Florida, North Carolina, California, and New Mexico are at the forefront of this increase, collectively facilitating tens of thousands of additional abortions. On the flip side, Texas, Georgia, Tennessee, Louisiana, and Alabama experienced the steepest declines. The report emphasizes the strategic geographical positioning of states like Illinois and North Carolina, which have become vital access points for individuals traveling from states with stringent abortion laws. The data paints a picture of an America divided, with access to abortion increasingly dependent on one’s zip code. Looking forward, new restrictions looming in states that currently serve as abortion havens could significantly alter this landscape. North Carolina and Florida, in particular, are on the precipice of potential legislative changes that could curtail access. The Guttmacher Institute’s recent findings reinforce this narrative, noting a 31% drop in abortions in North Carolina following the implementation of a 12-week ban in July. Florida finds itself in a precarious position as well, with its Supreme Court currently deliberating a case that could usher in a six-week abortion ban. As America grapples with the aftermath of the Supreme Court’s decision, the fluctuating abortion rates across states paint a picture of a nation at a crossroads. The report from the Society of Family Planning not only highlights the shifting dynamics of abortion access but also emphasizes the crucial role that state borders play in shaping the choices available to individuals across the nation. As we look to the future, the landscape of abortion access remains uncertain, with the potential for further shifts and changes as states continue to navigate this complex and contentious issue.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Lone Star State Showdown: Texas Takes on Biden Over Border Security</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/25/Texas-Sues-Biden-Administration/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Lone Star State Showdown: Texas Takes on Biden Over Border Security" /><published>2023-10-25T12:52:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-25T12:52:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/25/Texas-Sues-Biden-Administration</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/25/Texas-Sues-Biden-Administration/">&lt;p&gt;Texas Attorney General Ken Paxton has initiated a lawsuit against the Biden Administration, accusing them of illegally interfering with the state’s border security measures. Paxton’s move represents a significant escalation in the ongoing battle over border security, with Texas taking a firm stand to protect its borders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The legal action is targeted at the Department of Homeland Security and Customs and Border Protection officials, whom Paxton alleges have been cutting or damaging the concertina wire positioned along the border. This wire is a crucial part of Texas’s strategy to deter illegal immigration and secure the border. By damaging the wire, the federal government is accused of not only destroying state property but also jeopardizing Texas’s ability to control its own borders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Paxton’s lawsuit, filed in the U.S. District Court for the Western District of Texas, is a bid to put an end to what he describes as an “ongoing, unlawful practice” that undermines the state’s border security efforts. He asserts that the federal government’s actions leave gaps in Texas’s border barriers, compromising the state’s ability to effectively manage and secure its territory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The timing of the lawsuit is significant, coinciding with a period of heightened tension and debate over immigration policy and border security in the United States. Texas has been at the forefront of this debate, taking proactive measures to fortify its borders and calling for stronger federal action to address the crisis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Governor Greg Abbott has been vocal about the situation, posting video evidence last month of Border Patrol agents apparently cutting the wire to allow migrants to pass through. In response, Abbott ordered the wire to be replaced immediately, highlighting Texas’s determination to maintain control over its borders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The lawsuit comes amidst record migrant crossings and increasing scrutiny of the Biden administration’s handling of the border crisis. Paxton’s legal challenge represents not just a defense of Texas’s border security measures, but also a broader statement on the importance of state rights and the need for a coherent, effective approach to immigration policy and border security in the United States.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the legal proceedings unfold, the nation’s attention will be riveted on the Lone Star State and the federal government, eager to see how this critical battle over border security and state rights will be resolved. The outcome of this lawsuit has the potential to shape the future of immigration policy and border security in the United States, making it a case of national significance.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Texas Attorney General Ken Paxton has initiated a lawsuit against the Biden Administration, accusing them of illegally interfering with the state’s border security measures. Paxton’s move represents a significant escalation in the ongoing battle over border security, with Texas taking a firm stand to protect its borders. The legal action is targeted at the Department of Homeland Security and Customs and Border Protection officials, whom Paxton alleges have been cutting or damaging the concertina wire positioned along the border. This wire is a crucial part of Texas’s strategy to deter illegal immigration and secure the border. By damaging the wire, the federal government is accused of not only destroying state property but also jeopardizing Texas’s ability to control its own borders. Paxton’s lawsuit, filed in the U.S. District Court for the Western District of Texas, is a bid to put an end to what he describes as an “ongoing, unlawful practice” that undermines the state’s border security efforts. He asserts that the federal government’s actions leave gaps in Texas’s border barriers, compromising the state’s ability to effectively manage and secure its territory. The timing of the lawsuit is significant, coinciding with a period of heightened tension and debate over immigration policy and border security in the United States. Texas has been at the forefront of this debate, taking proactive measures to fortify its borders and calling for stronger federal action to address the crisis. Governor Greg Abbott has been vocal about the situation, posting video evidence last month of Border Patrol agents apparently cutting the wire to allow migrants to pass through. In response, Abbott ordered the wire to be replaced immediately, highlighting Texas’s determination to maintain control over its borders. The lawsuit comes amidst record migrant crossings and increasing scrutiny of the Biden administration’s handling of the border crisis. Paxton’s legal challenge represents not just a defense of Texas’s border security measures, but also a broader statement on the importance of state rights and the need for a coherent, effective approach to immigration policy and border security in the United States. As the legal proceedings unfold, the nation’s attention will be riveted on the Lone Star State and the federal government, eager to see how this critical battle over border security and state rights will be resolved. The outcome of this lawsuit has the potential to shape the future of immigration policy and border security in the United States, making it a case of national significance.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Breaking a Century-Old Tradition: Biden’s Unprecedented Move in New Hampshire</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/25/Biden-New-Hampshire-Tradition/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Breaking a Century-Old Tradition: Biden’s Unprecedented Move in New Hampshire" /><published>2023-10-25T11:38:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-25T11:38:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/25/Biden-New-Hampshire-Tradition</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/25/Biden-New-Hampshire-Tradition/">&lt;p&gt;President Joe Biden has decided to break with a longstanding tradition, opting not to file his name on New Hampshire’s Democratic presidential primary ballot for the upcoming 2024 elections. This move has sent ripples through the political landscape, as New Hampshire has proudly held the first presidential primary for both major political parties for a century.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Biden 2024 re-election campaign, led by campaign manager Julie Chávez Rodríguez, announced this decision on Tuesday, citing compliance with the Democratic National Committee’s (DNC) new rules as the primary reason. The DNC is looking to shake up the traditional presidential nominating calendar, and as a result, has pledged to penalize candidates who participate in unsanctioned primaries. New Hampshire, planning to hold its primary ahead of South Carolina, is set to be non-compliant with these new rules.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While this decision aligns with the DNC’s strategic shift to empower minority voters and redistribute the influence of early voting states, it also breaks a century-old tradition that has been a point of pride for New Hampshire. New Hampshire Secretary of State Dave Scanlan has made it clear that the state’s primary will proceed as planned, regardless of the DNC’s alterations to the nominating calendar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This move by President Biden could potentially open the door for other Democratic candidates to gain traction in New Hampshire. The state’s primary has been a crucial stepping stone for presidential hopefuls, and Biden’s absence from the ballot could lead to a protest vote or boost the visibility of other candidates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Among those considering a run is Rep. Dean Phillips of Minnesota, who is reportedly mulling a primary challenge against Biden. Phillips’ potential entry into the race could stir the political pot even further, introducing new dynamics to an already unconventional election cycle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite these changes, top Democrats in New Hampshire are gearing up for a write-in campaign for Biden, demonstrating their continued support for the President. However, this does not negate the fact that Biden’s decision has left a mark on the state’s political tradition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Biden’s strategy reflects a broader shift in the Democratic Party, emphasizing the importance of diversity and representation in the election process. The DNC’s new calendar positions South Carolina, a state with a significant African American voting bloc, as the first primary, followed by New Hampshire and Nevada.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Republicans have opted to keep their nominating calendar largely unchanged, the Democrats’ strategic shakeup aims to better align the party’s values with its voter base. As the 2024 election approaches, all eyes will be on how these changes impact the race for the Democratic nomination and whether Biden’s unconventional move pays off in the long run.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, President Biden’s decision to skip the New Hampshire primary marks a significant departure from tradition, reflecting the Democratic Party’s evolving strategy and the shifting dynamics of presidential elections.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">President Joe Biden has decided to break with a longstanding tradition, opting not to file his name on New Hampshire’s Democratic presidential primary ballot for the upcoming 2024 elections. This move has sent ripples through the political landscape, as New Hampshire has proudly held the first presidential primary for both major political parties for a century. The Biden 2024 re-election campaign, led by campaign manager Julie Chávez Rodríguez, announced this decision on Tuesday, citing compliance with the Democratic National Committee’s (DNC) new rules as the primary reason. The DNC is looking to shake up the traditional presidential nominating calendar, and as a result, has pledged to penalize candidates who participate in unsanctioned primaries. New Hampshire, planning to hold its primary ahead of South Carolina, is set to be non-compliant with these new rules. While this decision aligns with the DNC’s strategic shift to empower minority voters and redistribute the influence of early voting states, it also breaks a century-old tradition that has been a point of pride for New Hampshire. New Hampshire Secretary of State Dave Scanlan has made it clear that the state’s primary will proceed as planned, regardless of the DNC’s alterations to the nominating calendar. This move by President Biden could potentially open the door for other Democratic candidates to gain traction in New Hampshire. The state’s primary has been a crucial stepping stone for presidential hopefuls, and Biden’s absence from the ballot could lead to a protest vote or boost the visibility of other candidates. Among those considering a run is Rep. Dean Phillips of Minnesota, who is reportedly mulling a primary challenge against Biden. Phillips’ potential entry into the race could stir the political pot even further, introducing new dynamics to an already unconventional election cycle. Despite these changes, top Democrats in New Hampshire are gearing up for a write-in campaign for Biden, demonstrating their continued support for the President. However, this does not negate the fact that Biden’s decision has left a mark on the state’s political tradition. Biden’s strategy reflects a broader shift in the Democratic Party, emphasizing the importance of diversity and representation in the election process. The DNC’s new calendar positions South Carolina, a state with a significant African American voting bloc, as the first primary, followed by New Hampshire and Nevada. While Republicans have opted to keep their nominating calendar largely unchanged, the Democrats’ strategic shakeup aims to better align the party’s values with its voter base. As the 2024 election approaches, all eyes will be on how these changes impact the race for the Democratic nomination and whether Biden’s unconventional move pays off in the long run. In conclusion, President Biden’s decision to skip the New Hampshire primary marks a significant departure from tradition, reflecting the Democratic Party’s evolving strategy and the shifting dynamics of presidential elections.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Navigating Troubled Waters: Biden’s Stance on Inflation, Immigration, and Jobs</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/25/Biden-Inflation-Jobs/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Navigating Troubled Waters: Biden’s Stance on Inflation, Immigration, and Jobs" /><published>2023-10-25T10:35:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-25T10:35:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/25/Biden-Inflation-Jobs</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/25/Biden-Inflation-Jobs/">&lt;p&gt;Recent polls conducted by Harvard/Harris show that a majority of voters continue to express discontent with President Joe Biden’s handling of crucial issues such as inflation, immigration, and the job market. Despite this, there have been noted improvements in public perception across these areas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The online survey, encompassing the opinions of 2,116 registered voters conducted between October 18-19, places inflation as the primary concern at 32%, closely followed by immigration at 27%, and the economy and job market at 24%. The results of this poll come with a margin of error of +/- 2 percentage points.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it comes to handling inflation, only 40% of respondents either strongly or somewhat approve of Biden’s approach, albeit a 5-percentage point increase from September. Similarly, his handling of the economy sees a 3-percentage point bump to 41% approval. On stimulating job growth, Biden’s performance was rated positively by 49% of the participants, marking a 3-point increase from the previous month.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, immigration continues to be a challenging issue for Biden, with only 39% of respondents expressing approval of his performance, though this too has seen a 3-point increase since September. Biden’s overall job approval has climbed to 44%, a 2-point increase from the previous month, while those disapproving of his performance have decreased by 1 point, standing at 53%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking ahead to the 2024 presidential election, a potential matchup between Biden and former President Donald Trump reveals Biden trailing behind at 41% to Trump’s 46%. This has slightly changed from September, where Trump led 44%-40%. Considering voters who lean towards a particular party, Trump’s lead extends to 52%-48%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the Biden administration continues to navigate these challenging issues, the slight improvements in public opinion reflect a complex political landscape. The focus on inflation, immigration, and jobs is bound to remain significant, potentially shaping voter sentiment and decisions in the run-up to the 2024 elections.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Recent polls conducted by Harvard/Harris show that a majority of voters continue to express discontent with President Joe Biden’s handling of crucial issues such as inflation, immigration, and the job market. Despite this, there have been noted improvements in public perception across these areas. The online survey, encompassing the opinions of 2,116 registered voters conducted between October 18-19, places inflation as the primary concern at 32%, closely followed by immigration at 27%, and the economy and job market at 24%. The results of this poll come with a margin of error of +/- 2 percentage points. When it comes to handling inflation, only 40% of respondents either strongly or somewhat approve of Biden’s approach, albeit a 5-percentage point increase from September. Similarly, his handling of the economy sees a 3-percentage point bump to 41% approval. On stimulating job growth, Biden’s performance was rated positively by 49% of the participants, marking a 3-point increase from the previous month. On the other hand, immigration continues to be a challenging issue for Biden, with only 39% of respondents expressing approval of his performance, though this too has seen a 3-point increase since September. Biden’s overall job approval has climbed to 44%, a 2-point increase from the previous month, while those disapproving of his performance have decreased by 1 point, standing at 53%. Looking ahead to the 2024 presidential election, a potential matchup between Biden and former President Donald Trump reveals Biden trailing behind at 41% to Trump’s 46%. This has slightly changed from September, where Trump led 44%-40%. Considering voters who lean towards a particular party, Trump’s lead extends to 52%-48%. As the Biden administration continues to navigate these challenging issues, the slight improvements in public opinion reflect a complex political landscape. The focus on inflation, immigration, and jobs is bound to remain significant, potentially shaping voter sentiment and decisions in the run-up to the 2024 elections.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Biden’s Proposed Menthol Cigarette Ban: A Potential Stumbling Block for 2024</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/25/Menthol-Cigarette-Ban/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Biden’s Proposed Menthol Cigarette Ban: A Potential Stumbling Block for 2024" /><published>2023-10-25T09:23:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-25T09:23:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/25/Menthol-Cigarette-Ban</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/25/Menthol-Cigarette-Ban/">&lt;p&gt;The Biden administration’s call to ban menthol cigarettes and flavored cigars is raising eyebrows and stirring controversy, potentially becoming a significant issue in the upcoming 2024 elections. The Food and Drug Administration (FDA) originally proposed these rules in April 2022, aiming to curb smoking among children and assist adults in quitting the habit. Despite the good intentions, the administration is now facing backlash, with political ad-makers ready to capitalize on the contentious issue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The FDA’s objective was clear: prevent the next generation from picking up smoking and encourage current smokers to quit. However, this proposed ban has sparked debates and divided opinions nationwide, especially among Black leaders. Some argue that this could lead to an increase in over-policing within the community, while others highlight the potential border issues with Mexican drug cartels looking to flood the U.S. market with prohibited products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Brian Colas, a seasoned Republican operative, didn’t hold back in his criticism, stating, “Criminalizing cigarettes while promoting heroin injection sites is bad policy and bad politics.” He foreshadows a wave of targeted campaign ads aimed at shop owners, law enforcement, and those directly impacted by the ban. It’s a sentiment echoed by several politicians, including Arkansas Sen. Tom Cotton, who pointed out the glaring contradictions in the administration’s policies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Senator Kyrsten Sinema, representing Arizona as an Independent, has also voiced her concerns, advocating for individual choice and urging for such decisions to be made at the state level. “My general perspective would be that as adults, people can make their own choices,” Sinema stated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the opposition, some groups praise the proposed rules, emphasizing the potential lives saved through these measures. The Campaign for Tobacco-Free Kids, backed by former New York City Mayor Michael Bloomberg, stands firmly in support, highlighting the positive impact on public health and the advancement of health equity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, Rev. Al Sharpton raises an important point about unintended consequences, especially on the Black community. The long-term effects on public safety, the illicit market, and community relations with law enforcement remain uncertain, sparking a nationwide debate that is sure to play a significant role in the 2024 elections.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The battle lines are drawn, and as the FDA nears the end of the rule-making process, the nation waits to see how this issue will unfold. Will the menthol cigarette ban become a liability for Biden in 2024, or will it pass as a well-intentioned public health measure? Only time will tell, but one thing is certain: the political arena is set for a heated debate on personal freedom, public health, and the role of government in our lives.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">The Biden administration’s call to ban menthol cigarettes and flavored cigars is raising eyebrows and stirring controversy, potentially becoming a significant issue in the upcoming 2024 elections. The Food and Drug Administration (FDA) originally proposed these rules in April 2022, aiming to curb smoking among children and assist adults in quitting the habit. Despite the good intentions, the administration is now facing backlash, with political ad-makers ready to capitalize on the contentious issue. The FDA’s objective was clear: prevent the next generation from picking up smoking and encourage current smokers to quit. However, this proposed ban has sparked debates and divided opinions nationwide, especially among Black leaders. Some argue that this could lead to an increase in over-policing within the community, while others highlight the potential border issues with Mexican drug cartels looking to flood the U.S. market with prohibited products. Brian Colas, a seasoned Republican operative, didn’t hold back in his criticism, stating, “Criminalizing cigarettes while promoting heroin injection sites is bad policy and bad politics.” He foreshadows a wave of targeted campaign ads aimed at shop owners, law enforcement, and those directly impacted by the ban. It’s a sentiment echoed by several politicians, including Arkansas Sen. Tom Cotton, who pointed out the glaring contradictions in the administration’s policies. Senator Kyrsten Sinema, representing Arizona as an Independent, has also voiced her concerns, advocating for individual choice and urging for such decisions to be made at the state level. “My general perspective would be that as adults, people can make their own choices,” Sinema stated. Despite the opposition, some groups praise the proposed rules, emphasizing the potential lives saved through these measures. The Campaign for Tobacco-Free Kids, backed by former New York City Mayor Michael Bloomberg, stands firmly in support, highlighting the positive impact on public health and the advancement of health equity. However, Rev. Al Sharpton raises an important point about unintended consequences, especially on the Black community. The long-term effects on public safety, the illicit market, and community relations with law enforcement remain uncertain, sparking a nationwide debate that is sure to play a significant role in the 2024 elections. The battle lines are drawn, and as the FDA nears the end of the rule-making process, the nation waits to see how this issue will unfold. Will the menthol cigarette ban become a liability for Biden in 2024, or will it pass as a well-intentioned public health measure? Only time will tell, but one thing is certain: the political arena is set for a heated debate on personal freedom, public health, and the role of government in our lives.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Shocking Replacement: Los Angeles Hotels Accused of Trading Union Workers for Border Crossers</title><link href="/news/2023/10/25/Los-Angeles-Hotels-Union-Workers/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Shocking Replacement: Los Angeles Hotels Accused of Trading Union Workers for Border Crossers" /><published>2023-10-25T08:04:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-25T08:04:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/25/Los-Angeles-Hotels-Union-Workers</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/25/Los-Angeles-Hotels-Union-Workers/">&lt;p&gt;Hotels situated in the sanctuary confines of Los Angeles County, California, stand accused of substituting their unionized workforce — presently on strike — with newly arrived border crossers and undocumented immigrants. This severe allegation has caught the attention of legal authorities, prompting the District Attorney’s Office to initiate an official investigation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The hospitality industry of Los Angeles finds itself in turmoil as hotel workers, represented by Unite Here Local 11, allege their employers of engaging in the unethical practice of replacing them with fresh border arrivals and illegal aliens. These replacements are reportedly sourced mainly from Venezuela and Colombia, having entered the United States via the southern border.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The crux of the controversy lies with the hotels allegedly targeting individuals residing in Skid Row, a notorious area of Los Angeles. Hotels are accused of exploiting these newly arrived individuals, offering them low-wage employment opportunities as an alternative to the striking unionized workers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;News reports indicate that since the commencement of intermittent strikes in early July, involving more than 15,000 workers across approximately 60 Southern California hotels, employers have resorted to filling the labor void with a mix of managers, temporary workers, and those recruited via staffing agencies, digital platforms like Instawork, and other means. Specific hotels named in these allegations include the Four Points by Sheraton, Holiday Inn LAX, and Le Meridien Delfina Santa Monica.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hannah Peterson, an organizer with Unite Here Local 11, highlighted that some of the individuals hired at the Le Meridien Delfina were part of the migrant groups transported to L.A. on buses by Texas Gov. Greg Abbott. This act, deemed a political stunt, was aimed at spotlighting the challenges sanctuary cities face and criticizing immigration policies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the Los Angeles County District Attorney’s Office now actively investigating these serious claims, those who have information or have been affected are urged to come forward. District Attorney George Gascon expressed his commitment to addressing these allegations, stating, “We take these egregious allegations with the utmost seriousness. The mistreatment of vulnerable workers and their exploitation will not be tolerated.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the nation’s largest sanctuary state, California currently hosts nearly five million illegal aliens and their U.S.-born children. This incident serves as a stark reminder of the complexities and challenges intertwined with immigration, labor rights, and ethical employment practices, bringing them to the forefront of public and legal discourse.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Hotels situated in the sanctuary confines of Los Angeles County, California, stand accused of substituting their unionized workforce — presently on strike — with newly arrived border crossers and undocumented immigrants. This severe allegation has caught the attention of legal authorities, prompting the District Attorney’s Office to initiate an official investigation. The hospitality industry of Los Angeles finds itself in turmoil as hotel workers, represented by Unite Here Local 11, allege their employers of engaging in the unethical practice of replacing them with fresh border arrivals and illegal aliens. These replacements are reportedly sourced mainly from Venezuela and Colombia, having entered the United States via the southern border. The crux of the controversy lies with the hotels allegedly targeting individuals residing in Skid Row, a notorious area of Los Angeles. Hotels are accused of exploiting these newly arrived individuals, offering them low-wage employment opportunities as an alternative to the striking unionized workers. News reports indicate that since the commencement of intermittent strikes in early July, involving more than 15,000 workers across approximately 60 Southern California hotels, employers have resorted to filling the labor void with a mix of managers, temporary workers, and those recruited via staffing agencies, digital platforms like Instawork, and other means. Specific hotels named in these allegations include the Four Points by Sheraton, Holiday Inn LAX, and Le Meridien Delfina Santa Monica. Hannah Peterson, an organizer with Unite Here Local 11, highlighted that some of the individuals hired at the Le Meridien Delfina were part of the migrant groups transported to L.A. on buses by Texas Gov. Greg Abbott. This act, deemed a political stunt, was aimed at spotlighting the challenges sanctuary cities face and criticizing immigration policies. With the Los Angeles County District Attorney’s Office now actively investigating these serious claims, those who have information or have been affected are urged to come forward. District Attorney George Gascon expressed his commitment to addressing these allegations, stating, “We take these egregious allegations with the utmost seriousness. The mistreatment of vulnerable workers and their exploitation will not be tolerated.” As the nation’s largest sanctuary state, California currently hosts nearly five million illegal aliens and their U.S.-born children. This incident serves as a stark reminder of the complexities and challenges intertwined with immigration, labor rights, and ethical employment practices, bringing them to the forefront of public and legal discourse.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Showbiz Shakeup: Next ‘Mission: Impossible’ Film Delayed Amid Ongoing Actors Strike</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/25/Mission-Impossible-Delayed-Actors-Strike/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Showbiz Shakeup: Next ‘Mission: Impossible’ Film Delayed Amid Ongoing Actors Strike" /><published>2023-10-25T07:01:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-25T07:01:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/25/Mission-Impossible-Delayed-Actors-Strike</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/25/Mission-Impossible-Delayed-Actors-Strike/">&lt;p&gt;Hollywood is facing a major shakeup as the highly anticipated eighth installment of the ‘Mission: Impossible’ franchise gets hit with a year-long delay, all due to the ongoing actors strike that has now surpassed a staggering three months of work stoppage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Paramount Pictures made the announcement this Monday, shifting the release date of the next ‘Mission: Impossible’ film from its original slot on June 28 to a new date on May 23, 2025. The halt in production can be traced back to July, when lead actor Tom Cruise and the rest of the crew took a break for an international promotion tour for ‘Mission: Impossible — Dead Reckoning Part One’.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The sequel, previously titled ‘Mission: Impossible — Dead Reckoning Part Two’, is now simply listed as ‘Mission: Impossible’. Despite the prior installment’s success, grossing a substantial $567.5 million worldwide, it fell short of its predecessor, ‘Fallout’ ($791.7 million globally), and Cruise’s other major hit, ‘Top Gun: Maverick’ ($1.5 billion). The 163-minute-long action thriller received high praise, yet it quickly found itself overshadowed by blockbuster giants ‘Barbie’ and ‘Oppenheimer’.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This actor strike has not just impacted the ‘Mission: Impossible’ franchise; it is sending ripples throughout Hollywood, upsetting release plans for other major films. From this fall’s ‘Dune: Part Two’ being postponed to March, to delays and indefinite postponements of various Marvel and ‘Venom’ films, and even ‘Spider-Man: Beyond the Spider-Verse’, the industry is in a state of flux.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In light of these delays, Paramount Pictures has also adjusted the release schedule for other titles in their lineup. ‘A Quiet Place: Day One’, a prequel to the popular post-apocalyptic horror series and featuring Lupita Nyong’o, has had its release pushed from March to June 28, filling the slot originally occupied by ‘Mission: Impossible’.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Negotiations between the Screen Actors Guild-American Federation of Television and Radio Artists and the studios are set to resume this Tuesday, leaving Hollywood and its eager audience in anticipation of what resolution—or further delays—may come.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Hollywood is facing a major shakeup as the highly anticipated eighth installment of the ‘Mission: Impossible’ franchise gets hit with a year-long delay, all due to the ongoing actors strike that has now surpassed a staggering three months of work stoppage. Paramount Pictures made the announcement this Monday, shifting the release date of the next ‘Mission: Impossible’ film from its original slot on June 28 to a new date on May 23, 2025. The halt in production can be traced back to July, when lead actor Tom Cruise and the rest of the crew took a break for an international promotion tour for ‘Mission: Impossible — Dead Reckoning Part One’. The sequel, previously titled ‘Mission: Impossible — Dead Reckoning Part Two’, is now simply listed as ‘Mission: Impossible’. Despite the prior installment’s success, grossing a substantial $567.5 million worldwide, it fell short of its predecessor, ‘Fallout’ ($791.7 million globally), and Cruise’s other major hit, ‘Top Gun: Maverick’ ($1.5 billion). The 163-minute-long action thriller received high praise, yet it quickly found itself overshadowed by blockbuster giants ‘Barbie’ and ‘Oppenheimer’. This actor strike has not just impacted the ‘Mission: Impossible’ franchise; it is sending ripples throughout Hollywood, upsetting release plans for other major films. From this fall’s ‘Dune: Part Two’ being postponed to March, to delays and indefinite postponements of various Marvel and ‘Venom’ films, and even ‘Spider-Man: Beyond the Spider-Verse’, the industry is in a state of flux. In light of these delays, Paramount Pictures has also adjusted the release schedule for other titles in their lineup. ‘A Quiet Place: Day One’, a prequel to the popular post-apocalyptic horror series and featuring Lupita Nyong’o, has had its release pushed from March to June 28, filling the slot originally occupied by ‘Mission: Impossible’. Negotiations between the Screen Actors Guild-American Federation of Television and Radio Artists and the studios are set to resume this Tuesday, leaving Hollywood and its eager audience in anticipation of what resolution—or further delays—may come.</summary></entry></feed>