<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-09-12T12:20:21-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/09/12/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-09-12T12:20:21-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-12T12:20:21-04:00</updated><id>/2023/09/12/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/12/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Iconic ‘Halloween’ Movie House Hits the Market</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/12/Halloween-House-Sale/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Iconic ‘Halloween’ Movie House Hits the Market" /><published>2023-09-12T12:02:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-12T12:02:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/12/Halloween-House-Sale</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/12/Halloween-House-Sale/">&lt;p&gt;For fans of the legendary horror film “Halloween,” a unique opportunity has arisen. The infamous Pasadena home that served as the backdrop for Laurie Strode’s (played by Jamie Lee Curtis) nightmarish encounters with the relentless Michael Meyers is now listed for sale.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This iconic property, which provided the setting for the chilling events of Haddonfield, Illinois, in the 1978 movie, has remained with one family for three generations. Now, according to the New York Daily News, it awaits a new owner with a listed price of $1.799 million.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The realtor’s description emphasizes the home’s cinematic significance, drawing attention to its familiar stoop: “If you watch the film, you’ll recognize the infamous stoop that Jamie Lee Curtis sat on, holding a pumpkin.” But beyond its filmic connections, the house has undergone transformations over the years. Originally portrayed as a single-family residence, it has since been subdivided into three separate units.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The property also boasts a historic fruit-bearing avocado tree, a remnant from the 1940s, planted by the sellers’ grandfather. This detail provides a touch of nostalgia to the otherwise eerie history of the home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jamie Lee Curtis, now 64, has an intimate bond with the Halloween series, crediting it with many positive turns in her life. Reflecting on her connection to Laurie, she told People magazine, “everything good in my life can be traced back to Laurie.” Curtis even recalls spotting her now-husband of 37 years, Christopher Guest, in a 1984 Rolling Stone article while she was with Debra Hill, the writer of the original Halloween. “Life is scary. But Laurie taught me that life can also be beautiful, filled with love and art and life!” Curtis expressed, cherishing her role’s impact on her personal and professional journey.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The so-called “murder house” wasn’t only featured in the original film. It made a return in the 2021 sequel, “Halloween Kills,” where a harrowing scene involving firefighters unfolds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Realtor Heidi Babcock captures the allure of this unique listing, stating, “This exceptional property is a wonderful place to live, work, and play in one of the most desirable communities in greater LA.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For horror aficionados or fans of cinematic history, this property presents a once-in-a-lifetime chance. Who will be the next to claim this piece of Hollywood horror legacy?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">For fans of the legendary horror film “Halloween,” a unique opportunity has arisen. The infamous Pasadena home that served as the backdrop for Laurie Strode’s (played by Jamie Lee Curtis) nightmarish encounters with the relentless Michael Meyers is now listed for sale. This iconic property, which provided the setting for the chilling events of Haddonfield, Illinois, in the 1978 movie, has remained with one family for three generations. Now, according to the New York Daily News, it awaits a new owner with a listed price of $1.799 million. The realtor’s description emphasizes the home’s cinematic significance, drawing attention to its familiar stoop: “If you watch the film, you’ll recognize the infamous stoop that Jamie Lee Curtis sat on, holding a pumpkin.” But beyond its filmic connections, the house has undergone transformations over the years. Originally portrayed as a single-family residence, it has since been subdivided into three separate units. The property also boasts a historic fruit-bearing avocado tree, a remnant from the 1940s, planted by the sellers’ grandfather. This detail provides a touch of nostalgia to the otherwise eerie history of the home. Jamie Lee Curtis, now 64, has an intimate bond with the Halloween series, crediting it with many positive turns in her life. Reflecting on her connection to Laurie, she told People magazine, “everything good in my life can be traced back to Laurie.” Curtis even recalls spotting her now-husband of 37 years, Christopher Guest, in a 1984 Rolling Stone article while she was with Debra Hill, the writer of the original Halloween. “Life is scary. But Laurie taught me that life can also be beautiful, filled with love and art and life!” Curtis expressed, cherishing her role’s impact on her personal and professional journey. The so-called “murder house” wasn’t only featured in the original film. It made a return in the 2021 sequel, “Halloween Kills,” where a harrowing scene involving firefighters unfolds. Realtor Heidi Babcock captures the allure of this unique listing, stating, “This exceptional property is a wonderful place to live, work, and play in one of the most desirable communities in greater LA.” For horror aficionados or fans of cinematic history, this property presents a once-in-a-lifetime chance. Who will be the next to claim this piece of Hollywood horror legacy?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Waltz Warns - The Danger of Iran Prisoner Swaps</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/12/Hostage-Incentive-Iran/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Waltz Warns - The Danger of Iran Prisoner Swaps" /><published>2023-09-12T11:06:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-12T11:06:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/12/Hostage-Incentive-Iran</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/12/Hostage-Incentive-Iran/">&lt;p&gt;In a candid conversation with “Rob Schmitt Tonight,” Rep. Michael Waltz, R-Fla., voiced his concerns regarding the United States’ recent decision to partake in prisoner swaps with Iran. Highlighting the potential repercussions of such moves, Waltz emphasized that this could unintentionally encourage more hostage-taking incidents by hostile entities in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Waltz, expressing his sympathy and heartbreak for the affected families, recounted an earlier incident in 2015 involving the Iran deal. “One of these hostages was left behind back in 2015 with the original Iran deal. John Kerry, [Then-Secretary of State], was promised the hostage’s release. However, even after the hostage remained in captivity, Kerry went ahead and signed the deal.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Drawing parallels with the current scenario, Waltz expressed his concerns: “The problem with this deal is that future Americans are at risk of being taken hostage all over again.” Waltz’s argument is based on a simple yet concerning principle: When nations like the US give in to the demands of hostage-takers, it provides a strong incentive for other hostile actors, whether they are nations like Iran or Russia, or even terrorist groups, to follow suit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He further added, “There’s no downside for these hostage-takers. In most scenarios, they find themselves in advantageous positions, either financially or through swaps.” Drawing attention to a recent swap involving the world’s largest arms dealer for Brittney Griner, Waltz underlined the troubling pattern that seems to be emerging.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adding another layer to his criticism, Waltz voiced his concerns regarding the lack of transparency from the current administration. “This is just a horrific deal. Despite being a member of both the Intelligence Committee and the Foreign Affairs Committee, we are still in the dark about who these Iranians are that Biden’s administration is releasing.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Decisions involving prisoner swaps are always delicate, with multiple facets to consider. Yet, Waltz’s caution serves as a reminder that, while the immediate resolution of a crisis is paramount, it’s equally essential to consider the long-term implications of such decisions. The well-being and safety of future American citizens overseas might very well depend on the choices made today.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a candid conversation with “Rob Schmitt Tonight,” Rep. Michael Waltz, R-Fla., voiced his concerns regarding the United States’ recent decision to partake in prisoner swaps with Iran. Highlighting the potential repercussions of such moves, Waltz emphasized that this could unintentionally encourage more hostage-taking incidents by hostile entities in the future. Waltz, expressing his sympathy and heartbreak for the affected families, recounted an earlier incident in 2015 involving the Iran deal. “One of these hostages was left behind back in 2015 with the original Iran deal. John Kerry, [Then-Secretary of State], was promised the hostage’s release. However, even after the hostage remained in captivity, Kerry went ahead and signed the deal.” Drawing parallels with the current scenario, Waltz expressed his concerns: “The problem with this deal is that future Americans are at risk of being taken hostage all over again.” Waltz’s argument is based on a simple yet concerning principle: When nations like the US give in to the demands of hostage-takers, it provides a strong incentive for other hostile actors, whether they are nations like Iran or Russia, or even terrorist groups, to follow suit. He further added, “There’s no downside for these hostage-takers. In most scenarios, they find themselves in advantageous positions, either financially or through swaps.” Drawing attention to a recent swap involving the world’s largest arms dealer for Brittney Griner, Waltz underlined the troubling pattern that seems to be emerging. Adding another layer to his criticism, Waltz voiced his concerns regarding the lack of transparency from the current administration. “This is just a horrific deal. Despite being a member of both the Intelligence Committee and the Foreign Affairs Committee, we are still in the dark about who these Iranians are that Biden’s administration is releasing.” Decisions involving prisoner swaps are always delicate, with multiple facets to consider. Yet, Waltz’s caution serves as a reminder that, while the immediate resolution of a crisis is paramount, it’s equally essential to consider the long-term implications of such decisions. The well-being and safety of future American citizens overseas might very well depend on the choices made today.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Rising Concerns - 1 in 5 Workers Fear Tech Will Make Their Jobs Extinct</title><link href="/news/2023/09/12/Technology-Job-Obsolescence/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rising Concerns - 1 in 5 Workers Fear Tech Will Make Their Jobs Extinct" /><published>2023-09-12T10:01:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-12T10:01:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/12/Technology-Job-Obsolescence</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/12/Technology-Job-Obsolescence/">&lt;p&gt;A growing number of Americans are apprehensive about the role technology might play in phasing out their employment. A new Gallup poll suggests that over one in five American workers now harbor concerns about their job’s future due to rapid technological advancements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rising Concern Over Time&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Published this Monday, the poll reveals that 22% of Americans worry that technology might render their jobs redundant. These concerns have seen a marked increase over the years since Gallup first started monitoring this sentiment in August 2017. At that time, a mere 13% expressed such fears. The figure showed a modest rise to 15% in 2019 and 17% in 2020, only to dip back to 15% in 2021. An interesting observation tied to this is the increasing prevalence and attention on artificial intelligence since the 2021 poll.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education and Concerns&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gallup’s data shows a significant shift in concerns among the college-educated workforce, with their fears spiking from 8% to 20%. On the other hand, workers without a college degree have maintained a nearly constant worry level at 24%. This indicates that the disparity in technological replacement concerns between the college-educated and non-college-educated workers has narrowed, with both groups now exhibiting parallel anxiety levels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Demographic Differences in Concern&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The poll further underscores the generational difference in apprehension, indicating that younger workers are more concerned about technology making their jobs obsolete than their older counterparts. Additionally, those earning less than $100,000 annually express more anxiety compared to those with higher incomes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other Workplace Fears&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the dread of technology-induced job redundancy, the Gallup poll highlighted other significant worries among American workers. The leading concern is a potential reduction in wages or benefits. While 31% of the respondents fear a cut in their benefits, 24% are anxious about a potential wage decrease. Concurrently, 20% of those polled are concerned about potential layoffs, with 19% fearing a reduction in working hours. Interestingly, only 7% expressed worry over their jobs being outsourced overseas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Survey Details&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For this research, Gallup interviewed 491 part-time or full-time adult workers in the U.S. between August 1 and August 23. The findings have a margin of error of ±5 percentage points.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">A growing number of Americans are apprehensive about the role technology might play in phasing out their employment. A new Gallup poll suggests that over one in five American workers now harbor concerns about their job’s future due to rapid technological advancements. Rising Concern Over Time Published this Monday, the poll reveals that 22% of Americans worry that technology might render their jobs redundant. These concerns have seen a marked increase over the years since Gallup first started monitoring this sentiment in August 2017. At that time, a mere 13% expressed such fears. The figure showed a modest rise to 15% in 2019 and 17% in 2020, only to dip back to 15% in 2021. An interesting observation tied to this is the increasing prevalence and attention on artificial intelligence since the 2021 poll. Education and Concerns Gallup’s data shows a significant shift in concerns among the college-educated workforce, with their fears spiking from 8% to 20%. On the other hand, workers without a college degree have maintained a nearly constant worry level at 24%. This indicates that the disparity in technological replacement concerns between the college-educated and non-college-educated workers has narrowed, with both groups now exhibiting parallel anxiety levels. Demographic Differences in Concern The poll further underscores the generational difference in apprehension, indicating that younger workers are more concerned about technology making their jobs obsolete than their older counterparts. Additionally, those earning less than $100,000 annually express more anxiety compared to those with higher incomes. Other Workplace Fears Beyond the dread of technology-induced job redundancy, the Gallup poll highlighted other significant worries among American workers. The leading concern is a potential reduction in wages or benefits. While 31% of the respondents fear a cut in their benefits, 24% are anxious about a potential wage decrease. Concurrently, 20% of those polled are concerned about potential layoffs, with 19% fearing a reduction in working hours. Interestingly, only 7% expressed worry over their jobs being outsourced overseas. Survey Details For this research, Gallup interviewed 491 part-time or full-time adult workers in the U.S. between August 1 and August 23. The findings have a margin of error of ±5 percentage points.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Aaron Rodgers’ New York Jets Debut Cut Short by Ankle Injury</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/12/Rodgers-Injury-Debut/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Aaron Rodgers’ New York Jets Debut Cut Short by Ankle Injury" /><published>2023-09-12T09:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-12T09:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/12/Rodgers-Injury-Debut</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/12/Rodgers-Injury-Debut/">&lt;p&gt;Monday night’s highly awaited game between the New York Jets and the Buffalo Bills saw an unexpected turn as Aaron Rodgers, the newly acquired Jets quarterback, had to exit early. After being on the field for only a few minutes into his debut with the Jets, Rodgers suffered an ankle injury, putting a damper on the night for Jets fans.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The injury occurred when Buffalo Bills linebacker Leonard Floyd managed to sack Rodgers. Although Rodgers initially attempted to brush off the setback, he soon needed assistance to leave the field. This was a sight no sports fan ever wishes to see – a prominent player being escorted off the field, especially during a debut.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Subsequent broadcasts from ESPN showed Rodgers, with evident difficulty, making his way onto a cart that transported him towards the stadium’s tunnel. He was then spotted limping towards the locker room, and later, with a protective boot on his injured ankle. Before this unfortunate turn of events, Rodgers had yet to complete a pass, with a record of 0-for-1.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With Rodgers out of the picture, the Jets had to rely on Zach Wilson, their former starting quarterback. Wilson, who started for the Jets during his first two seasons, was supposed to be the backup to Rodgers after losing his primary spot towards the end of 2022.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For Rodgers, this game was meant to be an exhilarating first with the Jets, having recently showcased his prowess in a preseason match against the New York Giants where he threw an impressive touchdown pass to Garrett Wilson. Pre-game, he had spoken about the “butterflies” he felt during that preseason match.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a light-hearted moment before the game, when asked about his feelings on stepping onto the field for his Jets’ debut, Rodgers had humorously remarked that he’d probably be “sobbing.” He had further added that he looked forward to the experience and the energy of the crowd.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately for Rodgers and the Jets, the night didn’t go as planned. The extent of Rodgers’ injury remains to be seen, and fans across the nation are hoping for a swift recovery for the renowned quarterback.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Monday night’s highly awaited game between the New York Jets and the Buffalo Bills saw an unexpected turn as Aaron Rodgers, the newly acquired Jets quarterback, had to exit early. After being on the field for only a few minutes into his debut with the Jets, Rodgers suffered an ankle injury, putting a damper on the night for Jets fans. The injury occurred when Buffalo Bills linebacker Leonard Floyd managed to sack Rodgers. Although Rodgers initially attempted to brush off the setback, he soon needed assistance to leave the field. This was a sight no sports fan ever wishes to see – a prominent player being escorted off the field, especially during a debut. Subsequent broadcasts from ESPN showed Rodgers, with evident difficulty, making his way onto a cart that transported him towards the stadium’s tunnel. He was then spotted limping towards the locker room, and later, with a protective boot on his injured ankle. Before this unfortunate turn of events, Rodgers had yet to complete a pass, with a record of 0-for-1. With Rodgers out of the picture, the Jets had to rely on Zach Wilson, their former starting quarterback. Wilson, who started for the Jets during his first two seasons, was supposed to be the backup to Rodgers after losing his primary spot towards the end of 2022. For Rodgers, this game was meant to be an exhilarating first with the Jets, having recently showcased his prowess in a preseason match against the New York Giants where he threw an impressive touchdown pass to Garrett Wilson. Pre-game, he had spoken about the “butterflies” he felt during that preseason match. In a light-hearted moment before the game, when asked about his feelings on stepping onto the field for his Jets’ debut, Rodgers had humorously remarked that he’d probably be “sobbing.” He had further added that he looked forward to the experience and the energy of the crowd. Unfortunately for Rodgers and the Jets, the night didn’t go as planned. The extent of Rodgers’ injury remains to be seen, and fans across the nation are hoping for a swift recovery for the renowned quarterback.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Biden’s Absence - A Misstep in 9/11 Commemoration?</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/12/Biden-911-Decision/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Biden’s Absence - A Misstep in 9/11 Commemoration?" /><published>2023-09-12T08:02:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-12T08:02:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/12/Biden-911-Decision</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/12/Biden-911-Decision/">&lt;p&gt;In a concerning development that seems to further highlight the tone-deaf approach of the Biden administration, President Joe Biden made the decision to abstain from attending this year’s ceremonies dedicated to the harrowing memories of the Sept. 11, 2001, terrorist attacks. This event, deeply etched in the psyche of Americans, deserved the President’s presence and acknowledgement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Senator Ted Cruz, in his candid discussion on “Rob Schmitt Tonight,” expressed no surprise at the President’s decision. Cruz emphatically stated that this wasn’t the first time the administration’s actions have come across as out of touch with the sentiments of the American public, especially those directly affected by the attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It’s a mistake. I think the president has an obligation to tell the American people what it was about, to bring them together,” Cruz rightly pointed out. This view gains even more significance when one considers the recent news surrounding plea deals involving Khalid Sheikh Mohammed, believed to be a primary architect of the 9/11 attacks. The Pentagon, under the Biden administration, was seemingly inclined towards these plea deals, ostensibly to circumvent the death penalty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The unsettling nature of these potential plea deals sparked widespread condemnation. Cruz, along with Representative Nicole Malliotakis from New York, sent a clarion call against such decisions. Their voices, echoing the anguish and concerns of millions of Americans, seem to have resonated, with the administration consequently backing down from the proposed plan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cruz didn’t hold back in highlighting a pattern of concerning decisions: “But when it comes to this administration and foreign policy, they’ve put politics ahead of everything. This administration doesn’t want to talk about 9/11. They want to put 9/11 behind them.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Making matters worse is the perceived connection between these questionable decisions and the 2021 Afghanistan withdrawal. The move was hurriedly executed, seemingly to align with the 9/11 anniversary, notwithstanding serious apprehensions from officials.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s clear that the Biden administration needs to reevaluate its approach, ensuring that the emotions and sentiments of the American populace aren’t treated as mere afterthoughts.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a concerning development that seems to further highlight the tone-deaf approach of the Biden administration, President Joe Biden made the decision to abstain from attending this year’s ceremonies dedicated to the harrowing memories of the Sept. 11, 2001, terrorist attacks. This event, deeply etched in the psyche of Americans, deserved the President’s presence and acknowledgement. Senator Ted Cruz, in his candid discussion on “Rob Schmitt Tonight,” expressed no surprise at the President’s decision. Cruz emphatically stated that this wasn’t the first time the administration’s actions have come across as out of touch with the sentiments of the American public, especially those directly affected by the attacks. “It’s a mistake. I think the president has an obligation to tell the American people what it was about, to bring them together,” Cruz rightly pointed out. This view gains even more significance when one considers the recent news surrounding plea deals involving Khalid Sheikh Mohammed, believed to be a primary architect of the 9/11 attacks. The Pentagon, under the Biden administration, was seemingly inclined towards these plea deals, ostensibly to circumvent the death penalty. The unsettling nature of these potential plea deals sparked widespread condemnation. Cruz, along with Representative Nicole Malliotakis from New York, sent a clarion call against such decisions. Their voices, echoing the anguish and concerns of millions of Americans, seem to have resonated, with the administration consequently backing down from the proposed plan. Cruz didn’t hold back in highlighting a pattern of concerning decisions: “But when it comes to this administration and foreign policy, they’ve put politics ahead of everything. This administration doesn’t want to talk about 9/11. They want to put 9/11 behind them.” Making matters worse is the perceived connection between these questionable decisions and the 2021 Afghanistan withdrawal. The move was hurriedly executed, seemingly to align with the 9/11 anniversary, notwithstanding serious apprehensions from officials. It’s clear that the Biden administration needs to reevaluate its approach, ensuring that the emotions and sentiments of the American populace aren’t treated as mere afterthoughts.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Austin’s Jewel - West Bouldin Creek Greenbelt, Despoiled by Homeless Camps</title><link href="/news/2023/09/12/Austin-Greenbelt-Damage/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Austin’s Jewel - West Bouldin Creek Greenbelt, Despoiled by Homeless Camps" /><published>2023-09-12T07:01:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-12T07:01:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/12/Austin-Greenbelt-Damage</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/12/Austin-Greenbelt-Damage/">&lt;p&gt;Austin, Texas, a city renowned for its vibrant arts scene and natural beauty, is grappling with an escalating issue — the extensive damage caused to its West Bouldin Creek Greenbelt by a homeless encampment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Gem No More?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Monday, a set of distressing videos were shared on Twitter by local activist Jamie Hammonds. The footage paints a bleak picture of the greenbelt — trash, including liquor bottles, needles, and other debris, stretches “as far as the eye can see.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hammonds candidly commented on the video, lamenting, “It’s just been destroyed.” He compared the situation to the degradation of the Violet Crown, another greenbelt compromised by a homeless encampment earlier in the year. “It is so much worse than the Violet Crown Trail,” Hammonds emphasized.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;City’s Response&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Following the alarming deterioration of the greenbelt, approximately 72 encampment residents, along with their pets, were moved to the city-managed Southbridge shelter in mid-August, an action under Austin’s Housing-Focused Encampment Assistance Link (HEAL) Initiative. The city’s approach to the escalating homelessness issue is focused on relocating encampments that present significant “public health and safety risks.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, this wasn’t the first time such an intervention was deemed necessary. In under two years, Austin officials have had to relocate residents from similar encampments twice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Austin is currently orchestrating a cleanup operation for West Bouldin Creek. With multiple departments on the task, the cleanup could span from weeks to potentially several months.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Safety Concerns&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The relocation followed incidents around the encampment that roused public safety apprehensions. Earlier this year, a SWAT team recovered stolen military-grade weapons and ammunition from the camp. Recent reports also include a brush fire igniting at another homeless camp near MoPac and Park Bend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;City Funding and the Way Forward&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Austin has earmarked a staggering $55 million for housing stabilization, crisis response, and public space management. Furthermore, they’ve channeled over $100 million from the American Rescue Plan Act into enhancing homeless services and related system improvements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Austin Council Member José “Chito” Vela emphasized the critical need for mental health and substance use treatments. He highlighted these treatments, when combined with housing, will play a pivotal role in a holistic homelessness prevention strategy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For locals like Greg Smith, who resides near the West Bouldin Creek, there’s still hope. While acknowledging the complexity of the challenge ahead, he believes that the solution, though possibly spanning several years, is within reach. Smith’s faith remains unwavering in Austin’s community spirit. “I believe that Austin residents…will do whatever they can to help those folks who are experiencing homelessness and get their green space back,” Smith concluded.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Austin, Texas, a city renowned for its vibrant arts scene and natural beauty, is grappling with an escalating issue — the extensive damage caused to its West Bouldin Creek Greenbelt by a homeless encampment. A Gem No More? On Monday, a set of distressing videos were shared on Twitter by local activist Jamie Hammonds. The footage paints a bleak picture of the greenbelt — trash, including liquor bottles, needles, and other debris, stretches “as far as the eye can see.” Hammonds candidly commented on the video, lamenting, “It’s just been destroyed.” He compared the situation to the degradation of the Violet Crown, another greenbelt compromised by a homeless encampment earlier in the year. “It is so much worse than the Violet Crown Trail,” Hammonds emphasized. City’s Response Following the alarming deterioration of the greenbelt, approximately 72 encampment residents, along with their pets, were moved to the city-managed Southbridge shelter in mid-August, an action under Austin’s Housing-Focused Encampment Assistance Link (HEAL) Initiative. The city’s approach to the escalating homelessness issue is focused on relocating encampments that present significant “public health and safety risks.” However, this wasn’t the first time such an intervention was deemed necessary. In under two years, Austin officials have had to relocate residents from similar encampments twice. Austin is currently orchestrating a cleanup operation for West Bouldin Creek. With multiple departments on the task, the cleanup could span from weeks to potentially several months. Safety Concerns The relocation followed incidents around the encampment that roused public safety apprehensions. Earlier this year, a SWAT team recovered stolen military-grade weapons and ammunition from the camp. Recent reports also include a brush fire igniting at another homeless camp near MoPac and Park Bend. City Funding and the Way Forward Austin has earmarked a staggering $55 million for housing stabilization, crisis response, and public space management. Furthermore, they’ve channeled over $100 million from the American Rescue Plan Act into enhancing homeless services and related system improvements. Austin Council Member José “Chito” Vela emphasized the critical need for mental health and substance use treatments. He highlighted these treatments, when combined with housing, will play a pivotal role in a holistic homelessness prevention strategy. For locals like Greg Smith, who resides near the West Bouldin Creek, there’s still hope. While acknowledging the complexity of the challenge ahead, he believes that the solution, though possibly spanning several years, is within reach. Smith’s faith remains unwavering in Austin’s community spirit. “I believe that Austin residents…will do whatever they can to help those folks who are experiencing homelessness and get their green space back,” Smith concluded.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Communists Attack Freedom of Speech - Jason Aldean’s ‘Try That in a Small Town’ Stands Strong</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/12/Defending-Aldean/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Communists Attack Freedom of Speech - Jason Aldean’s ‘Try That in a Small Town’ Stands Strong" /><published>2023-09-12T06:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-12T06:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/12/Defending-Aldean</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/12/Defending-Aldean/">&lt;p&gt;In an alarming display of extremist fervor, The Revolution Club of Chicago — a self-proclaimed communist group — burned the American flag in protest of country music star Jason Aldean’s hit single, “Try That in a Small Town.” Their blatant disrespect for national symbols and freedom of expression is unsettling to say the least.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Happening outside one of Aldean’s recent concerts in Chicago, the group’s heated demonstration involved vitriolic chants against the U.S. and the artist. Their distorted perception labels the country anthem, which celebrates the core values of America, as “fascist.” It’s a reminder of the far-left’s increasing intolerance towards differing viewpoints and its attempts to stifle voices that challenge their narratives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite such aggressive antics, Jason Aldean remains unfazed, with his song’s popularity soaring to the top of several charts. This is a testament to the song’s resonance with vast sections of the American populace, who identify with its message. It’s ironic that while corporate giants like Paramount-owned CMT chose to censor the song’s music video, the public responded by amplifying its reach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Critics, likely driven by political biases, have wrongfully labelled the song as racist, without providing substantive evidence. Aldean’s track, in reality, critiques the unchecked rioting and lawlessness witnessed in 2020, emphasizing a need for order and respect for community values.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Among the prominent figures defending Aldean’s right to freedom of speech is former President Donald Trump. He lauded the country singer on Truth Social, highlighting Aldean’s genuine talent and urging the public to support him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s clear that while extreme factions like the Revolution Club may shout loudly, their voice doesn’t reflect the majority. Jason Aldean’s music, standing strong amidst the turmoil, is a testament to the enduring power of artistic freedom and its deep roots in American culture.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">In an alarming display of extremist fervor, The Revolution Club of Chicago — a self-proclaimed communist group — burned the American flag in protest of country music star Jason Aldean’s hit single, “Try That in a Small Town.” Their blatant disrespect for national symbols and freedom of expression is unsettling to say the least. Happening outside one of Aldean’s recent concerts in Chicago, the group’s heated demonstration involved vitriolic chants against the U.S. and the artist. Their distorted perception labels the country anthem, which celebrates the core values of America, as “fascist.” It’s a reminder of the far-left’s increasing intolerance towards differing viewpoints and its attempts to stifle voices that challenge their narratives. Despite such aggressive antics, Jason Aldean remains unfazed, with his song’s popularity soaring to the top of several charts. This is a testament to the song’s resonance with vast sections of the American populace, who identify with its message. It’s ironic that while corporate giants like Paramount-owned CMT chose to censor the song’s music video, the public responded by amplifying its reach. Critics, likely driven by political biases, have wrongfully labelled the song as racist, without providing substantive evidence. Aldean’s track, in reality, critiques the unchecked rioting and lawlessness witnessed in 2020, emphasizing a need for order and respect for community values. Among the prominent figures defending Aldean’s right to freedom of speech is former President Donald Trump. He lauded the country singer on Truth Social, highlighting Aldean’s genuine talent and urging the public to support him. It’s clear that while extreme factions like the Revolution Club may shout loudly, their voice doesn’t reflect the majority. Jason Aldean’s music, standing strong amidst the turmoil, is a testament to the enduring power of artistic freedom and its deep roots in American culture.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Unexpected Horror - U.S. Tourists Ambushed by Cartel Near Texas-Mexico Border</title><link href="/news/2023/09/11/Cartel-Attack-Tourists/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Unexpected Horror - U.S. Tourists Ambushed by Cartel Near Texas-Mexico Border" /><published>2023-09-11T18:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-11T18:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/11/Cartel-Attack-Tourists</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/11/Cartel-Attack-Tourists/">&lt;p&gt;The tranquility of a tourist convoy was shattered early Saturday morning when a group of nearly 20 U.S. tourists, fresh from crossing the Texas border into Mexico, faced a harrowing attack by cartel gunmen in the town of Los Guerra, Tamaulipas. This incident underscores the volatile nature of areas along the Mexico-Texas border, particularly amidst ongoing cartel conflicts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Driving through Los Guerra en route to the Mexican state of San Luis Potosi, the tourists were ambushed along the Riberena highway near the El Angel statue. Employing a makeshift armored vehicle, the assailants rammed the cars in the convoy, immediately following which additional gunmen opened fire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The motive? A possible case of mistaken identity. Sources within law enforcement have shared with Breitbart Texas that these Gulf Cartel gunmen likely misconstrued the tourists as rival gang members or police forces encroaching on their territory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The aftermath of this violent encounter left at least seven tourists with varying injuries. Swift action by local authorities ensured these individuals were rushed to the Miguel Aleman-Roma port of entry, where U.S. ambulances promptly transported them to hospitals for medical care.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This incident is an unsettling reminder of the precarious environment near the Tamaulipas border. The Gulf Cartel, embroiled in territorial disputes with opposing factions, has not only been clashing with rivals but has also accrued a dark record of attacking tourists, committing kidnappings, extortions, and executing murders targeting unsuspecting individuals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With such a backdrop of volatility, this episode accentuates the need for heightened caution for those traveling in the region. As investigations proceed, questions abound: Could this have been prevented? And what can be done to ensure the safety of innocent travelers in such high-risk zones?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">The tranquility of a tourist convoy was shattered early Saturday morning when a group of nearly 20 U.S. tourists, fresh from crossing the Texas border into Mexico, faced a harrowing attack by cartel gunmen in the town of Los Guerra, Tamaulipas. This incident underscores the volatile nature of areas along the Mexico-Texas border, particularly amidst ongoing cartel conflicts. Driving through Los Guerra en route to the Mexican state of San Luis Potosi, the tourists were ambushed along the Riberena highway near the El Angel statue. Employing a makeshift armored vehicle, the assailants rammed the cars in the convoy, immediately following which additional gunmen opened fire. The motive? A possible case of mistaken identity. Sources within law enforcement have shared with Breitbart Texas that these Gulf Cartel gunmen likely misconstrued the tourists as rival gang members or police forces encroaching on their territory. The aftermath of this violent encounter left at least seven tourists with varying injuries. Swift action by local authorities ensured these individuals were rushed to the Miguel Aleman-Roma port of entry, where U.S. ambulances promptly transported them to hospitals for medical care. This incident is an unsettling reminder of the precarious environment near the Tamaulipas border. The Gulf Cartel, embroiled in territorial disputes with opposing factions, has not only been clashing with rivals but has also accrued a dark record of attacking tourists, committing kidnappings, extortions, and executing murders targeting unsuspecting individuals. With such a backdrop of volatility, this episode accentuates the need for heightened caution for those traveling in the region. As investigations proceed, questions abound: Could this have been prevented? And what can be done to ensure the safety of innocent travelers in such high-risk zones?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Justice Alito Stands Firm Against Partisan Pressure</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/11/Justice-Alito-Stands-Firm/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Justice Alito Stands Firm Against Partisan Pressure" /><published>2023-09-11T17:07:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-11T17:07:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/11/Justice-Alito-Stands-Firm</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/11/Justice-Alito-Stands-Firm/">&lt;p&gt;In a display of unwavering integrity and dedication to the principles of the American legal system, Justice Samuel Alito firmly dismissed the ill-founded demands of Senate Democrats for his recusal from the upcoming Supreme Court case. Leading the charge, Sen. Dick Durbin, D-Ill., based his feeble argument on a benign interview Alito gave to the Wall Street Journal, where one of the attending journalists, David B. Rivkin, happened to be an attorney involved in the case.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Justice Alito, highlighting the shallow waters in which Durbin’s argument wades, stated unequivocally, “This argument is unsound,” further adding, “There is no valid reason for my recusal in this case.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One cannot ignore the unending pressures from Democrats on the Senate Judiciary Committee, who have been tirelessly targeting Alito and his peers for not adopting their prescribed ethics code. This, despite the ethical quandaries arising from undisclosed trips by justices, which are not exclusive to the conservative members of the bench.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Durbin’s zealous attempt to undermine the integrity of the Supreme Court, he has failed to recognize the clear distinction between professional courtesy and potential conflict of interest. Alito’s interactions with Rivkin were nothing more than a standard journalistic interaction. Suggesting that Alito’s capacity to remain impartial is compromised based on this interaction is not only a stretch but an affront to the dignity of the justice’s position.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Durbin’s accusations are amplified by the alarming assertion that Alito’s views on Congressional authority over the Supreme Court are controversial. Alito’s remarks about Congress lacking the “authority” to regulate the Supreme Court underscores the doctrine of separation of powers – a foundational principle of the U.S. Constitution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In response to the partisan jabs, Justice Alito expertly articulated the complexities and nuances of the Supreme Court’s operations. He explained, “We have no control over the attorneys whom parties select to represent them… If we recused in such cases, we would regularly have less than a full bench, and the Court’s work would be substantially disrupted and distorted.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Justice Alito’s resolute stance against the Democrats’ untenable demands serves as a beacon of hope for many who cherish the sanctity of America’s judicial system. It is paramount for the Supreme Court to remain above the fray of partisan politics, ensuring that justice is dispensed fairly, impartially, and according to the rule of law. Anything less would undermine the very fabric of American democracy.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a display of unwavering integrity and dedication to the principles of the American legal system, Justice Samuel Alito firmly dismissed the ill-founded demands of Senate Democrats for his recusal from the upcoming Supreme Court case. Leading the charge, Sen. Dick Durbin, D-Ill., based his feeble argument on a benign interview Alito gave to the Wall Street Journal, where one of the attending journalists, David B. Rivkin, happened to be an attorney involved in the case. Justice Alito, highlighting the shallow waters in which Durbin’s argument wades, stated unequivocally, “This argument is unsound,” further adding, “There is no valid reason for my recusal in this case.” One cannot ignore the unending pressures from Democrats on the Senate Judiciary Committee, who have been tirelessly targeting Alito and his peers for not adopting their prescribed ethics code. This, despite the ethical quandaries arising from undisclosed trips by justices, which are not exclusive to the conservative members of the bench. In Durbin’s zealous attempt to undermine the integrity of the Supreme Court, he has failed to recognize the clear distinction between professional courtesy and potential conflict of interest. Alito’s interactions with Rivkin were nothing more than a standard journalistic interaction. Suggesting that Alito’s capacity to remain impartial is compromised based on this interaction is not only a stretch but an affront to the dignity of the justice’s position. Durbin’s accusations are amplified by the alarming assertion that Alito’s views on Congressional authority over the Supreme Court are controversial. Alito’s remarks about Congress lacking the “authority” to regulate the Supreme Court underscores the doctrine of separation of powers – a foundational principle of the U.S. Constitution. In response to the partisan jabs, Justice Alito expertly articulated the complexities and nuances of the Supreme Court’s operations. He explained, “We have no control over the attorneys whom parties select to represent them… If we recused in such cases, we would regularly have less than a full bench, and the Court’s work would be substantially disrupted and distorted.” Justice Alito’s resolute stance against the Democrats’ untenable demands serves as a beacon of hope for many who cherish the sanctity of America’s judicial system. It is paramount for the Supreme Court to remain above the fray of partisan politics, ensuring that justice is dispensed fairly, impartially, and according to the rule of law. Anything less would undermine the very fabric of American democracy.</summary></entry></feed>