<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-09-23T18:13:21-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/09/23/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-09-23T18:13:21-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-23T18:13:21-04:00</updated><id>/2023/09/23/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/23/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">McCormick’s Second Shot - A Fresh Hope for Pennsylvania Republicans?</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/23/McCormick-Run-For-Senate/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="McCormick’s Second Shot - A Fresh Hope for Pennsylvania Republicans?" /><published>2023-09-23T15:45:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-23T15:45:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/23/McCormick-Run-For-Senate</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/23/McCormick-Run-For-Senate/">&lt;p&gt;David McCormick, the businessman and Army veteran who narrowly missed out on a Republican nomination for the U.S. Senate seats in Pennsylvania last year, is back with renewed fervor. This time, he is setting his sights on another seat, voicing his intention to contest against Democrat Sen. Bob Casey Jr. He made this announcement at Heinz History Center in Pittsburgh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-vision-for-change&quot;&gt;A Vision for Change&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;McCormick declared his commitment to combating what he perceives as the failures of President Joe Biden’s leadership, promising to usher in positive change. He cited concerns over the country’s alleged decline economically, militarily, and spiritually and expressed his vision for a brighter future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-strong-republican-candidate&quot;&gt;A Strong Republican Candidate&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;McCormick’s re-entry into the political fray has been welcomed by key Republicans, like Sen. Steve Daines of Montana, highlighting his unique profile as a West Point graduate, combat veteran, and job creator in Pennsylvania. His ability to self-finance and his high-profile status are considered assets that could potentially tip the scales in one of the most competitive states.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;motivations-and-goals&quot;&gt;Motivations and Goals&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a subsequent interview with Fox News, McCormick outlined several motivating factors for his decision, including the prevailing border crisis, rampant inflation, and the perceived attack on the domestic energy sector. He criticized Sen. Casey for his alleged ineffectiveness and unwavering support for Biden’s policies during his long tenure in politics, pledging to be a “force for good” in opposing such policies if elected.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-critical-state&quot;&gt;A Critical State&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;McCormick’s bid comes at a crucial time for Pennsylvania, a state pivotal for the Republican Party’s aspirations to regain control of the Senate in 2024. Currently, Republicans are just two seats short of a majority and one from a split chamber.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;previous-run-and-future-prospects&quot;&gt;Previous Run and Future Prospects&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In his previous run, McCormick competed for the seat of retiring Republican Sen. Pat Toomey, narrowly losing to Dr. Mehmet Oz in the primary. With Pennsylvania being a focal point in upcoming political battles, McCormick’s campaign may serve as a crucial component for Republicans to make significant inroads.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;McCormick’s announcement to run against Sen. Casey marks a renewed hope for Pennsylvania Republicans. With his strong background and commitment to addressing key issues, McCormick is poised to be a formidable contender, promising to reshape the political landscape and bring forth substantive change to the state’s Senate representation.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">David McCormick, the businessman and Army veteran who narrowly missed out on a Republican nomination for the U.S. Senate seats in Pennsylvania last year, is back with renewed fervor. This time, he is setting his sights on another seat, voicing his intention to contest against Democrat Sen. Bob Casey Jr. He made this announcement at Heinz History Center in Pittsburgh. A Vision for Change McCormick declared his commitment to combating what he perceives as the failures of President Joe Biden’s leadership, promising to usher in positive change. He cited concerns over the country’s alleged decline economically, militarily, and spiritually and expressed his vision for a brighter future. A Strong Republican Candidate McCormick’s re-entry into the political fray has been welcomed by key Republicans, like Sen. Steve Daines of Montana, highlighting his unique profile as a West Point graduate, combat veteran, and job creator in Pennsylvania. His ability to self-finance and his high-profile status are considered assets that could potentially tip the scales in one of the most competitive states. Motivations and Goals In a subsequent interview with Fox News, McCormick outlined several motivating factors for his decision, including the prevailing border crisis, rampant inflation, and the perceived attack on the domestic energy sector. He criticized Sen. Casey for his alleged ineffectiveness and unwavering support for Biden’s policies during his long tenure in politics, pledging to be a “force for good” in opposing such policies if elected. A Critical State McCormick’s bid comes at a crucial time for Pennsylvania, a state pivotal for the Republican Party’s aspirations to regain control of the Senate in 2024. Currently, Republicans are just two seats short of a majority and one from a split chamber. Previous Run and Future Prospects In his previous run, McCormick competed for the seat of retiring Republican Sen. Pat Toomey, narrowly losing to Dr. Mehmet Oz in the primary. With Pennsylvania being a focal point in upcoming political battles, McCormick’s campaign may serve as a crucial component for Republicans to make significant inroads. Conclusion McCormick’s announcement to run against Sen. Casey marks a renewed hope for Pennsylvania Republicans. With his strong background and commitment to addressing key issues, McCormick is poised to be a formidable contender, promising to reshape the political landscape and bring forth substantive change to the state’s Senate representation.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Harmonizing Politics and Pop - Taylor Swift’s Concert Tour Amplifies Left-Wing Voter Registration!</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/23/Swift-Left-Wing-Push/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Harmonizing Politics and Pop - Taylor Swift’s Concert Tour Amplifies Left-Wing Voter Registration!" /><published>2023-09-23T14:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-23T14:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/23/Swift-Left-Wing-Push</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/23/Swift-Left-Wing-Push/">&lt;p&gt;As the lights dim and the music starts, fans attending Taylor Swift’s latest concert series experience more than just the infectious melodies of the pop sensation; they encounter Swift’s pronounced left-wing political activism, with the artist using her platform to advocate for voter registration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-concert-with-a-cause&quot;&gt;A Concert with a Cause&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Swift, known for her superlative contributions to the music industry, is now harnessing her influence to emphasize the importance of political participation. Her music tour has become a fertile ground for fostering civic engagement, with the pop icon explicitly encouraging her fans, endearingly called “Swifties”, to register to vote, emphasizing her alignment with progressive ideologies and Democratic candidates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During her performances, Swift interlaces her setlist with fervent appeals to her fans to ensure their voices are heard in the upcoming elections. “I’ve been so lucky to see so many of you guys at my US shows recently,” Swift shared on Instagram Stories, illustrating her continuous commitment to encouraging young fans to partake in the democratic process. “I’ve heard you raise your voices, and I know how powerful they are. Make sure you’re ready to use them in our elections this year!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;swifts-progressive-stance&quot;&gt;Swift’s Progressive Stance&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Swift’s foray into political discourse is not a new phenomenon. She has consistently used her substantial platform to voice her opinions on an array of socio-political issues, from LGBTQIA+ rights to women’s rights, and has never shied away from expressing her support for the Democratic party.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her outspoken stance on various progressive causes has long been a subject of public discourse, catalyzing conversations about the intersection of celebrity and politics. Swift’s decision to intertwine her musical pursuits with political activism reflects her conviction in leveraging her reach to foster change and her belief in the power of collective voices to shape the nation’s future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2020, Swift officially endorsed Joe Biden’s bid for the White House, putting her colossal influence in the service of the Democratic presidential ticket. She highlighted issues such as abortion and gay rights as pivotal in her endorsement, illustrating her alignment with progressive values and her commitment to advocating for social justice and equality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;impactful-resonance-or-political-noise&quot;&gt;Impactful Resonance or Political Noise?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Swift’s synthesis of music and political dialogue raises questions about the role of artists in shaping political landscapes and whether her calls for voter registration may sway her vast fan base towards left-leaning ideologies. The blending of entertainment and politics through her music tour opens up debates on the influence celebrities wield in political realms and whether their platforms should be used to advance particular political agendas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While her advocacy surely resonates with a segment of her fans, aligning with their own ideological stances, it also risks alienating those who may not share her political views. The interplay of music and politics in Swift’s tour emphasizes the potential impact of celebrity voices in political discourses and reflects the evolving role of artists in societal conversations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Swift’s initiative to promote voter registration and her unabashed exposition of her political leanings showcase the multifaceted nature of her career, where melodies harmonize with messages of political empowerment and activism. Whether it results in a symphony of civic engagement or discordant political debates, Swift’s political symphony is playing a noteworthy role in the larger narrative of celebrity and politics.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">As the lights dim and the music starts, fans attending Taylor Swift’s latest concert series experience more than just the infectious melodies of the pop sensation; they encounter Swift’s pronounced left-wing political activism, with the artist using her platform to advocate for voter registration. A Concert with a Cause Swift, known for her superlative contributions to the music industry, is now harnessing her influence to emphasize the importance of political participation. Her music tour has become a fertile ground for fostering civic engagement, with the pop icon explicitly encouraging her fans, endearingly called “Swifties”, to register to vote, emphasizing her alignment with progressive ideologies and Democratic candidates. During her performances, Swift interlaces her setlist with fervent appeals to her fans to ensure their voices are heard in the upcoming elections. “I’ve been so lucky to see so many of you guys at my US shows recently,” Swift shared on Instagram Stories, illustrating her continuous commitment to encouraging young fans to partake in the democratic process. “I’ve heard you raise your voices, and I know how powerful they are. Make sure you’re ready to use them in our elections this year!” Swift’s Progressive Stance Swift’s foray into political discourse is not a new phenomenon. She has consistently used her substantial platform to voice her opinions on an array of socio-political issues, from LGBTQIA+ rights to women’s rights, and has never shied away from expressing her support for the Democratic party. Her outspoken stance on various progressive causes has long been a subject of public discourse, catalyzing conversations about the intersection of celebrity and politics. Swift’s decision to intertwine her musical pursuits with political activism reflects her conviction in leveraging her reach to foster change and her belief in the power of collective voices to shape the nation’s future. In 2020, Swift officially endorsed Joe Biden’s bid for the White House, putting her colossal influence in the service of the Democratic presidential ticket. She highlighted issues such as abortion and gay rights as pivotal in her endorsement, illustrating her alignment with progressive values and her commitment to advocating for social justice and equality. Impactful Resonance or Political Noise? Swift’s synthesis of music and political dialogue raises questions about the role of artists in shaping political landscapes and whether her calls for voter registration may sway her vast fan base towards left-leaning ideologies. The blending of entertainment and politics through her music tour opens up debates on the influence celebrities wield in political realms and whether their platforms should be used to advance particular political agendas. While her advocacy surely resonates with a segment of her fans, aligning with their own ideological stances, it also risks alienating those who may not share her political views. The interplay of music and politics in Swift’s tour emphasizes the potential impact of celebrity voices in political discourses and reflects the evolving role of artists in societal conversations. Swift’s initiative to promote voter registration and her unabashed exposition of her political leanings showcase the multifaceted nature of her career, where melodies harmonize with messages of political empowerment and activism. Whether it results in a symphony of civic engagement or discordant political debates, Swift’s political symphony is playing a noteworthy role in the larger narrative of celebrity and politics.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A Forgotten Handshake - Biden’s Blunder with Brazil’s President Questions His Capacity to Lead</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/23/Biden-Forgotten-Handshake/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Forgotten Handshake - Biden’s Blunder with Brazil’s President Questions His Capacity to Lead" /><published>2023-09-23T11:35:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-23T11:35:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/23/Biden-Forgotten-Handshake</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/23/Biden-Forgotten-Handshake/">&lt;p&gt;When President Joe Biden neglected to shake hands with Brazilian President Luiz Inácio Lula da Silva at the United Nations, the gesture – or lack thereof – didn’t go unnoticed. This most recent lapse, coupled with a repeated, verbatim anecdote during a fundraiser, has intensified discussions regarding his age and suitability for the presidential role.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;forgotten-gestures-and-lost-words&quot;&gt;Forgotten Gestures and Lost Words&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;President Biden, after speaking about workers’ rights at the United Nations in New York City, conspicuously left Brazilian President Lula hanging, exiting the stage after shaking hands with another dignitary. This disregard, perhaps unintended, visibly irked President Lula, drawing the eyes of the international community to Biden’s actions or the lack thereof.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;recurring-narratives-spark-concern&quot;&gt;Recurring Narratives Spark Concern&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To compound matters, the president echoed the same story, nearly word for word, within minutes at a separate fundraiser event. This, rapidly highlighted on social media, brought forth renewed speculation about the effects of his age on his presidential duties, creating a ruckus in the online and offline political domains.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;age-related-speculations-and-public-opinion&quot;&gt;Age-Related Speculations and Public Opinion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These instances have triggered a fresh wave of skepticism about Biden’s aptitude for a second term, spotlighting his age as a potential hindrance to effective leadership. A recent poll by Associated Press-NORC indicated widespread concern, with 77% of respondents, including a substantial 69% of Democrats, questioning his fitness for another term.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;implications-of-minor-slip-ups&quot;&gt;Implications of Minor Slip-ups&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While seemingly inconsequential, such slip-ups raise imperative questions about Biden’s competency and the possible ramifications of such oversights on a global stage. The world meticulously scrutinizes a president’s every move, and minor mishaps can have substantial repercussions, shaping national and international perceptions and influencing subsequent policy decisions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The essence of the discourse now revolves around whether such lapses are mere innocuous blunders or indicative of deeper, more serious issues related to aging and capability that warrant immediate attention. It is crucial to ponder how these narratives might alter public opinion and potentially reconfigure the political scenario in the forthcoming days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In an environment where leadership demands meticulous attention to detail and nuanced understanding of international relations, Biden’s forgetful moment and repeated tales are more than just trivial errors; they are critical lapses that call his capacity to lead into question. Whether these are mere aberrations or symbols of declining competence is a crucial query that remains unanswered, leaving a shadow of doubt hanging over the presidency.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">When President Joe Biden neglected to shake hands with Brazilian President Luiz Inácio Lula da Silva at the United Nations, the gesture – or lack thereof – didn’t go unnoticed. This most recent lapse, coupled with a repeated, verbatim anecdote during a fundraiser, has intensified discussions regarding his age and suitability for the presidential role. Forgotten Gestures and Lost Words President Biden, after speaking about workers’ rights at the United Nations in New York City, conspicuously left Brazilian President Lula hanging, exiting the stage after shaking hands with another dignitary. This disregard, perhaps unintended, visibly irked President Lula, drawing the eyes of the international community to Biden’s actions or the lack thereof. Recurring Narratives Spark Concern To compound matters, the president echoed the same story, nearly word for word, within minutes at a separate fundraiser event. This, rapidly highlighted on social media, brought forth renewed speculation about the effects of his age on his presidential duties, creating a ruckus in the online and offline political domains. Age-Related Speculations and Public Opinion These instances have triggered a fresh wave of skepticism about Biden’s aptitude for a second term, spotlighting his age as a potential hindrance to effective leadership. A recent poll by Associated Press-NORC indicated widespread concern, with 77% of respondents, including a substantial 69% of Democrats, questioning his fitness for another term. Implications of Minor Slip-ups While seemingly inconsequential, such slip-ups raise imperative questions about Biden’s competency and the possible ramifications of such oversights on a global stage. The world meticulously scrutinizes a president’s every move, and minor mishaps can have substantial repercussions, shaping national and international perceptions and influencing subsequent policy decisions. The essence of the discourse now revolves around whether such lapses are mere innocuous blunders or indicative of deeper, more serious issues related to aging and capability that warrant immediate attention. It is crucial to ponder how these narratives might alter public opinion and potentially reconfigure the political scenario in the forthcoming days. In an environment where leadership demands meticulous attention to detail and nuanced understanding of international relations, Biden’s forgetful moment and repeated tales are more than just trivial errors; they are critical lapses that call his capacity to lead into question. Whether these are mere aberrations or symbols of declining competence is a crucial query that remains unanswered, leaving a shadow of doubt hanging over the presidency.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Gone in the Wake of Scandal - The Shocking Disappearance of Qin Gang after Alleged Affair Leads to American Child</title><link href="/news/2023/09/23/Mysterious-Vanishing/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Gone in the Wake of Scandal - The Shocking Disappearance of Qin Gang after Alleged Affair Leads to American Child" /><published>2023-09-23T09:12:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-23T09:12:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/23/Mysterious-Vanishing</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/23/Mysterious-Vanishing/">&lt;p&gt;The unraveling enigma of China’s ex-Foreign Minister, Qin Gang, disappearing after unproven rumors of an illicit affair and a subsequent child born in the United States has sent shockwaves around the world, highlighting the hidden tensions and clandestine operations within the complex tapestry of Chinese politics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-rapid-and-mysterious-departure&quot;&gt;A Rapid and Mysterious Departure&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Qin Gang’s swift and secretive disappearance has ignited global intrigue, particularly given his previous status as a celebrated protégé of Xi Jinping. His tenure as the Foreign Minister of China was abruptly cut short, lasting a mere seven months before he was inexplicably replaced, creating a fertile ground for speculations and conspiracy theories about internal conflicts and cover-ups within the Chinese government.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;swirling-rumors-and-unverified-reports&quot;&gt;Swirling Rumors and Unverified Reports&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The official stance on Qin’s disappearance remains deliberately vague and non-committal. However, whispers have surfaced, primarily from The Wall Street Journal’s sources, suggesting that his sudden exit is related to undisclosed “lifestyle issues,” commonly interpreted as a euphemism for sexual indiscretions within the Chinese Communist Party. These unconfirmed reports suggest a possible extramarital affair resulting in a child born on American soil. However, the veracity of these claims is yet to be substantiated, and the Chinese authorities maintain a conspicuous silence regarding his current whereabouts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-political-embarrassment&quot;&gt;A Political Embarrassment?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The abrupt and disorderly handling of Qin’s position has raised several eyebrows and fuelled speculations of internal power struggles and a potential source of embarrassment for Xi Jinping. While political purges are not a rarity in China, the typically meticulous and calculated approach to high-level transitions seems to be conspicuously absent in Qin’s case, indicating possible deeper turmoil and unrest within the ranks of the government.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;internal-strife-and-questions-of-governance&quot;&gt;Internal Strife and Questions of Governance&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amidst Qin’s mysterious disappearance, China, under Xi Jinping’s leadership, is grappling with pervasive internal corruption and facing an increasingly scrutinous global eye. The unfolding events are causing the world to question the stability, transparency, and integrity of China’s political framework and governance models, and the real story behind Qin Gang’s disappearance continues to be a closely guarded secret, shrouded in mystery and speculation.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">The unraveling enigma of China’s ex-Foreign Minister, Qin Gang, disappearing after unproven rumors of an illicit affair and a subsequent child born in the United States has sent shockwaves around the world, highlighting the hidden tensions and clandestine operations within the complex tapestry of Chinese politics. A Rapid and Mysterious Departure Qin Gang’s swift and secretive disappearance has ignited global intrigue, particularly given his previous status as a celebrated protégé of Xi Jinping. His tenure as the Foreign Minister of China was abruptly cut short, lasting a mere seven months before he was inexplicably replaced, creating a fertile ground for speculations and conspiracy theories about internal conflicts and cover-ups within the Chinese government. Swirling Rumors and Unverified Reports The official stance on Qin’s disappearance remains deliberately vague and non-committal. However, whispers have surfaced, primarily from The Wall Street Journal’s sources, suggesting that his sudden exit is related to undisclosed “lifestyle issues,” commonly interpreted as a euphemism for sexual indiscretions within the Chinese Communist Party. These unconfirmed reports suggest a possible extramarital affair resulting in a child born on American soil. However, the veracity of these claims is yet to be substantiated, and the Chinese authorities maintain a conspicuous silence regarding his current whereabouts. A Political Embarrassment? The abrupt and disorderly handling of Qin’s position has raised several eyebrows and fuelled speculations of internal power struggles and a potential source of embarrassment for Xi Jinping. While political purges are not a rarity in China, the typically meticulous and calculated approach to high-level transitions seems to be conspicuously absent in Qin’s case, indicating possible deeper turmoil and unrest within the ranks of the government. Internal Strife and Questions of Governance Amidst Qin’s mysterious disappearance, China, under Xi Jinping’s leadership, is grappling with pervasive internal corruption and facing an increasingly scrutinous global eye. The unfolding events are causing the world to question the stability, transparency, and integrity of China’s political framework and governance models, and the real story behind Qin Gang’s disappearance continues to be a closely guarded secret, shrouded in mystery and speculation.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Elevating Standards - RNC Ups Ante for Third Presidential Debate</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/23/GOP-Debate/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Elevating Standards - RNC Ups Ante for Third Presidential Debate" /><published>2023-09-23T08:16:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-23T08:16:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/23/GOP-Debate</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/23/GOP-Debate/">&lt;p&gt;The Republican National Committee (RNC) is raising the stakes for presidential candidates, enforcing stricter qualifying criteria for the third debate in November. This decision intensifies the competitive atmosphere surrounding the GOP’s presidential nomination debates, as candidates must now meet higher polling and donor thresholds to make it to the stage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;stricter-criteria-for-candidates&quot;&gt;Stricter Criteria for Candidates&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Candidates aiming to participate in the third debate must secure a minimum of 70,000 unique donors, along with 200 donors from at least 20 states, to their campaign or exploratory committee. The decision on these thresholds was taken during a debate committee conference call and is seen as a notable escalation from the previous debates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to donor support, candidates must also garner 4% support in two national polls or achieve 4% in one national and two statewide polls in Iowa, New Hampshire, Nevada, or South Carolina, which are the first four states in the Republican presidential nominating calendar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-evolving-debate-landscape&quot;&gt;The Evolving Debate Landscape&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The qualifying thresholds have been steadily rising with each debate. The first debate, hosted by Fox News in Milwaukee, required candidates to attain 1% in the polls and secure 40,000 donors, allowing eight contenders to face off. For the upcoming second debate, which is set at the Ronald Reagan Presidential Library and Museum in California, the criteria were raised to 3% in the polls and 50,000 donors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Six out of the eight candidates from the first debate have already met the RNC’s heightened criteria for the second debate, including prominent figures like former New Jersey Gov. Chris Christie, Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis, and former Vice President Mike Pence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;allegiance-to-the-party&quot;&gt;Allegiance to the Party&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Apart from meeting donor and polling thresholds, candidates must also sign a pledge committing their support to the eventual Republican presidential nominee. This agreement prohibits candidates from participating in non-RNC sanctioned debates for the remainder of the 2024 election cycle and mandates data-sharing with the national party committee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;former-presidents-stand&quot;&gt;Former President’s Stand&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, former President Donald Trump, who met the donor and polling criteria, chose not to sign the RNC’s pledge, citing his significant lead over other candidates. Consequently, he did not attend the first debate and has already arranged alternative plans for the next showdown.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;impact-on-the-race&quot;&gt;Impact on the Race&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The imposition of these stringent norms signifies the RNC’s attempt to streamline the nomination process and ensure that only the most competitive and supported candidates make it to the debate stage. This move is likely to bring forth more focused and substantive discussions, allowing voters to make informed decisions in the run-up to the 2024 Presidential Election. Whether this elevated bar will serve to clarify or complicate the field remains a point of intrigue as the debates unfold.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">The Republican National Committee (RNC) is raising the stakes for presidential candidates, enforcing stricter qualifying criteria for the third debate in November. This decision intensifies the competitive atmosphere surrounding the GOP’s presidential nomination debates, as candidates must now meet higher polling and donor thresholds to make it to the stage. Stricter Criteria for Candidates Candidates aiming to participate in the third debate must secure a minimum of 70,000 unique donors, along with 200 donors from at least 20 states, to their campaign or exploratory committee. The decision on these thresholds was taken during a debate committee conference call and is seen as a notable escalation from the previous debates. In addition to donor support, candidates must also garner 4% support in two national polls or achieve 4% in one national and two statewide polls in Iowa, New Hampshire, Nevada, or South Carolina, which are the first four states in the Republican presidential nominating calendar. The Evolving Debate Landscape The qualifying thresholds have been steadily rising with each debate. The first debate, hosted by Fox News in Milwaukee, required candidates to attain 1% in the polls and secure 40,000 donors, allowing eight contenders to face off. For the upcoming second debate, which is set at the Ronald Reagan Presidential Library and Museum in California, the criteria were raised to 3% in the polls and 50,000 donors. Six out of the eight candidates from the first debate have already met the RNC’s heightened criteria for the second debate, including prominent figures like former New Jersey Gov. Chris Christie, Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis, and former Vice President Mike Pence. Allegiance to the Party Apart from meeting donor and polling thresholds, candidates must also sign a pledge committing their support to the eventual Republican presidential nominee. This agreement prohibits candidates from participating in non-RNC sanctioned debates for the remainder of the 2024 election cycle and mandates data-sharing with the national party committee. Former President’s Stand Interestingly, former President Donald Trump, who met the donor and polling criteria, chose not to sign the RNC’s pledge, citing his significant lead over other candidates. Consequently, he did not attend the first debate and has already arranged alternative plans for the next showdown. Impact on the Race The imposition of these stringent norms signifies the RNC’s attempt to streamline the nomination process and ensure that only the most competitive and supported candidates make it to the debate stage. This move is likely to bring forth more focused and substantive discussions, allowing voters to make informed decisions in the run-up to the 2024 Presidential Election. Whether this elevated bar will serve to clarify or complicate the field remains a point of intrigue as the debates unfold.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Taking Charge - Kamala Harris Heads New Office of Gun Violence Prevention</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/23/Gun-Control-Initiative/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Taking Charge - Kamala Harris Heads New Office of Gun Violence Prevention" /><published>2023-09-23T07:09:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-23T07:09:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/23/Gun-Control-Initiative</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/23/Gun-Control-Initiative/">&lt;p&gt;Vice President Kamala Harris has been chosen by President Joe Biden to lead a groundbreaking new executive-level Office of Gun Violence Prevention. This announcement came to light as Biden revealed the establishment of the office, marking a significant step in the administration’s effort to curb gun violence in the United States.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-strategic-stand-against-gun-violence&quot;&gt;A Strategic Stand Against Gun Violence&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The newly formed office aims to serve as a centralized hub to oversee national policy, conduct research, and allocate resources in a coordinated manner to tackle gun violence. It will work in collaboration with the White House, the Community Justice Action Fund, and Everytown for Gun Safety, ensuring a unified approach to addressing this critical issue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-praise-worthy-move&quot;&gt;A Praise-Worthy Move&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The creation of this specialized office has been hailed by various advocates and organizations, highlighting its potential to bring meaningful change. Shannon Watts, founder of Moms Demand Action and affiliated with Mike Bloomberg, emphasized the significance of having a single point of leadership on gun violence within the administration. She expressed that this development is “a very big deal for the movement,” implying that the office would be more than symbolic; it represents a crucial turning point in the fight against gun violence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;harriss-commitment&quot;&gt;Harris’s Commitment&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Vice President Kamala Harris, appointed to oversee this initiative, has expressed her unwavering commitment to the cause. She vowed not to stop working to end the epidemic of gun violence in every community, stressing the urgency of the matter as “we do not have a moment, nor a life to spare.” Harris conveyed that the office would play a crucial role in actualizing the administration’s efforts to reduce violence while also engaging various stakeholders including Congressional, state and local leaders, and advocates to build on the progress made to save lives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-beacon-of-hope&quot;&gt;A Beacon of Hope&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This initiative by the Biden administration underscores a proactive approach to mitigating the longstanding issue of gun violence in the country. It signifies a beacon of hope for those advocating for stricter gun control measures and those affected by gun-related incidents. The promise of a governmental focal point dedicated to creating a structured framework for overseeing national policy provides optimism for more comprehensive solutions to emerge in the battle against gun violence. The success of this endeavor heavily relies on the collective efforts of the leaders, advocates, and the general public to support and reinforce the objectives of the new Office of Gun Violence Prevention.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Vice President Kamala Harris has been chosen by President Joe Biden to lead a groundbreaking new executive-level Office of Gun Violence Prevention. This announcement came to light as Biden revealed the establishment of the office, marking a significant step in the administration’s effort to curb gun violence in the United States. A Strategic Stand Against Gun Violence The newly formed office aims to serve as a centralized hub to oversee national policy, conduct research, and allocate resources in a coordinated manner to tackle gun violence. It will work in collaboration with the White House, the Community Justice Action Fund, and Everytown for Gun Safety, ensuring a unified approach to addressing this critical issue. A Praise-Worthy Move The creation of this specialized office has been hailed by various advocates and organizations, highlighting its potential to bring meaningful change. Shannon Watts, founder of Moms Demand Action and affiliated with Mike Bloomberg, emphasized the significance of having a single point of leadership on gun violence within the administration. She expressed that this development is “a very big deal for the movement,” implying that the office would be more than symbolic; it represents a crucial turning point in the fight against gun violence. Harris’s Commitment Vice President Kamala Harris, appointed to oversee this initiative, has expressed her unwavering commitment to the cause. She vowed not to stop working to end the epidemic of gun violence in every community, stressing the urgency of the matter as “we do not have a moment, nor a life to spare.” Harris conveyed that the office would play a crucial role in actualizing the administration’s efforts to reduce violence while also engaging various stakeholders including Congressional, state and local leaders, and advocates to build on the progress made to save lives. A Beacon of Hope This initiative by the Biden administration underscores a proactive approach to mitigating the longstanding issue of gun violence in the country. It signifies a beacon of hope for those advocating for stricter gun control measures and those affected by gun-related incidents. The promise of a governmental focal point dedicated to creating a structured framework for overseeing national policy provides optimism for more comprehensive solutions to emerge in the battle against gun violence. The success of this endeavor heavily relies on the collective efforts of the leaders, advocates, and the general public to support and reinforce the objectives of the new Office of Gun Violence Prevention.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Sweet Melodies of Love - Tim McGraw &amp;amp; Faith Hill’s Enchanting Marriage</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/23/Country-Love/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sweet Melodies of Love - Tim McGraw &amp;amp; Faith Hill’s Enchanting Marriage" /><published>2023-09-23T06:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-23T06:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/23/Country-Love</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/23/Country-Love/">&lt;p&gt;Country music’s power couple, Tim McGraw and Faith Hill, have never been shy to express their love and admiration for each other. Recently, McGraw warmed millions of hearts with his sweet birthday message to his wife, shedding light on their harmonious life together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-love-note-that-strikes-a-chord&quot;&gt;A Love Note that Strikes a Chord&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Celebrating 27 years of togetherness, McGraw took to Instagram to share a public love note on Hill’s 56th birthday. Calling her his “best friend,” “partner,” and the “love of his life,” he shared a glamorous photo of Hill, adding, “You light up every room you walk into. And you light up my heart and soul.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The message was not only a testament to their enduring bond but also a reminder of the couple’s mutual respect and admiration, with McGraw emphasizing, “I love you more than I could ever express in a million years. This is your day my love!!!!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;echoes-of-family-love&quot;&gt;Echoes of Family Love&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Their three grown daughters, Gracie, Maggie, and Audrey, also share in their parents’ mutual adoration, with 21-year-old Audrey commenting on the post, “The most beautiful. Inside and outside.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;keeping-the-flame-alive&quot;&gt;Keeping the Flame Alive&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;McGraw attributes a significant part of his successful career and 15-year sobriety journey to his marriage with Hill. He believes that without her, his career would probably have “ran into the ground,” and he wouldn’t be where he is today. Now as empty-nesters, the couple enjoys frequent romantic date nights, filled with ’80s music and candlelight dinners, keeping the flame of their love alive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-journey-of-melodies-and-love&quot;&gt;A Journey of Melodies and Love&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meeting first in 1994 and falling in love while touring together in 1996, their journey has been nothing short of a country love song. Despite some initial hesitation due to uncertainties about marrying another country star, Hill finally said ‘Yes!’ to McGraw’s proposal before he went on stage at a festival. The response, written in lipstick on a mirror, still holds a special place in their lives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;celebrating-achievements-together&quot;&gt;Celebrating Achievements Together&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Both McGraw and Hill have seen immense success in their careers, supporting and celebrating each other’s achievements along the way. Hill expressed her pride and admiration for McGraw after the release of his album “Standing Room Only,” calling him “an absolute master of [his] art.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tim McGraw and Faith Hill’s enduring love story is a sweet melody in the country music world, inspiring fans and fellow artists alike. Their mutual respect, shared joys, and the harmonious blending of their lives and careers, illustrate the timeless beauty of love and companionship in the world of music and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Country music’s power couple, Tim McGraw and Faith Hill, have never been shy to express their love and admiration for each other. Recently, McGraw warmed millions of hearts with his sweet birthday message to his wife, shedding light on their harmonious life together. A Love Note that Strikes a Chord Celebrating 27 years of togetherness, McGraw took to Instagram to share a public love note on Hill’s 56th birthday. Calling her his “best friend,” “partner,” and the “love of his life,” he shared a glamorous photo of Hill, adding, “You light up every room you walk into. And you light up my heart and soul.” The message was not only a testament to their enduring bond but also a reminder of the couple’s mutual respect and admiration, with McGraw emphasizing, “I love you more than I could ever express in a million years. This is your day my love!!!!” Echoes of Family Love Their three grown daughters, Gracie, Maggie, and Audrey, also share in their parents’ mutual adoration, with 21-year-old Audrey commenting on the post, “The most beautiful. Inside and outside.” Keeping the Flame Alive McGraw attributes a significant part of his successful career and 15-year sobriety journey to his marriage with Hill. He believes that without her, his career would probably have “ran into the ground,” and he wouldn’t be where he is today. Now as empty-nesters, the couple enjoys frequent romantic date nights, filled with ’80s music and candlelight dinners, keeping the flame of their love alive. A Journey of Melodies and Love Meeting first in 1994 and falling in love while touring together in 1996, their journey has been nothing short of a country love song. Despite some initial hesitation due to uncertainties about marrying another country star, Hill finally said ‘Yes!’ to McGraw’s proposal before he went on stage at a festival. The response, written in lipstick on a mirror, still holds a special place in their lives. Celebrating Achievements Together Both McGraw and Hill have seen immense success in their careers, supporting and celebrating each other’s achievements along the way. Hill expressed her pride and admiration for McGraw after the release of his album “Standing Room Only,” calling him “an absolute master of [his] art.” Conclusion Tim McGraw and Faith Hill’s enduring love story is a sweet melody in the country music world, inspiring fans and fellow artists alike. Their mutual respect, shared joys, and the harmonious blending of their lives and careers, illustrate the timeless beauty of love and companionship in the world of music and beyond.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Dress Code Debacle - Joe Manchin Disagrees with Schumer on Senate Attire</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/22/Dress-Code-Controversy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dress Code Debacle - Joe Manchin Disagrees with Schumer on Senate Attire" /><published>2023-09-22T17:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-22T17:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/22/Dress-Code-Controversy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/22/Dress-Code-Controversy/">&lt;p&gt;Sen. Joe Manchin (D-WV) is reportedly on a mission to reinstate the traditional Senate dress code, a policy recently relaxed by Senate Majority Leader Chuck Schumer (D-NY). This development suggests a rising disagreement within the party lines over the decorum of the Senate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;return-to-formality&quot;&gt;Return to Formality?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Manchin is believed to be circulating a proposal to restore the formal dress code, requiring Senators to don business attire on the Senate floor. This push comes in direct contrast to Schumer’s recent pronouncement, allowing Senators to choose their preferred dress while on the Senate floor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;fettermans-fashion-statement&quot;&gt;Fetterman’s Fashion Statement&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sen. John Fetterman (D-PA) is particularly noticeable under the new dress code, appearing in sweatshirts and shorts in the Capitol. His unconventional attire, in alignment with his “blue-collar tough guy” persona, contrasts sharply with his Harvard education and seemingly affluent background. His attire has sparked conversations on authenticity, with many questioning the sincerity behind his average joe portrayal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;voices-in-opposition&quot;&gt;Voices in Opposition&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many Republicans and even some Democrats seem to support the return to a more formal dress code. They argue that maintaining a degree of formality and dignity is crucial to uphold the reputation of the Senate. Sen. Tommy Tuberville expressed his displeasure with the relaxed dress code, emphasizing his discontent with the casual attires. Similarly, Sen. Susan Collins believes that maintaining a formal dress code is integral to preserving the dignity of the Senate institution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-reflection-of-a-deeper-issue&quot;&gt;A Reflection of a Deeper Issue?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This dispute over dress code may reflect deeper tensions within the Senate, touching on notions of decorum, respect, and the image senators wish to project. While some view the relaxed dress code as a degradation of Senate traditions, others may see it as a step towards modernization and authenticity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this scenario, Manchin’s move to restore formal attire could be interpreted as a pursuit to maintain the sanctity and the revered image of the Senate. Whether his proposal will gain enough traction remains to be seen, but it certainly highlights the differing perspectives within the Senate on maintaining tradition versus embracing change.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Sen. Joe Manchin (D-WV) is reportedly on a mission to reinstate the traditional Senate dress code, a policy recently relaxed by Senate Majority Leader Chuck Schumer (D-NY). This development suggests a rising disagreement within the party lines over the decorum of the Senate. Return to Formality? Manchin is believed to be circulating a proposal to restore the formal dress code, requiring Senators to don business attire on the Senate floor. This push comes in direct contrast to Schumer’s recent pronouncement, allowing Senators to choose their preferred dress while on the Senate floor. Fetterman’s Fashion Statement Sen. John Fetterman (D-PA) is particularly noticeable under the new dress code, appearing in sweatshirts and shorts in the Capitol. His unconventional attire, in alignment with his “blue-collar tough guy” persona, contrasts sharply with his Harvard education and seemingly affluent background. His attire has sparked conversations on authenticity, with many questioning the sincerity behind his average joe portrayal. Voices in Opposition Many Republicans and even some Democrats seem to support the return to a more formal dress code. They argue that maintaining a degree of formality and dignity is crucial to uphold the reputation of the Senate. Sen. Tommy Tuberville expressed his displeasure with the relaxed dress code, emphasizing his discontent with the casual attires. Similarly, Sen. Susan Collins believes that maintaining a formal dress code is integral to preserving the dignity of the Senate institution. A Reflection of a Deeper Issue? This dispute over dress code may reflect deeper tensions within the Senate, touching on notions of decorum, respect, and the image senators wish to project. While some view the relaxed dress code as a degradation of Senate traditions, others may see it as a step towards modernization and authenticity. In this scenario, Manchin’s move to restore formal attire could be interpreted as a pursuit to maintain the sanctity and the revered image of the Senate. Whether his proposal will gain enough traction remains to be seen, but it certainly highlights the differing perspectives within the Senate on maintaining tradition versus embracing change.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A Cry for Freedom - Ben Carson Warns Against Repeat of COVID Controls</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/22/COVID-Mandates-Carson/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Cry for Freedom - Ben Carson Warns Against Repeat of COVID Controls" /><published>2023-09-22T16:18:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-22T16:18:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/22/COVID-Mandates-Carson</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/22/COVID-Mandates-Carson/">&lt;p&gt;Ben Carson, the former Secretary of Housing and Urban Development, raises the alarm on what he perceives as attempts by the U.S. government to control the American populace through mandates related to COVID-19. In a discussion on Newsmax’s “American Agenda,” he voiced concerns over the significant influence and control exercised by the authorities during the pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-impact-on-education&quot;&gt;The Impact on Education&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Carson criticized the sweeping measures, such as school shutdowns, arguing they have had severe and long-lasting impacts on the learning and development of children. He believes it could take years, if not decades, for the educational setbacks experienced during the pandemic to be reversed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;allegations-of-manipulation&quot;&gt;Allegations of Manipulation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The former HUD Secretary accuses the government of not prioritizing the welfare of the citizens and focusing instead on controlling and manipulating people. He fears the grave implications if such practices continue and calls for a critical examination of the repercussions of the mandates imposed during the pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;funding-for-at-home-covid-tests&quot;&gt;Funding for At-Home COVID Tests&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In response to the Biden administration’s recent announcement of a $600 million funding to produce new at-home COVID-19 tests, Carson emphasized the importance of not succumbing to fear and manipulation. This funding initiative is aimed at averting possible shortages during an anticipated rise in coronavirus cases during the colder months and resolving supply chain issues experienced during past surges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;carsons-clarion-call&quot;&gt;Carson’s Clarion Call&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Carson’s strong message to the American people is to not be “manipulated and terrified by COVID.” He urges rationality and an understanding of the facts surrounding the virus, such as its evolving, typically weaker variants. He warns against unnecessary fear due to increased positive test results and calls for resistance against any attempts to impose further business and school shutdowns which could lead to economic distress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;we-the-people&quot;&gt;We, The People&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, Carson’s plea is for vigilance and a unified stance by the people against government overreach and control. He emphasizes that it is the collective responsibility of the citizens to assert their rights and safeguard their freedoms against any perceived attempts to disrupt lives and livelihoods under the guise of public health measures. He argues that a repeat of the stringent controls and mandates witnessed during the pandemic could have devastating and lasting impacts on the society and economy, making it imperative for the people to be informed, rational, and resolute in their response.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Ben Carson, the former Secretary of Housing and Urban Development, raises the alarm on what he perceives as attempts by the U.S. government to control the American populace through mandates related to COVID-19. In a discussion on Newsmax’s “American Agenda,” he voiced concerns over the significant influence and control exercised by the authorities during the pandemic. The Impact on Education Carson criticized the sweeping measures, such as school shutdowns, arguing they have had severe and long-lasting impacts on the learning and development of children. He believes it could take years, if not decades, for the educational setbacks experienced during the pandemic to be reversed. Allegations of Manipulation The former HUD Secretary accuses the government of not prioritizing the welfare of the citizens and focusing instead on controlling and manipulating people. He fears the grave implications if such practices continue and calls for a critical examination of the repercussions of the mandates imposed during the pandemic. Funding for At-Home COVID Tests In response to the Biden administration’s recent announcement of a $600 million funding to produce new at-home COVID-19 tests, Carson emphasized the importance of not succumbing to fear and manipulation. This funding initiative is aimed at averting possible shortages during an anticipated rise in coronavirus cases during the colder months and resolving supply chain issues experienced during past surges. Carson’s Clarion Call Carson’s strong message to the American people is to not be “manipulated and terrified by COVID.” He urges rationality and an understanding of the facts surrounding the virus, such as its evolving, typically weaker variants. He warns against unnecessary fear due to increased positive test results and calls for resistance against any attempts to impose further business and school shutdowns which could lead to economic distress. We, The People In conclusion, Carson’s plea is for vigilance and a unified stance by the people against government overreach and control. He emphasizes that it is the collective responsibility of the citizens to assert their rights and safeguard their freedoms against any perceived attempts to disrupt lives and livelihoods under the guise of public health measures. He argues that a repeat of the stringent controls and mandates witnessed during the pandemic could have devastating and lasting impacts on the society and economy, making it imperative for the people to be informed, rational, and resolute in their response.</summary></entry></feed>