<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-10-13T09:20:49-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/13/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-13T09:20:49-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-13T09:20:49-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/13/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/13/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/13/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-13T09:20:49-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-13T09:20:49-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/13/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/13/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/">&lt;p&gt;Recent surprise attacks by Hamas on Israel has fueled ongoing tensions between staunchly conservative commentators and the progressive “Squad” Democrats known for criticizing Israel. The intensity of the backlash highlights the deep political divide over foreign policy in the Middle East.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Hamas’ shocking attack, several members of the “Squad,” including Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.), called for a “ceasefire and de-escalation,” condemning the violence. The absence of a statement from Rep. Rashida Tlaib (D-Mich.) was notably called out by conservative media outlets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;South Carolina GOP Rep. Nancy Mace quickly labeled Ocasio-Cortez a “Hamas apologist” in response to her call for peace and de-escalation. Rep. Ilhan Omar (D-Minn.), no stranger to controversy surrounding her views on Israel, echoed the call for de-escalation and ceasefire. Omar’s prior statements comparing the US and Israel to terrorist groups like Hamas and the Taliban resurfaced in the debate, fueling more criticisms. Omar’s 2019 tweet, where she opined that “Israel has hypnotized the world,” also continues to haunt her political career, often cited by critics to challenge her stance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conservative commentators have been especially vocal. “FOX &amp;amp; Friends Weekend” co-host Rachel Campos-Duffy took aim at Omar, saying she fails to recognize the peace in the Middle East under Trump’s administration. Conservative pundit John Hasson also called out Omar, claiming she insinuated that attacks on IDF forces were acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Massachusetts Democrat Rep. Ayanna Pressley’s concerns over the “devastating attacks on Israelis” were met with skepticism. A prominent conservative online personality, Comfortably Smug, accused the “Squad” of advising Israel to back down after the nation suffered massive attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Jamaal Bowman’s call for an end to the Gaza blockade, in addition to condemning the Hamas attacks, was met with criticism from conservative radio host Jason Rantz. He accused Bowman of pairing his condemnation of terrorism with unwarranted criticisms of Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Cori Bush emphasized the urgent need for a ceasefire, while pushing for an end to “U.S. support for Israeli military occupation and apartheid.” Defense attorney Marina Medvin criticized Bush, suggesting that she equates the death of Palestinian terrorists to the horrific acts committed against Jewish civilians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amidst the political turmoil and intense debate, the attacks have taken a heavy toll. Israeli media report over 300 dead due to the wide-ranging assault. Gaza health officials note that at least 200 Palestinians have perished in the retaliatory Israeli air strikes following the initial Hamas attack. As the situation remains volatile, both sides continue to count their casualties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This divisive issue showcases the challenge America faces in crafting a unified approach to foreign policy, with deeply entrenched political divides at play. As the situation develops, the debate is bound to intensify, shedding light on the complexities of U.S. politics in the global arena.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Music World Mourns: Rudolph Isley, Iconic Member of The Isley Brothers, Passes Away at 84</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/13/Isley-Brothers-Legend/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Music World Mourns: Rudolph Isley, Iconic Member of The Isley Brothers, Passes Away at 84" /><published>2023-10-13T09:15:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-13T09:15:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/13/Isley-Brothers-Legend</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/13/Isley-Brothers-Legend/">&lt;p&gt;In a heartbreaking announcement, Rudolph Isley, the founding member of the iconic R&amp;amp;B group The Isley Brothers, has passed away at the age of 84. The loss deeply resonates with fans and music enthusiasts who’ve been influenced by the timeless hits of the band.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Isley Brothers, celebrated for their chart-topping songs such as “Shout!”, “Twist and Shout,” and “This Old Heart of Mine,” have left an indelible mark on the world of music. Rudolph’s contribution as a key member has made him an integral part of the band’s success and journey.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ronald Isley, Rudolph’s brother, expressed his deep sorrow in a statement to Fox News Digital, “There are no words to express my feelings and the love I have for my brother. Our family will miss him. But I know he’s in a better place.” The specific details surrounding Rudolph’s death remain undisclosed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Isley Brothers’ story began in the 1950s, when Rudolph, along with his brothers Ronald, Vernon, and O’Kelly Isley, formed the group. The band faced a tragic setback when Vernon, at just 13, died in a bicycle accident. Despite this early loss, the Isleys’ passion for music didn’t waver. Rudolph, O’Kelly, and Ronald persisted and eventually wrote “Shout!”, a song that not only skyrocketed their fame but also found a cherished place in pop culture, notably in the film “National Lampoon’s Animal House.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the years rolled on, the younger Isley siblings, Ernie and Marvin, teamed up with Chris Jasper, their brother-in-law, expanding The Isley Brothers’ lineup. Their collective efforts and iconic songs cemented the band’s reputation in the music world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Isley Brothers’ talents and contributions haven’t gone unrecognized. In 1992, the group received one of the highest accolades in the music industry, with their induction into the Rock ‘n Roll Hall of Fame. This was followed by another monumental honor in 2014 when they were presented with the Grammy lifetime achievement award.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the passing of Rudolph Isley, the music world has lost a shining star. But as fans from all over the globe pay tribute, it’s clear that his legacy and the magic of The Isley Brothers’ music will continue to inspire and entertain generations to come.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">In a heartbreaking announcement, Rudolph Isley, the founding member of the iconic R&amp;amp;B group The Isley Brothers, has passed away at the age of 84. The loss deeply resonates with fans and music enthusiasts who’ve been influenced by the timeless hits of the band. The Isley Brothers, celebrated for their chart-topping songs such as “Shout!”, “Twist and Shout,” and “This Old Heart of Mine,” have left an indelible mark on the world of music. Rudolph’s contribution as a key member has made him an integral part of the band’s success and journey. Ronald Isley, Rudolph’s brother, expressed his deep sorrow in a statement to Fox News Digital, “There are no words to express my feelings and the love I have for my brother. Our family will miss him. But I know he’s in a better place.” The specific details surrounding Rudolph’s death remain undisclosed. The Isley Brothers’ story began in the 1950s, when Rudolph, along with his brothers Ronald, Vernon, and O’Kelly Isley, formed the group. The band faced a tragic setback when Vernon, at just 13, died in a bicycle accident. Despite this early loss, the Isleys’ passion for music didn’t waver. Rudolph, O’Kelly, and Ronald persisted and eventually wrote “Shout!”, a song that not only skyrocketed their fame but also found a cherished place in pop culture, notably in the film “National Lampoon’s Animal House.” As the years rolled on, the younger Isley siblings, Ernie and Marvin, teamed up with Chris Jasper, their brother-in-law, expanding The Isley Brothers’ lineup. Their collective efforts and iconic songs cemented the band’s reputation in the music world. The Isley Brothers’ talents and contributions haven’t gone unrecognized. In 1992, the group received one of the highest accolades in the music industry, with their induction into the Rock ‘n Roll Hall of Fame. This was followed by another monumental honor in 2014 when they were presented with the Grammy lifetime achievement award. With the passing of Rudolph Isley, the music world has lost a shining star. But as fans from all over the globe pay tribute, it’s clear that his legacy and the magic of The Isley Brothers’ music will continue to inspire and entertain generations to come.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Bombshell Guilty Plea: Ex-IRS Contractor Admits to Leaking Trump’s Taxes</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/13/Trump-Tax-Leak/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bombshell Guilty Plea: Ex-IRS Contractor Admits to Leaking Trump’s Taxes" /><published>2023-10-13T08:16:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-13T08:16:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/13/Trump-Tax-Leak</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/13/Trump-Tax-Leak/">&lt;p&gt;In a significant development related to the unauthorized leaks of tax return details of many, including former President Donald Trump, a former contractor of the Internal Revenue Service (IRS) has pleaded guilty. This acknowledgment has led to an intense debate around privacy, data security, and the implications for high-profile figures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Thursday, the Justice Department formally charged Charles Edward Littlejohn, a 38-year-old from Washington, D.C., for stealing and leaking tax return information of thousands, including the former President. The leaks spanned between 2018 and 2020 and were handed over to two major news outlets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;U.S. District Judge Ana Reyes expressed her profound concern over the leaks, underscoring the importance of the rule of law. In a statement, she remarked, “When we have people, for whatever reason, take the law into their own hands society doesn’t function.” She further emphasized that no justification could make such acts acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Littlejohn’s plea pertains to the unauthorized disclosure of tax returns, a charge that can lead to a prison term of up to five years. The final decision on the sentence, however, rests with the judge and will be announced on January 29. Details on whether Littlejohn cooperated with the prosecutors or if the plea was a result of a deal remain under wraps, as his attorney, Lisa Manning, chose not to comment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the charges did not specify the news outlets involved, the time frame and nature of the leaks point towards The New York Times and ProPublica. The former had published a revealing report in 2020 about Trump’s federal income tax, indicating he paid merely $750 the year he assumed office. ProPublica’s 2021 expose, on the other hand, showcased the minimal tax contributions of America’s wealthiest, igniting a passionate debate on tax reforms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The unauthorized leaks have not only sparked political and social debates but also raised valid concerns regarding data security and the sanctity of taxpayer information. As a direct response to the revelations, the IRS reaffirmed its commitment to taxpayer data confidentiality, revealing new measures to bolster its security mechanisms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the nation awaits Littlejohn’s sentencing and further details on the leak, questions about data privacy, the role of journalism, and the ethics of revealing such information continue to dominate discussions.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a significant development related to the unauthorized leaks of tax return details of many, including former President Donald Trump, a former contractor of the Internal Revenue Service (IRS) has pleaded guilty. This acknowledgment has led to an intense debate around privacy, data security, and the implications for high-profile figures. On Thursday, the Justice Department formally charged Charles Edward Littlejohn, a 38-year-old from Washington, D.C., for stealing and leaking tax return information of thousands, including the former President. The leaks spanned between 2018 and 2020 and were handed over to two major news outlets. U.S. District Judge Ana Reyes expressed her profound concern over the leaks, underscoring the importance of the rule of law. In a statement, she remarked, “When we have people, for whatever reason, take the law into their own hands society doesn’t function.” She further emphasized that no justification could make such acts acceptable. Littlejohn’s plea pertains to the unauthorized disclosure of tax returns, a charge that can lead to a prison term of up to five years. The final decision on the sentence, however, rests with the judge and will be announced on January 29. Details on whether Littlejohn cooperated with the prosecutors or if the plea was a result of a deal remain under wraps, as his attorney, Lisa Manning, chose not to comment. While the charges did not specify the news outlets involved, the time frame and nature of the leaks point towards The New York Times and ProPublica. The former had published a revealing report in 2020 about Trump’s federal income tax, indicating he paid merely $750 the year he assumed office. ProPublica’s 2021 expose, on the other hand, showcased the minimal tax contributions of America’s wealthiest, igniting a passionate debate on tax reforms. The unauthorized leaks have not only sparked political and social debates but also raised valid concerns regarding data security and the sanctity of taxpayer information. As a direct response to the revelations, the IRS reaffirmed its commitment to taxpayer data confidentiality, revealing new measures to bolster its security mechanisms. As the nation awaits Littlejohn’s sentencing and further details on the leak, questions about data privacy, the role of journalism, and the ethics of revealing such information continue to dominate discussions.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Is Underestimating Biden a Risk for his Opponents?</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/13/Biden-Reelection-Potential/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Is Underestimating Biden a Risk for his Opponents?" /><published>2023-10-13T07:12:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-13T07:12:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/13/Biden-Reelection-Potential</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/13/Biden-Reelection-Potential/">&lt;p&gt;In a recent conversation centered on his New York Times bestseller, &lt;em&gt;Breaking Biden&lt;/em&gt;, Breitbart’s Editor-in-Chief Alex Marlow made a compelling case about President Joe Biden’s resilience and potential for reelection. During an interview on The Charlie Kirk Show, Marlow emphasized that it’s a grave error to not “take this guy seriously.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Marlow’s research paints Biden as an intricate political player with a vast network established over 50 years. While many have questioned how Biden, often criticized for his gaffes and lacking a captivating ideological stance, reached the White House, Marlow believes he understands the formula. According to him, Biden was instrumental in crafting the Democrat Party’s machinery that eventually selected him. “He wasn’t just propped up — the guy was forging a lot of the gears that made the machinery of the Democrat Party,” Marlow explained.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One fascinating aspect that Marlow touched upon was Biden’s initial intention to hand over his political legacy to his son, Beau. But with Beau’s untimely passing and no clear successor to former President Barack Obama, Biden, with his immense knowledge of the party’s inner workings, emerged as the most viable candidate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Highlighting the Democrat’s strategy, Marlow remarked, “They are looking for operators, and Joe was the ultimate operator.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contrary to popular belief that Biden’s regular slip-ups are a recent development, Marlow stated, “He’s always done this nutty stuff.” He stressed that Biden’s behavior is consistent over the years. While he acknowledges some extent of mental deterioration, he believes much of the criticism is misplaced. Biden has “always been this way,” Marlow reiterated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perhaps Marlow’s most significant point of the interview was his cautionary statement regarding Biden’s potential to clinch another term. Despite the president’s seemingly bumbling demeanor, his track record shows a series of wins. If the opposition continues to underestimate him, they might be setting themselves up for a surprise. “We can’t shake this guy, and that’s why the hard reset needs to take place,” Marlow advised.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In closing, Marlow urged a change in the way opponents perceive Biden. Recognizing his strengths, understanding his strategies, and crafting a robust counter-narrative would be crucial for those aiming to challenge him in the next election cycle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Marlow’s book, &lt;em&gt;Breaking Biden: Exposing the Hidden Forces and Secret Money Machine Behind Joe Biden, His Family, and His Administration&lt;/em&gt;, dives deeper into these insights and is available in multiple formats for those eager to delve deeper into the Biden phenomenon.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a recent conversation centered on his New York Times bestseller, Breaking Biden, Breitbart’s Editor-in-Chief Alex Marlow made a compelling case about President Joe Biden’s resilience and potential for reelection. During an interview on The Charlie Kirk Show, Marlow emphasized that it’s a grave error to not “take this guy seriously.” Marlow’s research paints Biden as an intricate political player with a vast network established over 50 years. While many have questioned how Biden, often criticized for his gaffes and lacking a captivating ideological stance, reached the White House, Marlow believes he understands the formula. According to him, Biden was instrumental in crafting the Democrat Party’s machinery that eventually selected him. “He wasn’t just propped up — the guy was forging a lot of the gears that made the machinery of the Democrat Party,” Marlow explained. One fascinating aspect that Marlow touched upon was Biden’s initial intention to hand over his political legacy to his son, Beau. But with Beau’s untimely passing and no clear successor to former President Barack Obama, Biden, with his immense knowledge of the party’s inner workings, emerged as the most viable candidate. Highlighting the Democrat’s strategy, Marlow remarked, “They are looking for operators, and Joe was the ultimate operator.” Contrary to popular belief that Biden’s regular slip-ups are a recent development, Marlow stated, “He’s always done this nutty stuff.” He stressed that Biden’s behavior is consistent over the years. While he acknowledges some extent of mental deterioration, he believes much of the criticism is misplaced. Biden has “always been this way,” Marlow reiterated. Perhaps Marlow’s most significant point of the interview was his cautionary statement regarding Biden’s potential to clinch another term. Despite the president’s seemingly bumbling demeanor, his track record shows a series of wins. If the opposition continues to underestimate him, they might be setting themselves up for a surprise. “We can’t shake this guy, and that’s why the hard reset needs to take place,” Marlow advised. In closing, Marlow urged a change in the way opponents perceive Biden. Recognizing his strengths, understanding his strategies, and crafting a robust counter-narrative would be crucial for those aiming to challenge him in the next election cycle. Marlow’s book, Breaking Biden: Exposing the Hidden Forces and Secret Money Machine Behind Joe Biden, His Family, and His Administration, dives deeper into these insights and is available in multiple formats for those eager to delve deeper into the Biden phenomenon.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Steve Scalise Abandons Bid for House Speaker</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/13/House-Speaker-Race/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Steve Scalise Abandons Bid for House Speaker" /><published>2023-10-13T06:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-13T06:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/13/House-Speaker-Race</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/13/House-Speaker-Race/">&lt;p&gt;In a surprising twist, House Majority Leader Steve Scalise, a prominent Republican figure from Louisiana, recently withdrew his name from contention for the role of House speaker. This decision comes on the heels of a turbulent political period marked by the removal of Kevin McCarthy from the speaker position just last week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Scalise’s decision was revealed post a confidential meeting with his fellow GOP members. During a subsequent press conference, Scalise emphasized the importance of unity within the Republican Party. He urged members to set aside personal agendas for the greater good of the nation, saying, “This country is counting on us to come back together.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He further highlighted the need for harmony within the GOP, stating, “Our conference still has to come together and is not there. There are still some people that have their own agendas.” Scalise stressed the urgency of the situation, asserting that the House of Representatives needed a speaker to streamline operations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Scalise’s dedication to his role as the Majority Leader remains evident, he clarified his position on the speaker race: “I never came here for a title… I’m the Majority Leader of the House, and I love the job I have.” He expressed his hope for a swift election of a new speaker, yet refrained from endorsing anyone, maintaining, “It’s got to be people that aren’t doing it for themselves and their own personal interests.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The race for House speaker has been closely watched, with Scalise previously winning a GOP conference nomination over Rep. Jim Jordan from Ohio. However, the support was divided. Several Republican members expressed their reluctance to back Scalise in the House floor vote.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the conference, Rep. Ralph Norman, a Republican from South Carolina, vocalized his lack of surprise over Scalise’s decision. Norman conveyed his support for Jim Jordan, expressing confidence in Jordan’s potential to secure the necessary votes for the speaker role. Rep. Jim Banks from Indiana, another supporter of Jordan, affirmed his commitment, stating he would do “everything I can to help elect him the next Speaker of the House.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The unfolding political drama and race for the House speaker position serve as a significant event in US politics. The speaker role is crucial, holding the second place in the presidential order of succession. With the House having voted 216-210 to oust Kevin McCarthy from the position recently, it remains to be seen who will rise to occupy this esteemed role next.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a surprising twist, House Majority Leader Steve Scalise, a prominent Republican figure from Louisiana, recently withdrew his name from contention for the role of House speaker. This decision comes on the heels of a turbulent political period marked by the removal of Kevin McCarthy from the speaker position just last week. Scalise’s decision was revealed post a confidential meeting with his fellow GOP members. During a subsequent press conference, Scalise emphasized the importance of unity within the Republican Party. He urged members to set aside personal agendas for the greater good of the nation, saying, “This country is counting on us to come back together.” He further highlighted the need for harmony within the GOP, stating, “Our conference still has to come together and is not there. There are still some people that have their own agendas.” Scalise stressed the urgency of the situation, asserting that the House of Representatives needed a speaker to streamline operations. While Scalise’s dedication to his role as the Majority Leader remains evident, he clarified his position on the speaker race: “I never came here for a title… I’m the Majority Leader of the House, and I love the job I have.” He expressed his hope for a swift election of a new speaker, yet refrained from endorsing anyone, maintaining, “It’s got to be people that aren’t doing it for themselves and their own personal interests.” The race for House speaker has been closely watched, with Scalise previously winning a GOP conference nomination over Rep. Jim Jordan from Ohio. However, the support was divided. Several Republican members expressed their reluctance to back Scalise in the House floor vote. After the conference, Rep. Ralph Norman, a Republican from South Carolina, vocalized his lack of surprise over Scalise’s decision. Norman conveyed his support for Jim Jordan, expressing confidence in Jordan’s potential to secure the necessary votes for the speaker role. Rep. Jim Banks from Indiana, another supporter of Jordan, affirmed his commitment, stating he would do “everything I can to help elect him the next Speaker of the House.” The unfolding political drama and race for the House speaker position serve as a significant event in US politics. The speaker role is crucial, holding the second place in the presidential order of succession. With the House having voted 216-210 to oust Kevin McCarthy from the position recently, it remains to be seen who will rise to occupy this esteemed role next.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Disney’s ‘Loki’ in Hot Water: AI Allegedly Used for Promotional Poster</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/12/Disney-Loki-AI-Controversy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Disney’s ‘Loki’ in Hot Water: AI Allegedly Used for Promotional Poster" /><published>2023-10-12T17:37:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-12T17:37:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/12/Disney-Loki-AI-Controversy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/12/Disney-Loki-AI-Controversy/">&lt;p&gt;In a controversial revelation, Disney’s hit television series “Loki” has been put in the spotlight for its alleged use of artificial intelligence (AI) in crafting its season 2 promotional poster. The incident has led to a wider discussion about AI’s growing role in the entertainment and design industry, raising both eyebrows and concerns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to a report by The Verge, the recent promotional poster for “Loki” seems to have ties to an image from Shutterstock, a renowned stock photography company. Such a connection becomes problematic when considering Disney Plus’s stringent licensing agreement, which highlights regulations against AI-generated content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Illustrator Katria Raden was one of the first professionals to express her disappointment in the company. She shared her concerns on X (previously known as Twitter), pointing out the AI-generated characteristics evident in the “Loki” poster. Amid various opinions on the matter, Raden emphasized the unnatural aspects of the poster, noting the bizarre transformations akin to “meaningless squiggles” often seen in AI-created imagery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The heart of the controversy stems from the observation that the “Loki” poster’s background seemingly resembles a Shutterstock stock image titled “Surreal Infinity Time Spiral Space Antique.” Notably, AI image checkers have identified this stock image as AI-generated. Shutterstock’s own guidelines are strict against licensing AI-generated content unless it is produced by their proprietary AI-image generator. This internal tool ensures Shutterstock maintains intellectual property rights over the content on their platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this digital age, it’s imperative for artists and creators to be assured of the authenticity and uniqueness of their creations. With tools like AI, the lines between creativity and technology blur. As Katria Raden pointed out, countless artists rely on stock sites to earn a livelihood. She believes that using AI-generated imagery, a byproduct of tech built on “mass exploitation and wage theft,” is no different from sidelining Disney’s own dedicated employees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Disney’s relationship with AI seems to be a recurring topic. Earlier this year, the entertainment giant faced criticism for reportedly employing AI in the opening credits for another Disney+ Marvel series, “Secret Invasion.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As AI continues to advance, industries across the board will need to determine its ethical and appropriate use. The “Loki” controversy underscores the vital conversation about AI’s place in artistic expression and the potential challenges it poses to creative professions.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">In a controversial revelation, Disney’s hit television series “Loki” has been put in the spotlight for its alleged use of artificial intelligence (AI) in crafting its season 2 promotional poster. The incident has led to a wider discussion about AI’s growing role in the entertainment and design industry, raising both eyebrows and concerns. According to a report by The Verge, the recent promotional poster for “Loki” seems to have ties to an image from Shutterstock, a renowned stock photography company. Such a connection becomes problematic when considering Disney Plus’s stringent licensing agreement, which highlights regulations against AI-generated content. Illustrator Katria Raden was one of the first professionals to express her disappointment in the company. She shared her concerns on X (previously known as Twitter), pointing out the AI-generated characteristics evident in the “Loki” poster. Amid various opinions on the matter, Raden emphasized the unnatural aspects of the poster, noting the bizarre transformations akin to “meaningless squiggles” often seen in AI-created imagery. The heart of the controversy stems from the observation that the “Loki” poster’s background seemingly resembles a Shutterstock stock image titled “Surreal Infinity Time Spiral Space Antique.” Notably, AI image checkers have identified this stock image as AI-generated. Shutterstock’s own guidelines are strict against licensing AI-generated content unless it is produced by their proprietary AI-image generator. This internal tool ensures Shutterstock maintains intellectual property rights over the content on their platform. In this digital age, it’s imperative for artists and creators to be assured of the authenticity and uniqueness of their creations. With tools like AI, the lines between creativity and technology blur. As Katria Raden pointed out, countless artists rely on stock sites to earn a livelihood. She believes that using AI-generated imagery, a byproduct of tech built on “mass exploitation and wage theft,” is no different from sidelining Disney’s own dedicated employees. Disney’s relationship with AI seems to be a recurring topic. Earlier this year, the entertainment giant faced criticism for reportedly employing AI in the opening credits for another Disney+ Marvel series, “Secret Invasion.” As AI continues to advance, industries across the board will need to determine its ethical and appropriate use. The “Loki” controversy underscores the vital conversation about AI’s place in artistic expression and the potential challenges it poses to creative professions.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">BWI Airport Faces Bomb Scare: Fast Response Ensures Public Safety</title><link href="/news/2023/10/12/BWI-Airport-Bomb-Threat/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="BWI Airport Faces Bomb Scare: Fast Response Ensures Public Safety" /><published>2023-10-12T16:18:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-12T16:18:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/12/BWI-Airport-Bomb-Threat</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/12/BWI-Airport-Bomb-Threat/">&lt;p&gt;In a nerve-wracking series of events on Wednesday afternoon, officials at Baltimore/Washington International (BWI) Thurgood Marshall Airport went on high alert due to a potential bomb threat. Quick action and a coordinated response ensured that the situation was deftly handled, with the suspect swiftly taken into custody.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At approximately 3:10 p.m., BWI officials announced via social media that they had closed Terminal Roadway for a pressing law enforcement investigation. As a result, all vehicular traffic inching towards the airport was halted. Additionally, individuals present in the lower level terminal were instructed to stay put for their safety.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This rapid response was spurred by a distressing report. According to FOX 5 in Washington, D.C., a man made a chilling declaration to law enforcement: he claimed to have explosives stashed in his vehicle, which he had parked at the airport. Such alarming statements demand immediate and robust reactions, and that’s exactly what ensued.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In just a little over an hour after the initial announcement, by 4:30 p.m., the Maryland Transportation Authority Police provided a much-needed update. They confirmed that the upper level of the airport terminal road was safe and reopened for traffic. More importantly, they assured the public that there was no prevailing threat to their safety.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Maryland Transportation Authority Police have since confirmed that they have the individual, who sparked the entire incident, under arrest. They said, “Based on statements made by the individual, officers took precautionary measures.” Ensuring public safety remains a top priority, and the authority’s prompt actions certainly reflect their commitment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Transportation Security Administration (TSA), when probed for deeper insights, directed inquiries to the Maryland Transportation Authority Police, underlining the latter’s role as the primary law enforcement agency overseeing this case.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The situation at BWI serves as a stark reminder of the constant vigilance required in today’s age. Threats, be they genuine or mere claims, can’t be taken lightly. While the reasons behind the individual’s actions remain unclear, what stands out is the efficient and effective response of the law enforcement agencies involved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As investigations continue into the precise nature of the threat and the motivations behind it, one thing is clear: the quick-thinking and decisive actions of the Maryland Transportation Authority Police played a crucial role in averting a potential crisis.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a nerve-wracking series of events on Wednesday afternoon, officials at Baltimore/Washington International (BWI) Thurgood Marshall Airport went on high alert due to a potential bomb threat. Quick action and a coordinated response ensured that the situation was deftly handled, with the suspect swiftly taken into custody. At approximately 3:10 p.m., BWI officials announced via social media that they had closed Terminal Roadway for a pressing law enforcement investigation. As a result, all vehicular traffic inching towards the airport was halted. Additionally, individuals present in the lower level terminal were instructed to stay put for their safety. This rapid response was spurred by a distressing report. According to FOX 5 in Washington, D.C., a man made a chilling declaration to law enforcement: he claimed to have explosives stashed in his vehicle, which he had parked at the airport. Such alarming statements demand immediate and robust reactions, and that’s exactly what ensued. In just a little over an hour after the initial announcement, by 4:30 p.m., the Maryland Transportation Authority Police provided a much-needed update. They confirmed that the upper level of the airport terminal road was safe and reopened for traffic. More importantly, they assured the public that there was no prevailing threat to their safety. The Maryland Transportation Authority Police have since confirmed that they have the individual, who sparked the entire incident, under arrest. They said, “Based on statements made by the individual, officers took precautionary measures.” Ensuring public safety remains a top priority, and the authority’s prompt actions certainly reflect their commitment. The Transportation Security Administration (TSA), when probed for deeper insights, directed inquiries to the Maryland Transportation Authority Police, underlining the latter’s role as the primary law enforcement agency overseeing this case. The situation at BWI serves as a stark reminder of the constant vigilance required in today’s age. Threats, be they genuine or mere claims, can’t be taken lightly. While the reasons behind the individual’s actions remain unclear, what stands out is the efficient and effective response of the law enforcement agencies involved. As investigations continue into the precise nature of the threat and the motivations behind it, one thing is clear: the quick-thinking and decisive actions of the Maryland Transportation Authority Police played a crucial role in averting a potential crisis.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Biden’s Controversial Palestine Funding: Flirting with Anti-Terrorism Laws?</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/12/Biden-Palestine-Funding-Critique/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Biden’s Controversial Palestine Funding: Flirting with Anti-Terrorism Laws?" /><published>2023-10-12T15:08:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-12T15:08:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/12/Biden-Palestine-Funding-Critique</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/12/Biden-Palestine-Funding-Critique/">&lt;p&gt;In what many critics describe as a questionable move, President Joe Biden’s decision to resume hefty financial support to Palestinian entities is now under judicial scrutiny. U.S. District Court Judge Matthew J. Kacsmaryk has stepped in to grant a much-needed review, prompted by concerns that Biden’s generosity may be in stark violation of established anti-terrorism laws.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This legal review comes on the heels of a lawsuit initiated by Rep. Ronny Jackson, R-Texas, and the America First Legal Foundation (AFL). Their shared contention is that the Biden administration may be carelessly allowing Economic Support Funds, meant for humanitarian purposes, to be misused. Such funds, instead of uplifting the Palestinian people, could be financing terrorist activities in the West Bank and Gaza.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Biden’s decision to rekindle financial relations with the Palestinian National Authority stands in sharp contrast to the more cautious approach of his predecessor. Former President Donald Trump had prudently halted any payments, heeding the Taylor Force Act of 2018, which clearly restricts U.S. financial assistance to Palestine while it continues supporting imprisoned terrorists and their dependents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the heart of the issue is a staggering sum of approximately $500 million greenlit by Biden, representing a lion’s share of the total U.S. aid to Palestine. And as if to add fuel to the fire, an additional $700 million was routed to a UN agency in the region — an agency Trump had wisely exited.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The gravity of this decision becomes even more palpable against the backdrop of the recent devastating terrorist attacks on Israel, attributed to Hamas and Hezbollah. Both groups, as The Wall Street Journal points out, are under the financial and operational umbrella of Iran.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The human toll of these conflicts is alarming: Israel mourns the loss of over 1,200 souls, with another 3,400 nursing injuries and more than 200 held hostage. Palestinian sources too paint a grim picture with over 1,100 dead, 5,400 wounded, and a startling 263,000 individuals displaced, according to the United Nations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Washington Free Beacon has also unearthed unsettling findings. Despite being armed with internal reports suggesting that such funding might embolden Hamas, the Biden administration moved forward, seemingly undeterred.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the judicial review progresses, many hope it brings clarity to the situation. However, Biden’s decision to potentially put U.S. funds in the hands of extremist groups, directly or indirectly, is a matter that will undoubtedly cast a long shadow over his presidency.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In what many critics describe as a questionable move, President Joe Biden’s decision to resume hefty financial support to Palestinian entities is now under judicial scrutiny. U.S. District Court Judge Matthew J. Kacsmaryk has stepped in to grant a much-needed review, prompted by concerns that Biden’s generosity may be in stark violation of established anti-terrorism laws. This legal review comes on the heels of a lawsuit initiated by Rep. Ronny Jackson, R-Texas, and the America First Legal Foundation (AFL). Their shared contention is that the Biden administration may be carelessly allowing Economic Support Funds, meant for humanitarian purposes, to be misused. Such funds, instead of uplifting the Palestinian people, could be financing terrorist activities in the West Bank and Gaza. Biden’s decision to rekindle financial relations with the Palestinian National Authority stands in sharp contrast to the more cautious approach of his predecessor. Former President Donald Trump had prudently halted any payments, heeding the Taylor Force Act of 2018, which clearly restricts U.S. financial assistance to Palestine while it continues supporting imprisoned terrorists and their dependents. At the heart of the issue is a staggering sum of approximately $500 million greenlit by Biden, representing a lion’s share of the total U.S. aid to Palestine. And as if to add fuel to the fire, an additional $700 million was routed to a UN agency in the region — an agency Trump had wisely exited. The gravity of this decision becomes even more palpable against the backdrop of the recent devastating terrorist attacks on Israel, attributed to Hamas and Hezbollah. Both groups, as The Wall Street Journal points out, are under the financial and operational umbrella of Iran. The human toll of these conflicts is alarming: Israel mourns the loss of over 1,200 souls, with another 3,400 nursing injuries and more than 200 held hostage. Palestinian sources too paint a grim picture with over 1,100 dead, 5,400 wounded, and a startling 263,000 individuals displaced, according to the United Nations. The Washington Free Beacon has also unearthed unsettling findings. Despite being armed with internal reports suggesting that such funding might embolden Hamas, the Biden administration moved forward, seemingly undeterred. As the judicial review progresses, many hope it brings clarity to the situation. However, Biden’s decision to potentially put U.S. funds in the hands of extremist groups, directly or indirectly, is a matter that will undoubtedly cast a long shadow over his presidency.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Arnold Schwarzenegger’s Bold Take on Democrats</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/12/Schwarzenegger-Democrats-Statement/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Arnold Schwarzenegger’s Bold Take on Democrats" /><published>2023-10-12T14:06:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-12T14:06:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/12/Schwarzenegger-Democrats-Statement</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/12/Schwarzenegger-Democrats-Statement/">&lt;p&gt;In an upcoming episode of the “Literally” podcast hosted by Rob Lowe, Hollywood legend and former California Governor Arnold Schwarzenegger shared some strong views on the Democratic Party. Known for his no-holds-barred commentary, the &lt;em&gt;Terminator&lt;/em&gt; star stated that Democrats aim to “&lt;em&gt;ruin every city in America&lt;/em&gt;.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the interview, when Lowe recounted Republican principles as explained by former California Republican Congressman David Dreier, Schwarzenegger pointed out that a key principle missing from the list was “Strong law enforcement.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When Lowe queried the &lt;em&gt;Predator&lt;/em&gt; star about his thoughts on what Democrats stand for, Schwarzenegger responded emphatically, saying, “&lt;em&gt;We want to f&lt;/em&gt;ck up every city in America. That seems to be the theme right now*.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The statement was a reflection of the actor’s view of Democrat-led regimes in major American cities, which are currently grappling with debt, crime, and a decline in citizens and businesses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, Schwarzenegger’s controversial statements and political stance have been a matter of debate even among Republicans. Despite being a self-proclaimed Republican, Schwarzenegger’s views often tilt towards the left. His support for issues such as pro-choice and climate change, and his strong stance on COVID-19 safety measures, have sometimes clashed with conservative ideals. In fact, in 2021, he famously told conservatives “&lt;em&gt;screw your freedom&lt;/em&gt;” when many opposed the government’s measures to combat the pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moreover, Schwarzenegger’s 2021 comparison of Trump’s administration to Adolf Hitler’s Nazi Party further drew ire from many conservatives. Yet, in a recent interview with the New York Times, the &lt;em&gt;Commando&lt;/em&gt; actor reaffirmed his allegiance to the Republican Party.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether or not you agree with Schwarzenegger’s opinions, his outspoken nature ensures that he continues to remain a significant and polarizing figure in both the entertainment and political arenas. The full episode of the “Literally with Rob Lowe” podcast featuring Arnold Schwarzenegger is set to release this Thursday.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">In an upcoming episode of the “Literally” podcast hosted by Rob Lowe, Hollywood legend and former California Governor Arnold Schwarzenegger shared some strong views on the Democratic Party. Known for his no-holds-barred commentary, the Terminator star stated that Democrats aim to “ruin every city in America.” During the interview, when Lowe recounted Republican principles as explained by former California Republican Congressman David Dreier, Schwarzenegger pointed out that a key principle missing from the list was “Strong law enforcement.” When Lowe queried the Predator star about his thoughts on what Democrats stand for, Schwarzenegger responded emphatically, saying, “We want to fck up every city in America. That seems to be the theme right now*.” The statement was a reflection of the actor’s view of Democrat-led regimes in major American cities, which are currently grappling with debt, crime, and a decline in citizens and businesses. However, Schwarzenegger’s controversial statements and political stance have been a matter of debate even among Republicans. Despite being a self-proclaimed Republican, Schwarzenegger’s views often tilt towards the left. His support for issues such as pro-choice and climate change, and his strong stance on COVID-19 safety measures, have sometimes clashed with conservative ideals. In fact, in 2021, he famously told conservatives “screw your freedom” when many opposed the government’s measures to combat the pandemic. Moreover, Schwarzenegger’s 2021 comparison of Trump’s administration to Adolf Hitler’s Nazi Party further drew ire from many conservatives. Yet, in a recent interview with the New York Times, the Commando actor reaffirmed his allegiance to the Republican Party. Whether or not you agree with Schwarzenegger’s opinions, his outspoken nature ensures that he continues to remain a significant and polarizing figure in both the entertainment and political arenas. The full episode of the “Literally with Rob Lowe” podcast featuring Arnold Schwarzenegger is set to release this Thursday.</summary></entry></feed>