<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-10-19T18:14:22-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/19/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-19T18:14:22-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-19T18:14:22-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/19/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/19/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/19/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-19T18:14:22-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-19T18:14:22-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/19/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/19/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/">&lt;p&gt;Recent surprise attacks by Hamas on Israel has fueled ongoing tensions between staunchly conservative commentators and the progressive “Squad” Democrats known for criticizing Israel. The intensity of the backlash highlights the deep political divide over foreign policy in the Middle East.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Hamas’ shocking attack, several members of the “Squad,” including Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.), called for a “ceasefire and de-escalation,” condemning the violence. The absence of a statement from Rep. Rashida Tlaib (D-Mich.) was notably called out by conservative media outlets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;South Carolina GOP Rep. Nancy Mace quickly labeled Ocasio-Cortez a “Hamas apologist” in response to her call for peace and de-escalation. Rep. Ilhan Omar (D-Minn.), no stranger to controversy surrounding her views on Israel, echoed the call for de-escalation and ceasefire. Omar’s prior statements comparing the US and Israel to terrorist groups like Hamas and the Taliban resurfaced in the debate, fueling more criticisms. Omar’s 2019 tweet, where she opined that “Israel has hypnotized the world,” also continues to haunt her political career, often cited by critics to challenge her stance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conservative commentators have been especially vocal. “FOX &amp;amp; Friends Weekend” co-host Rachel Campos-Duffy took aim at Omar, saying she fails to recognize the peace in the Middle East under Trump’s administration. Conservative pundit John Hasson also called out Omar, claiming she insinuated that attacks on IDF forces were acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Massachusetts Democrat Rep. Ayanna Pressley’s concerns over the “devastating attacks on Israelis” were met with skepticism. A prominent conservative online personality, Comfortably Smug, accused the “Squad” of advising Israel to back down after the nation suffered massive attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Jamaal Bowman’s call for an end to the Gaza blockade, in addition to condemning the Hamas attacks, was met with criticism from conservative radio host Jason Rantz. He accused Bowman of pairing his condemnation of terrorism with unwarranted criticisms of Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Cori Bush emphasized the urgent need for a ceasefire, while pushing for an end to “U.S. support for Israeli military occupation and apartheid.” Defense attorney Marina Medvin criticized Bush, suggesting that she equates the death of Palestinian terrorists to the horrific acts committed against Jewish civilians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amidst the political turmoil and intense debate, the attacks have taken a heavy toll. Israeli media report over 300 dead due to the wide-ranging assault. Gaza health officials note that at least 200 Palestinians have perished in the retaliatory Israeli air strikes following the initial Hamas attack. As the situation remains volatile, both sides continue to count their casualties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This divisive issue showcases the challenge America faces in crafting a unified approach to foreign policy, with deeply entrenched political divides at play. As the situation develops, the debate is bound to intensify, shedding light on the complexities of U.S. politics in the global arena.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Explosion Rocks Cruise Ship in Maine: Hundreds Evacuated</title><link href="/news/2023/10/19/Cruise-Ship-Explosion/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Explosion Rocks Cruise Ship in Maine: Hundreds Evacuated" /><published>2023-10-19T16:43:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-19T16:43:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/19/Cruise-Ship-Explosion</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/19/Cruise-Ship-Explosion/">&lt;p&gt;An unsettling explosion on the American Queen Voyages’ Ocean Navigator, a popular cruise ship docked in Maine’s Portland Harbor, prompted the immediate evacuation of hundreds aboard. The explosion, originating from the engine room, sent shockwaves throughout the community and the wider cruise industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to local reports, a crew member faced grave injuries following the incident and was rushed to a nearby hospital. This individual suffered serious burns to the arms and hands, as cited by the Daily Mail. In addition to the injured crew member, 128 passengers were hurriedly escorted off the ship. The remainder, 82 in total, were the ship’s employees, as confirmed by WGME, a local TV station.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Taking a closer look at the Ocean Navigator, this 286-foot cruise vessel can accommodate 202 people. On that fateful Wednesday, the ship had just positioned itself at the Ocean Gateway Terminal when, around 7:25 a.m., a fire broke out in a generator within the engine room. Thankfully, swift actions by the Portland firefighters and the ship’s own crew ensured the flames were doused quickly. Presently, efforts are underway to clear the smoke from the ship. However, the U.S. Coast Guard has stated that passengers will not be permitted to reboard, as reported by WPFO.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Ocean Navigator, constructed in 2001 and subsequently refurbished in 2019, now faces an extensive investigation to pinpoint the exact cause of the explosion. While the inquiry remains ongoing, American Queen Voyages released a statement addressing the event: “Ocean Navigator encountered a generator fire this morning in Portland, ME. Thankfully, no passengers were harmed. Due to our crew’s rapid response, everyone was evacuated safely. One crew member, unfortunately, sustained injuries and is under medical care. The fire has been managed, and we’re working closely with the local fire department to gauge the damage. Currently, guests have been accommodated in a local hotel.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;American Queen Voyages, headquartered in Fort Lauderdale, Florida, is recognized for its diverse cruising options. They offer an array of journeys, spanning river cruises, lake cruises, and expansive ocean voyages. Their reach extends to various destinations, including the Southeast, the Great Lakes, Alaska, New England, Canada, Mexico, and even Costa Rica.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With safety at the forefront of concerns, all eyes are now on the investigative results and the measures that will be undertaken to prevent such incidents in the future.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">An unsettling explosion on the American Queen Voyages’ Ocean Navigator, a popular cruise ship docked in Maine’s Portland Harbor, prompted the immediate evacuation of hundreds aboard. The explosion, originating from the engine room, sent shockwaves throughout the community and the wider cruise industry. According to local reports, a crew member faced grave injuries following the incident and was rushed to a nearby hospital. This individual suffered serious burns to the arms and hands, as cited by the Daily Mail. In addition to the injured crew member, 128 passengers were hurriedly escorted off the ship. The remainder, 82 in total, were the ship’s employees, as confirmed by WGME, a local TV station. Taking a closer look at the Ocean Navigator, this 286-foot cruise vessel can accommodate 202 people. On that fateful Wednesday, the ship had just positioned itself at the Ocean Gateway Terminal when, around 7:25 a.m., a fire broke out in a generator within the engine room. Thankfully, swift actions by the Portland firefighters and the ship’s own crew ensured the flames were doused quickly. Presently, efforts are underway to clear the smoke from the ship. However, the U.S. Coast Guard has stated that passengers will not be permitted to reboard, as reported by WPFO. The Ocean Navigator, constructed in 2001 and subsequently refurbished in 2019, now faces an extensive investigation to pinpoint the exact cause of the explosion. While the inquiry remains ongoing, American Queen Voyages released a statement addressing the event: “Ocean Navigator encountered a generator fire this morning in Portland, ME. Thankfully, no passengers were harmed. Due to our crew’s rapid response, everyone was evacuated safely. One crew member, unfortunately, sustained injuries and is under medical care. The fire has been managed, and we’re working closely with the local fire department to gauge the damage. Currently, guests have been accommodated in a local hotel.” American Queen Voyages, headquartered in Fort Lauderdale, Florida, is recognized for its diverse cruising options. They offer an array of journeys, spanning river cruises, lake cruises, and expansive ocean voyages. Their reach extends to various destinations, including the Southeast, the Great Lakes, Alaska, New England, Canada, Mexico, and even Costa Rica. With safety at the forefront of concerns, all eyes are now on the investigative results and the measures that will be undertaken to prevent such incidents in the future.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Biden Contemplates Hefty Aid Package: $60B for Ukraine and $10B for Israel</title><link href="/news/2023/10/19/US-Aid-Israel-Ukraine/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Biden Contemplates Hefty Aid Package: $60B for Ukraine and $10B for Israel" /><published>2023-10-19T15:09:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-19T15:09:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/19/US-Aid-Israel-Ukraine</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/19/US-Aid-Israel-Ukraine/">&lt;p&gt;Amidst ongoing global tensions, President Joe Biden’s administration is said to be weighing a substantial assistance package for two key allies: Ukraine and Israel. A trusted source revealed on Wednesday that Biden is considering $60 billion in aid for Ukraine and an additional $10 billion for Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The motivation behind this potential aid stems from recent international incidents. Israel, on one side, is recovering from the October 7 attack led by Hamas militants. On the other, Ukraine continues to confront the challenges posed by a Russian invasion. The U.S., as a longstanding supporter of both nations, seeks to bolster their positions during these difficult times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Biden’s commitment to these allies is evident, he is also believed to be exploring a broader supplemental request of approximately $100 billion. This would not only fortify Israel and Ukraine but also extend defense aid to Taiwan. Moreover, part of this funding aims to enhance security measures along the U.S.-Mexico border.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sen. Jim Risch, a leading Republican voice on the Senate Foreign Relations Committee, expressed unfamiliarity with the $100 billion figure outside of news coverage. However, he acknowledged hearing rumors of the administration’s $10 billion consideration for Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As of now, it remains uncertain what the final figures will look like, as Biden has yet to settle on definitive numbers. Furthermore, the administration has not shared a detailed breakdown with Congress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it’s crucial to note that, under U.S. legislation, Congress holds the purse strings and controls expenditures, not the executive branch. This means that, irrespective of Biden’s proposals, Congress will have the final say on the distribution of these funds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the world watches closely, the forthcoming days will shed more light on how the U.S. plans to back its allies in their hour of need and the role Congress will play in these pivotal decisions.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Amidst ongoing global tensions, President Joe Biden’s administration is said to be weighing a substantial assistance package for two key allies: Ukraine and Israel. A trusted source revealed on Wednesday that Biden is considering $60 billion in aid for Ukraine and an additional $10 billion for Israel. The motivation behind this potential aid stems from recent international incidents. Israel, on one side, is recovering from the October 7 attack led by Hamas militants. On the other, Ukraine continues to confront the challenges posed by a Russian invasion. The U.S., as a longstanding supporter of both nations, seeks to bolster their positions during these difficult times. While Biden’s commitment to these allies is evident, he is also believed to be exploring a broader supplemental request of approximately $100 billion. This would not only fortify Israel and Ukraine but also extend defense aid to Taiwan. Moreover, part of this funding aims to enhance security measures along the U.S.-Mexico border. Sen. Jim Risch, a leading Republican voice on the Senate Foreign Relations Committee, expressed unfamiliarity with the $100 billion figure outside of news coverage. However, he acknowledged hearing rumors of the administration’s $10 billion consideration for Israel. As of now, it remains uncertain what the final figures will look like, as Biden has yet to settle on definitive numbers. Furthermore, the administration has not shared a detailed breakdown with Congress. However, it’s crucial to note that, under U.S. legislation, Congress holds the purse strings and controls expenditures, not the executive branch. This means that, irrespective of Biden’s proposals, Congress will have the final say on the distribution of these funds. As the world watches closely, the forthcoming days will shed more light on how the U.S. plans to back its allies in their hour of need and the role Congress will play in these pivotal decisions.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Biden’s Controversial Move with Labor Secretary Ignites GOP Firestorm</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/19/Biden-Decision-Labor-Secretary/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Biden’s Controversial Move with Labor Secretary Ignites GOP Firestorm" /><published>2023-10-19T14:04:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-19T14:04:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/19/Biden-Decision-Labor-Secretary</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/19/Biden-Decision-Labor-Secretary/">&lt;p&gt;The Biden administration faces growing criticism after its decision to include Acting Secretary of Labor Julie Su in the presidential line of succession. This move has sparked significant backlash, particularly as Su’s nomination for the role has yet to be confirmed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alabama GOP Sen. Katie Britt spearheaded a letter, signed by 29 Republican Senate colleagues, addressed to President Biden. The letter voices their “grave concerns” and seeks clarification about Su’s eligibility to potentially assume the office of the President under the Presidential Succession Act of 1947.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The senators highlighted that since March 14, 2023, Ms. Su’s nomination has not been confirmed, pointing out a lack of bipartisan support for her position. The White House, however, continues to recognize her as Acting Secretary of Labor and has included her name on its official website in the “order of succession to the Presidency.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Su, who served as California’s labor secretary from 2019 to 2021 under Gov. Gavin Newsom, is currently ninth in line for the presidency. The GOP senators have called out the administration for potentially disregarding congressional intent, stating it would be “antithetical to our system of governance.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The senators’ concerns also touch on the 25th Amendment to the U.S. Constitution, which gives Congress the authority to set the presidential line of succession beyond the Vice President. The letter further emphasizes that Ms. Su has not been “appointed, by and with the advice and consent of the Senate,” urging the administration to clarify its stance on her position in the line of succession.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a direct quote from the letter, the senators wrote, “It is unimaginable to think that this Administration believes someone who has neither been duly elected nor confirmed by the Senate… could be President of the United States.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Besides the ongoing controversy surrounding her place in the line of succession, Su’s nomination has faced considerable challenges from both sides of the aisle. While she has been serving as acting secretary since Marty Walsh’s resignation earlier this year, her official confirmation remains uncertain. Su’s nomination saw intense pushback due to her stance on gig work regulations in California and her perceived lack of cooperation with ICE officials during her tenure as the state’s top labor official.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The GOP senators have reiterated their call for President Biden to reconsider Su’s nomination, suggesting he put forward a nominee capable of garnering bipartisan support.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With both parties voicing concerns over Su’s nomination, this situation serves as another flashpoint in the already tense relationship between the Biden administration and Senate Republicans. The resolution to this debate will likely have significant implications for the administration’s relations with Congress and its ability to navigate future political challenges.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">The Biden administration faces growing criticism after its decision to include Acting Secretary of Labor Julie Su in the presidential line of succession. This move has sparked significant backlash, particularly as Su’s nomination for the role has yet to be confirmed. Alabama GOP Sen. Katie Britt spearheaded a letter, signed by 29 Republican Senate colleagues, addressed to President Biden. The letter voices their “grave concerns” and seeks clarification about Su’s eligibility to potentially assume the office of the President under the Presidential Succession Act of 1947. The senators highlighted that since March 14, 2023, Ms. Su’s nomination has not been confirmed, pointing out a lack of bipartisan support for her position. The White House, however, continues to recognize her as Acting Secretary of Labor and has included her name on its official website in the “order of succession to the Presidency.” Su, who served as California’s labor secretary from 2019 to 2021 under Gov. Gavin Newsom, is currently ninth in line for the presidency. The GOP senators have called out the administration for potentially disregarding congressional intent, stating it would be “antithetical to our system of governance.” The senators’ concerns also touch on the 25th Amendment to the U.S. Constitution, which gives Congress the authority to set the presidential line of succession beyond the Vice President. The letter further emphasizes that Ms. Su has not been “appointed, by and with the advice and consent of the Senate,” urging the administration to clarify its stance on her position in the line of succession. In a direct quote from the letter, the senators wrote, “It is unimaginable to think that this Administration believes someone who has neither been duly elected nor confirmed by the Senate… could be President of the United States.” Besides the ongoing controversy surrounding her place in the line of succession, Su’s nomination has faced considerable challenges from both sides of the aisle. While she has been serving as acting secretary since Marty Walsh’s resignation earlier this year, her official confirmation remains uncertain. Su’s nomination saw intense pushback due to her stance on gig work regulations in California and her perceived lack of cooperation with ICE officials during her tenure as the state’s top labor official. The GOP senators have reiterated their call for President Biden to reconsider Su’s nomination, suggesting he put forward a nominee capable of garnering bipartisan support. With both parties voicing concerns over Su’s nomination, this situation serves as another flashpoint in the already tense relationship between the Biden administration and Senate Republicans. The resolution to this debate will likely have significant implications for the administration’s relations with Congress and its ability to navigate future political challenges.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Britney Spears Drops Bombshell: Reveals Past Abortion with Justin Timberlake</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/19/Britney-Justin-Revelation/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Britney Spears Drops Bombshell: Reveals Past Abortion with Justin Timberlake" /><published>2023-10-19T12:57:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-19T12:57:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/19/Britney-Justin-Revelation</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/19/Britney-Justin-Revelation/">&lt;p&gt;Britney Spears, the beloved pop sensation, is opening up about her life in her new memoir, “The Woman in Me,” set to be released on October 24th. One of the most shocking revelations from the excerpts released on Tuesday is the disclosure of her abortion during her relationship with pop icon Justin Timberlake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Spears candidly writes, “If it had been left up to me alone, I never would have done it,” referring to the abortion. She further elaborates, sharing that Timberlake “was so sure that he didn’t want to be a father.” This personal revelation is set to provide readers with an intimate look into the singer’s private struggles and decisions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their whirlwind romance began when both Spears and Timberlake were young performers on Disney’s Mickey Mouse Club. The duo later started dating in their late teens, swiftly becoming the talk of Tinseltown and one of the most-watched couples in the entertainment arena. Their high-profile relationship ended in 2002.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The “Baby One More Time” singer recalls Timberlake’s reaction to her pregnancy, sharing he “definitely wasn’t happy about the pregnancy.” Spears adds, “He said we weren’t ready to have a baby in our lives, that we were way too young.” The heartbreak and emotional turmoil from the abortion are evident in her words, as she describes it as “one of the most agonizing things I have ever experienced in my life.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Britney’s memoir doesn’t stop at her relationship with Timberlake. She dives deep into the controversial conservatorship that dominated her life for 14 years. Under this legal guardianship, she felt her autonomy stripped away. Spears recalls the conservatorship’s control over even her reproductive rights, sharing that she was prevented from removing a contraceptive IUD despite wanting another child. “The conservatorship stripped me of my womanhood, made me into a child,” Spears remarks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reflecting on the extended period of control her father and his associates had over her personal and financial affairs, Spears writes, “I think back now… and it makes me feel sick.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The pop sensation’s memoir is also expected to touch upon her personal life after Timberlake. Spears had two sons with her second husband, Kevin Federline. Following a very public breakdown in 2008, Spears entered into the previously mentioned conservatorship led by her father, Jamie. Fortunately, this conservatorship came to an end in November 2021.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, life hasn’t been entirely rosy for the star since. In 2022, she announced a miscarriage and later, in August, her third husband, Sam Asghari, stated they were filing for divorce.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The Woman in Me” promises to be a compelling read, providing fans with an unfiltered look into the life of a pop music legend.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Britney Spears, the beloved pop sensation, is opening up about her life in her new memoir, “The Woman in Me,” set to be released on October 24th. One of the most shocking revelations from the excerpts released on Tuesday is the disclosure of her abortion during her relationship with pop icon Justin Timberlake. Spears candidly writes, “If it had been left up to me alone, I never would have done it,” referring to the abortion. She further elaborates, sharing that Timberlake “was so sure that he didn’t want to be a father.” This personal revelation is set to provide readers with an intimate look into the singer’s private struggles and decisions. Their whirlwind romance began when both Spears and Timberlake were young performers on Disney’s Mickey Mouse Club. The duo later started dating in their late teens, swiftly becoming the talk of Tinseltown and one of the most-watched couples in the entertainment arena. Their high-profile relationship ended in 2002. The “Baby One More Time” singer recalls Timberlake’s reaction to her pregnancy, sharing he “definitely wasn’t happy about the pregnancy.” Spears adds, “He said we weren’t ready to have a baby in our lives, that we were way too young.” The heartbreak and emotional turmoil from the abortion are evident in her words, as she describes it as “one of the most agonizing things I have ever experienced in my life.” Britney’s memoir doesn’t stop at her relationship with Timberlake. She dives deep into the controversial conservatorship that dominated her life for 14 years. Under this legal guardianship, she felt her autonomy stripped away. Spears recalls the conservatorship’s control over even her reproductive rights, sharing that she was prevented from removing a contraceptive IUD despite wanting another child. “The conservatorship stripped me of my womanhood, made me into a child,” Spears remarks. Reflecting on the extended period of control her father and his associates had over her personal and financial affairs, Spears writes, “I think back now… and it makes me feel sick.” The pop sensation’s memoir is also expected to touch upon her personal life after Timberlake. Spears had two sons with her second husband, Kevin Federline. Following a very public breakdown in 2008, Spears entered into the previously mentioned conservatorship led by her father, Jamie. Fortunately, this conservatorship came to an end in November 2021. However, life hasn’t been entirely rosy for the star since. In 2022, she announced a miscarriage and later, in August, her third husband, Sam Asghari, stated they were filing for divorce. “The Woman in Me” promises to be a compelling read, providing fans with an unfiltered look into the life of a pop music legend.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump Takes the Lead Over Biden: CNBC Economic Survey Results</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/19/Trump-Biden-Israel-Survey/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump Takes the Lead Over Biden: CNBC Economic Survey Results" /><published>2023-10-19T11:45:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-19T11:45:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/19/Trump-Biden-Israel-Survey</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/19/Trump-Biden-Israel-Survey/">&lt;p&gt;Recent findings from CNBC’s All-America Economic Survey reveal that if elections were held today, former President Donald Trump would edge out current President Joe Biden by a margin of 4%. The poll, which took place between October 11th and 15th, paints a detailed picture of Americans’ political and economic sentiments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Biden’s approval ratings have seen a downturn, with only 37% of Americans showing approval and 58% expressing disapproval. This marks a concerning period for the Biden administration, having the second-lowest approval and second-highest disapproval during his tenure. Particularly concerning for Biden is his approval rating on economic matters, which stands at a mere 32% against a 63% disapproval.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, amidst the political tussles, a notable highlight from the survey is the strong American support for Israel. In the aftermath of recent attacks by Hamas on Israel, a whopping 74% of respondents believed it’s crucial for the U.S. to continue providing military aid to Israel. This backing for Israel’s military assistance surpasses support for several other key issues, including securing the U.S.-Mexico border, foreign humanitarian aid at 72%, and military assistance to Ukraine at 61%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moreover, Biden’s swift show of support for Israel and promises of additional aid during the conflict did not earn him much favor. Only 31% approved of his handling of foreign policy, and a significant 60% disapproved. Interestingly, this decline isn’t limited to the opposition. Within the Democratic party, Biden’s foreign policy decisions are approved by just 66% of members, and 74% support his economic strategy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The survey also highlights the polarization in the American political landscape. Regarding the Israel-Hamas conflict, 57% of Republicans lean toward supporting Israelis, in contrast to 29% of Democrats and 27% of independents. Meanwhile, a significant chunk of Democrats (44%) and independents (47%) favor a balanced stance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An intriguing insight from this study is a shift in sentiment when comparing current data with a 2014 survey. Older Americans, especially those above 35, are now more in favor of supporting Israel than before. Young Americans, aged 18 to 34, seem more inclined towards a neutral stance, with 46% believing both sides in the Israel-Hamas conflict should be treated equally.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In terms of government funding priorities, the survey indicated clear party-line preferences. Republicans and independents showed a leaning towards securing the U.S.-Mexico border and then military funding for Israel. Democrats, however, placed military aid for Ukraine and foreign humanitarian aid at the top of their list.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This CNBC survey, with a sample size of 1,001 Americans, provides a comprehensive understanding of the current American political mood and is crucial as we approach future elections.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Recent findings from CNBC’s All-America Economic Survey reveal that if elections were held today, former President Donald Trump would edge out current President Joe Biden by a margin of 4%. The poll, which took place between October 11th and 15th, paints a detailed picture of Americans’ political and economic sentiments. Biden’s approval ratings have seen a downturn, with only 37% of Americans showing approval and 58% expressing disapproval. This marks a concerning period for the Biden administration, having the second-lowest approval and second-highest disapproval during his tenure. Particularly concerning for Biden is his approval rating on economic matters, which stands at a mere 32% against a 63% disapproval. However, amidst the political tussles, a notable highlight from the survey is the strong American support for Israel. In the aftermath of recent attacks by Hamas on Israel, a whopping 74% of respondents believed it’s crucial for the U.S. to continue providing military aid to Israel. This backing for Israel’s military assistance surpasses support for several other key issues, including securing the U.S.-Mexico border, foreign humanitarian aid at 72%, and military assistance to Ukraine at 61%. Moreover, Biden’s swift show of support for Israel and promises of additional aid during the conflict did not earn him much favor. Only 31% approved of his handling of foreign policy, and a significant 60% disapproved. Interestingly, this decline isn’t limited to the opposition. Within the Democratic party, Biden’s foreign policy decisions are approved by just 66% of members, and 74% support his economic strategy. The survey also highlights the polarization in the American political landscape. Regarding the Israel-Hamas conflict, 57% of Republicans lean toward supporting Israelis, in contrast to 29% of Democrats and 27% of independents. Meanwhile, a significant chunk of Democrats (44%) and independents (47%) favor a balanced stance. An intriguing insight from this study is a shift in sentiment when comparing current data with a 2014 survey. Older Americans, especially those above 35, are now more in favor of supporting Israel than before. Young Americans, aged 18 to 34, seem more inclined towards a neutral stance, with 46% believing both sides in the Israel-Hamas conflict should be treated equally. In terms of government funding priorities, the survey indicated clear party-line preferences. Republicans and independents showed a leaning towards securing the U.S.-Mexico border and then military funding for Israel. Democrats, however, placed military aid for Ukraine and foreign humanitarian aid at the top of their list. This CNBC survey, with a sample size of 1,001 Americans, provides a comprehensive understanding of the current American political mood and is crucial as we approach future elections.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">San Diego’s Streets Full of Prostitutes: The Unintended Consequences of SB 357</title><link href="/news/2023/10/19/San-Diego-Prostitution-Uproar/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="San Diego’s Streets Full of Prostitutes: The Unintended Consequences of SB 357" /><published>2023-10-19T10:31:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-19T10:31:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/19/San-Diego-Prostitution-Uproar</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/19/San-Diego-Prostitution-Uproar/">&lt;p&gt;San Diego is currently grappling with a sharp rise in street prostitution, a disturbing trend following the recent implementation of California’s controversial Senate Bill 357. This law, signed by California Gov. Gavin Newsom in July 2022, repealed an earlier law banning loitering with the intent of engaging in prostitution. Its primary aim was to protect transgender women and other vulnerable communities from targeted police harassment. However, it seems the bill may have led to some unintended consequences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Local businesses have borne the brunt of this uptick in overt prostitution activities. Additional security measures have been implemented, with many installing lights to deter unwanted attention. Ironically, prostitutes are now using these very lights to attract customers. A long-time San Diego business owner lamented to Fox News Digital, “Costs for business, costs for security. We’ve had to put lights — at our cost — on the roof…the lights now help them when they want to come in front of my building to shake and do different things.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Crime related to the prostitution surge is also on the rise. Many business owners have reported break-ins, tire slashing, and thefts, which they believe to be retaliation acts by pimps or prostitutes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the center of the issue is the “Safer Streets Act” (Senate Bill 357). The law was designed to prevent the disproportionate harassment of Black and brown women and members of the LGBTQ community. While it doesn’t legalize prostitution, it eliminates provisions that led to the said harassment. Nevertheless, its implementation has led to significant challenges for San Diego’s streets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since the law took effect in January, many argue that it has empowered prostitutes and pimps, giving them the freedom to openly solicit customers without fear of legal repercussions. This visibility has caused discomfort for many residents, especially parents who must now explain to their young children the sight of near-naked women attempting to flag down vehicles during morning school commutes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the increasing issues, many feel that local politicians are not addressing the problem adequately. The business owner shared that no one from the city council’s office has reached out to understand the gravity of the situation or discuss potential solutions. The business owner added, “I have yet to have anybody from the local city council’s office contact anybody here in the neighborhood, come by, try to say, ‘Hey, we’re trying to help. How can we put some resources in like maybe some additional lights, maybe some additional cameras?’”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the mayor’s office maintains that efforts are being made to tackle the problem. Mayor Gloria, who has spoken publicly about the issue, emphasized the police department’s sting operations, which led to numerous arrests earlier this year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the challenges posed by SB 357 becoming increasingly evident, many hope for its repeal or at least a revisitation to address its shortcomings. As San Diego struggles, the need for a proactive approach becomes ever more critical to restore peace and security to its streets.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">San Diego is currently grappling with a sharp rise in street prostitution, a disturbing trend following the recent implementation of California’s controversial Senate Bill 357. This law, signed by California Gov. Gavin Newsom in July 2022, repealed an earlier law banning loitering with the intent of engaging in prostitution. Its primary aim was to protect transgender women and other vulnerable communities from targeted police harassment. However, it seems the bill may have led to some unintended consequences. Local businesses have borne the brunt of this uptick in overt prostitution activities. Additional security measures have been implemented, with many installing lights to deter unwanted attention. Ironically, prostitutes are now using these very lights to attract customers. A long-time San Diego business owner lamented to Fox News Digital, “Costs for business, costs for security. We’ve had to put lights — at our cost — on the roof…the lights now help them when they want to come in front of my building to shake and do different things.” Crime related to the prostitution surge is also on the rise. Many business owners have reported break-ins, tire slashing, and thefts, which they believe to be retaliation acts by pimps or prostitutes. At the center of the issue is the “Safer Streets Act” (Senate Bill 357). The law was designed to prevent the disproportionate harassment of Black and brown women and members of the LGBTQ community. While it doesn’t legalize prostitution, it eliminates provisions that led to the said harassment. Nevertheless, its implementation has led to significant challenges for San Diego’s streets. Since the law took effect in January, many argue that it has empowered prostitutes and pimps, giving them the freedom to openly solicit customers without fear of legal repercussions. This visibility has caused discomfort for many residents, especially parents who must now explain to their young children the sight of near-naked women attempting to flag down vehicles during morning school commutes. Despite the increasing issues, many feel that local politicians are not addressing the problem adequately. The business owner shared that no one from the city council’s office has reached out to understand the gravity of the situation or discuss potential solutions. The business owner added, “I have yet to have anybody from the local city council’s office contact anybody here in the neighborhood, come by, try to say, ‘Hey, we’re trying to help. How can we put some resources in like maybe some additional lights, maybe some additional cameras?’” However, the mayor’s office maintains that efforts are being made to tackle the problem. Mayor Gloria, who has spoken publicly about the issue, emphasized the police department’s sting operations, which led to numerous arrests earlier this year. With the challenges posed by SB 357 becoming increasingly evident, many hope for its repeal or at least a revisitation to address its shortcomings. As San Diego struggles, the need for a proactive approach becomes ever more critical to restore peace and security to its streets.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Dramatic Interruption: Woman Approaches Trump During Trial</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/19/Trump-Trial-Interruption/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dramatic Interruption: Woman Approaches Trump During Trial" /><published>2023-10-19T09:24:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-19T09:24:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/19/Trump-Trial-Interruption</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/19/Trump-Trial-Interruption/">&lt;p&gt;A startling scene unfolded at Donald Trump’s civil trial on Wednesday, as a court system employee caused an uproar by attempting to approach the former president during a testimony.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This unprecedented incident saw the woman rise from her seat and stride towards the area where Trump sat. Expressing a will to assist Trump, her actions raised concerns, albeit momentarily. The court assured that the safety of Trump and others present was never compromised. Lucian Chalfen, a court spokesperson, clarified that she faced arrest due to contempt for disrupting the proceedings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, Trump seemed unaware of the event, later querying reporters, “Who got arrested? We didn’t know anything about it.” This detachment indicates the intense focus on the allegations made against him by &lt;strong&gt;New York Attorney General Letitia James&lt;/strong&gt;. Trump is accused of misleading banks and insurers through exaggerated statements of his net worth and asset values.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The court employee, upon being apprehended, voiced her distress outside the courtroom. She expressed her rights as an American citizen and as a court employee, emphasizing her presence to support Trump. The woman, however, complied with court officers’ directions and insisted she had been observing the proceedings peacefully. Following the incident, she has been barred from state courts during the ongoing investigations and placed on administrative leave.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the trial resumed, another unusual instance surfaced. Trump displayed apparent frustration, leading to animated discussions with his attorneys. This drew the court’s attention, with Judge Arthur Engoron emphasizing decorum and cautioning against potential attempts to influence testimonies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amidst these episodes, the core issue remains — the allegations against Trump and his company for defrauding banks and insurers. Evidence presented at the trial indicates that financial statements were pivotal for Trump in securing deals and loans. For instance, a 2015 refinancing offer required the delivery of Trump’s financial statements and tax returns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The defense sought to challenge claims that Trump’s top corporate deputies inflated property values. An intense exchange occurred as Trump’s lawyer Lazaro Fields questioned real estate appraiser Doug Larson about a projected valuation discrepancy. The trial’s intensity, marked by such heated exchanges, underscores the gravity of the allegations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Throughout, Trump maintains his innocence, asserting that his assets were undervalued and that provided numbers came with disclaimers. Trump has consistently labeled the trial as a political move to hinder his potential return to the White House.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the trial continues, episodes like the woman’s interruption and Trump’s animated gestures add layers of intrigue to an already riveting case. Whatever the outcome, this trial, with its blend of political, legal, and human drama, will undoubtedly leave an imprint on American history.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">A startling scene unfolded at Donald Trump’s civil trial on Wednesday, as a court system employee caused an uproar by attempting to approach the former president during a testimony. This unprecedented incident saw the woman rise from her seat and stride towards the area where Trump sat. Expressing a will to assist Trump, her actions raised concerns, albeit momentarily. The court assured that the safety of Trump and others present was never compromised. Lucian Chalfen, a court spokesperson, clarified that she faced arrest due to contempt for disrupting the proceedings. Interestingly, Trump seemed unaware of the event, later querying reporters, “Who got arrested? We didn’t know anything about it.” This detachment indicates the intense focus on the allegations made against him by New York Attorney General Letitia James. Trump is accused of misleading banks and insurers through exaggerated statements of his net worth and asset values. The court employee, upon being apprehended, voiced her distress outside the courtroom. She expressed her rights as an American citizen and as a court employee, emphasizing her presence to support Trump. The woman, however, complied with court officers’ directions and insisted she had been observing the proceedings peacefully. Following the incident, she has been barred from state courts during the ongoing investigations and placed on administrative leave. As the trial resumed, another unusual instance surfaced. Trump displayed apparent frustration, leading to animated discussions with his attorneys. This drew the court’s attention, with Judge Arthur Engoron emphasizing decorum and cautioning against potential attempts to influence testimonies. Amidst these episodes, the core issue remains — the allegations against Trump and his company for defrauding banks and insurers. Evidence presented at the trial indicates that financial statements were pivotal for Trump in securing deals and loans. For instance, a 2015 refinancing offer required the delivery of Trump’s financial statements and tax returns. The defense sought to challenge claims that Trump’s top corporate deputies inflated property values. An intense exchange occurred as Trump’s lawyer Lazaro Fields questioned real estate appraiser Doug Larson about a projected valuation discrepancy. The trial’s intensity, marked by such heated exchanges, underscores the gravity of the allegations. Throughout, Trump maintains his innocence, asserting that his assets were undervalued and that provided numbers came with disclaimers. Trump has consistently labeled the trial as a political move to hinder his potential return to the White House. While the trial continues, episodes like the woman’s interruption and Trump’s animated gestures add layers of intrigue to an already riveting case. Whatever the outcome, this trial, with its blend of political, legal, and human drama, will undoubtedly leave an imprint on American history.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Quentin Tarantino Surprises IDF Soldiers with Morale-Boosting Visit</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/19/Tarantino-Israel-Visit/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Quentin Tarantino Surprises IDF Soldiers with Morale-Boosting Visit" /><published>2023-10-19T08:12:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-19T08:12:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/19/Tarantino-Israel-Visit</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/19/Tarantino-Israel-Visit/">&lt;p&gt;In an unexpected gesture of support, esteemed film director Quentin Tarantino made an appearance at an Israeli military base last Friday. His visit aimed to uplift spirits and provide a morale boost to the soldiers of the Israeli Defense Forces (IDF) after they faced severe terror attacks in southern Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Photos capturing the iconic &lt;em&gt;Reservoir Dogs&lt;/em&gt; director’s visit showcased Tarantino in earnest discussions with the troops. One standout image featured him posing with IDF members against the backdrop of a military helicopter. These photographs quickly circulated on the Israel War Room X Twitter account. The post acknowledged, “Legendary filmmaker Quentin Tarantino visits an Israeli base in southern Israel to boost IDF morale.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A non-profit group, &lt;em&gt;Stand With Us&lt;/em&gt;, also shared insights from the visit on their Instagram page. The post praised Tarantino’s significant gesture, stating, “Legendary filmmaker Quentin Tarantino showed his solidarity with the Israeli people by making a surprise visit to southern Israel, affected gravely by Hamas’ continuous terror war. Interacting with both soldiers and locals, he kindled a social media storm filled with selfies and videos, symbolizing his heartfelt support.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tarantino, known for his masterpieces in cinema, has a deep personal connection to Israel. He resides in Tel Aviv with his wife, the Israeli singer Daniella Pick The couple tied the knot in 2018 after their first meeting in Israel back in 2009. Tarantino’s love for the country and its people is evident in his words, “I love the country, and the people are really nice, very nice to me, and they seem excited that I’m here.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The director had planned to divide his time between Israel and Los Angeles. However, the global pandemic led him to stay put in Tel Aviv since 2019. In 2021, Tarantino even experienced the threat of a Hamas rocket attack. On a lighter note, after this experience, his Israeli friends humorously claimed that he was now an “official Israeli.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Quentin Tarantino’s recent visit underscores the power of solidarity and support in challenging times. It serves as a testament to how influential figures in the entertainment world can bridge divides and stand by communities during adversities.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">In an unexpected gesture of support, esteemed film director Quentin Tarantino made an appearance at an Israeli military base last Friday. His visit aimed to uplift spirits and provide a morale boost to the soldiers of the Israeli Defense Forces (IDF) after they faced severe terror attacks in southern Israel. Photos capturing the iconic Reservoir Dogs director’s visit showcased Tarantino in earnest discussions with the troops. One standout image featured him posing with IDF members against the backdrop of a military helicopter. These photographs quickly circulated on the Israel War Room X Twitter account. The post acknowledged, “Legendary filmmaker Quentin Tarantino visits an Israeli base in southern Israel to boost IDF morale.” A non-profit group, Stand With Us, also shared insights from the visit on their Instagram page. The post praised Tarantino’s significant gesture, stating, “Legendary filmmaker Quentin Tarantino showed his solidarity with the Israeli people by making a surprise visit to southern Israel, affected gravely by Hamas’ continuous terror war. Interacting with both soldiers and locals, he kindled a social media storm filled with selfies and videos, symbolizing his heartfelt support.” Tarantino, known for his masterpieces in cinema, has a deep personal connection to Israel. He resides in Tel Aviv with his wife, the Israeli singer Daniella Pick The couple tied the knot in 2018 after their first meeting in Israel back in 2009. Tarantino’s love for the country and its people is evident in his words, “I love the country, and the people are really nice, very nice to me, and they seem excited that I’m here.” The director had planned to divide his time between Israel and Los Angeles. However, the global pandemic led him to stay put in Tel Aviv since 2019. In 2021, Tarantino even experienced the threat of a Hamas rocket attack. On a lighter note, after this experience, his Israeli friends humorously claimed that he was now an “official Israeli.” Quentin Tarantino’s recent visit underscores the power of solidarity and support in challenging times. It serves as a testament to how influential figures in the entertainment world can bridge divides and stand by communities during adversities.</summary></entry></feed>