<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-09-22T21:05:36-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/09/22/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-09-22T21:05:36-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-22T21:05:36-04:00</updated><id>/2023/09/22/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/22/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Dress Code Debacle - Joe Manchin Disagrees with Schumer on Senate Attire</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/22/Dress-Code-Controversy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dress Code Debacle - Joe Manchin Disagrees with Schumer on Senate Attire" /><published>2023-09-22T17:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-22T17:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/22/Dress-Code-Controversy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/22/Dress-Code-Controversy/">&lt;p&gt;Sen. Joe Manchin (D-WV) is reportedly on a mission to reinstate the traditional Senate dress code, a policy recently relaxed by Senate Majority Leader Chuck Schumer (D-NY). This development suggests a rising disagreement within the party lines over the decorum of the Senate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;return-to-formality&quot;&gt;Return to Formality?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Manchin is believed to be circulating a proposal to restore the formal dress code, requiring Senators to don business attire on the Senate floor. This push comes in direct contrast to Schumer’s recent pronouncement, allowing Senators to choose their preferred dress while on the Senate floor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;fettermans-fashion-statement&quot;&gt;Fetterman’s Fashion Statement&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sen. John Fetterman (D-PA) is particularly noticeable under the new dress code, appearing in sweatshirts and shorts in the Capitol. His unconventional attire, in alignment with his “blue-collar tough guy” persona, contrasts sharply with his Harvard education and seemingly affluent background. His attire has sparked conversations on authenticity, with many questioning the sincerity behind his average joe portrayal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;voices-in-opposition&quot;&gt;Voices in Opposition&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many Republicans and even some Democrats seem to support the return to a more formal dress code. They argue that maintaining a degree of formality and dignity is crucial to uphold the reputation of the Senate. Sen. Tommy Tuberville expressed his displeasure with the relaxed dress code, emphasizing his discontent with the casual attires. Similarly, Sen. Susan Collins believes that maintaining a formal dress code is integral to preserving the dignity of the Senate institution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-reflection-of-a-deeper-issue&quot;&gt;A Reflection of a Deeper Issue?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This dispute over dress code may reflect deeper tensions within the Senate, touching on notions of decorum, respect, and the image senators wish to project. While some view the relaxed dress code as a degradation of Senate traditions, others may see it as a step towards modernization and authenticity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this scenario, Manchin’s move to restore formal attire could be interpreted as a pursuit to maintain the sanctity and the revered image of the Senate. Whether his proposal will gain enough traction remains to be seen, but it certainly highlights the differing perspectives within the Senate on maintaining tradition versus embracing change.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Sen. Joe Manchin (D-WV) is reportedly on a mission to reinstate the traditional Senate dress code, a policy recently relaxed by Senate Majority Leader Chuck Schumer (D-NY). This development suggests a rising disagreement within the party lines over the decorum of the Senate. Return to Formality? Manchin is believed to be circulating a proposal to restore the formal dress code, requiring Senators to don business attire on the Senate floor. This push comes in direct contrast to Schumer’s recent pronouncement, allowing Senators to choose their preferred dress while on the Senate floor. Fetterman’s Fashion Statement Sen. John Fetterman (D-PA) is particularly noticeable under the new dress code, appearing in sweatshirts and shorts in the Capitol. His unconventional attire, in alignment with his “blue-collar tough guy” persona, contrasts sharply with his Harvard education and seemingly affluent background. His attire has sparked conversations on authenticity, with many questioning the sincerity behind his average joe portrayal. Voices in Opposition Many Republicans and even some Democrats seem to support the return to a more formal dress code. They argue that maintaining a degree of formality and dignity is crucial to uphold the reputation of the Senate. Sen. Tommy Tuberville expressed his displeasure with the relaxed dress code, emphasizing his discontent with the casual attires. Similarly, Sen. Susan Collins believes that maintaining a formal dress code is integral to preserving the dignity of the Senate institution. A Reflection of a Deeper Issue? This dispute over dress code may reflect deeper tensions within the Senate, touching on notions of decorum, respect, and the image senators wish to project. While some view the relaxed dress code as a degradation of Senate traditions, others may see it as a step towards modernization and authenticity. In this scenario, Manchin’s move to restore formal attire could be interpreted as a pursuit to maintain the sanctity and the revered image of the Senate. Whether his proposal will gain enough traction remains to be seen, but it certainly highlights the differing perspectives within the Senate on maintaining tradition versus embracing change.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A Cry for Freedom - Ben Carson Warns Against Repeat of COVID Controls</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/22/COVID-Mandates-Carson/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Cry for Freedom - Ben Carson Warns Against Repeat of COVID Controls" /><published>2023-09-22T16:18:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-22T16:18:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/22/COVID-Mandates-Carson</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/22/COVID-Mandates-Carson/">&lt;p&gt;Ben Carson, the former Secretary of Housing and Urban Development, raises the alarm on what he perceives as attempts by the U.S. government to control the American populace through mandates related to COVID-19. In a discussion on Newsmax’s “American Agenda,” he voiced concerns over the significant influence and control exercised by the authorities during the pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-impact-on-education&quot;&gt;The Impact on Education&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Carson criticized the sweeping measures, such as school shutdowns, arguing they have had severe and long-lasting impacts on the learning and development of children. He believes it could take years, if not decades, for the educational setbacks experienced during the pandemic to be reversed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;allegations-of-manipulation&quot;&gt;Allegations of Manipulation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The former HUD Secretary accuses the government of not prioritizing the welfare of the citizens and focusing instead on controlling and manipulating people. He fears the grave implications if such practices continue and calls for a critical examination of the repercussions of the mandates imposed during the pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;funding-for-at-home-covid-tests&quot;&gt;Funding for At-Home COVID Tests&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In response to the Biden administration’s recent announcement of a $600 million funding to produce new at-home COVID-19 tests, Carson emphasized the importance of not succumbing to fear and manipulation. This funding initiative is aimed at averting possible shortages during an anticipated rise in coronavirus cases during the colder months and resolving supply chain issues experienced during past surges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;carsons-clarion-call&quot;&gt;Carson’s Clarion Call&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Carson’s strong message to the American people is to not be “manipulated and terrified by COVID.” He urges rationality and an understanding of the facts surrounding the virus, such as its evolving, typically weaker variants. He warns against unnecessary fear due to increased positive test results and calls for resistance against any attempts to impose further business and school shutdowns which could lead to economic distress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;we-the-people&quot;&gt;We, The People&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, Carson’s plea is for vigilance and a unified stance by the people against government overreach and control. He emphasizes that it is the collective responsibility of the citizens to assert their rights and safeguard their freedoms against any perceived attempts to disrupt lives and livelihoods under the guise of public health measures. He argues that a repeat of the stringent controls and mandates witnessed during the pandemic could have devastating and lasting impacts on the society and economy, making it imperative for the people to be informed, rational, and resolute in their response.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Ben Carson, the former Secretary of Housing and Urban Development, raises the alarm on what he perceives as attempts by the U.S. government to control the American populace through mandates related to COVID-19. In a discussion on Newsmax’s “American Agenda,” he voiced concerns over the significant influence and control exercised by the authorities during the pandemic. The Impact on Education Carson criticized the sweeping measures, such as school shutdowns, arguing they have had severe and long-lasting impacts on the learning and development of children. He believes it could take years, if not decades, for the educational setbacks experienced during the pandemic to be reversed. Allegations of Manipulation The former HUD Secretary accuses the government of not prioritizing the welfare of the citizens and focusing instead on controlling and manipulating people. He fears the grave implications if such practices continue and calls for a critical examination of the repercussions of the mandates imposed during the pandemic. Funding for At-Home COVID Tests In response to the Biden administration’s recent announcement of a $600 million funding to produce new at-home COVID-19 tests, Carson emphasized the importance of not succumbing to fear and manipulation. This funding initiative is aimed at averting possible shortages during an anticipated rise in coronavirus cases during the colder months and resolving supply chain issues experienced during past surges. Carson’s Clarion Call Carson’s strong message to the American people is to not be “manipulated and terrified by COVID.” He urges rationality and an understanding of the facts surrounding the virus, such as its evolving, typically weaker variants. He warns against unnecessary fear due to increased positive test results and calls for resistance against any attempts to impose further business and school shutdowns which could lead to economic distress. We, The People In conclusion, Carson’s plea is for vigilance and a unified stance by the people against government overreach and control. He emphasizes that it is the collective responsibility of the citizens to assert their rights and safeguard their freedoms against any perceived attempts to disrupt lives and livelihoods under the guise of public health measures. He argues that a repeat of the stringent controls and mandates witnessed during the pandemic could have devastating and lasting impacts on the society and economy, making it imperative for the people to be informed, rational, and resolute in their response.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Standoff at Capitol Hill - Trump Provokes GOP to Use Shutdown as Leverage</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/22/Trump-Government-Shutdown/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Standoff at Capitol Hill - Trump Provokes GOP to Use Shutdown as Leverage" /><published>2023-09-22T15:08:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-22T15:08:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/22/Trump-Government-Shutdown</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/22/Trump-Government-Shutdown/">&lt;p&gt;With the tides of politics swirling, former President Donald Trump steps into the current fray, encouraging the Republican party to use potential government shutdowns as leverage against the policies of the current administration led by President Joe Biden. This confrontation is bringing to light the battle lines drawn within the GOP, as House Speaker Kevin McCarthy faces internal opposition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;fiscal-stalemate&quot;&gt;Fiscal Stalemate&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The internal strife within the GOP is marked by fiscal debates, as conservative demands for individual appropriation bills clash with the broader party agenda. Trump’s recent involvement in this dispute emphasizes his enduring influence within the party, as he urges Republicans to “defund all aspects” of what he calls a “weaponized Government” under Biden.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;trumps-rallying-cry&quot;&gt;Trump’s Rallying Cry&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a recent post on Truth Social, Trump argued that the Republicans “can and must” obstruct Biden’s policies, depicting the current administration as hostile and accusing it of treating “half the Country as Enemies of the State.” Trump insists this is the opportune moment for Republicans to retaliate against what he perceives as political prosecutions aimed at him and other conservatives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;pressure-on-mccarthy&quot;&gt;Pressure on McCarthy&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The GOP’s internal discord is heightened by figures like Rep. Matt Gaetz, a known critic of McCarthy, who echoes Trump’s calls for Republicans to hold firm against the continuing resolution (C.R.) to maintain government funding at existing levels. This presents an additional challenge to McCarthy’s attempts at holding together differing factions within the party, amidst growing pressure and opposition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-wall-the-shutdown-and-the-aftermath&quot;&gt;The Wall, The Shutdown, and The Aftermath&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reminders of the longest government shutdown in history, stretching over Christmas break from December 2018 to January 2019 under Trump’s administration, hang heavily over these debates. The protracted battle then was over Trump’s sought-after border wall funding, which the Republicans struggled to secure against Democratic opposition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-bipartisan-struggle&quot;&gt;The Bipartisan Struggle&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To avoid another government shutdown on Oct. 1, both the House and the Democrat-led Senate need to converge on spending legislation acceptable to President Biden. However, Republican plans are meeting substantial resistance from Senate Democrats and the White House. Conservative Republicans are demanding a stringent fiscal approach, with appropriations not exceeding a&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">With the tides of politics swirling, former President Donald Trump steps into the current fray, encouraging the Republican party to use potential government shutdowns as leverage against the policies of the current administration led by President Joe Biden. This confrontation is bringing to light the battle lines drawn within the GOP, as House Speaker Kevin McCarthy faces internal opposition. Fiscal Stalemate The internal strife within the GOP is marked by fiscal debates, as conservative demands for individual appropriation bills clash with the broader party agenda. Trump’s recent involvement in this dispute emphasizes his enduring influence within the party, as he urges Republicans to “defund all aspects” of what he calls a “weaponized Government” under Biden. Trump’s Rallying Cry In a recent post on Truth Social, Trump argued that the Republicans “can and must” obstruct Biden’s policies, depicting the current administration as hostile and accusing it of treating “half the Country as Enemies of the State.” Trump insists this is the opportune moment for Republicans to retaliate against what he perceives as political prosecutions aimed at him and other conservatives. Pressure on McCarthy The GOP’s internal discord is heightened by figures like Rep. Matt Gaetz, a known critic of McCarthy, who echoes Trump’s calls for Republicans to hold firm against the continuing resolution (C.R.) to maintain government funding at existing levels. This presents an additional challenge to McCarthy’s attempts at holding together differing factions within the party, amidst growing pressure and opposition. The Wall, The Shutdown, and The Aftermath Reminders of the longest government shutdown in history, stretching over Christmas break from December 2018 to January 2019 under Trump’s administration, hang heavily over these debates. The protracted battle then was over Trump’s sought-after border wall funding, which the Republicans struggled to secure against Democratic opposition. The Bipartisan Struggle To avoid another government shutdown on Oct. 1, both the House and the Democrat-led Senate need to converge on spending legislation acceptable to President Biden. However, Republican plans are meeting substantial resistance from Senate Democrats and the White House. Conservative Republicans are demanding a stringent fiscal approach, with appropriations not exceeding a</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Unlocking Nature’s Secrets - AI Bridges Communication Gap Between Humans and Animals!</title><link href="/news/2023/09/22/Talking-To-Animals/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Unlocking Nature’s Secrets - AI Bridges Communication Gap Between Humans and Animals!" /><published>2023-09-22T14:06:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-22T14:06:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/22/Talking-To-Animals</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/22/Talking-To-Animals/">&lt;p&gt;The fascinating prospect of communicating with animals has been a tantalizing fantasy, filling the pages of countless science fiction stories and movies. Now, it seems this fantasy is on the brink of becoming a reality, as scientific innovations and Artificial Intelligence (AI) are forging paths to decode the languages of our fellow earthlings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-whisper-to-the-whales-a-chirp-to-the-birds&quot;&gt;A Whisper to the Whales, A Chirp to the Birds&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Imagine understanding the sophisticated clicks of sperm whales or the varied chirps of birds! Researchers are using advanced AI to interpret and translate the communications of various animals, ranging from the familiar barks of dogs to the enchanting songs of whales.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aza Raskin, co-founder of the Earth Species Project, believes that we are nearing a time when having “conversations” with animals will be feasible. He envisions a future where understanding expressions of ‘grief’, ‘mother’, or ‘hunger’ will be common across different species.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;beyond-barks-and-tweets&quot;&gt;Beyond Barks and Tweets&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s not just about the sounds; researchers are delving deeper, aiming to interpret expressions, postures, and other forms of communication. Dr. Con Slobodchikoff, an animal language researcher, is working on models that translate not just the barks of dogs but also their facial expressions, giving pet owners a clearer understanding of what their furry companions are trying to convey.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The endeavors are not restricted to our traditional pets. Shane Gero, the lead biologist for Project CETI, is employing AI to decipher the intricate patterns of sperm whale sounds, with the hopeful outcome of creating a “whale chatbot.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;bridging-the-great-divide&quot;&gt;Bridging the Great Divide&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This revolutionary research is about more than mere translation; it’s about bridging the great communication divide between humans and the rest of the animal kingdom. The Cornell Lab of Ornithology has developed a tool capable of distinguishing the sounds of over a thousand bird species, and AI-generated bird calls are being tested on zebra finches by the Earth Species Project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;towards-a-mutual-understanding&quot;&gt;Towards a Mutual Understanding&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This cutting-edge research is poised to redefine our relationship with the animal world, leading us into an era of mutual respect and understanding. It unveils the potential for an enriched coexistence and a deeper appreciation of the myriad forms of life sharing this planet with us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Who knows what wonders and knowledge we may uncover as we venture into uncharted territories of interspecies communication, taking us a step closer to harmonious living with all creatures great and small!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">The fascinating prospect of communicating with animals has been a tantalizing fantasy, filling the pages of countless science fiction stories and movies. Now, it seems this fantasy is on the brink of becoming a reality, as scientific innovations and Artificial Intelligence (AI) are forging paths to decode the languages of our fellow earthlings. A Whisper to the Whales, A Chirp to the Birds Imagine understanding the sophisticated clicks of sperm whales or the varied chirps of birds! Researchers are using advanced AI to interpret and translate the communications of various animals, ranging from the familiar barks of dogs to the enchanting songs of whales. Aza Raskin, co-founder of the Earth Species Project, believes that we are nearing a time when having “conversations” with animals will be feasible. He envisions a future where understanding expressions of ‘grief’, ‘mother’, or ‘hunger’ will be common across different species. Beyond Barks and Tweets It’s not just about the sounds; researchers are delving deeper, aiming to interpret expressions, postures, and other forms of communication. Dr. Con Slobodchikoff, an animal language researcher, is working on models that translate not just the barks of dogs but also their facial expressions, giving pet owners a clearer understanding of what their furry companions are trying to convey. The endeavors are not restricted to our traditional pets. Shane Gero, the lead biologist for Project CETI, is employing AI to decipher the intricate patterns of sperm whale sounds, with the hopeful outcome of creating a “whale chatbot.” Bridging the Great Divide This revolutionary research is about more than mere translation; it’s about bridging the great communication divide between humans and the rest of the animal kingdom. The Cornell Lab of Ornithology has developed a tool capable of distinguishing the sounds of over a thousand bird species, and AI-generated bird calls are being tested on zebra finches by the Earth Species Project. Towards a Mutual Understanding This cutting-edge research is poised to redefine our relationship with the animal world, leading us into an era of mutual respect and understanding. It unveils the potential for an enriched coexistence and a deeper appreciation of the myriad forms of life sharing this planet with us. Who knows what wonders and knowledge we may uncover as we venture into uncharted territories of interspecies communication, taking us a step closer to harmonious living with all creatures great and small!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Bravery in Action - Good Guy with a Gun Stops Robbery in Its Tracks!</title><link href="/news/2023/09/22/Good-Guy-With-Gun/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bravery in Action - Good Guy with a Gun Stops Robbery in Its Tracks!" /><published>2023-09-22T13:17:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-22T13:17:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/22/Good-Guy-With-Gun</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/22/Good-Guy-With-Gun/">&lt;p&gt;In the face of increasing unrest and criminal activity, stories of valor and righteous intervention are more important than ever. Such a tale unfolded in Ft. Lauderdale, Florida, where an ordinary citizen, armed and vigilant, intervened in a potentially fatal situation, safeguarding a store clerk from the clutches of armed robbers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-robbery-gone-awry&quot;&gt;A Robbery Gone Awry&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nicolas Richard Lee Deas and another man allegedly entered a Family Dollar store under the pretense of retrieving a forgotten cellphone. Once inside, they revealed their true colors, threatening the employee and demanding money, eventually making away with $1,200 from the safe and assaulting the employee in the process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-beacon-of-courage&quot;&gt;A Beacon of Courage&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Little did the robbers know, a store owner nearby had noticed the disturbance and bravely decided to confront the situation. He walked into a volatile scenario and, demonstrating quick thinking and courage, drew his firearm, commanding Deas to drop his weapon and surrender. The second suspect chose discretion over valor and hastily departed the scene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-hands-of-justice&quot;&gt;The Hands of Justice&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The armed Good Samaritan diligently held his ground until law enforcement arrived, leading to Deas’ arrest on multiple charges, including armed robbery and aggravated assault. The weapon Deas used was identified as stolen. The second suspect remains unidentified and at large.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-light-in-the-darkness&quot;&gt;A Light in the Darkness&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This episode is a shining example of how everyday bravery and a moral compass can bring light to the shadows cast by violence and deceit in today’s world. This unnamed hero made the decision to confront danger head-on, embodying the essence of true heroism and civic duty. Such acts of benevolence and courage deserve our recognition and respect, as they guide us towards a path of solidarity and virtue in a world often overshadowed by turmoil and malevolence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a world where malevolence often overshadows goodness, it is imperative that we remember and celebrate acts of kindness and bravery, reflecting on the potential for goodness within us all.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In the face of increasing unrest and criminal activity, stories of valor and righteous intervention are more important than ever. Such a tale unfolded in Ft. Lauderdale, Florida, where an ordinary citizen, armed and vigilant, intervened in a potentially fatal situation, safeguarding a store clerk from the clutches of armed robbers. A Robbery Gone Awry Nicolas Richard Lee Deas and another man allegedly entered a Family Dollar store under the pretense of retrieving a forgotten cellphone. Once inside, they revealed their true colors, threatening the employee and demanding money, eventually making away with $1,200 from the safe and assaulting the employee in the process. A Beacon of Courage Little did the robbers know, a store owner nearby had noticed the disturbance and bravely decided to confront the situation. He walked into a volatile scenario and, demonstrating quick thinking and courage, drew his firearm, commanding Deas to drop his weapon and surrender. The second suspect chose discretion over valor and hastily departed the scene. The Hands of Justice The armed Good Samaritan diligently held his ground until law enforcement arrived, leading to Deas’ arrest on multiple charges, including armed robbery and aggravated assault. The weapon Deas used was identified as stolen. The second suspect remains unidentified and at large. A Light in the Darkness This episode is a shining example of how everyday bravery and a moral compass can bring light to the shadows cast by violence and deceit in today’s world. This unnamed hero made the decision to confront danger head-on, embodying the essence of true heroism and civic duty. Such acts of benevolence and courage deserve our recognition and respect, as they guide us towards a path of solidarity and virtue in a world often overshadowed by turmoil and malevolence. In a world where malevolence often overshadows goodness, it is imperative that we remember and celebrate acts of kindness and bravery, reflecting on the potential for goodness within us all.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Battle over Free Speech - Rumble Resists Calls to Demonetize Russell Brand</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/22/Rumble-Russell-Brand-Controversy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Battle over Free Speech - Rumble Resists Calls to Demonetize Russell Brand" /><published>2023-09-22T12:04:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-22T12:04:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/22/Rumble-Russell-Brand-Controversy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/22/Rumble-Russell-Brand-Controversy/">&lt;p&gt;Streaming platform Rumble is facing intense scrutiny and pressure from the UK Parliament but is choosing to stand its ground. A formal letter from the UK Parliament’s Culture, Media, and Sports Committee Chairwoman, Conservative MP Caroline Dinenage, asked Rumble whether it planned to demonetize comedian and commentator Russell Brand’s channel following serious allegations of rape and sexual assault against him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;parliaments-appeal-and-rumbles-stance&quot;&gt;Parliament’s Appeal and Rumble’s Stance&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The appeal to Rumble came in the wake of YouTube’s decision to demonetize Brand’s account. The UK Parliament expressed concerns over Brand profiting from content on Rumble amidst the grave accusations and inquired about Rumble’s intentions regarding Brand’s ability to earn money on the platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, Rumble issued a staunch response, refusing to demonetize Brand’s channel and labelled the Parliament’s letter as “disturbing”. They defended their stance on the grounds of upholding free speech and the principle that every individual is entitled to a full and serious investigation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Rumble stands for very different values. We have devoted ourselves to the vital cause of defending a free internet – meaning an internet where no one arbitrarily dictates which ideas can or cannot be heard, or which citizens may or may not be entitled to a platform,” Rumble said in a statement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-allegations-against-brand&quot;&gt;The Allegations Against Brand&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Multiple women have accused Russell Brand of rape and sexual assault, as reported by Channel 4 news network and the Sunday Times in Britain. Brand, however, has vehemently denied all the allegations against him. These serious accusations have led various platforms to review their relationships with Brand, and some, like YouTube, to take decisive action against him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;wider-implications-and-repercussions&quot;&gt;Wider Implications and Repercussions&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rumble argues that the allegations against Brand, which are yet to be proven in a court of law, are not related to his video content, and it is “deeply inappropriate and dangerous” for the UK Parliament to attempt to control who is allowed to speak on their platform or to earn a living from doing so. They highlighted the absence of any connection between the allegations and his content on Rumble as a significant factor in their decision.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TikTok and other media outlets, including the BBC, Channel 4, and GB News, have also been approached by the committee for clarification on their positions regarding Brand and his ability to monetize his posts, especially those related to the allegations against him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;reflecting-on-freedom-of-speech-and-accountability&quot;&gt;Reflecting on Freedom of Speech and Accountability&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This ongoing situation brings to the forefront the delicate balance between freedom of speech and accountability. Rumble’s refusal to bend to the pressure from Parliament underscores the debate around the extent of control and influence governmental bodies should have over content on internet platforms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a world where the lines between free speech, censorship, and accountability are continually being redrawn, situations like these serve as crucial talking points and reflections on the values we uphold and the lengths we are willing to go to defend them.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Streaming platform Rumble is facing intense scrutiny and pressure from the UK Parliament but is choosing to stand its ground. A formal letter from the UK Parliament’s Culture, Media, and Sports Committee Chairwoman, Conservative MP Caroline Dinenage, asked Rumble whether it planned to demonetize comedian and commentator Russell Brand’s channel following serious allegations of rape and sexual assault against him. Parliament’s Appeal and Rumble’s Stance The appeal to Rumble came in the wake of YouTube’s decision to demonetize Brand’s account. The UK Parliament expressed concerns over Brand profiting from content on Rumble amidst the grave accusations and inquired about Rumble’s intentions regarding Brand’s ability to earn money on the platform. However, Rumble issued a staunch response, refusing to demonetize Brand’s channel and labelled the Parliament’s letter as “disturbing”. They defended their stance on the grounds of upholding free speech and the principle that every individual is entitled to a full and serious investigation. “Rumble stands for very different values. We have devoted ourselves to the vital cause of defending a free internet – meaning an internet where no one arbitrarily dictates which ideas can or cannot be heard, or which citizens may or may not be entitled to a platform,” Rumble said in a statement. The Allegations Against Brand Multiple women have accused Russell Brand of rape and sexual assault, as reported by Channel 4 news network and the Sunday Times in Britain. Brand, however, has vehemently denied all the allegations against him. These serious accusations have led various platforms to review their relationships with Brand, and some, like YouTube, to take decisive action against him. Wider Implications and Repercussions Rumble argues that the allegations against Brand, which are yet to be proven in a court of law, are not related to his video content, and it is “deeply inappropriate and dangerous” for the UK Parliament to attempt to control who is allowed to speak on their platform or to earn a living from doing so. They highlighted the absence of any connection between the allegations and his content on Rumble as a significant factor in their decision. TikTok and other media outlets, including the BBC, Channel 4, and GB News, have also been approached by the committee for clarification on their positions regarding Brand and his ability to monetize his posts, especially those related to the allegations against him. Reflecting on Freedom of Speech and Accountability This ongoing situation brings to the forefront the delicate balance between freedom of speech and accountability. Rumble’s refusal to bend to the pressure from Parliament underscores the debate around the extent of control and influence governmental bodies should have over content on internet platforms. In a world where the lines between free speech, censorship, and accountability are continually being redrawn, situations like these serve as crucial talking points and reflections on the values we uphold and the lengths we are willing to go to defend them.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Rising Tide - Kari Lake Amplifies GOP Stature</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/22/Kari-Lake-Profile-Boost/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rising Tide - Kari Lake Amplifies GOP Stature" /><published>2023-09-22T11:02:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-22T11:02:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/22/Kari-Lake-Profile-Boost</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/22/Kari-Lake-Profile-Boost/">&lt;p&gt;In a series of moves that have shaken up the political landscape, former Arizona gubernatorial candidate Kari Lake has significantly increased her national profile as a steadfast surrogate for former President Donald Trump and a fervent supporter of Republican candidates. This transformation comes ahead of her anticipated declaration to contest a U.S. Senate seat, furthering the battle for control in the region.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-potential-political-maverick&quot;&gt;A Potential Political Maverick&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lake, a conservative emblem and former news anchor, has been traversing the country, participating in numerous events and speaking engagements to back Republican candidates. Her vigorous efforts are particularly focused on advocating for Trump’s presidential campaign, along with endorsing other GOP candidates across different states. With this aggressive strategy, Lake is likely preparing the ground for her rumored Senate run, scheduled to be announced in the second week of October.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;paving-the-road-for-republicans&quot;&gt;Paving the Road for Republicans&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lake’s impassioned campaigning isn’t limited to Arizona; she has journeyed through 14 states over the past three months to lead events and support Republican organizations on various levels. She has endorsed several candidates in Senate races and even thrown her weight behind Mayor Trent Staggs of Riverton, Utah, and businessman Bernie Moreno in Ohio, portraying her as a significant figure in the Republican realm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;in-trumps-corner&quot;&gt;In Trump’s Corner&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lake has been fervently supporting Trump on the campaign trail, emphasizing her alignment with the former President’s policies and visions. Sources intimate that she will continue this trajectory, appearing in California as Trump’s surrogate for the second Republican presidential debate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-fight-for-arizona&quot;&gt;The Fight for Arizona&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Early polls suggest Lake could be a leading contender in a hypothetical Republican primary. She faces potential competition from figures like Pinal County Sheriff Mark Lamb and businessman Blake Masters. On the Democrat side, Congressman Ruben Gallego is considered the front-runner, with current independent Arizona Senator Kyrsten Sinema’s intentions still unclear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;controversy-and-allegations&quot;&gt;Controversy and Allegations&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lake’s earlier gubernatorial run was marked by controversy, as she maintained the presence of significant voter fraud which favored the Democrats. Her stance on such contentious issues and her alignment with Trump’s viewpoints might impact her appeal to the moderate voters in the critical swing state of Arizona.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;lakes-national-ascendancy&quot;&gt;Lake’s National Ascendancy&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The strategic endeavors of Kari Lake reflect her ambitious goals and the broader Republican objective to regain control over both the Senate and the White House. Her increasing national presence and her alignment with Donald Trump underscore her determination to elevate the conservative agenda. The anticipation surrounding her potential Senate run is soaring, and the political circuits are abuzz, waiting to see how her strategies and alliances shape the course of the upcoming electoral battles.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a series of moves that have shaken up the political landscape, former Arizona gubernatorial candidate Kari Lake has significantly increased her national profile as a steadfast surrogate for former President Donald Trump and a fervent supporter of Republican candidates. This transformation comes ahead of her anticipated declaration to contest a U.S. Senate seat, furthering the battle for control in the region. A Potential Political Maverick Lake, a conservative emblem and former news anchor, has been traversing the country, participating in numerous events and speaking engagements to back Republican candidates. Her vigorous efforts are particularly focused on advocating for Trump’s presidential campaign, along with endorsing other GOP candidates across different states. With this aggressive strategy, Lake is likely preparing the ground for her rumored Senate run, scheduled to be announced in the second week of October. Paving the Road for Republicans Lake’s impassioned campaigning isn’t limited to Arizona; she has journeyed through 14 states over the past three months to lead events and support Republican organizations on various levels. She has endorsed several candidates in Senate races and even thrown her weight behind Mayor Trent Staggs of Riverton, Utah, and businessman Bernie Moreno in Ohio, portraying her as a significant figure in the Republican realm. In Trump’s Corner Lake has been fervently supporting Trump on the campaign trail, emphasizing her alignment with the former President’s policies and visions. Sources intimate that she will continue this trajectory, appearing in California as Trump’s surrogate for the second Republican presidential debate. The Fight for Arizona Early polls suggest Lake could be a leading contender in a hypothetical Republican primary. She faces potential competition from figures like Pinal County Sheriff Mark Lamb and businessman Blake Masters. On the Democrat side, Congressman Ruben Gallego is considered the front-runner, with current independent Arizona Senator Kyrsten Sinema’s intentions still unclear. Controversy and Allegations Lake’s earlier gubernatorial run was marked by controversy, as she maintained the presence of significant voter fraud which favored the Democrats. Her stance on such contentious issues and her alignment with Trump’s viewpoints might impact her appeal to the moderate voters in the critical swing state of Arizona. Lake’s National Ascendancy The strategic endeavors of Kari Lake reflect her ambitious goals and the broader Republican objective to regain control over both the Senate and the White House. Her increasing national presence and her alignment with Donald Trump underscore her determination to elevate the conservative agenda. The anticipation surrounding her potential Senate run is soaring, and the political circuits are abuzz, waiting to see how her strategies and alliances shape the course of the upcoming electoral battles.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Surge in the Race - Sen. Scott Bags a Cool Million</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/22/Scott-Fundraising-Momentum/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Surge in the Race - Sen. Scott Bags a Cool Million" /><published>2023-09-22T10:07:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-22T10:07:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/22/Scott-Fundraising-Momentum</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/22/Scott-Fundraising-Momentum/">&lt;p&gt;In a powerful display of political momentum, Sen. Tim Scott of South Carolina, a hopeful candidate for the White House from the Republican party, has managed to amass an impressive $1 million in campaign contributions within a mere 24 hours. This substantial windfall was revealed by a spokesperson from Scott’s campaign during his speaking engagements in New York City and Charleston, South Carolina.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;newfound-momentum&quot;&gt;Newfound Momentum&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This fundraising achievement could indicate a possible surge in momentum for Sen. Scott, who, until now, had been trailing behind some of his fellow competitors in national polling data. Scott’s campaign is seemingly catching speed, and his performance in the polls in Iowa—a state known for its pivotal role in determining the fate of presidential candidates—is promising.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;eyes-on-the-prize&quot;&gt;Eyes on the Prize&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the second Republican debate looming, this spike in contributions is particularly crucial. The debate is seen as a golden opportunity for GOP presidential aspirants to position themselves as the alternative to former President Donald Trump, who is currently the front-runner by a significant margin. Trump, however, has chosen not to participate in this debate, opting instead to speak at an event in Detroit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Scott’s spokesperson, Matt Gorman, emphasized that Scott is ready to return to the debate stage to highlight the serious policy distinctions between the candidates, conveying that, “Tim is prepared to have a conversation with voters, be the adult in the room, and demonstrate why he is the strongest candidate to beat Joe Biden.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;against-the-odds&quot;&gt;Against the Odds&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite the efforts of all the contenders, surpassing Trump’s dominance in the polls remains a considerable challenge. While the Iowa caucuses are still a few months away, giving candidates ample time to strategize and gain traction, how and when the field will narrow down in the lead-up to this crucial event is still uncertain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;scotts-strategy&quot;&gt;Scott’s Strategy&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sen. Scott is gearing up to leverage this debate to showcase his viewpoints on various pressing issues like the economy and parental rights and to present his vision for the country. He aims to engage with the voters effectively and demonstrate why he is the ideal candidate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-road-ahead&quot;&gt;The Road Ahead&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This million-dollar boost is certainly a beacon of hope for Sen. Scott’s campaign. As the debate nears, all eyes will be on how he and his fellow candidates capitalize on this opportunity to present themselves as viable contenders and how they will strategize to gain an edge in the race against the dominant presence of Trump. The political arena is buzzing with anticipation as the Republican candidates brace themselves for the challenges and opportunities that lie ahead in the race to the White House.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a powerful display of political momentum, Sen. Tim Scott of South Carolina, a hopeful candidate for the White House from the Republican party, has managed to amass an impressive $1 million in campaign contributions within a mere 24 hours. This substantial windfall was revealed by a spokesperson from Scott’s campaign during his speaking engagements in New York City and Charleston, South Carolina. Newfound Momentum This fundraising achievement could indicate a possible surge in momentum for Sen. Scott, who, until now, had been trailing behind some of his fellow competitors in national polling data. Scott’s campaign is seemingly catching speed, and his performance in the polls in Iowa—a state known for its pivotal role in determining the fate of presidential candidates—is promising. Eyes on the Prize With the second Republican debate looming, this spike in contributions is particularly crucial. The debate is seen as a golden opportunity for GOP presidential aspirants to position themselves as the alternative to former President Donald Trump, who is currently the front-runner by a significant margin. Trump, however, has chosen not to participate in this debate, opting instead to speak at an event in Detroit. Scott’s spokesperson, Matt Gorman, emphasized that Scott is ready to return to the debate stage to highlight the serious policy distinctions between the candidates, conveying that, “Tim is prepared to have a conversation with voters, be the adult in the room, and demonstrate why he is the strongest candidate to beat Joe Biden.” Against the Odds Despite the efforts of all the contenders, surpassing Trump’s dominance in the polls remains a considerable challenge. While the Iowa caucuses are still a few months away, giving candidates ample time to strategize and gain traction, how and when the field will narrow down in the lead-up to this crucial event is still uncertain. Scott’s Strategy Sen. Scott is gearing up to leverage this debate to showcase his viewpoints on various pressing issues like the economy and parental rights and to present his vision for the country. He aims to engage with the voters effectively and demonstrate why he is the ideal candidate. The Road Ahead This million-dollar boost is certainly a beacon of hope for Sen. Scott’s campaign. As the debate nears, all eyes will be on how he and his fellow candidates capitalize on this opportunity to present themselves as viable contenders and how they will strategize to gain an edge in the race against the dominant presence of Trump. The political arena is buzzing with anticipation as the Republican candidates brace themselves for the challenges and opportunities that lie ahead in the race to the White House.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Baltimore’s Educational Crisis - Zero Proficiency in Math across 13 High Schools</title><link href="/news/2023/09/22/Educational-Crisis-Baltimore/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Baltimore’s Educational Crisis - Zero Proficiency in Math across 13 High Schools" /><published>2023-09-22T09:15:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-22T09:15:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/22/Educational-Crisis-Baltimore</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/22/Educational-Crisis-Baltimore/">&lt;p&gt;In a shocking revelation, state math exams have found that not a single student from 13 high schools in Baltimore, Maryland, demonstrated proficiency in math. This alarming statistic has triggered severe concern over the state of education in the region, with officials and experts calling it “educational homicide.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-grave-scenario&quot;&gt;A Grave Scenario&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The 13 schools in question, including renowned names like Patterson High School and Frederick Douglass, are part of 33 city schools in Baltimore. This implies a whopping 40% of the city schools are entangled in this educational crisis. Jason Rodriguez, deputy director of a local non-profit People Empowered by the Struggle, called out the rampant system, emphasizing a dire need for accountability rather than funding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;numbers-speak-volumes&quot;&gt;Numbers Speak Volumes&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of the 1,736 students who took the test in these 13 schools, a staggering 1,295 students, making up 74.5%, scored one out of four— the lowest possible score. This situation is especially startling considering the substantial financial resources invested in the district. Last school year, Baltimore City Schools received a record $1.6 billion from taxpayers, and an additional $799 million in Covid relief funding from the federal government.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-recurring-issue&quot;&gt;A Recurring Issue&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This isn’t the first time Baltimore City Schools have been under the scanner for such dismal educational outcomes. A comparable report by Project Baltimore in 2017 also highlighted zero math proficiency in 13 schools, some of which continue to struggle with the same issue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-response&quot;&gt;The Response&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;City Schools attribute these results to years of underfunding and the recent pandemic. They argue that recent increments in funds don’t nullify the damage caused by chronic underfunding over the years, and that improvement in such a situation would require significant time and effort.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;beyond-the-tests&quot;&gt;Beyond the Tests&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This predicament goes beyond mere numbers and test scores, shedding light on deeper, systemic issues in education. The reality of these alarming scores opens up urgent discussions on the structure, functionality, and effectiveness of the educational systems in place and raises critical questions about the future of the students affected by it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The consistent educational crisis in Baltimore, marked by zero proficiency in math across several high schools, is a disturbing indicator of deep-rooted issues in the educational landscape. This situation demands immediate attention, thorough investigation, and robust reforms to ensure that every student has access to quality education, which is essential for shaping a prosperous and equitable future.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a shocking revelation, state math exams have found that not a single student from 13 high schools in Baltimore, Maryland, demonstrated proficiency in math. This alarming statistic has triggered severe concern over the state of education in the region, with officials and experts calling it “educational homicide.” A Grave Scenario The 13 schools in question, including renowned names like Patterson High School and Frederick Douglass, are part of 33 city schools in Baltimore. This implies a whopping 40% of the city schools are entangled in this educational crisis. Jason Rodriguez, deputy director of a local non-profit People Empowered by the Struggle, called out the rampant system, emphasizing a dire need for accountability rather than funding. Numbers Speak Volumes Of the 1,736 students who took the test in these 13 schools, a staggering 1,295 students, making up 74.5%, scored one out of four— the lowest possible score. This situation is especially startling considering the substantial financial resources invested in the district. Last school year, Baltimore City Schools received a record $1.6 billion from taxpayers, and an additional $799 million in Covid relief funding from the federal government. A Recurring Issue This isn’t the first time Baltimore City Schools have been under the scanner for such dismal educational outcomes. A comparable report by Project Baltimore in 2017 also highlighted zero math proficiency in 13 schools, some of which continue to struggle with the same issue. The Response City Schools attribute these results to years of underfunding and the recent pandemic. They argue that recent increments in funds don’t nullify the damage caused by chronic underfunding over the years, and that improvement in such a situation would require significant time and effort. Beyond the Tests This predicament goes beyond mere numbers and test scores, shedding light on deeper, systemic issues in education. The reality of these alarming scores opens up urgent discussions on the structure, functionality, and effectiveness of the educational systems in place and raises critical questions about the future of the students affected by it. Conclusion The consistent educational crisis in Baltimore, marked by zero proficiency in math across several high schools, is a disturbing indicator of deep-rooted issues in the educational landscape. This situation demands immediate attention, thorough investigation, and robust reforms to ensure that every student has access to quality education, which is essential for shaping a prosperous and equitable future.</summary></entry></feed>