<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-10-22T09:16:20-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/22/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-22T09:16:20-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-22T09:16:20-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/22/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/22/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/22/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-22T09:16:20-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-22T09:16:20-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/22/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/22/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/">&lt;p&gt;Recent surprise attacks by Hamas on Israel has fueled ongoing tensions between staunchly conservative commentators and the progressive “Squad” Democrats known for criticizing Israel. The intensity of the backlash highlights the deep political divide over foreign policy in the Middle East.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Hamas’ shocking attack, several members of the “Squad,” including Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.), called for a “ceasefire and de-escalation,” condemning the violence. The absence of a statement from Rep. Rashida Tlaib (D-Mich.) was notably called out by conservative media outlets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;South Carolina GOP Rep. Nancy Mace quickly labeled Ocasio-Cortez a “Hamas apologist” in response to her call for peace and de-escalation. Rep. Ilhan Omar (D-Minn.), no stranger to controversy surrounding her views on Israel, echoed the call for de-escalation and ceasefire. Omar’s prior statements comparing the US and Israel to terrorist groups like Hamas and the Taliban resurfaced in the debate, fueling more criticisms. Omar’s 2019 tweet, where she opined that “Israel has hypnotized the world,” also continues to haunt her political career, often cited by critics to challenge her stance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conservative commentators have been especially vocal. “FOX &amp;amp; Friends Weekend” co-host Rachel Campos-Duffy took aim at Omar, saying she fails to recognize the peace in the Middle East under Trump’s administration. Conservative pundit John Hasson also called out Omar, claiming she insinuated that attacks on IDF forces were acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Massachusetts Democrat Rep. Ayanna Pressley’s concerns over the “devastating attacks on Israelis” were met with skepticism. A prominent conservative online personality, Comfortably Smug, accused the “Squad” of advising Israel to back down after the nation suffered massive attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Jamaal Bowman’s call for an end to the Gaza blockade, in addition to condemning the Hamas attacks, was met with criticism from conservative radio host Jason Rantz. He accused Bowman of pairing his condemnation of terrorism with unwarranted criticisms of Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Cori Bush emphasized the urgent need for a ceasefire, while pushing for an end to “U.S. support for Israeli military occupation and apartheid.” Defense attorney Marina Medvin criticized Bush, suggesting that she equates the death of Palestinian terrorists to the horrific acts committed against Jewish civilians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amidst the political turmoil and intense debate, the attacks have taken a heavy toll. Israeli media report over 300 dead due to the wide-ranging assault. Gaza health officials note that at least 200 Palestinians have perished in the retaliatory Israeli air strikes following the initial Hamas attack. As the situation remains volatile, both sides continue to count their casualties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This divisive issue showcases the challenge America faces in crafting a unified approach to foreign policy, with deeply entrenched political divides at play. As the situation develops, the debate is bound to intensify, shedding light on the complexities of U.S. politics in the global arena.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">The Rise of ‘Funflation’: Bidenomics and the Decline of Affordable Entertainment</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/22/Funflation-Impact/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Rise of ‘Funflation’: Bidenomics and the Decline of Affordable Entertainment" /><published>2023-10-22T08:08:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-22T08:08:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/22/Funflation-Impact</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/22/Funflation-Impact/">&lt;p&gt;Biden’s economic policies are posing a direct challenge to affordable entertainment in the US, with almost 60% of Americans reportedly reducing their expenditure on live entertainment. This cutback, ranging from amusement parks to rock concerts and performing arts, is a repercussion of skyrocketing prices, reveals a survey conducted by the Wall Street Journal and Credit Karma.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further insights from the survey indicate a worrying trend: around 26% of respondents have stopped spending on live entertainment altogether. This percentage has seen a sharp rise from 16% pre-pandemic. This phenomenon, aptly named “funflation”, signifies that a substantial segment of American families is grappling with President Joe Biden’s economic reforms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2022, data from the Bureau of Labor Statistics Consumer Expenditures Survey exposed that entertainment admissions and fee costs increased at a more rapid pace than essentials like food and gasoline. To offer some perspective, food-at-home prices surged by a staggering 19.6% since February 2021.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Disney theme parks, a favorite for many, aren’t insulated from these economic headwinds. Julie Gibbs, an Indiana-based university administration worker, shared her personal experience, recounting her past visits to Walt Disney World in Orlando, which were reduced drastically owing to Disney’s escalating prices. Julie and her family are now reorienting their leisure activities to more economical options, a sentiment echoed by many.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Disney’s continuous price increases give me the feeling that they’re perpetually demanding more. It’s not a pleasant sensation,” Julie expressed to the Journal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The term “funflation” was recently introduced by Bank of America analyst Jessica Reif Ehrlich. She emphasized the skyrocketing prices in her investor note, stating, “Prices for live, experiential activities are spiraling.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Highlighting this trend, Disney has once again upped the admission charges for its theme parks, with some passes witnessing an increase of up to 21%. The music industry too isn’t spared from this price surge. Concert tickets for big names like Taylor Swift and Bruce Springsteen have become exorbitantly priced.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To accentuate the dire state of the entertainment world, the Bruce Springsteen fan magazine, Backstreets, announced its closure after 43 years. The soaring ticket prices, reaching up to $5,000, have doused fans’ enthusiasm, the magazine’s publisher remarked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As America grapples with these economic challenges, the repercussions on the entertainment sector manifest the strain on household budgets and underscore the need for revisiting economic strategies.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Biden’s economic policies are posing a direct challenge to affordable entertainment in the US, with almost 60% of Americans reportedly reducing their expenditure on live entertainment. This cutback, ranging from amusement parks to rock concerts and performing arts, is a repercussion of skyrocketing prices, reveals a survey conducted by the Wall Street Journal and Credit Karma. Further insights from the survey indicate a worrying trend: around 26% of respondents have stopped spending on live entertainment altogether. This percentage has seen a sharp rise from 16% pre-pandemic. This phenomenon, aptly named “funflation”, signifies that a substantial segment of American families is grappling with President Joe Biden’s economic reforms. In 2022, data from the Bureau of Labor Statistics Consumer Expenditures Survey exposed that entertainment admissions and fee costs increased at a more rapid pace than essentials like food and gasoline. To offer some perspective, food-at-home prices surged by a staggering 19.6% since February 2021. Disney theme parks, a favorite for many, aren’t insulated from these economic headwinds. Julie Gibbs, an Indiana-based university administration worker, shared her personal experience, recounting her past visits to Walt Disney World in Orlando, which were reduced drastically owing to Disney’s escalating prices. Julie and her family are now reorienting their leisure activities to more economical options, a sentiment echoed by many. “Disney’s continuous price increases give me the feeling that they’re perpetually demanding more. It’s not a pleasant sensation,” Julie expressed to the Journal. The term “funflation” was recently introduced by Bank of America analyst Jessica Reif Ehrlich. She emphasized the skyrocketing prices in her investor note, stating, “Prices for live, experiential activities are spiraling.” Highlighting this trend, Disney has once again upped the admission charges for its theme parks, with some passes witnessing an increase of up to 21%. The music industry too isn’t spared from this price surge. Concert tickets for big names like Taylor Swift and Bruce Springsteen have become exorbitantly priced. To accentuate the dire state of the entertainment world, the Bruce Springsteen fan magazine, Backstreets, announced its closure after 43 years. The soaring ticket prices, reaching up to $5,000, have doused fans’ enthusiasm, the magazine’s publisher remarked. As America grapples with these economic challenges, the repercussions on the entertainment sector manifest the strain on household budgets and underscore the need for revisiting economic strategies.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Rep. Mike Johnson Declares Candidacy for House Speaker Position</title><link href="/news/2023/10/22/House-Speaker-Race/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rep. Mike Johnson Declares Candidacy for House Speaker Position" /><published>2023-10-22T07:06:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-22T07:06:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/22/House-Speaker-Race</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/22/House-Speaker-Race/">&lt;p&gt;The race for the House Speaker position gets even hotter as Rep. Mike Johnson, R-La., proclaims, “I’m in.” Johnson, a key figure in both the House Judiciary Committee and the House Republican Conference, officially declared his intentions this past Saturday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a letter addressed to his GOP colleagues, Johnson emphasized the need for “principled leadership.” He stated he hadn’t initially dreamt of the Speaker’s role, but the urging of numerous members inspired him to step up. Johnson’s letter conveyed the urgency of this moment, “It is incumbent upon us now to decide upon a consensus candidate who can serve as a trusted caretaker and a good steward of the gavel.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Renowned as a socially and fiscally conservative constitutional law attorney, Johnson has been a part of the House since 2017. He also took on the role of chairing the Republican Study Committee, which is the House’s largest panel. His vision for himself? A “team player and a bridge-builder.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This announcement comes amidst the backdrop of a vacant speakership, following Rep. Jim Jordan, R-Ohio, bowing out after his third unsuccessful attempt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But Johnson is far from the only hopeful. Other contenders include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rep. Kevin Hern, R-Okla.&lt;/strong&gt; – Currently chairs the conservative Republican Study Committee.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rep. Austin Scott, R-Ga.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rep. Pete Sessions, R-Texas&lt;/strong&gt; – Holds the title of House Rules Committee chair.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rep. Jack Bergman, R-Mich.&lt;/strong&gt; – Retired Marine Corps lieutenant general.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rep. Tom Emmer, R-Minn.&lt;/strong&gt; – The third-ranking Republican in the House, also renowned as a former ice hockey coach. Emmer’s mission? “To bring our conference together and get back to work.”&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rep. Byron Donalds, R-Fla.&lt;/strong&gt; – Member of the stringent House Freedom Caucus.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rep. Hakeem Jeffries, D-N.Y.&lt;/strong&gt; – Currently the minority leader and has received unwavering support from Democrats since the GOP seized the majority.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s also speculation about potential entrants to the race, such as Rep. Tom Cole, R-Okla., and Rep. Jodey Arrington, R-Texas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, some notable figures like Rep. Steve Scalise, R-La., and Rep. Jim Jordan, R-Ohio, have decided against the pursuit after being unable to secure the necessary votes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the line-up brimming with potential, it remains to be seen who will clinch the esteemed position. As the race intensifies, America watches closely.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">The race for the House Speaker position gets even hotter as Rep. Mike Johnson, R-La., proclaims, “I’m in.” Johnson, a key figure in both the House Judiciary Committee and the House Republican Conference, officially declared his intentions this past Saturday. In a letter addressed to his GOP colleagues, Johnson emphasized the need for “principled leadership.” He stated he hadn’t initially dreamt of the Speaker’s role, but the urging of numerous members inspired him to step up. Johnson’s letter conveyed the urgency of this moment, “It is incumbent upon us now to decide upon a consensus candidate who can serve as a trusted caretaker and a good steward of the gavel.” Renowned as a socially and fiscally conservative constitutional law attorney, Johnson has been a part of the House since 2017. He also took on the role of chairing the Republican Study Committee, which is the House’s largest panel. His vision for himself? A “team player and a bridge-builder.” This announcement comes amidst the backdrop of a vacant speakership, following Rep. Jim Jordan, R-Ohio, bowing out after his third unsuccessful attempt. But Johnson is far from the only hopeful. Other contenders include: Rep. Kevin Hern, R-Okla. – Currently chairs the conservative Republican Study Committee. Rep. Austin Scott, R-Ga. Rep. Pete Sessions, R-Texas – Holds the title of House Rules Committee chair. Rep. Jack Bergman, R-Mich. – Retired Marine Corps lieutenant general. Rep. Tom Emmer, R-Minn. – The third-ranking Republican in the House, also renowned as a former ice hockey coach. Emmer’s mission? “To bring our conference together and get back to work.” Rep. Byron Donalds, R-Fla. – Member of the stringent House Freedom Caucus. Rep. Hakeem Jeffries, D-N.Y. – Currently the minority leader and has received unwavering support from Democrats since the GOP seized the majority. There’s also speculation about potential entrants to the race, such as Rep. Tom Cole, R-Okla., and Rep. Jodey Arrington, R-Texas. However, some notable figures like Rep. Steve Scalise, R-La., and Rep. Jim Jordan, R-Ohio, have decided against the pursuit after being unable to secure the necessary votes. With the line-up brimming with potential, it remains to be seen who will clinch the esteemed position. As the race intensifies, America watches closely.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Sen. Blackburn Challenges Biden’s Aid Proposal for Gaza</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/22/Biden-Gaza-Aid/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sen. Blackburn Challenges Biden’s Aid Proposal for Gaza" /><published>2023-10-22T06:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-22T06:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/22/Biden-Gaza-Aid</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/22/Biden-Gaza-Aid/">&lt;p&gt;Sen. Marsha Blackburn, a Republican from Tennessee, expressed deep concern over President Joe Biden’s recent supplemental aid request to Congress. This proposal includes humanitarian assistance for Gaza. Blackburn’s primary worry? That the aid may inadvertently fund terrorism in the region.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Blackburn shared her concerns with Fox News Digital, highlighting reports from just a week prior where Hamas, labeled a terrorist organization by multiple nations including the United States, allegedly intercepted aid. This includes essentials like food, money, medical supplies, and fuel meant for the citizens of Gaza.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This isn’t the first time concerns over aid misappropriation have surfaced. The United Nations agency that oversees aid distribution to Palestinians recently reported theft of medical supplies and fuel by Hamas leaders in Gaza, although this statement was subsequently retracted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the emergency supplemental request presented by Biden, a whopping $105 billion is outlined. This sum is allocated for various purposes, with $9 billion specifically designated for Ukraine, Israel, and Gaza. Blackburn emphasizes the sentiment of the American majority, which she believes backs Israel. She underscores the importance of ensuring the aid genuinely reaches those in dire need.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, Blackburn didn’t stop at the concern over aid. She pointedly criticized members of the progressive “Squad” in Congress, such as Reps. Rashida Tlaib and Ilhan Omar. She accused them of behaving like “Hamas sympathizers,” noting their calls for a ceasefire in Gaza and resistance to increasing funds for Israel’s defense.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Highlighting a broader geopolitical standpoint, Blackburn has actively called for a freeze on the $6 billion in Iranian assets. She, along with other GOP members, authored a letter addressed to Sen. Majority Leader Chuck Schumer and Sen. Minority Leader Mitch McConnell. The letter proposed splitting Biden’s supplemental request into separate packages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why the split? The lawmakers argued that merging the aid for Israel and Ukraine could be problematic. They believe the two are distinct conflicts and should not be tied together. Bundling them could complicate the process and even risk a government shutdown, diminishing the chances of approving the funding package.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next week promises to be crucial as Congress convenes to deliberate on Biden’s supplemental request. The goal? To finalize and approve a package that the White House can endorse. Amidst political turbulence and global unrest, the journey of this aid proposal exemplifies the challenges faced in international relations and the quest for peace.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Sen. Marsha Blackburn, a Republican from Tennessee, expressed deep concern over President Joe Biden’s recent supplemental aid request to Congress. This proposal includes humanitarian assistance for Gaza. Blackburn’s primary worry? That the aid may inadvertently fund terrorism in the region. Blackburn shared her concerns with Fox News Digital, highlighting reports from just a week prior where Hamas, labeled a terrorist organization by multiple nations including the United States, allegedly intercepted aid. This includes essentials like food, money, medical supplies, and fuel meant for the citizens of Gaza. This isn’t the first time concerns over aid misappropriation have surfaced. The United Nations agency that oversees aid distribution to Palestinians recently reported theft of medical supplies and fuel by Hamas leaders in Gaza, although this statement was subsequently retracted. In the emergency supplemental request presented by Biden, a whopping $105 billion is outlined. This sum is allocated for various purposes, with $9 billion specifically designated for Ukraine, Israel, and Gaza. Blackburn emphasizes the sentiment of the American majority, which she believes backs Israel. She underscores the importance of ensuring the aid genuinely reaches those in dire need. However, Blackburn didn’t stop at the concern over aid. She pointedly criticized members of the progressive “Squad” in Congress, such as Reps. Rashida Tlaib and Ilhan Omar. She accused them of behaving like “Hamas sympathizers,” noting their calls for a ceasefire in Gaza and resistance to increasing funds for Israel’s defense. Highlighting a broader geopolitical standpoint, Blackburn has actively called for a freeze on the $6 billion in Iranian assets. She, along with other GOP members, authored a letter addressed to Sen. Majority Leader Chuck Schumer and Sen. Minority Leader Mitch McConnell. The letter proposed splitting Biden’s supplemental request into separate packages. Why the split? The lawmakers argued that merging the aid for Israel and Ukraine could be problematic. They believe the two are distinct conflicts and should not be tied together. Bundling them could complicate the process and even risk a government shutdown, diminishing the chances of approving the funding package. Next week promises to be crucial as Congress convenes to deliberate on Biden’s supplemental request. The goal? To finalize and approve a package that the White House can endorse. Amidst political turbulence and global unrest, the journey of this aid proposal exemplifies the challenges faced in international relations and the quest for peace.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump’s Email Blast: ‘Crooked Joe’ and the $200,000 Mystery</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/21/Trump-Biden-Fundraising/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump’s Email Blast: ‘Crooked Joe’ and the $200,000 Mystery" /><published>2023-10-21T17:15:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-21T17:15:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/21/Trump-Biden-Fundraising</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/21/Trump-Biden-Fundraising/">&lt;p&gt;In a recent fundraising email, former President Donald Trump intensified his attack on President Joe Biden, alleging financial missteps and a possible money trail connecting Biden to his family’s business dealings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The email surfaced after James Comer, the House Oversight Committee Chair and Republican representative from Kentucky, revealed evidence of a $200,000 check transaction. This check, from Biden’s brother, James Biden, was directed to “Joseph R. Biden Jr.” This discovery follows Biden’s earlier response to bribery allegations, where he quipped, “Where’s the money?” A question that the GOP, backed by Trump, now claims to have answered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, this isn’t where the money trail ends. Trump’s email also highlighted James Biden’s loan history from Americore, a rural hospital operator. Bankruptcy court documents unveiled that in 2018, James acquired a substantial $600,000 loan from Americore. The reasoning? Allegedly, it was based on James’ surname “Biden” which would purportedly “open doors” and secure significant investments from the Middle East due to his political affiliations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a striking sequence of events, $200,000 was wired to James and Sara Biden from Americore in March of 2018. And astonishingly, on that same day, a check of $200,000 was penned to Joe Biden from his brother, James.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In response to these revelations, Trump’s campaign rekindled the moniker, “Crooked Joe Biden.” This branding is a pivot from the once-popular “Sleepy Joe” label, primarily due to the mounting allegations of deception in Biden’s acknowledgment of his family’s financial affairs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Concluding his fundraising email, Trump stated, “The coincidences just keep piling up.” Making it clear, he, along with many others, sees more than mere coincidence in these monetary exchanges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chair James Comer has assured the public that this isn’t the last they’ll hear about these findings. While the House Oversight Committee zeroes in on the mysterious $200,000 “loan repayment,” they have listed immediate questions that President Biden must address. These queries revolve around Biden’s financial exchanges with family members, particularly regarding the astounding sum transferred from James Biden.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amid these evolving political dramas, the American public awaits clarity. As allegations mount and political tensions rise, it’s evident that the financial dealings of the Biden family will remain a topic of national discussion for some time to come.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a recent fundraising email, former President Donald Trump intensified his attack on President Joe Biden, alleging financial missteps and a possible money trail connecting Biden to his family’s business dealings. The email surfaced after James Comer, the House Oversight Committee Chair and Republican representative from Kentucky, revealed evidence of a $200,000 check transaction. This check, from Biden’s brother, James Biden, was directed to “Joseph R. Biden Jr.” This discovery follows Biden’s earlier response to bribery allegations, where he quipped, “Where’s the money?” A question that the GOP, backed by Trump, now claims to have answered. However, this isn’t where the money trail ends. Trump’s email also highlighted James Biden’s loan history from Americore, a rural hospital operator. Bankruptcy court documents unveiled that in 2018, James acquired a substantial $600,000 loan from Americore. The reasoning? Allegedly, it was based on James’ surname “Biden” which would purportedly “open doors” and secure significant investments from the Middle East due to his political affiliations. In a striking sequence of events, $200,000 was wired to James and Sara Biden from Americore in March of 2018. And astonishingly, on that same day, a check of $200,000 was penned to Joe Biden from his brother, James. In response to these revelations, Trump’s campaign rekindled the moniker, “Crooked Joe Biden.” This branding is a pivot from the once-popular “Sleepy Joe” label, primarily due to the mounting allegations of deception in Biden’s acknowledgment of his family’s financial affairs. Concluding his fundraising email, Trump stated, “The coincidences just keep piling up.” Making it clear, he, along with many others, sees more than mere coincidence in these monetary exchanges. Chair James Comer has assured the public that this isn’t the last they’ll hear about these findings. While the House Oversight Committee zeroes in on the mysterious $200,000 “loan repayment,” they have listed immediate questions that President Biden must address. These queries revolve around Biden’s financial exchanges with family members, particularly regarding the astounding sum transferred from James Biden. Amid these evolving political dramas, the American public awaits clarity. As allegations mount and political tensions rise, it’s evident that the financial dealings of the Biden family will remain a topic of national discussion for some time to come.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Maher’s Take: Elite Colleges - A Breeding Ground for Ignorance?</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/21/Elite-Colleges-Criticism/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Maher’s Take: Elite Colleges - A Breeding Ground for Ignorance?" /><published>2023-10-21T16:01:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-21T16:01:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/21/Elite-Colleges-Criticism</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/21/Elite-Colleges-Criticism/">&lt;p&gt;In a bold and controversial stance, HBO’s “Real Time” host Bill Maher has urged America’s youth to reconsider their dreams of attending elite colleges. According to Maher, an Ivy League graduate himself, these prestigious institutions are nothing short of “North Korean re-education camps” that foster ignorance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maher’s critique of elite colleges comes as a fresh wave of concern over the state of higher education in America. He claims these institutions have evolved into hotbeds of indoctrination where “bad ideas” take root, and the nuances of global politics are reduced to oversimplified binaries of “oppressors” and “oppressed.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Diving into the Israel-Palestinian conflict as an example, Maher highlighted the disturbing trend of uninformed students supporting radical ideas without understanding the intricate historical and political background. He quipped about students labeling words as violence while simultaneously endorsing extreme actions against the state of Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Elaborating on his point, Maher expressed dismay at the widespread ignorance among elite college students. “They don’t know much of anything, actually. But it doesn’t deter them from having an opinion,” Maher said. He criticized the modern college curriculum for its lack of historical depth, suggesting that students are more interested in surfing TikTok than delving deep into academic pursuits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Drawing parallels between college life and “North Korean re-education camps,” Maher took a swipe at the perceived power dynamics within universities. He painted a grim picture of institutions where student whims dictate institutional decisions, rendering college presidents voiceless.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adding to his barrage of criticisms, Maher called out elite institutions for promoting segregation under the guise of inclusion and diversity. He raised concerns about all-black dorms, segregated graduation ceremonies, and orientation programs. Moreover, Maher didn’t shy away from addressing the controversial topic of racial bias against Asian applicants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a closing salvo, Maher remarked on the irony of elite institutions producing right-wing figures who publicly decry elitism. In his eyes, this performance of anti-elitism by Ivy League graduates is nothing short of “repulsive.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a world where college prestige often dictates career trajectories, Maher’s words serve as a cautionary tale. They beckon young aspirants to look beyond the ivy-covered walls and question whether the education they’re receiving genuinely broadens their horizons or narrows them.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">In a bold and controversial stance, HBO’s “Real Time” host Bill Maher has urged America’s youth to reconsider their dreams of attending elite colleges. According to Maher, an Ivy League graduate himself, these prestigious institutions are nothing short of “North Korean re-education camps” that foster ignorance. Maher’s critique of elite colleges comes as a fresh wave of concern over the state of higher education in America. He claims these institutions have evolved into hotbeds of indoctrination where “bad ideas” take root, and the nuances of global politics are reduced to oversimplified binaries of “oppressors” and “oppressed.” Diving into the Israel-Palestinian conflict as an example, Maher highlighted the disturbing trend of uninformed students supporting radical ideas without understanding the intricate historical and political background. He quipped about students labeling words as violence while simultaneously endorsing extreme actions against the state of Israel. Elaborating on his point, Maher expressed dismay at the widespread ignorance among elite college students. “They don’t know much of anything, actually. But it doesn’t deter them from having an opinion,” Maher said. He criticized the modern college curriculum for its lack of historical depth, suggesting that students are more interested in surfing TikTok than delving deep into academic pursuits. Drawing parallels between college life and “North Korean re-education camps,” Maher took a swipe at the perceived power dynamics within universities. He painted a grim picture of institutions where student whims dictate institutional decisions, rendering college presidents voiceless. Adding to his barrage of criticisms, Maher called out elite institutions for promoting segregation under the guise of inclusion and diversity. He raised concerns about all-black dorms, segregated graduation ceremonies, and orientation programs. Moreover, Maher didn’t shy away from addressing the controversial topic of racial bias against Asian applicants. As a closing salvo, Maher remarked on the irony of elite institutions producing right-wing figures who publicly decry elitism. In his eyes, this performance of anti-elitism by Ivy League graduates is nothing short of “repulsive.” In a world where college prestige often dictates career trajectories, Maher’s words serve as a cautionary tale. They beckon young aspirants to look beyond the ivy-covered walls and question whether the education they’re receiving genuinely broadens their horizons or narrows them.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A Grave Mistake: White House Accidentally Exposes Special Forces in Biden Photo-Op</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/21/Special-Forces-Doxxing-Incident/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Grave Mistake: White House Accidentally Exposes Special Forces in Biden Photo-Op" /><published>2023-10-21T16:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-21T16:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/21/Special-Forces-Doxxing-Incident</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/21/Special-Forces-Doxxing-Incident/">&lt;p&gt;In an alarming incident this week, the White House admitted to accidentally revealing the identities of American Special Forces in Israel during President Joe Biden’s visit. The blunder occurred when a photo, featuring the President with the Special Forces, was posted on the White House’s Instagram account, which boasts a following of 7.6 million. The photo inadvertently exposed the faces of these highly confidential operatives, placing their safety, as well as that of their families, in jeopardy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The White House’s failure to blur or conceal the identities of the Special Forces has drawn widespread criticism and concern. Visible in the photo were also unique identifiers such as tattoos, further jeopardizing the anonymity of the personnel. The caption of the now-removed photo read, “In Israel, President Biden met with first responders to thank them for their bravery and the work they’re doing in response to the Hamas terrorist attacks.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After retired Army Chief Warrant Officer 2 Samuel Shoemate brought this severe oversight to public attention, and after the photo had already reached hundreds of thousands of viewers, the White House acted swiftly to remove the image and issued an apology. “As soon as this was brought to our attention, we immediately deleted the photo. We regret the error and any issues this may have caused,” the White House stated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, accountability for this blunder remains unclear, as the White House has not disclosed who was responsible for the error. When the Pentagon was approached for comments, they redirected inquiries back to the White House. “I’d have to refer you to the White House on that. I just don’t have any information to provide,” was the response from Pentagon press secretary Brig. Gen. Pat Ryder during a press conference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This incident raises questions about the integrity of Biden’s promise to never use troops for political purposes, a pledge he made during his first visit to the Pentagon as President, stating, “I will never dishonor you. I will never disrespect you. I will never politicize the work you do.” This promise seems to be contradicted by his actions, as this is not the first instance where Biden has utilized troops as political props. In September 2022, Biden delivered a highly charged political speech, positioning two Marine sentries directly behind him, drawing sharp criticism from various quarters including Republican officials, conservative commentators, Marine veterans, military spouses, and even corporate news journalists.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This latest incident, therefore, not only jeopardizes the safety of the exposed Special Forces but also brings to light the ongoing issue of the politicization of the military, a matter that requires immediate attention and rectification.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In an alarming incident this week, the White House admitted to accidentally revealing the identities of American Special Forces in Israel during President Joe Biden’s visit. The blunder occurred when a photo, featuring the President with the Special Forces, was posted on the White House’s Instagram account, which boasts a following of 7.6 million. The photo inadvertently exposed the faces of these highly confidential operatives, placing their safety, as well as that of their families, in jeopardy. The White House’s failure to blur or conceal the identities of the Special Forces has drawn widespread criticism and concern. Visible in the photo were also unique identifiers such as tattoos, further jeopardizing the anonymity of the personnel. The caption of the now-removed photo read, “In Israel, President Biden met with first responders to thank them for their bravery and the work they’re doing in response to the Hamas terrorist attacks.” After retired Army Chief Warrant Officer 2 Samuel Shoemate brought this severe oversight to public attention, and after the photo had already reached hundreds of thousands of viewers, the White House acted swiftly to remove the image and issued an apology. “As soon as this was brought to our attention, we immediately deleted the photo. We regret the error and any issues this may have caused,” the White House stated. However, accountability for this blunder remains unclear, as the White House has not disclosed who was responsible for the error. When the Pentagon was approached for comments, they redirected inquiries back to the White House. “I’d have to refer you to the White House on that. I just don’t have any information to provide,” was the response from Pentagon press secretary Brig. Gen. Pat Ryder during a press conference. This incident raises questions about the integrity of Biden’s promise to never use troops for political purposes, a pledge he made during his first visit to the Pentagon as President, stating, “I will never dishonor you. I will never disrespect you. I will never politicize the work you do.” This promise seems to be contradicted by his actions, as this is not the first instance where Biden has utilized troops as political props. In September 2022, Biden delivered a highly charged political speech, positioning two Marine sentries directly behind him, drawing sharp criticism from various quarters including Republican officials, conservative commentators, Marine veterans, military spouses, and even corporate news journalists. This latest incident, therefore, not only jeopardizes the safety of the exposed Special Forces but also brings to light the ongoing issue of the politicization of the military, a matter that requires immediate attention and rectification.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A New Arena for Political Rivalry: Truth Social Welcomes Biden</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/21/Truth-Social-Political-Platform/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A New Arena for Political Rivalry: Truth Social Welcomes Biden" /><published>2023-10-21T14:54:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-21T14:54:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/21/Truth-Social-Political-Platform</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/21/Truth-Social-Political-Platform/">&lt;p&gt;In an unexpected twist of digital diplomacy, Truth Social, the brainchild of former President Donald Trump, has rolled out the welcome mat for none other than its founder’s 2024 rival, President Joe Biden. The Biden-Harris HQ campaign account made its debut on the platform with a cheeky post: “Well. Let’s see how this goes. Converts welcome!”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This embrace of the platform by Biden’s reelection campaign has caught the eyes of political enthusiasts and analysts alike. It raises questions about the balance of power in the digital realm, as political heavyweights look to engage and influence potential voters on varying platforms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Devin Nunes, former Rep. and now CEO of Trump Media and Technology Group, voiced his perspective on Newsmax’s “The Chris Salcedo Show”. “We’re a free speech platform,” Nunes declared, distinguishing Truth Social from social media giants like Twitter, Facebook, and Instagram. “We welcome anyone and everyone. Contrary to perhaps popular belief, we aren’t looking to ban or kick off the Biden campaign.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By the end of the week, Biden-Harris HQ’s follower count stood at an impressive 33,600 - surpassing even the follower count of the Team Trump account. However, Trump’s primary account remains a juggernaut with a whopping 6.45 million followers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nunes took a jibe at media outlets, calling them out for spinning narratives about Biden’s follower count. He mused over the idea of Biden potentially overtaking Trump on Truth Social, remarking, “If that happens, great for him. But most of those following Biden are likely doing so to engage with his campaign, often critically.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nunes alluded to the swathes of comments under Biden’s posts that seem to be real-time fact-checking the president’s campaign, a testament to the interactive and unfiltered nature of the platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the 2024 election season heats up, the use of platforms like Truth Social offers an uncharted territory for campaigns to navigate. With both major parties marking their territory on the platform, it’s clear that the battle for the White House will be fought as fiercely online as off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In today’s digital age, where a tweet can sway public opinion and a post can ignite a debate, platforms like Truth Social are more than just social networks. They are political battlegrounds, and the game has just begun.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In an unexpected twist of digital diplomacy, Truth Social, the brainchild of former President Donald Trump, has rolled out the welcome mat for none other than its founder’s 2024 rival, President Joe Biden. The Biden-Harris HQ campaign account made its debut on the platform with a cheeky post: “Well. Let’s see how this goes. Converts welcome!”. This embrace of the platform by Biden’s reelection campaign has caught the eyes of political enthusiasts and analysts alike. It raises questions about the balance of power in the digital realm, as political heavyweights look to engage and influence potential voters on varying platforms. Devin Nunes, former Rep. and now CEO of Trump Media and Technology Group, voiced his perspective on Newsmax’s “The Chris Salcedo Show”. “We’re a free speech platform,” Nunes declared, distinguishing Truth Social from social media giants like Twitter, Facebook, and Instagram. “We welcome anyone and everyone. Contrary to perhaps popular belief, we aren’t looking to ban or kick off the Biden campaign.” By the end of the week, Biden-Harris HQ’s follower count stood at an impressive 33,600 - surpassing even the follower count of the Team Trump account. However, Trump’s primary account remains a juggernaut with a whopping 6.45 million followers. Nunes took a jibe at media outlets, calling them out for spinning narratives about Biden’s follower count. He mused over the idea of Biden potentially overtaking Trump on Truth Social, remarking, “If that happens, great for him. But most of those following Biden are likely doing so to engage with his campaign, often critically.” Nunes alluded to the swathes of comments under Biden’s posts that seem to be real-time fact-checking the president’s campaign, a testament to the interactive and unfiltered nature of the platform. As the 2024 election season heats up, the use of platforms like Truth Social offers an uncharted territory for campaigns to navigate. With both major parties marking their territory on the platform, it’s clear that the battle for the White House will be fought as fiercely online as off. In today’s digital age, where a tweet can sway public opinion and a post can ignite a debate, platforms like Truth Social are more than just social networks. They are political battlegrounds, and the game has just begun.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Sky-High Tensions: US-Chinese Aerial Confrontations on the Rise</title><link href="/news/2023/10/21/US-China-Aerial-Tensions/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sky-High Tensions: US-Chinese Aerial Confrontations on the Rise" /><published>2023-10-21T13:47:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-21T13:47:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/21/US-China-Aerial-Tensions</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/21/US-China-Aerial-Tensions/">&lt;p&gt;Recent data from the U.S. Department of Defense (DOD) signals an alarming increase in dangerous encounters between American and Chinese aircraft. The DOD voiced concerns about the “coercive and risky” behaviors demonstrated by Chinese planes in their interactions with U.S. aircraft.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During a press briefing on Tuesday, DOD officials showcased newly declassified images and footage illustrating these precarious situations. Ely Ratner, the Assistant Defense Secretary for Indo-Pacific Security Affairs, articulated the gravity of the situation. “From 2021 onward, over 180 incidents involving risky behaviors from People’s Liberation Army (PLA) operators have been reported, more than what we saw in the preceding decade,” Ratner stated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These behaviors include aggressive maneuvers, rapid approaches, and even the firing of flares dangerously close to U.S. aircraft. Such actions are perceived as attempts by the PLA to challenge and obstruct U.S. military operations within regions internationally recognized as global commons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ratner emphasized that the People’s Liberation Army (PLA) doesn’t limit its disruptive antics to U.S. aircraft. When factoring in similar confrontations against aircraft belonging to U.S. allies and partners, the number jumps to almost 300 incidents in the same timeframe. Such statistics underline a broader trend of hostility and provocation in east Asian territories.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Images released by the DOD paint a concerning picture of these interactions. One particularly distressing image displays a PLA fighter jet, mere feet away from a U.S. aircraft, maneuvering in a way that could compromise the safety of both planes. Another document captures a PLA pilot resorting to crude language after being radioed by the U.S. operator.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Admiral John Aquilino, the Indo-Pacom Commander, offered a perspective on these incidents. “While aerial intercepts occur frequently worldwide, they predominantly transpire without mishaps. There’s no reason for the interactions in the Indo-Pacific with the PRC to deviate from this norm,” he stated. Aquilino highlighted the paramount importance of the safety of U.S. servicemembers, asserting the need to spotlight and mitigate these hazardous behaviors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though the DOD has shed light on the rising aerial confrontations, they did not provide a concise delineation between what they termed as “coercive” and “risky” versus more commonly used descriptors like “unsafe” or “unprofessional.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With tensions escalating in the skies, it remains imperative for both nations to find avenues of communication and collaboration, ensuring the safety and security of all involved.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Recent data from the U.S. Department of Defense (DOD) signals an alarming increase in dangerous encounters between American and Chinese aircraft. The DOD voiced concerns about the “coercive and risky” behaviors demonstrated by Chinese planes in their interactions with U.S. aircraft. During a press briefing on Tuesday, DOD officials showcased newly declassified images and footage illustrating these precarious situations. Ely Ratner, the Assistant Defense Secretary for Indo-Pacific Security Affairs, articulated the gravity of the situation. “From 2021 onward, over 180 incidents involving risky behaviors from People’s Liberation Army (PLA) operators have been reported, more than what we saw in the preceding decade,” Ratner stated. These behaviors include aggressive maneuvers, rapid approaches, and even the firing of flares dangerously close to U.S. aircraft. Such actions are perceived as attempts by the PLA to challenge and obstruct U.S. military operations within regions internationally recognized as global commons. Ratner emphasized that the People’s Liberation Army (PLA) doesn’t limit its disruptive antics to U.S. aircraft. When factoring in similar confrontations against aircraft belonging to U.S. allies and partners, the number jumps to almost 300 incidents in the same timeframe. Such statistics underline a broader trend of hostility and provocation in east Asian territories. Images released by the DOD paint a concerning picture of these interactions. One particularly distressing image displays a PLA fighter jet, mere feet away from a U.S. aircraft, maneuvering in a way that could compromise the safety of both planes. Another document captures a PLA pilot resorting to crude language after being radioed by the U.S. operator. Admiral John Aquilino, the Indo-Pacom Commander, offered a perspective on these incidents. “While aerial intercepts occur frequently worldwide, they predominantly transpire without mishaps. There’s no reason for the interactions in the Indo-Pacific with the PRC to deviate from this norm,” he stated. Aquilino highlighted the paramount importance of the safety of U.S. servicemembers, asserting the need to spotlight and mitigate these hazardous behaviors. Though the DOD has shed light on the rising aerial confrontations, they did not provide a concise delineation between what they termed as “coercive” and “risky” versus more commonly used descriptors like “unsafe” or “unprofessional.” With tensions escalating in the skies, it remains imperative for both nations to find avenues of communication and collaboration, ensuring the safety and security of all involved.</summary></entry></feed>