<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-09-16T09:15:42-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/09/16/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-09-16T09:15:42-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-16T09:15:42-04:00</updated><id>/2023/09/16/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/16/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">TikTok in Hot Water - Slapped with $368M Fine in Europe</title><link href="/news/2023/09/16/TikTok-Fined-In-Europe/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="TikTok in Hot Water - Slapped with $368M Fine in Europe" /><published>2023-09-16T08:01:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-16T08:01:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/16/TikTok-Fined-In-Europe</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/16/TikTok-Fined-In-Europe/">&lt;p&gt;European watchdogs have put TikTok under the scanner, fining the company a staggering $368 million for failing to adequately safeguard children’s privacy. This penalty marks the maiden time TikTok has faced repercussions under Europe’s stringent data privacy regulations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The lion’s share of Big Tech companies have their European headquarters situated in Dublin. It is here that Ireland’s Data Protection Commission decreed the fine of 345 million euros. TikTok is under fire for transgressions stemming from the latter half of 2020, primarily concerning the default settings of the accounts for teenagers. These default configurations left the accounts public, enabling unrestricted access to and commentary on their videos.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, the “family pairing” feature, intended to allow parental oversight, had a loophole. This laxity permitted adults to activate direct messaging for users within the age bracket of 16 and 17, bypassing their consent. Moreover, TikTok reportedly nudged its younger demographic towards selecting more “privacy intrusive” alternatives during their sign-up and content upload procedures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While TikTok has rebuffed the ruling, particularly balking at the quantum of the fine, they have indicated that most of the grievances addressed by the regulatory body were outdated. The platform underscored its proactive measures, such as making accounts of those under 16 private by default and deactivating direct messaging capabilities for the 13 to 15 age group, initiated well before the inquiry’s commencement in September 2021.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite these arguments, it’s evident that the European Union is taking a stand, with Brussels now stepping up to the plate to ensure stricter regulations and curb missteps in the digital realm. The essence is to retain its vanguard position in the sphere of tech regulation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Simultaneously, the onus of social media firms is crystal clear. They need to present options without bias, especially to the younger generation, to ensure the preservation of their privacy rights. Data privacy is an ongoing global concern, with TikTok’s data sharing with China adding another layer of complexity. The European community’s reservations regarding the potential for sensitive user information making its way to China have led TikTok to establish a data center in Dublin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the broader panorama, other tech behemoths like Instagram, WhatsApp, and Meta have faced the music in Europe, indicating the continent’s no-nonsense approach to data privacy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TikTok’s journey ahead seems fraught with challenges, not only to assuage the concerns of the European regulators but also to regain the trust of its vast user base.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">European watchdogs have put TikTok under the scanner, fining the company a staggering $368 million for failing to adequately safeguard children’s privacy. This penalty marks the maiden time TikTok has faced repercussions under Europe’s stringent data privacy regulations. The lion’s share of Big Tech companies have their European headquarters situated in Dublin. It is here that Ireland’s Data Protection Commission decreed the fine of 345 million euros. TikTok is under fire for transgressions stemming from the latter half of 2020, primarily concerning the default settings of the accounts for teenagers. These default configurations left the accounts public, enabling unrestricted access to and commentary on their videos. Furthermore, the “family pairing” feature, intended to allow parental oversight, had a loophole. This laxity permitted adults to activate direct messaging for users within the age bracket of 16 and 17, bypassing their consent. Moreover, TikTok reportedly nudged its younger demographic towards selecting more “privacy intrusive” alternatives during their sign-up and content upload procedures. While TikTok has rebuffed the ruling, particularly balking at the quantum of the fine, they have indicated that most of the grievances addressed by the regulatory body were outdated. The platform underscored its proactive measures, such as making accounts of those under 16 private by default and deactivating direct messaging capabilities for the 13 to 15 age group, initiated well before the inquiry’s commencement in September 2021. Despite these arguments, it’s evident that the European Union is taking a stand, with Brussels now stepping up to the plate to ensure stricter regulations and curb missteps in the digital realm. The essence is to retain its vanguard position in the sphere of tech regulation. Simultaneously, the onus of social media firms is crystal clear. They need to present options without bias, especially to the younger generation, to ensure the preservation of their privacy rights. Data privacy is an ongoing global concern, with TikTok’s data sharing with China adding another layer of complexity. The European community’s reservations regarding the potential for sensitive user information making its way to China have led TikTok to establish a data center in Dublin. In the broader panorama, other tech behemoths like Instagram, WhatsApp, and Meta have faced the music in Europe, indicating the continent’s no-nonsense approach to data privacy. TikTok’s journey ahead seems fraught with challenges, not only to assuage the concerns of the European regulators but also to regain the trust of its vast user base.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Another Misstep - Did Biden Just Link Ethnicity to Education Level?</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/16/Biden-Racist-Remarks/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Another Misstep - Did Biden Just Link Ethnicity to Education Level?" /><published>2023-09-16T07:03:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-16T07:03:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/16/Biden-Racist-Remarks</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/16/Biden-Racist-Remarks/">&lt;p&gt;In a week already rife with political tension, President Joe Biden added fuel to the fire with a statement that has left many outraged. During a recent speech, Biden seemed to link “African Americans and Hispanic workers” with individuals “without high school diplomas.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Discrepancy in Words&lt;/strong&gt;
During his speech at Prince George’s Community College in Largo, Md., President Biden remarked:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;We’ve seen record lows in unemployment particularly — and I’ve focused on this my whole career — particularly for African Americans and Hispanic workers and veterans, you know, the workers without high school diplomas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the White House’s transcript tells a slightly different story:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;We’ve seen record lows in unemployment, particularly — and I’ve focused on this my whole career — particularly for African Americans and Hispanic workers and veterans, you know, and the workers without high-school diplomas. The lowest unemployment rate in 70 years for women now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s evident that there’s a discrepancy between what Biden said and how the White House chose to transcribe it. The altered version seems to create more distance between minority communities and those without high school education.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Is this a Pattern?&lt;/strong&gt;
It’s important to put Biden’s comments into context. Over the years, he’s made several controversial remarks, leading some to label them as instances of ‘ignorant racism’. Among these, he referred to “poor kids” being “just as bright and just as talented as white kids,” and also described former President Barack Obama as “bright and clean.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With a history of questionable statements, this latest incident has further ignited debates about the President’s perspectives on race and ethnicity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As discussions around systemic racism and inequality continue to dominate the global narrative, leaders are expected to choose their words wisely, setting a tone of inclusivity and understanding. It remains to be seen whether this latest incident will be brushed under the rug or lead to broader conversations about the inherent biases that might still exist at the highest levels of governance.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a week already rife with political tension, President Joe Biden added fuel to the fire with a statement that has left many outraged. During a recent speech, Biden seemed to link “African Americans and Hispanic workers” with individuals “without high school diplomas.” A Discrepancy in Words During his speech at Prince George’s Community College in Largo, Md., President Biden remarked: We’ve seen record lows in unemployment particularly — and I’ve focused on this my whole career — particularly for African Americans and Hispanic workers and veterans, you know, the workers without high school diplomas. However, the White House’s transcript tells a slightly different story: We’ve seen record lows in unemployment, particularly — and I’ve focused on this my whole career — particularly for African Americans and Hispanic workers and veterans, you know, and the workers without high-school diplomas. The lowest unemployment rate in 70 years for women now. It’s evident that there’s a discrepancy between what Biden said and how the White House chose to transcribe it. The altered version seems to create more distance between minority communities and those without high school education. Is this a Pattern? It’s important to put Biden’s comments into context. Over the years, he’s made several controversial remarks, leading some to label them as instances of ‘ignorant racism’. Among these, he referred to “poor kids” being “just as bright and just as talented as white kids,” and also described former President Barack Obama as “bright and clean.” With a history of questionable statements, this latest incident has further ignited debates about the President’s perspectives on race and ethnicity. As discussions around systemic racism and inequality continue to dominate the global narrative, leaders are expected to choose their words wisely, setting a tone of inclusivity and understanding. It remains to be seen whether this latest incident will be brushed under the rug or lead to broader conversations about the inherent biases that might still exist at the highest levels of governance.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Stan Lee’s Final Chapter - A Battle Against Elder Abuse Concludes</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/16/Stan-Lee-Legal-Battle/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Stan Lee’s Final Chapter - A Battle Against Elder Abuse Concludes" /><published>2023-09-16T06:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-16T06:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/16/Stan-Lee-Legal-Battle</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/16/Stan-Lee-Legal-Battle/">&lt;p&gt;The enthralling world of superheroes often pits the forces of good against the sinister plots of villains. In a twist of reality mirroring fiction, the late Stan Lee, the genius behind many of Marvel’s iconic characters, found himself ensnared in a contentious elder abuse case that spanned five years. This week, the legal skirmish reached its conclusion, but not without a few cliffhangers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;superheros-tumultuous-last-days&quot;&gt;Superhero’s Tumultuous Last Days&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just before his death on November 12, 2018, Stan Lee had been the central figure in an elder abuse lawsuit. The suit accused his ex-business manager, Jerardo Olivarez, of siphoning a whopping $1.4 million from Lee’s accounts. Later, Uri Litvak, an attorney associated with Olivarez, found himself added to the litigation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These accusations trace back to the dynamic between the two defendants. Olivarez introduced Litvak to Lee, pressuring the comic legend to retain the latter’s legal services for his business endeavors. The resulting relationship, according to the complaint filed in 2018, led to significant financial losses for Lee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;continuing-the-fight&quot;&gt;Continuing The Fight&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Following Stan Lee’s passing, his daughter, Joan Lee, took on the mantle of the case as a trustee of his estate. The recent judgment brought a twist when the Los Angeles Superior Court ruled in favor of Litvak. The crux of the decision rested on the fact that the statute of limitations had expired by a mere five days when the case against Litvak was initiated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Lee estate fervently argued that Litvak’s professional interactions with the Marvel creator had extended beyond the lawsuit’s initial filing date, potentially halting the statute of limitations. However, arbitrator David Brickner cited evidence in the form of a letter from Lee in 2017, clarifying that Litvak’s services had been terminated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;end-of-an-era&quot;&gt;End Of An Era&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This conclusion draws the curtain on the legal battles that clouded Stan Lee’s final years. The legendary creator of superheroes such as Iron Man, Hulk, Spider-Man, and Thor faced personal battles that drew as much attention as his comic world exploits. These included conflicts with his daughter Joan, allegations against her for elder abuse, and accusations against former associates out for his fortune.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, as with most superhero tales, the story eventually found its resolution. The Marvel maestro, despite the shadows cast by these controversies, ultimately sided with his daughter. Their bond, it seems, was stronger than any adversarial plot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stan Lee’s legacy in the comic book realm is unmatched, having shaped the industry since 1939. And though the recent years saw him grappling with personal challenges, from health issues to the loss of his wife of nearly 70 years in 2017, his contribution to the world of comics and entertainment remains unparalleled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The end of this lawsuit may be seen by many as the final chapter in the storied life of a man who taught generations to dream, hope, and always fight for justice.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">The enthralling world of superheroes often pits the forces of good against the sinister plots of villains. In a twist of reality mirroring fiction, the late Stan Lee, the genius behind many of Marvel’s iconic characters, found himself ensnared in a contentious elder abuse case that spanned five years. This week, the legal skirmish reached its conclusion, but not without a few cliffhangers. Superhero’s Tumultuous Last Days Just before his death on November 12, 2018, Stan Lee had been the central figure in an elder abuse lawsuit. The suit accused his ex-business manager, Jerardo Olivarez, of siphoning a whopping $1.4 million from Lee’s accounts. Later, Uri Litvak, an attorney associated with Olivarez, found himself added to the litigation. These accusations trace back to the dynamic between the two defendants. Olivarez introduced Litvak to Lee, pressuring the comic legend to retain the latter’s legal services for his business endeavors. The resulting relationship, according to the complaint filed in 2018, led to significant financial losses for Lee. Continuing The Fight Following Stan Lee’s passing, his daughter, Joan Lee, took on the mantle of the case as a trustee of his estate. The recent judgment brought a twist when the Los Angeles Superior Court ruled in favor of Litvak. The crux of the decision rested on the fact that the statute of limitations had expired by a mere five days when the case against Litvak was initiated. The Lee estate fervently argued that Litvak’s professional interactions with the Marvel creator had extended beyond the lawsuit’s initial filing date, potentially halting the statute of limitations. However, arbitrator David Brickner cited evidence in the form of a letter from Lee in 2017, clarifying that Litvak’s services had been terminated. End Of An Era This conclusion draws the curtain on the legal battles that clouded Stan Lee’s final years. The legendary creator of superheroes such as Iron Man, Hulk, Spider-Man, and Thor faced personal battles that drew as much attention as his comic world exploits. These included conflicts with his daughter Joan, allegations against her for elder abuse, and accusations against former associates out for his fortune. However, as with most superhero tales, the story eventually found its resolution. The Marvel maestro, despite the shadows cast by these controversies, ultimately sided with his daughter. Their bond, it seems, was stronger than any adversarial plot. Stan Lee’s legacy in the comic book realm is unmatched, having shaped the industry since 1939. And though the recent years saw him grappling with personal challenges, from health issues to the loss of his wife of nearly 70 years in 2017, his contribution to the world of comics and entertainment remains unparalleled. The end of this lawsuit may be seen by many as the final chapter in the storied life of a man who taught generations to dream, hope, and always fight for justice.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ramaswamy Sounds Alarm - Biden as the ‘Sacrificial Lamb?’</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/15/Biden-Sacrificial-Lamb/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ramaswamy Sounds Alarm - Biden as the ‘Sacrificial Lamb?’" /><published>2023-09-15T17:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-15T17:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/15/Biden-Sacrificial-Lamb</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/15/Biden-Sacrificial-Lamb/">&lt;p&gt;As the 2024 elections loom, the political landscape appears to be in flux, with GOP hopeful Vivek Ramaswamy making a startling prediction regarding the fate of current President Joe Biden.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In an engaging discussion on FNC’s “Jesse Watters Primetime”, Ramaswamy posited that Biden, despite being the face of the Democratic Party, might soon be maneuvered “out of the way” by his very own political allies. Lending weight to this assertion, he hinted at a larger play at hand, labeling Biden as a potential “sacrificial lamb.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jesse Watters, noting the fluctuating poll numbers and evident tension within the Democratic camp, probed Ramaswamy for his take. “Joe Biden, not looking so good,” Watters began, “how are things looking to you as a Republican?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ramaswamy, never one to mince his words, confidently stated, “I was happy to see that I’m beating Joe Biden in that poll and doing just fine.” However, it was his subsequent remarks that raised eyebrows. Diving into the heart of the matter, he contended, “Joe Biden is a puppet for the managerial class… he’s a figurehead for the deep state and the managerial class.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Such statements, while audacious, frame the current state of U.S. politics in a new light. Ramaswamy’s observations suggest that there might be more to Biden’s presidency than what meets the eye. He believes that if Biden’s use reaches its end, the powers that be will merely “trot out the next puppet.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adding another layer of intrigue, he referred to the recent indictment involving Hunter Biden, calling it a potential “smokescreen” and hinting at its use to edge Joe Biden out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ramaswamy’s revelations, if accurate, depict a complicated and evolving political gameboard, with strategies and ploys going well beyond traditional party lines. As the countdown to the 2024 election begins, one can only anticipate more political drama to unfold.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">As the 2024 elections loom, the political landscape appears to be in flux, with GOP hopeful Vivek Ramaswamy making a startling prediction regarding the fate of current President Joe Biden. In an engaging discussion on FNC’s “Jesse Watters Primetime”, Ramaswamy posited that Biden, despite being the face of the Democratic Party, might soon be maneuvered “out of the way” by his very own political allies. Lending weight to this assertion, he hinted at a larger play at hand, labeling Biden as a potential “sacrificial lamb.” Jesse Watters, noting the fluctuating poll numbers and evident tension within the Democratic camp, probed Ramaswamy for his take. “Joe Biden, not looking so good,” Watters began, “how are things looking to you as a Republican?” Ramaswamy, never one to mince his words, confidently stated, “I was happy to see that I’m beating Joe Biden in that poll and doing just fine.” However, it was his subsequent remarks that raised eyebrows. Diving into the heart of the matter, he contended, “Joe Biden is a puppet for the managerial class… he’s a figurehead for the deep state and the managerial class.” Such statements, while audacious, frame the current state of U.S. politics in a new light. Ramaswamy’s observations suggest that there might be more to Biden’s presidency than what meets the eye. He believes that if Biden’s use reaches its end, the powers that be will merely “trot out the next puppet.” Adding another layer of intrigue, he referred to the recent indictment involving Hunter Biden, calling it a potential “smokescreen” and hinting at its use to edge Joe Biden out. Ramaswamy’s revelations, if accurate, depict a complicated and evolving political gameboard, with strategies and ploys going well beyond traditional party lines. As the countdown to the 2024 election begins, one can only anticipate more political drama to unfold.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Defending the Second - Woman’s Self-Defense Fires Debate on Gun Rights</title><link href="/news/2023/09/15/Second-Amendment-Victory/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Defending the Second - Woman’s Self-Defense Fires Debate on Gun Rights" /><published>2023-09-15T16:08:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-15T16:08:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/15/Second-Amendment-Victory</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/15/Second-Amendment-Victory/">&lt;p&gt;In a recent legal win, Maybi Izquierdo, a female long-haul trucker, reignites the national debate on the Second Amendment and the rights of gun owners. Following an incident involving an aggressive, reportedly intoxicated roommate, Izquierdo found herself facing serious legal consequences for defending herself. Her story and the subsequent courtroom drama serve as a powerful testament to the Second Amendment’s enduring importance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;from-birthday-in-jail-to-second-amendment-triumph&quot;&gt;From Birthday in Jail to Second Amendment Triumph&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Celebrating her birthday behind bars last year was perhaps the least of Izquierdo’s worries. After using her firearm to fend off an allegedly aggressive male roommate in San Bernardino, California, she was arrested. A year on, her case has been dismissed, highlighting the crucial role the Second Amendment played in ensuring her safety from unforeseen dangers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the evening in question, Izquierdo had completed household chores and was ready to wind down when the male roommate returned home. She believed he was drunk and was neither in the mood nor felt safe to engage in a conversation with him. What followed was a distressing sequence of events that saw the man persistently approach her, to the point where Izquierdo feared for her safety.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-turn-of-events&quot;&gt;A Turn of Events&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Izquierdo’s attempts to avoid confrontation proved fruitless. When she tried to shut herself inside a bathroom to elude him, the situation took a frightening turn. The man blocked the door, confirming Izquierdo’s fears that a dangerous confrontation was imminent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thankfully, California law permits residents to carry guns on private property without a permit. Equipped with a concealed carry permit and her association with the U.S. Concealed Carry Association, Izquierdo managed to retrieve her gun in the nick of time. Her decisive action kept her safe, but she was arrested and charged following the altercation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;legal-triumph-and-second-amendment-advocacy&quot;&gt;Legal Triumph and Second Amendment Advocacy&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After spending nearly three weeks in jail, Izquierdo recalled her membership with the U.S. Concealed Carry Association, which offers self-defense liability insurance. With the help of her legal team, including attorney Andy Beltran, it was demonstrated that she acted in self-defense. The persistent efforts of her defense team, coupled with the backing of the USCCA, led to her eventual exoneration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beltran’s advice post the trial was poignant: “Refrain from making any statements to the police even if you think you are in the right.” This case underscores how situations can swiftly turn and the importance of being knowledgeable about one’s rights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further emphasizing the relevance of being prepared, Jake Schmidt from the USCCA mentioned, “Responsible gun owners need to be mentally, physically and legally prepared for a self-defense incident. All USCCA members receive lifesaving education and training, plus self-defense liability insurance.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;an-immigrants-perspective&quot;&gt;An Immigrant’s Perspective&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Izquierdo’s experience as an immigrant from Cuba gave her unique insight into the significance of personal freedoms. Coming from a country where individual liberties were curtailed, she expressed gratitude for the rights afforded to her in the U.S. Despite the challenges of her arrest, Izquierdo showcased resilience and tenacity, highlighting, “Being prepared is not just carrying a weapon only… I am very happy that I made the right decision to have these lawyers and to have this [USCCA] insurance.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This landmark case not only affirms the rights of responsible gun owners but also illuminates the broader implications of the Second Amendment in the modern era.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a recent legal win, Maybi Izquierdo, a female long-haul trucker, reignites the national debate on the Second Amendment and the rights of gun owners. Following an incident involving an aggressive, reportedly intoxicated roommate, Izquierdo found herself facing serious legal consequences for defending herself. Her story and the subsequent courtroom drama serve as a powerful testament to the Second Amendment’s enduring importance. From Birthday in Jail to Second Amendment Triumph Celebrating her birthday behind bars last year was perhaps the least of Izquierdo’s worries. After using her firearm to fend off an allegedly aggressive male roommate in San Bernardino, California, she was arrested. A year on, her case has been dismissed, highlighting the crucial role the Second Amendment played in ensuring her safety from unforeseen dangers. On the evening in question, Izquierdo had completed household chores and was ready to wind down when the male roommate returned home. She believed he was drunk and was neither in the mood nor felt safe to engage in a conversation with him. What followed was a distressing sequence of events that saw the man persistently approach her, to the point where Izquierdo feared for her safety. A Turn of Events Izquierdo’s attempts to avoid confrontation proved fruitless. When she tried to shut herself inside a bathroom to elude him, the situation took a frightening turn. The man blocked the door, confirming Izquierdo’s fears that a dangerous confrontation was imminent. Thankfully, California law permits residents to carry guns on private property without a permit. Equipped with a concealed carry permit and her association with the U.S. Concealed Carry Association, Izquierdo managed to retrieve her gun in the nick of time. Her decisive action kept her safe, but she was arrested and charged following the altercation. Legal Triumph and Second Amendment Advocacy After spending nearly three weeks in jail, Izquierdo recalled her membership with the U.S. Concealed Carry Association, which offers self-defense liability insurance. With the help of her legal team, including attorney Andy Beltran, it was demonstrated that she acted in self-defense. The persistent efforts of her defense team, coupled with the backing of the USCCA, led to her eventual exoneration. Beltran’s advice post the trial was poignant: “Refrain from making any statements to the police even if you think you are in the right.” This case underscores how situations can swiftly turn and the importance of being knowledgeable about one’s rights. Further emphasizing the relevance of being prepared, Jake Schmidt from the USCCA mentioned, “Responsible gun owners need to be mentally, physically and legally prepared for a self-defense incident. All USCCA members receive lifesaving education and training, plus self-defense liability insurance.” An Immigrant’s Perspective Izquierdo’s experience as an immigrant from Cuba gave her unique insight into the significance of personal freedoms. Coming from a country where individual liberties were curtailed, she expressed gratitude for the rights afforded to her in the U.S. Despite the challenges of her arrest, Izquierdo showcased resilience and tenacity, highlighting, “Being prepared is not just carrying a weapon only… I am very happy that I made the right decision to have these lawyers and to have this [USCCA] insurance.” This landmark case not only affirms the rights of responsible gun owners but also illuminates the broader implications of the Second Amendment in the modern era.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump Steps Up - ‘I’ll Testify I Did Not Order Video Deletion’</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/15/Trump-Testify/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump Steps Up - ‘I’ll Testify I Did Not Order Video Deletion’" /><published>2023-09-15T15:05:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-15T15:05:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/15/Trump-Testify</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/15/Trump-Testify/">&lt;p&gt;In a recent development, former President Donald Trump, amidst swirling allegations, clarified his stance to NBC News, firmly stating that he did not instruct any staff member at Mar-a-Lago to delete security video footage. This follows charges in late July that alleged Trump and two of his employees tried to delete footage from his Florida estate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a candid conversation with “Meet the Press” moderator Kristen Welker, Trump categorically labeled the allegations against him as “false”. Emphasizing his point, when quizzed about his willingness to testify under oath, Trump didn’t flinch, asserting, “Sure, I’m going to — I’ll testify.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A significant revelation from Trump highlighted that the tapes in question were never deleted. “But more importantly, the tapes weren’t deleted. In other words, there was nothing done to them. And they were my tapes. I could have fought them. I didn’t even have to give them the tapes, I don’t think,” Trump emphasized.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Walt Nauta, Trump’s valet, and Carlos De Oliveira, a maintenance supervisor at Mar-a-Lago, have both been charged with obstruction, Trump has consistently maintained a clean slate. Prosecutors allege that the two, following a subpoena, instructed an unnamed staffer to delete the tapes, claiming that “the boss” had made the request.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump’s steadfast claim to innocence doesn’t stop with the tapes. The former President faces multiple trials, yet he remains undeterred, stating he’s done nothing wrong. Addressing the possibility of a self-pardon should he win the 2024 general election, Trump told NBC, “What, what did I do wrong? I didn’t do anything wrong. You mean, because I challenge an election, they want to put me in jail?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the nation watches closely, Trump’s interview with “Meet the Press” promises more insights and is scheduled to air this Sunday.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a recent development, former President Donald Trump, amidst swirling allegations, clarified his stance to NBC News, firmly stating that he did not instruct any staff member at Mar-a-Lago to delete security video footage. This follows charges in late July that alleged Trump and two of his employees tried to delete footage from his Florida estate. In a candid conversation with “Meet the Press” moderator Kristen Welker, Trump categorically labeled the allegations against him as “false”. Emphasizing his point, when quizzed about his willingness to testify under oath, Trump didn’t flinch, asserting, “Sure, I’m going to — I’ll testify.” A significant revelation from Trump highlighted that the tapes in question were never deleted. “But more importantly, the tapes weren’t deleted. In other words, there was nothing done to them. And they were my tapes. I could have fought them. I didn’t even have to give them the tapes, I don’t think,” Trump emphasized. While Walt Nauta, Trump’s valet, and Carlos De Oliveira, a maintenance supervisor at Mar-a-Lago, have both been charged with obstruction, Trump has consistently maintained a clean slate. Prosecutors allege that the two, following a subpoena, instructed an unnamed staffer to delete the tapes, claiming that “the boss” had made the request. Trump’s steadfast claim to innocence doesn’t stop with the tapes. The former President faces multiple trials, yet he remains undeterred, stating he’s done nothing wrong. Addressing the possibility of a self-pardon should he win the 2024 general election, Trump told NBC, “What, what did I do wrong? I didn’t do anything wrong. You mean, because I challenge an election, they want to put me in jail?” As the nation watches closely, Trump’s interview with “Meet the Press” promises more insights and is scheduled to air this Sunday.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Dark Secrets Behind a Philadelphia Teacher’s “Suicide”</title><link href="/news/2023/09/15/Philadelphia-Mystery/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Dark Secrets Behind a Philadelphia Teacher’s “Suicide”" /><published>2023-09-15T14:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-15T14:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/15/Philadelphia-Mystery</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/15/Philadelphia-Mystery/">&lt;p&gt;In what is shaping up to be one of the most baffling cases in recent memory, the 2011 death of Philadelphia teacher Ellen Greenberg has turned the spotlight on a host of investigative irregularities. Greenberg, who was discovered with an alarming 20 stab wounds, was ruled to have committed suicide, a conclusion that has drawn significant skepticism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-bizarre-crime-scene&quot;&gt;A Bizarre Crime Scene&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ellen was found in her apartment with a knife lodged in her chest, amidst a chilling January blizzard. Appellate court documents now disclose that her apartment was cleaned before the police, bearing a search warrant, arrived on the scene. An astounding revelation, considering the gravity of the situation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;scrutiny-on-authorities&quot;&gt;Scrutiny on Authorities&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The judiciary hasn’t turned a blind eye to the situation. In a recent ruling, judges voiced strong concerns over the investigative processes followed by the city police, prosecutors, and the medical examiner’s office. Commonwealth Judge Ellen Ceisler penned, “The facts surrounding this matter are extremely disturbing… The experts they enlisted have all raised serious factual questions…”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the evidence pointing to possible foul play, the ruling maintains Greenberg’s death as a suicide. This has left many, including Joe Podraza, the attorney for Ellen’s parents, utterly flabbergasted. “The majority opinion is a road map on how to commit murder and to not be held accountable,” Podraza commented.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;pleas-for-a-fresh-investigation&quot;&gt;Pleas for a Fresh Investigation&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adding to the maze of complexities, critical evidence from the scene seems to have been removed prior to official investigations. Ellen’s purse, three laptops, and two cellphones were reportedly taken from the apartment by her fiancé’s uncle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With external voices screaming foul play, the Chester County District Attorney’s Office is currently re-evaluating the circumstances of Greenberg’s demise. The family is resolute in their conviction that their daughter was a victim of foul play, and they are pushing for a separate civil lawsuit alleging evidence cover-up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-road-ahead&quot;&gt;The Road Ahead&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The family’s determination to find the truth remains undeterred. Their aim? To get Greenberg’s death certificate revised from “suicide” to “homicide” or “undetermined”. While the city of Philadelphia has expressed sympathy for the Greenberg family’s plight, the true course of justice remains to be seen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the words of Joe Podraza, emphasizing the need for a new investigation: “The fact that we have presented that magnitude of evidence… cries out for further investigation and plainly undermines a determination of suicide.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The case underscores the crucial importance of investigative transparency, especially in situations that leave more questions than answers.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In what is shaping up to be one of the most baffling cases in recent memory, the 2011 death of Philadelphia teacher Ellen Greenberg has turned the spotlight on a host of investigative irregularities. Greenberg, who was discovered with an alarming 20 stab wounds, was ruled to have committed suicide, a conclusion that has drawn significant skepticism. A Bizarre Crime Scene Ellen was found in her apartment with a knife lodged in her chest, amidst a chilling January blizzard. Appellate court documents now disclose that her apartment was cleaned before the police, bearing a search warrant, arrived on the scene. An astounding revelation, considering the gravity of the situation. Scrutiny on Authorities The judiciary hasn’t turned a blind eye to the situation. In a recent ruling, judges voiced strong concerns over the investigative processes followed by the city police, prosecutors, and the medical examiner’s office. Commonwealth Judge Ellen Ceisler penned, “The facts surrounding this matter are extremely disturbing… The experts they enlisted have all raised serious factual questions…” Despite the evidence pointing to possible foul play, the ruling maintains Greenberg’s death as a suicide. This has left many, including Joe Podraza, the attorney for Ellen’s parents, utterly flabbergasted. “The majority opinion is a road map on how to commit murder and to not be held accountable,” Podraza commented. Pleas for a Fresh Investigation Adding to the maze of complexities, critical evidence from the scene seems to have been removed prior to official investigations. Ellen’s purse, three laptops, and two cellphones were reportedly taken from the apartment by her fiancé’s uncle. With external voices screaming foul play, the Chester County District Attorney’s Office is currently re-evaluating the circumstances of Greenberg’s demise. The family is resolute in their conviction that their daughter was a victim of foul play, and they are pushing for a separate civil lawsuit alleging evidence cover-up. The Road Ahead The family’s determination to find the truth remains undeterred. Their aim? To get Greenberg’s death certificate revised from “suicide” to “homicide” or “undetermined”. While the city of Philadelphia has expressed sympathy for the Greenberg family’s plight, the true course of justice remains to be seen. In the words of Joe Podraza, emphasizing the need for a new investigation: “The fact that we have presented that magnitude of evidence… cries out for further investigation and plainly undermines a determination of suicide.” The case underscores the crucial importance of investigative transparency, especially in situations that leave more questions than answers.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Tim Scott Fires Back - Claims Democrat Party ‘Stuck in Jim Crow Era’</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/15/Tim-Scott-Response/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tim Scott Fires Back - Claims Democrat Party ‘Stuck in Jim Crow Era’" /><published>2023-09-15T13:03:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-15T13:03:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/15/Tim-Scott-Response</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/15/Tim-Scott-Response/">&lt;p&gt;In a recent appearance on FNC’s “Hannity,” Sen. Tim Scott (R-SC), who has thrown his hat into the ring for the 2024 Republican presidential nomination, provided a strong response to comments made on ABC’s “The View.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sunny Hostin, a co-host on “The View,” drew parallels between Scott and U.S. Supreme Court Justice Clarence Thomas, specifically noting the potential for Scott to marry a white woman, akin to Ginni Thomas, Justice Clarence Thomas’s wife. This sparked a discussion between Sean Hannity and Scott about the implications and motivations behind such comments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Addressing Hannity’s query on whether such remarks played the race card, Scott didn’t hold back. “Absolutely, Sean. The Democrat Party and the progressive left they are stuck in Jim Crow 1920s and ’30s. What they do not want is a black man who thinks for himself,” declared Scott. He further expressed his perspective that while a black individual in America has the liberty to be anything, being conservative seems to be an exception in the eyes of many. Scott labeled Hostin’s comments as “radical” and “disgusting.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a poignant conclusion, Scott emphasized his belief that narratives like his, showcasing the journey of black conservatives, are intentionally overlooked as they challenge the narratives espoused by the radical left. “They don’t want my life story to be told because it difficulties results the lies of the radical left,” Scott added. Expressing his disappointment, he remarked, “I can’t think of anything more disgusting and more disheartening to watch the Democrat Party descend down into the 1920s. Unbelievable.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The episode underscores the ongoing political and cultural debates that continue to permeate the nation’s discourse as the 2024 election season heats up.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a recent appearance on FNC’s “Hannity,” Sen. Tim Scott (R-SC), who has thrown his hat into the ring for the 2024 Republican presidential nomination, provided a strong response to comments made on ABC’s “The View.” Sunny Hostin, a co-host on “The View,” drew parallels between Scott and U.S. Supreme Court Justice Clarence Thomas, specifically noting the potential for Scott to marry a white woman, akin to Ginni Thomas, Justice Clarence Thomas’s wife. This sparked a discussion between Sean Hannity and Scott about the implications and motivations behind such comments. Addressing Hannity’s query on whether such remarks played the race card, Scott didn’t hold back. “Absolutely, Sean. The Democrat Party and the progressive left they are stuck in Jim Crow 1920s and ’30s. What they do not want is a black man who thinks for himself,” declared Scott. He further expressed his perspective that while a black individual in America has the liberty to be anything, being conservative seems to be an exception in the eyes of many. Scott labeled Hostin’s comments as “radical” and “disgusting.” In a poignant conclusion, Scott emphasized his belief that narratives like his, showcasing the journey of black conservatives, are intentionally overlooked as they challenge the narratives espoused by the radical left. “They don’t want my life story to be told because it difficulties results the lies of the radical left,” Scott added. Expressing his disappointment, he remarked, “I can’t think of anything more disgusting and more disheartening to watch the Democrat Party descend down into the 1920s. Unbelievable.” The episode underscores the ongoing political and cultural debates that continue to permeate the nation’s discourse as the 2024 election season heats up.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Escaping the Reality TV Limelight - Jill Duggar’s Emotional Unveiling</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/15/Jill-Duggar-Reality-TV/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Escaping the Reality TV Limelight - Jill Duggar’s Emotional Unveiling" /><published>2023-09-15T12:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-15T12:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/15/Jill-Duggar-Reality-TV</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/15/Jill-Duggar-Reality-TV/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jill Duggar&lt;/strong&gt;, one of the principal faces of the once-popular reality show “19 Kids and Counting,” sheds light on her tumultuous life both on and off the screen. Alongside her husband, &lt;strong&gt;Derick Dillard&lt;/strong&gt;, Duggar has penned a memoir titled “Counting the Cost,” wherein she delves into the intricate balance of maintaining familial ties while stepping out of the shadows of a life dominated by the TV lens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;from-reality-star-to-empowered-individual&quot;&gt;From Reality Star to Empowered Individual&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jill’s trajectory from the confines of her reality TV fame to where she stands today - on the edge of Arkansas and Oklahoma, cherishing the joys of motherhood to three boys - is nothing short of transformative. Sporting a nose ring, wearing pants, and embracing therapy, Jill exudes the aura of someone who has finally broken free from the shackles that once bound her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her memoir, which recently hit the bookshelves, serves not just as a tell-all but more importantly as a cathartic release. “It’s helped us process and disentangle our feelings,” Jill mentions. Reflecting on the broader implications of her story, she hopes it resonates with many, underscoring that the feelings of isolation stemming from control aren’t isolated to her life or the world of reality TV.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;delving-into-deep-waters&quot;&gt;Delving Into Deep Waters&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the glitter and glamour of the reality show realm lay the dark undercurrents of Jill’s relationship with her family, especially her father, &lt;strong&gt;Jim Bob Duggar&lt;/strong&gt;. Accusations fly high with claims of weaponizing her marriage and prioritizing the protection of her controversial brother, &lt;strong&gt;Josh Duggar&lt;/strong&gt;, over her well-being.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Counting the Cost” boldly brings to light the estrangement with her father, hinting at a bond now filled with “hornets and garter snakes.” While the future remains uncertain, Jill remains hopeful, expressing, “I hope and pray that it does get better. I love my dad… I love my family so much. And I don’t want to hurt them.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;walking-away---no-regrets&quot;&gt;Walking Away - No Regrets&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The decision to step away from the TV lens in 2017 wasn’t an easy one, yet Jill and Derick, looking back, have no second thoughts. Despite the love for their family, their need for autonomy and control over their narrative pushed them to make this monumental decision.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I wanted us to have more control of our lives,” states Jill, reflecting on the liberating sensation of being free from the reality show grind. The fears of detachment from the family loomed large, but the desire for a genuine life far from the cameras outweighed it all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-new-chapter&quot;&gt;A New Chapter&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With therapy as her guiding light and an unwavering faith, Jill Duggar is on a new journey. Her story, punctuated by highs and lows, serves as a testament to the strength of the human spirit. In her words, “Your story matters. Your voice matters.”&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Jill Duggar, one of the principal faces of the once-popular reality show “19 Kids and Counting,” sheds light on her tumultuous life both on and off the screen. Alongside her husband, Derick Dillard, Duggar has penned a memoir titled “Counting the Cost,” wherein she delves into the intricate balance of maintaining familial ties while stepping out of the shadows of a life dominated by the TV lens. From Reality Star to Empowered Individual Jill’s trajectory from the confines of her reality TV fame to where she stands today - on the edge of Arkansas and Oklahoma, cherishing the joys of motherhood to three boys - is nothing short of transformative. Sporting a nose ring, wearing pants, and embracing therapy, Jill exudes the aura of someone who has finally broken free from the shackles that once bound her. Her memoir, which recently hit the bookshelves, serves not just as a tell-all but more importantly as a cathartic release. “It’s helped us process and disentangle our feelings,” Jill mentions. Reflecting on the broader implications of her story, she hopes it resonates with many, underscoring that the feelings of isolation stemming from control aren’t isolated to her life or the world of reality TV. Delving Into Deep Waters Beyond the glitter and glamour of the reality show realm lay the dark undercurrents of Jill’s relationship with her family, especially her father, Jim Bob Duggar. Accusations fly high with claims of weaponizing her marriage and prioritizing the protection of her controversial brother, Josh Duggar, over her well-being. “Counting the Cost” boldly brings to light the estrangement with her father, hinting at a bond now filled with “hornets and garter snakes.” While the future remains uncertain, Jill remains hopeful, expressing, “I hope and pray that it does get better. I love my dad… I love my family so much. And I don’t want to hurt them.” Walking Away - No Regrets The decision to step away from the TV lens in 2017 wasn’t an easy one, yet Jill and Derick, looking back, have no second thoughts. Despite the love for their family, their need for autonomy and control over their narrative pushed them to make this monumental decision. “I wanted us to have more control of our lives,” states Jill, reflecting on the liberating sensation of being free from the reality show grind. The fears of detachment from the family loomed large, but the desire for a genuine life far from the cameras outweighed it all. A New Chapter With therapy as her guiding light and an unwavering faith, Jill Duggar is on a new journey. Her story, punctuated by highs and lows, serves as a testament to the strength of the human spirit. In her words, “Your story matters. Your voice matters.”</summary></entry></feed>