<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-10-14T08:27:50-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/14/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-14T08:27:50-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-14T08:27:50-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/14/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/14/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/14/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-14T08:27:50-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-14T08:27:50-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/14/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/14/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/">&lt;p&gt;Recent surprise attacks by Hamas on Israel has fueled ongoing tensions between staunchly conservative commentators and the progressive “Squad” Democrats known for criticizing Israel. The intensity of the backlash highlights the deep political divide over foreign policy in the Middle East.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Hamas’ shocking attack, several members of the “Squad,” including Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.), called for a “ceasefire and de-escalation,” condemning the violence. The absence of a statement from Rep. Rashida Tlaib (D-Mich.) was notably called out by conservative media outlets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;South Carolina GOP Rep. Nancy Mace quickly labeled Ocasio-Cortez a “Hamas apologist” in response to her call for peace and de-escalation. Rep. Ilhan Omar (D-Minn.), no stranger to controversy surrounding her views on Israel, echoed the call for de-escalation and ceasefire. Omar’s prior statements comparing the US and Israel to terrorist groups like Hamas and the Taliban resurfaced in the debate, fueling more criticisms. Omar’s 2019 tweet, where she opined that “Israel has hypnotized the world,” also continues to haunt her political career, often cited by critics to challenge her stance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conservative commentators have been especially vocal. “FOX &amp;amp; Friends Weekend” co-host Rachel Campos-Duffy took aim at Omar, saying she fails to recognize the peace in the Middle East under Trump’s administration. Conservative pundit John Hasson also called out Omar, claiming she insinuated that attacks on IDF forces were acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Massachusetts Democrat Rep. Ayanna Pressley’s concerns over the “devastating attacks on Israelis” were met with skepticism. A prominent conservative online personality, Comfortably Smug, accused the “Squad” of advising Israel to back down after the nation suffered massive attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Jamaal Bowman’s call for an end to the Gaza blockade, in addition to condemning the Hamas attacks, was met with criticism from conservative radio host Jason Rantz. He accused Bowman of pairing his condemnation of terrorism with unwarranted criticisms of Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Cori Bush emphasized the urgent need for a ceasefire, while pushing for an end to “U.S. support for Israeli military occupation and apartheid.” Defense attorney Marina Medvin criticized Bush, suggesting that she equates the death of Palestinian terrorists to the horrific acts committed against Jewish civilians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amidst the political turmoil and intense debate, the attacks have taken a heavy toll. Israeli media report over 300 dead due to the wide-ranging assault. Gaza health officials note that at least 200 Palestinians have perished in the retaliatory Israeli air strikes following the initial Hamas attack. As the situation remains volatile, both sides continue to count their casualties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This divisive issue showcases the challenge America faces in crafting a unified approach to foreign policy, with deeply entrenched political divides at play. As the situation develops, the debate is bound to intensify, shedding light on the complexities of U.S. politics in the global arena.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Hollywood Actors’ Strike Halts Amid Global ‘Day of Jihad’ Concerns</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/14/Hollywood-Actors-Strike-Safety/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hollywood Actors’ Strike Halts Amid Global ‘Day of Jihad’ Concerns" /><published>2023-10-14T08:01:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-14T08:01:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/14/Hollywood-Actors-Strike-Safety</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/14/Hollywood-Actors-Strike-Safety/">&lt;p&gt;Hollywood has always been a place of spectacle, but it’s not always about the latest blockbuster or red-carpet event. This year, the spotlight is on a strike by the members of SAG-AFTRA, Hollywood’s largest union representing actors and other media professionals. But what was supposed to be a demonstration of unity took a sudden turn when the union decided to halt picketing on Friday due to significant global security concerns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The decision came after Hamas, a Palestinian organization, declared a worldwide “Day of Jihad,” urging Muslims globally to take to the streets. While SAG-AFTRA’s leadership advised members to prioritize safety, they refrained from specifically mentioning the “Day of Jihad.” Instead, their statement simply urged members to “stay safe.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Major media outlets have presented varying interpretations of the Hamas declaration. While some labeled it a “day of rage” or “demonstrations,” others reported that Hamas described it as “The Friday of the Al-Aqsa Flood,” referencing a recent operation where the group initiated an attack that resulted in a tragic loss of over 1,200 Israeli lives. Regardless of the terminology, the message was clear: security forces worldwide braced themselves for potential unrest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In response to the impending event, the New York City Police Department (NYPD) took immediate action, directing all officers to be on duty in uniform on Friday, highlighting the gravity of the situation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s worth noting that SAG-AFTRA members initially began their strike on July 14, 2023, and have been in negotiations with studios since. This recent interruption in their protests comes after a surprising setback in their discussions. While the writers’ union successfully negotiated a new contract just days before, SAG-AFTRA’s recent proposals seemingly fell on deaf ears, leaving the entertainment industry in a state of uncertainty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This situation underscores the sometimes-unexpected interplay between global politics and the world of entertainment. With Hollywood actors pausing their strike due to concerns of potential global unrest, it’s a stark reminder that even the glittering world of showbiz is not immune to the larger events shaping our world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For now, as SAG-AFTRA members await further directives from their union leaders, the world watches, hoping for peaceful resolutions on both the entertainment and global fronts.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Hollywood has always been a place of spectacle, but it’s not always about the latest blockbuster or red-carpet event. This year, the spotlight is on a strike by the members of SAG-AFTRA, Hollywood’s largest union representing actors and other media professionals. But what was supposed to be a demonstration of unity took a sudden turn when the union decided to halt picketing on Friday due to significant global security concerns. The decision came after Hamas, a Palestinian organization, declared a worldwide “Day of Jihad,” urging Muslims globally to take to the streets. While SAG-AFTRA’s leadership advised members to prioritize safety, they refrained from specifically mentioning the “Day of Jihad.” Instead, their statement simply urged members to “stay safe.” Major media outlets have presented varying interpretations of the Hamas declaration. While some labeled it a “day of rage” or “demonstrations,” others reported that Hamas described it as “The Friday of the Al-Aqsa Flood,” referencing a recent operation where the group initiated an attack that resulted in a tragic loss of over 1,200 Israeli lives. Regardless of the terminology, the message was clear: security forces worldwide braced themselves for potential unrest. In response to the impending event, the New York City Police Department (NYPD) took immediate action, directing all officers to be on duty in uniform on Friday, highlighting the gravity of the situation. It’s worth noting that SAG-AFTRA members initially began their strike on July 14, 2023, and have been in negotiations with studios since. This recent interruption in their protests comes after a surprising setback in their discussions. While the writers’ union successfully negotiated a new contract just days before, SAG-AFTRA’s recent proposals seemingly fell on deaf ears, leaving the entertainment industry in a state of uncertainty. This situation underscores the sometimes-unexpected interplay between global politics and the world of entertainment. With Hollywood actors pausing their strike due to concerns of potential global unrest, it’s a stark reminder that even the glittering world of showbiz is not immune to the larger events shaping our world. For now, as SAG-AFTRA members await further directives from their union leaders, the world watches, hoping for peaceful resolutions on both the entertainment and global fronts.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">GOP’s Tug of War: Jim Jordan Secures Nomination, Yet House Speaker Seat Remains Vacant</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/14/GOP-Jim-Jordan-Nomination/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="GOP’s Tug of War: Jim Jordan Secures Nomination, Yet House Speaker Seat Remains Vacant" /><published>2023-10-14T07:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-14T07:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/14/GOP-Jim-Jordan-Nomination</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/14/GOP-Jim-Jordan-Nomination/">&lt;p&gt;The GOP’s search for the next House Speaker, one of the most powerful roles in U.S. politics, continues as Rep. Jim Jordan clinches the nomination but fails to secure enough votes to officially take on the role.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Friday, Jordan, a staunch conservative known for his vocal advocacy for the party’s right wing, earned the nomination to lead the U.S. House of Representatives. Notably, he has the backing of political heavyweights like former House Minority Leader Kevin McCarthy and former President Donald Trump, who’s currently leading the charge for the GOP’s 2024 presidential nomination.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the road to the speaker’s gavel is proving to be arduous for Jordan. In two consecutive voting rounds, he failed to achieve the 217 votes required, despite having the majority of House Republicans’ support. The initial vote saw Jordan triumph over Georgia lawmaker Austin Scott with a 124-81 vote. Subsequently, Jordan acquired a 152-55 victory in the second round but remained short of the necessary votes to assume the prestigious role.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This leadership crisis underscores the GOP’s internal struggles. Kevin McCarthy’s surprising ousting by a faction of Republican rebels on October 3rd left a void, making the party’s quest for a successor a central focus. Compounding these challenges are significant global events like the escalating Middle East war and Russia’s offensive on Ukraine. Moreover, with a looming government shutdown set for November 17, there’s an added urgency for the House to resolve its leadership quagmire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many within the GOP express concerns that go beyond finding the right leader. “There’s a lack of trust. There’s a lack of transparency,” noted Representative Kat Cammack, emphasizing the need to rebuild the party’s foundations before deciding on the House Speaker.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, Jordan’s nomination journey had an earlier setback when he lost to Steve Scalise, a frontrunner for the role. But Scalise’s aspirations were short-lived, as he soon abandoned his bid when uniting the Republicans behind him proved challenging.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amid these challenges, Jordan remains optimistic. “I think I can unite the conference, I think I can tell the country what we’re doing and why it matters,” he confidently shared with reporters pre-vote. Advocates for Jordan, like Representative Nicole Malliotakis, emphasize his resilience and negotiating prowess, especially when dealing with Democratic adversaries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the path forward remains murky. The last two Republican Speakers, John Boehner and Paul Ryan, faced intense pressure from the party’s right-wing factions. The GOP hopes to avoid past embarrassments and unite behind a strong leader who can navigate the tumultuous political landscape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For now, the wait continues, with the decisive vote for the next House Speaker slated for Monday at 6 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">The GOP’s search for the next House Speaker, one of the most powerful roles in U.S. politics, continues as Rep. Jim Jordan clinches the nomination but fails to secure enough votes to officially take on the role. On Friday, Jordan, a staunch conservative known for his vocal advocacy for the party’s right wing, earned the nomination to lead the U.S. House of Representatives. Notably, he has the backing of political heavyweights like former House Minority Leader Kevin McCarthy and former President Donald Trump, who’s currently leading the charge for the GOP’s 2024 presidential nomination. However, the road to the speaker’s gavel is proving to be arduous for Jordan. In two consecutive voting rounds, he failed to achieve the 217 votes required, despite having the majority of House Republicans’ support. The initial vote saw Jordan triumph over Georgia lawmaker Austin Scott with a 124-81 vote. Subsequently, Jordan acquired a 152-55 victory in the second round but remained short of the necessary votes to assume the prestigious role. This leadership crisis underscores the GOP’s internal struggles. Kevin McCarthy’s surprising ousting by a faction of Republican rebels on October 3rd left a void, making the party’s quest for a successor a central focus. Compounding these challenges are significant global events like the escalating Middle East war and Russia’s offensive on Ukraine. Moreover, with a looming government shutdown set for November 17, there’s an added urgency for the House to resolve its leadership quagmire. Many within the GOP express concerns that go beyond finding the right leader. “There’s a lack of trust. There’s a lack of transparency,” noted Representative Kat Cammack, emphasizing the need to rebuild the party’s foundations before deciding on the House Speaker. Interestingly, Jordan’s nomination journey had an earlier setback when he lost to Steve Scalise, a frontrunner for the role. But Scalise’s aspirations were short-lived, as he soon abandoned his bid when uniting the Republicans behind him proved challenging. Amid these challenges, Jordan remains optimistic. “I think I can unite the conference, I think I can tell the country what we’re doing and why it matters,” he confidently shared with reporters pre-vote. Advocates for Jordan, like Representative Nicole Malliotakis, emphasize his resilience and negotiating prowess, especially when dealing with Democratic adversaries. However, the path forward remains murky. The last two Republican Speakers, John Boehner and Paul Ryan, faced intense pressure from the party’s right-wing factions. The GOP hopes to avoid past embarrassments and unite behind a strong leader who can navigate the tumultuous political landscape. For now, the wait continues, with the decisive vote for the next House Speaker slated for Monday at 6 p.m.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Pro-Palestinian Protesters Arrested Outside Schumer’s NYC Residence</title><link href="/news/2023/10/14/Protest-NYC-Schumer/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Pro-Palestinian Protesters Arrested Outside Schumer’s NYC Residence" /><published>2023-10-14T06:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-14T06:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/14/Protest-NYC-Schumer</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/14/Protest-NYC-Schumer/">&lt;p&gt;Amid the heightened tensions and ongoing demonstrations surrounding the Israel-Hamas conflict, Senator Chuck Schumer’s New York City apartment became the center of attention on Friday night. Schumer, the Senate Majority Leader from New York, witnessed a pro-Palestinian protest right outside his residence, leading to several arrests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The protest, as confirmed by Fox News Digital, unfolded during the senator’s intimate Shabbat dinner with family. The gathering was particularly timely, as Schumer is on the cusp of a pivotal journey to Israel as part of a bipartisan CODEL (Congressional Delegation) trip set for the weekend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although the exact number of arrests remains undisclosed, a police spokesperson confirmed that multiple protesters were taken into custody. The incident in front of Schumer’s apartment is just one of several pro-Palestinian protests that have been staged across New York City in recent times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sen. Schumer has been a focal point of discussions lately, not only due to his prominent position in the Senate but also due to his imminent Israel trip. The visit is drawing attention as it’s expected to bring together a delegation of bipartisan lawmakers, aiming for constructive dialogues and strengthening ties amidst volatile times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earlier on the same day, another separate protest saw confrontations escalate between participants, resulting in the arrest of at least two individuals. Footage emerging from this demonstration showcased a sizable group of passionate protesters vocally demanding the release of the detained, chanting “Set him free!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The backdrop to these events is the devastating Israel-Hamas war, a conflict that has tragically claimed numerous lives. Current figures indicate that at least 2,800 people have lost their lives in this war, including a minimum of 1,200 innocent Israeli civilians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In an era of social and political upheaval, the role of the U.S. and its leaders in navigating these tumultuous waters is crucial. As Senator Schumer prepares for his visit to Israel, these protests in his home city underscore the complexities and emotional intensity surrounding the conflict.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the world watches, there’s hope that such bipartisan trips might pave the way for constructive dialogues, mutual understanding, and, ultimately, lasting peace in the region.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Amid the heightened tensions and ongoing demonstrations surrounding the Israel-Hamas conflict, Senator Chuck Schumer’s New York City apartment became the center of attention on Friday night. Schumer, the Senate Majority Leader from New York, witnessed a pro-Palestinian protest right outside his residence, leading to several arrests. The protest, as confirmed by Fox News Digital, unfolded during the senator’s intimate Shabbat dinner with family. The gathering was particularly timely, as Schumer is on the cusp of a pivotal journey to Israel as part of a bipartisan CODEL (Congressional Delegation) trip set for the weekend. Although the exact number of arrests remains undisclosed, a police spokesperson confirmed that multiple protesters were taken into custody. The incident in front of Schumer’s apartment is just one of several pro-Palestinian protests that have been staged across New York City in recent times. Sen. Schumer has been a focal point of discussions lately, not only due to his prominent position in the Senate but also due to his imminent Israel trip. The visit is drawing attention as it’s expected to bring together a delegation of bipartisan lawmakers, aiming for constructive dialogues and strengthening ties amidst volatile times. Earlier on the same day, another separate protest saw confrontations escalate between participants, resulting in the arrest of at least two individuals. Footage emerging from this demonstration showcased a sizable group of passionate protesters vocally demanding the release of the detained, chanting “Set him free!” The backdrop to these events is the devastating Israel-Hamas war, a conflict that has tragically claimed numerous lives. Current figures indicate that at least 2,800 people have lost their lives in this war, including a minimum of 1,200 innocent Israeli civilians. In an era of social and political upheaval, the role of the U.S. and its leaders in navigating these tumultuous waters is crucial. As Senator Schumer prepares for his visit to Israel, these protests in his home city underscore the complexities and emotional intensity surrounding the conflict. As the world watches, there’s hope that such bipartisan trips might pave the way for constructive dialogues, mutual understanding, and, ultimately, lasting peace in the region.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Drunken Intruder’s Midnight Romp in Kid’s Room Interrupted by Armed Dad</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/13/North-Dakota-Intrusion/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Drunken Intruder’s Midnight Romp in Kid’s Room Interrupted by Armed Dad" /><published>2023-10-13T15:07:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-13T15:07:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/13/North-Dakota-Intrusion</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/13/North-Dakota-Intrusion/">&lt;p&gt;In a bizarre incident that recently unfolded in North Dakota, a homeowner was confronted with the alarming sight of a naked and heavily inebriated man wreaking havoc in his daughter’s bedroom. The shocking event, taking place in the early hours, is a stark reminder of the unpredictability and potential dangers lurking even in familiar surroundings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the silent hours of a Friday morning, the family’s peace was shattered by loud banging noises resonating from within their residence. On investigating the disturbance, the father discovered the intruder, later identified as Alvin Ducheneaux, causing a ruckus in his daughter’s unoccupied room, tossing toys and clothes around in wild abandon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a swift response to the unexpected intrusion, the father grabbed his firearm and held Ducheneaux at gunpoint, while instructing his wife to immediately alert the police. Bismarck Police Department promptly arrived at the West Bowen Avenue residence, finding the scene as reported.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The turn of events raises questions on home security and the importance of remaining vigilant. The intruder, Ducheneaux, reportedly made his way into the home through an unlocked back door after the family had turned in for the night. On top of the sheer audacity of his naked intrusion, Ducheneaux compounded his criminal act by inflicting damage on the property, destroying a shoe rack and causing an estimated $200 worth of damage in the child’s room.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the exact motivations behind Ducheneaux’s actions remain unclear, the homeowners speculate that the inebriated man might have confused their home with a neighbor’s. This possibility, however faint, highlights the complexities and dangers of intoxication, with the potential for unexpected and severe consequences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The aftermath of the incident saw Ducheneaux charged with several offenses, including Burglary, Night (Class B Felony), Criminal Mischief, Willful Damage (Class B Misdemeanor), and Disorderly Conduct, Offensive Condition (Class B Misdemeanor). The seriousness of his actions has landed him in the local jail with a $5,000 cash bond. With his court appearance slated for November, Ducheneaux may confront up to a decade in prison for the felony charge alone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The shocking incident serves as a wakeup call for residents everywhere about the significance of home security and the unpredictable nature of such occurrences. As the family grapples with the aftermath of this startling episode, communities are reminded to remain vigilant and prioritize the safety of their homes and loved ones.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a bizarre incident that recently unfolded in North Dakota, a homeowner was confronted with the alarming sight of a naked and heavily inebriated man wreaking havoc in his daughter’s bedroom. The shocking event, taking place in the early hours, is a stark reminder of the unpredictability and potential dangers lurking even in familiar surroundings. In the silent hours of a Friday morning, the family’s peace was shattered by loud banging noises resonating from within their residence. On investigating the disturbance, the father discovered the intruder, later identified as Alvin Ducheneaux, causing a ruckus in his daughter’s unoccupied room, tossing toys and clothes around in wild abandon. In a swift response to the unexpected intrusion, the father grabbed his firearm and held Ducheneaux at gunpoint, while instructing his wife to immediately alert the police. Bismarck Police Department promptly arrived at the West Bowen Avenue residence, finding the scene as reported. The turn of events raises questions on home security and the importance of remaining vigilant. The intruder, Ducheneaux, reportedly made his way into the home through an unlocked back door after the family had turned in for the night. On top of the sheer audacity of his naked intrusion, Ducheneaux compounded his criminal act by inflicting damage on the property, destroying a shoe rack and causing an estimated $200 worth of damage in the child’s room. While the exact motivations behind Ducheneaux’s actions remain unclear, the homeowners speculate that the inebriated man might have confused their home with a neighbor’s. This possibility, however faint, highlights the complexities and dangers of intoxication, with the potential for unexpected and severe consequences. The aftermath of the incident saw Ducheneaux charged with several offenses, including Burglary, Night (Class B Felony), Criminal Mischief, Willful Damage (Class B Misdemeanor), and Disorderly Conduct, Offensive Condition (Class B Misdemeanor). The seriousness of his actions has landed him in the local jail with a $5,000 cash bond. With his court appearance slated for November, Ducheneaux may confront up to a decade in prison for the felony charge alone. The shocking incident serves as a wakeup call for residents everywhere about the significance of home security and the unpredictable nature of such occurrences. As the family grapples with the aftermath of this startling episode, communities are reminded to remain vigilant and prioritize the safety of their homes and loved ones.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">US Gears Up for Dual Threats: Is Defense Ready for Russia and China?</title><link href="/news/2023/10/13/US-Defense-Strategy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="US Gears Up for Dual Threats: Is Defense Ready for Russia and China?" /><published>2023-10-13T13:59:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-13T13:59:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/13/US-Defense-Strategy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/13/US-Defense-Strategy/">&lt;p&gt;Amid the rapidly evolving geopolitical landscape, a bipartisan panel appointed by Congress has sounded the alarm: the United States must bolster its defense mechanisms in readiness for potential simultaneous conflicts with Russia and China.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The findings, presented by the Strategic Posture Commission, come in the wake of escalating tensions. With China’s assertiveness over Taiwan and Russia’s controversial invasion of Ukraine, the international scene is heating up. Although no clear evidence indicates active nuclear cooperation between China and Russia, there are concerns of potential strategic coordination.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This report’s implications are immense. It essentially challenges the current US national security strategy, which revolves around deterring one conflict while winning another. Implementing the recommended changes would mean a considerable uptick in defense expenditure, the feasibility of which remains to be seen given the constraints of the congressional budget.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Acknowledging the financial implications, the report’s preface, penned by Democratic chair Madelyn Creedon, and vice-chair Jon Kyl, underscores the nation’s need for these investments. During the report’s release, Kyl further emphasized the importance of rallying public support for increased defense spending, arguing that it’s a minimal price for potentially averting a full-blown nuclear war involving the major players: the US, China, and Russia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These findings starkly contrast with President Joe Biden’s stance, which leans towards the sufficiency of the current US nuclear arsenal in deterring combined threats from Russia and China. Responses from advocacy groups like the Arms Control Association echo this sentiment, suggesting that the existing arsenal already surpasses deterrent needs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the Strategic Posture Commission remains firm: to uphold the values of the U.S.-led international order, the nation and its allies must be adequately equipped to deter and overcome both adversaries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Created in 2022, this panel of equal Democratic and Republican representation set out to evaluate long-term threats and suggest modifications in the US’s defense approach. Their evaluation warns of the acute threats from China and Russia, especially between 2027-2035. As China expands its nuclear arsenal – projected to reach 1,500 warheads by 2035 – the US faces the challenge of contending with two primary nuclear adversaries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 145-page report is comprehensive, advocating for the complete funding of the 30-year US nuclear arms modernization program initiated in 2010. Among the many recommendations, it pushes for the deployment of increased tactical nuclear weapons across Asia and Europe, more B-21 stealth bombers, new Columbia-class nuclear submarines, and consideration for deploying reserve US nuclear warheads.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ultimate takeaway? The US needs to amplify the “size, type, and posture” of its conventional forces in collaboration with allies. Without these enhancements, the nation might find itself leaning heavily on its nuclear arsenal – a situation the world would be better off avoiding.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Amid the rapidly evolving geopolitical landscape, a bipartisan panel appointed by Congress has sounded the alarm: the United States must bolster its defense mechanisms in readiness for potential simultaneous conflicts with Russia and China. The findings, presented by the Strategic Posture Commission, come in the wake of escalating tensions. With China’s assertiveness over Taiwan and Russia’s controversial invasion of Ukraine, the international scene is heating up. Although no clear evidence indicates active nuclear cooperation between China and Russia, there are concerns of potential strategic coordination. This report’s implications are immense. It essentially challenges the current US national security strategy, which revolves around deterring one conflict while winning another. Implementing the recommended changes would mean a considerable uptick in defense expenditure, the feasibility of which remains to be seen given the constraints of the congressional budget. Acknowledging the financial implications, the report’s preface, penned by Democratic chair Madelyn Creedon, and vice-chair Jon Kyl, underscores the nation’s need for these investments. During the report’s release, Kyl further emphasized the importance of rallying public support for increased defense spending, arguing that it’s a minimal price for potentially averting a full-blown nuclear war involving the major players: the US, China, and Russia. These findings starkly contrast with President Joe Biden’s stance, which leans towards the sufficiency of the current US nuclear arsenal in deterring combined threats from Russia and China. Responses from advocacy groups like the Arms Control Association echo this sentiment, suggesting that the existing arsenal already surpasses deterrent needs. However, the Strategic Posture Commission remains firm: to uphold the values of the U.S.-led international order, the nation and its allies must be adequately equipped to deter and overcome both adversaries. Created in 2022, this panel of equal Democratic and Republican representation set out to evaluate long-term threats and suggest modifications in the US’s defense approach. Their evaluation warns of the acute threats from China and Russia, especially between 2027-2035. As China expands its nuclear arsenal – projected to reach 1,500 warheads by 2035 – the US faces the challenge of contending with two primary nuclear adversaries. The 145-page report is comprehensive, advocating for the complete funding of the 30-year US nuclear arms modernization program initiated in 2010. Among the many recommendations, it pushes for the deployment of increased tactical nuclear weapons across Asia and Europe, more B-21 stealth bombers, new Columbia-class nuclear submarines, and consideration for deploying reserve US nuclear warheads. The ultimate takeaway? The US needs to amplify the “size, type, and posture” of its conventional forces in collaboration with allies. Without these enhancements, the nation might find itself leaning heavily on its nuclear arsenal – a situation the world would be better off avoiding.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Biden’s Dual Focus: Standing with Israel and Addressing Economic Concerns</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/13/Biden-Israel-Junk-Fees/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Biden’s Dual Focus: Standing with Israel and Addressing Economic Concerns" /><published>2023-10-13T12:45:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-13T12:45:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/13/Biden-Israel-Junk-Fees</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/13/Biden-Israel-Junk-Fees/">&lt;p&gt;As the political landscape gets more intricate by the day, President Joe Biden reaffirms his commitment to standing by Israel during its ongoing conflict, while simultaneously addressing domestic concerns, particularly the economic “junk fees.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;John Kirby, White House National Security Council Coordinator for Strategic Communications, recently shared insights on MSNBC’s “The Beat” concerning the President’s plan of action. Kirby emphasized Biden’s dedication to continuously discuss the Middle East conflict and assure unwavering support for Israel. This commitment is further cemented by Biden’s endeavors to release hostages held by Hamas and to express solidarity with the affected families.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the domestic front, the President’s plate is no less full. Economic challenges, particularly the so-called “junk fees,” are at the forefront of his concerns. Kirby highlights that addressing these issues is crucial in governing and demonstrates the President’s capacity to multitask – dealing with pressing global concerns while not sidelining urgent domestic matters. As Kirby succinctly put it, “That’s what being President is, that’s what being commander-in-chief is. You’ve got to handle it all, and he’s more than equipped and more than ready to do that.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given the global importance of the ongoing Middle East conflict, Ari Melber, the host of the show, questioned whether President Biden would consider addressing the nation or Congress formally. Kirby’s response, though non-specific, hinted at future communications from the President on the subject. However, he also mentioned that President Biden would touch upon other international topics, including situations in Ukraine and the Indo-Pacific region.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The dual focus of President Biden – emphasizing unwavering support for allies in distress and tackling domestic issues head-on – paints a picture of a leader capable of multitasking on the global stage. As the days ahead promise more challenges, both internationally and domestically, America waits to hear more from the Commander-in-Chief, hoping for resolutions and pathways to a more secure future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In an era where news cycles shift rapidly, and global events can often overshadow domestic concerns, Biden’s commitment to juggle both with equal fervor marks a significant leadership stance. As the nation and the world continue to evolve and confront new challenges, such leadership traits will be crucial in steering the course.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">As the political landscape gets more intricate by the day, President Joe Biden reaffirms his commitment to standing by Israel during its ongoing conflict, while simultaneously addressing domestic concerns, particularly the economic “junk fees.” John Kirby, White House National Security Council Coordinator for Strategic Communications, recently shared insights on MSNBC’s “The Beat” concerning the President’s plan of action. Kirby emphasized Biden’s dedication to continuously discuss the Middle East conflict and assure unwavering support for Israel. This commitment is further cemented by Biden’s endeavors to release hostages held by Hamas and to express solidarity with the affected families. On the domestic front, the President’s plate is no less full. Economic challenges, particularly the so-called “junk fees,” are at the forefront of his concerns. Kirby highlights that addressing these issues is crucial in governing and demonstrates the President’s capacity to multitask – dealing with pressing global concerns while not sidelining urgent domestic matters. As Kirby succinctly put it, “That’s what being President is, that’s what being commander-in-chief is. You’ve got to handle it all, and he’s more than equipped and more than ready to do that.” Given the global importance of the ongoing Middle East conflict, Ari Melber, the host of the show, questioned whether President Biden would consider addressing the nation or Congress formally. Kirby’s response, though non-specific, hinted at future communications from the President on the subject. However, he also mentioned that President Biden would touch upon other international topics, including situations in Ukraine and the Indo-Pacific region. The dual focus of President Biden – emphasizing unwavering support for allies in distress and tackling domestic issues head-on – paints a picture of a leader capable of multitasking on the global stage. As the days ahead promise more challenges, both internationally and domestically, America waits to hear more from the Commander-in-Chief, hoping for resolutions and pathways to a more secure future. In an era where news cycles shift rapidly, and global events can often overshadow domestic concerns, Biden’s commitment to juggle both with equal fervor marks a significant leadership stance. As the nation and the world continue to evolve and confront new challenges, such leadership traits will be crucial in steering the course.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Dramatic Confrontation in Minnesota: Five Officers Shot During Warrant Service</title><link href="/news/2023/10/13/Minnesota-Officers-Shot/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dramatic Confrontation in Minnesota: Five Officers Shot During Warrant Service" /><published>2023-10-13T11:30:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-13T11:30:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/13/Minnesota-Officers-Shot</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/13/Minnesota-Officers-Shot/">&lt;p&gt;A tense situation unfurled in Glendorado Township, Minnesota, as five officers came under fire while serving a warrant on Thursday morning. Thankfully, the injuries sustained by the officers are not believed to be life-threatening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The individual responsible for the gunfire was promptly apprehended and airlifted from the crime scene, as reported by FOX9 Minneapolis. The details surrounding the suspect’s apprehension remain under wraps. This incident garnered significant attention, with various public safety agencies assisting the Benton County Sheriff’s Office during this “critical incident.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Three of the officers injured during the altercation received medical attention at the North Memorial Health Hospital, while the remaining two were taken to a medical facility in St. Cloud. Robbinsdale Police Capt. John Elder confirmed that these officers hailed from multiple law enforcement agencies. He further reiterated the non-critical nature of their injuries, bringing a sigh of relief to concerned citizens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The vivid imagery captured by local news showcased an array of law enforcement vehicles congregating at the scene. Officers, donning tactical gear, were visibly alert and vigilant. FOX9 Minneapolis KMSP featured footage of an armored vehicle patrolling the outskirts of a field, highlighting the gravity of the situation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s been an increase in public interest around events that concern law enforcement, and this incident has been no exception. The state Bureau of Criminal Apprehension confirmed their involvement in the response, pointing to the significance of the situation and the necessity for coordinated efforts across agencies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Such incidents underscore the myriad risks law enforcement officers face while performing their duties. Their commitment to maintaining public safety often places them in perilous situations, which, at times, escalate dramatically, as seen in Glendorado Township.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the community awaits more details surrounding the incident and the circumstances leading up to it, the overarching sentiment remains one of gratitude for the officers’ safety and swift response by backup units. The collaborative efforts of various agencies highlight the unity and commitment of the broader law enforcement community in Minnesota and across the country.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Residents of Glendorado Township and surrounding areas will undoubtedly remain watchful for further updates. Meanwhile, the incident serves as a poignant reminder of the challenges and uncertainties that come with upholding law and order.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">A tense situation unfurled in Glendorado Township, Minnesota, as five officers came under fire while serving a warrant on Thursday morning. Thankfully, the injuries sustained by the officers are not believed to be life-threatening. The individual responsible for the gunfire was promptly apprehended and airlifted from the crime scene, as reported by FOX9 Minneapolis. The details surrounding the suspect’s apprehension remain under wraps. This incident garnered significant attention, with various public safety agencies assisting the Benton County Sheriff’s Office during this “critical incident.” Three of the officers injured during the altercation received medical attention at the North Memorial Health Hospital, while the remaining two were taken to a medical facility in St. Cloud. Robbinsdale Police Capt. John Elder confirmed that these officers hailed from multiple law enforcement agencies. He further reiterated the non-critical nature of their injuries, bringing a sigh of relief to concerned citizens. The vivid imagery captured by local news showcased an array of law enforcement vehicles congregating at the scene. Officers, donning tactical gear, were visibly alert and vigilant. FOX9 Minneapolis KMSP featured footage of an armored vehicle patrolling the outskirts of a field, highlighting the gravity of the situation. There’s been an increase in public interest around events that concern law enforcement, and this incident has been no exception. The state Bureau of Criminal Apprehension confirmed their involvement in the response, pointing to the significance of the situation and the necessity for coordinated efforts across agencies. Such incidents underscore the myriad risks law enforcement officers face while performing their duties. Their commitment to maintaining public safety often places them in perilous situations, which, at times, escalate dramatically, as seen in Glendorado Township. As the community awaits more details surrounding the incident and the circumstances leading up to it, the overarching sentiment remains one of gratitude for the officers’ safety and swift response by backup units. The collaborative efforts of various agencies highlight the unity and commitment of the broader law enforcement community in Minnesota and across the country. Residents of Glendorado Township and surrounding areas will undoubtedly remain watchful for further updates. Meanwhile, the incident serves as a poignant reminder of the challenges and uncertainties that come with upholding law and order.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Inflation Tremors Rock Wall Street: Key Indexes Slide as Rates Rise</title><link href="/news/2023/10/13/Wall-Street-Inflation/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Inflation Tremors Rock Wall Street: Key Indexes Slide as Rates Rise" /><published>2023-10-13T10:23:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-13T10:23:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/13/Wall-Street-Inflation</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/13/Wall-Street-Inflation/">&lt;p&gt;Wall Street found itself on a tumultuous ride this Thursday as surging inflation figures sent shockwaves through the market. Key indexes took a hit, with investors closely watching as U.S. Treasury bond yields climbed, and consumer prices surged higher than initial projections for September.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The rise in consumer prices can be attributed to mounting shelter costs. However, if we set aside the inconsistent food and energy sectors, the yearly growth in the core figure is the lowest it’s been in two years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Early trading saw the S&amp;amp;P 500 wavering between profits and losses. But by 1 p.m. EDT, after a U.S. Treasury auction for 30-year bonds witnessed lukewarm demand, the index took a definitive downturn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Michael James, the Managing Director of Equity Trading at Wedbush Securities in Los Angeles, highlighted, “The past two months have seen the market grappling with escalating interest rates. Any substantial fluctuation can lead to noticeable ripples in equities.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Post-auction, the S&amp;amp;P 500 recorded a dip of 27.50 points (0.63%), settling at 4,349.45 points. The Nasdaq Composite wasn’t spared either, dropping by 85.46 points (0.63%) to reach 13,574.22. Meanwhile, the Dow Jones Industrial Average slid by 173.77 points (0.51%) and stood at 33,631.10.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;U.S. benchmark 10-year yields observed a spike after unveiling the inflation data, reaching a high of 4.728% following a two-day decline. This upsurge primarily weighed down on rate-sensitive sectors like utilities and real estate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Simultaneously, the iShares Home Construction ETF experienced a drop, and the homebuilding stocks felt the pressure, especially with the afternoon surge in bond yields.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, not all sectors felt the heat equally. Energy and information technology sectors of the S&amp;amp;P 500 appeared to be relatively more resilient during the trading hours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the present climate, traders predict a probable interest-rate hike by the Federal Reserve before year-end, followed by sustained higher rates into the next year. Boston Fed President, Susan Collins, hinted at more potential interest rate hikes, emphasizing their goal to align inflation back to its target.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In other news, Israel continues its operations in the Gaza Strip, with a focus on securing its hostages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As Wall Street braces itself, investors are keenly waiting for the earnings season, set to kick off this Friday. Financial giants like JPMorgan Chase, Wells Fargo, and Citigroup are scheduled to reveal their quarterly results before the trading bell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the stocks’ front, Fastenal saw a surge post beating their third-quarter profit predictions. Conversely, Ford Motor witnessed a decline after the United Auto Workers (UAW) union broadened its strike at Ford’s most lucrative factory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With financial landscapes constantly evolving, Wall Street remains the epicenter of activity, drawing attention from global investors as they navigate the ebb and flow of the market.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Wall Street found itself on a tumultuous ride this Thursday as surging inflation figures sent shockwaves through the market. Key indexes took a hit, with investors closely watching as U.S. Treasury bond yields climbed, and consumer prices surged higher than initial projections for September. The rise in consumer prices can be attributed to mounting shelter costs. However, if we set aside the inconsistent food and energy sectors, the yearly growth in the core figure is the lowest it’s been in two years. Early trading saw the S&amp;amp;P 500 wavering between profits and losses. But by 1 p.m. EDT, after a U.S. Treasury auction for 30-year bonds witnessed lukewarm demand, the index took a definitive downturn. Michael James, the Managing Director of Equity Trading at Wedbush Securities in Los Angeles, highlighted, “The past two months have seen the market grappling with escalating interest rates. Any substantial fluctuation can lead to noticeable ripples in equities.” Post-auction, the S&amp;amp;P 500 recorded a dip of 27.50 points (0.63%), settling at 4,349.45 points. The Nasdaq Composite wasn’t spared either, dropping by 85.46 points (0.63%) to reach 13,574.22. Meanwhile, the Dow Jones Industrial Average slid by 173.77 points (0.51%) and stood at 33,631.10. U.S. benchmark 10-year yields observed a spike after unveiling the inflation data, reaching a high of 4.728% following a two-day decline. This upsurge primarily weighed down on rate-sensitive sectors like utilities and real estate. Simultaneously, the iShares Home Construction ETF experienced a drop, and the homebuilding stocks felt the pressure, especially with the afternoon surge in bond yields. However, not all sectors felt the heat equally. Energy and information technology sectors of the S&amp;amp;P 500 appeared to be relatively more resilient during the trading hours. With the present climate, traders predict a probable interest-rate hike by the Federal Reserve before year-end, followed by sustained higher rates into the next year. Boston Fed President, Susan Collins, hinted at more potential interest rate hikes, emphasizing their goal to align inflation back to its target. In other news, Israel continues its operations in the Gaza Strip, with a focus on securing its hostages. As Wall Street braces itself, investors are keenly waiting for the earnings season, set to kick off this Friday. Financial giants like JPMorgan Chase, Wells Fargo, and Citigroup are scheduled to reveal their quarterly results before the trading bell. On the stocks’ front, Fastenal saw a surge post beating their third-quarter profit predictions. Conversely, Ford Motor witnessed a decline after the United Auto Workers (UAW) union broadened its strike at Ford’s most lucrative factory. With financial landscapes constantly evolving, Wall Street remains the epicenter of activity, drawing attention from global investors as they navigate the ebb and flow of the market.</summary></entry></feed>