<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-09-13T22:20:35-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/09/13/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-09-13T22:20:35-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-13T22:20:35-04:00</updated><id>/2023/09/13/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/13/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Virginia Candidate’s Web Antics - A Brazen Display of Poor Judgment?</title><link href="/news/2023/09/13/Virginia-Candidate-Scandal/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Virginia Candidate’s Web Antics - A Brazen Display of Poor Judgment?" /><published>2023-09-13T18:43:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-13T18:43:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/13/Virginia-Candidate-Scandal</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/13/Virginia-Candidate-Scandal/">&lt;p&gt;In an era where the line between private and public life is increasingly blurred, revelations regarding the personal choices of individuals seeking public office have emerged once more. Susanna Gibson, a Democratic contender for a pivotal seat in the Virginia House of Delegates, has recently come under scrutiny for her online activities, a series of questionable decisions that cast doubt on her fitness for public service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though Gibson is involved in a tight race for her seat, her online behavior seems to have overshadowed her political aspirations. As reported by reputable sources, including the far-left Associated Press, Gibson engaged in explicit acts alongside her husband, broadcasted live for a global audience. What’s even more startling is her monetization approach – charging viewers for specific requests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One might argue that what someone does in their personal life is their business alone, but Gibson’s actions were far from private. Her online handle, “HotWifeExperience,” reveals a calculated choice to parade these exploits on Chaturbate, a platform that merges the worlds of chat and adult entertainment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gibson’s attempts to rationalize her actions, labeling them as “fundraising” endeavors for her campaign, only magnify the recklessness of her decisions. She went so far as to claim the videos going public as some form of “sex crime.” However, by definition, revenge porn entails the dissemination of private photos or videos out of malice. Gibson’s content was available on a public platform, making it crystal clear that she intended for these videos to be consumed by the masses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The implications of this revelation go beyond just personal indiscretion. It calls into question Gibson’s decision-making capabilities, her vulnerability to potential blackmail, and the ethical boundaries she’s willing to cross.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though her opponent, Republican David Owen, has opted for a compassionate stance, focusing solely on his campaign, the underlying concern remains. Would Gibson’s unchecked actions leave her susceptible to external influence?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In an era that demands transparency and accountability from public officials, Gibson’s actions serve as a reminder that character, integrity, and judgment remain paramount. Voters, now more than ever, need representatives who not only champion their causes but also reflect the values and principles they hold dear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It remains to be seen how this scandal will affect the upcoming elections, but one thing is certain: it’s a stark reminder of the weight of choices and the magnifying lens of public office.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In an era where the line between private and public life is increasingly blurred, revelations regarding the personal choices of individuals seeking public office have emerged once more. Susanna Gibson, a Democratic contender for a pivotal seat in the Virginia House of Delegates, has recently come under scrutiny for her online activities, a series of questionable decisions that cast doubt on her fitness for public service. Though Gibson is involved in a tight race for her seat, her online behavior seems to have overshadowed her political aspirations. As reported by reputable sources, including the far-left Associated Press, Gibson engaged in explicit acts alongside her husband, broadcasted live for a global audience. What’s even more startling is her monetization approach – charging viewers for specific requests. One might argue that what someone does in their personal life is their business alone, but Gibson’s actions were far from private. Her online handle, “HotWifeExperience,” reveals a calculated choice to parade these exploits on Chaturbate, a platform that merges the worlds of chat and adult entertainment. Gibson’s attempts to rationalize her actions, labeling them as “fundraising” endeavors for her campaign, only magnify the recklessness of her decisions. She went so far as to claim the videos going public as some form of “sex crime.” However, by definition, revenge porn entails the dissemination of private photos or videos out of malice. Gibson’s content was available on a public platform, making it crystal clear that she intended for these videos to be consumed by the masses. The implications of this revelation go beyond just personal indiscretion. It calls into question Gibson’s decision-making capabilities, her vulnerability to potential blackmail, and the ethical boundaries she’s willing to cross. Though her opponent, Republican David Owen, has opted for a compassionate stance, focusing solely on his campaign, the underlying concern remains. Would Gibson’s unchecked actions leave her susceptible to external influence? In an era that demands transparency and accountability from public officials, Gibson’s actions serve as a reminder that character, integrity, and judgment remain paramount. Voters, now more than ever, need representatives who not only champion their causes but also reflect the values and principles they hold dear. It remains to be seen how this scandal will affect the upcoming elections, but one thing is certain: it’s a stark reminder of the weight of choices and the magnifying lens of public office.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hunter Biden’s Attorneys Under Fire - Accusations of Intimidating IRS Whistleblowers Emerge</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/13/Biden-Attorneys-Accused/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hunter Biden’s Attorneys Under Fire - Accusations of Intimidating IRS Whistleblowers Emerge" /><published>2023-09-13T17:42:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-13T17:42:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/13/Biden-Attorneys-Accused</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/13/Biden-Attorneys-Accused/">&lt;p&gt;In a rapidly escalating political development, House Republicans have addressed a strongly-worded letter to Attorney General Merrick Garland. This letter, penned by prominent Republican figures, alleges that Hunter Biden’s legal team actively sought to “intimidate and harass” two key whistleblowers from the Internal Revenue Service (IRS) during the ongoing tax investigation into the President’s son.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reps. Jim Jordan (R-OH), Jason Smith (R-MO), and James Comer (R-KY) named the IRS whistleblowers as Gary Shapley and Joseph Ziegler. These individuals recently came forward, suggesting that political machinations interfered with prosecutorial decisions spanning the extensive federal examination of Hunter Biden.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Notably, the letter levels severe accusations at Biden’s attorneys, asserting they “slandered” Shapley and Ziegler, painting them as “disgruntled”. Furthermore, it contends that Biden’s legal team pressured the Department of Justice to seek prosecution against these whistleblowers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Federal law safeguards whistleblowers from undue retaliation. The overt efforts to coerce these whistleblowers spark grave concerns about possible obstructions in our Committees’ inquiry,” the GOP leaders penned in the letter. They subsequently requested details on any endeavors by Hunter Biden’s lawyers to coax the Department into taking punitive action against the mentioned IRS whistleblowers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a revealing highlight, the letter references a New York Times report. According to this article, Biden’s legal team argued with the Justice Department that the whistleblowers “violated the law by sharing investigation details with Congress and should consequently face legal proceedings.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the clock ticking, the Republicans have given the DOJ a deadline until September 26, 5 p.m., to present any correspondences from Hunter Biden’s attorneys that “call for the investigation or prosecution” of the whistleblowers. Additionally, any documented communication between Biden’s lawyers and the DOJ about potential criminal investigations against Shapley or Ziegler is also sought.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the horizon, Attorney General Garland is slated to appear before the House Judiciary Committee on September 20 for a routine oversight hearing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This news coincides with the expectation that House Speaker Kevin McCarthy (R-CA) will soon endorse an impeachment inquiry into President Biden, focusing on allegations tied to his son’s controversial business associations.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a rapidly escalating political development, House Republicans have addressed a strongly-worded letter to Attorney General Merrick Garland. This letter, penned by prominent Republican figures, alleges that Hunter Biden’s legal team actively sought to “intimidate and harass” two key whistleblowers from the Internal Revenue Service (IRS) during the ongoing tax investigation into the President’s son. Reps. Jim Jordan (R-OH), Jason Smith (R-MO), and James Comer (R-KY) named the IRS whistleblowers as Gary Shapley and Joseph Ziegler. These individuals recently came forward, suggesting that political machinations interfered with prosecutorial decisions spanning the extensive federal examination of Hunter Biden. Notably, the letter levels severe accusations at Biden’s attorneys, asserting they “slandered” Shapley and Ziegler, painting them as “disgruntled”. Furthermore, it contends that Biden’s legal team pressured the Department of Justice to seek prosecution against these whistleblowers. “Federal law safeguards whistleblowers from undue retaliation. The overt efforts to coerce these whistleblowers spark grave concerns about possible obstructions in our Committees’ inquiry,” the GOP leaders penned in the letter. They subsequently requested details on any endeavors by Hunter Biden’s lawyers to coax the Department into taking punitive action against the mentioned IRS whistleblowers. In a revealing highlight, the letter references a New York Times report. According to this article, Biden’s legal team argued with the Justice Department that the whistleblowers “violated the law by sharing investigation details with Congress and should consequently face legal proceedings.” With the clock ticking, the Republicans have given the DOJ a deadline until September 26, 5 p.m., to present any correspondences from Hunter Biden’s attorneys that “call for the investigation or prosecution” of the whistleblowers. Additionally, any documented communication between Biden’s lawyers and the DOJ about potential criminal investigations against Shapley or Ziegler is also sought. On the horizon, Attorney General Garland is slated to appear before the House Judiciary Committee on September 20 for a routine oversight hearing. This news coincides with the expectation that House Speaker Kevin McCarthy (R-CA) will soon endorse an impeachment inquiry into President Biden, focusing on allegations tied to his son’s controversial business associations.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Major Blow to Gulf Cartel - Top Enforcer Arrested near Texas Border</title><link href="/news/2023/09/13/Gulf-Cartel-Enforcer/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Major Blow to Gulf Cartel - Top Enforcer Arrested near Texas Border" /><published>2023-09-13T16:50:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-13T16:50:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/13/Gulf-Cartel-Enforcer</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/13/Gulf-Cartel-Enforcer/">&lt;p&gt;Amidst the chaos of the cartel battles brewing near the Texas border, a critical arrest was made. One of the Gulf Cartel’s top enforcers in Reynosa, Roque “Rocky, Metro 58 or Comandante Roque” Cruz Fuentes, known for his leadership in the Metros faction’s security forces, is now behind bars.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On an early Thursday morning, Mexican Navy’s elite force, popularly referred to as Marinos, established strategic perimeters across the Las Fuentes and Olmitos neighborhoods. This was the backdrop for the meticulously executed raids targeting Roque and his operations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Throughout the operation, three helicopters, armed with sharpshooters, blanketed the skies, providing invaluable air support. Simultaneously, a diversionary raid was underway, a strategic move to distract and deter any gunmen attempting to intervene and rescue their leader.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the arrest wasn’t the only significant outcome of this operation. Authorities, during their mission, successfully liberated a woman kidnapped and held by El Roque in his hideout.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Following the arrest, El Roque, along with eight of his armed associates, was swiftly transported to Matamoros. There, at the local Mexico Attorney General’s Office, the processing began. Post-processing, they were then moved to Mexico City, where El Roque is slated to face a federal judge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Breitbart Texas’ law enforcement sources have disclosed that El Roque, as a high-ranking member of Los Metros, was implicated in an extensive list of violent acts. From orchestrating shootouts to commissioning a slew of kidnappings and murders, his actions were part of a larger ongoing feud with the Matamoros faction of the Gulf Cartel, known as Los Escorpiones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This arrest marks a significant step in curbing the violence and dominance of cartel factions in the region. But as history has shown, the ever-resilient cartels often bounce back, potentially escalating the tension in the already volatile borderlands.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Amidst the chaos of the cartel battles brewing near the Texas border, a critical arrest was made. One of the Gulf Cartel’s top enforcers in Reynosa, Roque “Rocky, Metro 58 or Comandante Roque” Cruz Fuentes, known for his leadership in the Metros faction’s security forces, is now behind bars. On an early Thursday morning, Mexican Navy’s elite force, popularly referred to as Marinos, established strategic perimeters across the Las Fuentes and Olmitos neighborhoods. This was the backdrop for the meticulously executed raids targeting Roque and his operations. Throughout the operation, three helicopters, armed with sharpshooters, blanketed the skies, providing invaluable air support. Simultaneously, a diversionary raid was underway, a strategic move to distract and deter any gunmen attempting to intervene and rescue their leader. However, the arrest wasn’t the only significant outcome of this operation. Authorities, during their mission, successfully liberated a woman kidnapped and held by El Roque in his hideout. Following the arrest, El Roque, along with eight of his armed associates, was swiftly transported to Matamoros. There, at the local Mexico Attorney General’s Office, the processing began. Post-processing, they were then moved to Mexico City, where El Roque is slated to face a federal judge. Breitbart Texas’ law enforcement sources have disclosed that El Roque, as a high-ranking member of Los Metros, was implicated in an extensive list of violent acts. From orchestrating shootouts to commissioning a slew of kidnappings and murders, his actions were part of a larger ongoing feud with the Matamoros faction of the Gulf Cartel, known as Los Escorpiones. This arrest marks a significant step in curbing the violence and dominance of cartel factions in the region. But as history has shown, the ever-resilient cartels often bounce back, potentially escalating the tension in the already volatile borderlands.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Amy Schumer’s Online Jest - Triggers Controversy Over Masterson Support</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/13/Amy-Schumer-Controversy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Amy Schumer’s Online Jest - Triggers Controversy Over Masterson Support" /><published>2023-09-13T14:45:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-13T14:45:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/13/Amy-Schumer-Controversy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/13/Amy-Schumer-Controversy/">&lt;p&gt;The unpredictable landscape of celebrity social media took another twist when comedian Amy Schumer found herself in the midst of a storm after jesting about Ashton Kutcher and Mila Kunis’ support for Danny Masterson, recently convicted of rape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The incident began when Schumer, attempting to apologize for a post seen as “cyberbullying” towards actress Nicole Kidman, made a sarcastic reference to Kutcher and Kunis’ letters of support for Masterson. These letters were sent to a judge prior to Masterson’s sentencing hearing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amy’s apology read, “I want to apologize to all the people I hurt posting a photo of Nicole Kidman and alluding to her being an alien. I will be asking the cast of that ’70s show to write letters advocating for my forgiveness.” She appended her message with the hashtag “#takingtimetoheal.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, this joke did not land well with the online audience. Comments poured in from fans and critics alike, denouncing Schumer for making light of such a grave issue. Reactions varied from accusing Schumer of being “tasteless” to questioning her decision to jest about a sensitive matter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adding to the complexity of the situation is the fact that Masterson was recently sentenced to a rigorous 30 years to life in prison, post his conviction on two counts of forcible rape. Kutcher and Kunis’ letters were among nearly 50 submitted to the court in support of Masterson. Astonishingly, in Kutcher’s letter, he praised Masterson as a “role model” and credited him for keeping him away from drugs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both Kutcher and Kunis later took to Instagram, expressing regret for their letters, clarifying that they were not meant to belittle Masterson’s victims in any way. “We support victims,” Kunis asserted, reiterating their dedication to supporting victims through their philanthropic endeavors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Masterson’s legal journey isn’t over yet. His legal team has expressed their intent to appeal the guilty verdict. Shawn Holley, Masterson’s attorney, stated, “Mr. Masterson did not commit the crimes for which he has been convicted… we are confident that these convictions will be overturned.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This tangled web of celebrity opinions, legal ramifications, and public sentiment showcases the ever-blurring lines between personal opinions, public images, and the weight of social media in today’s age.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">The unpredictable landscape of celebrity social media took another twist when comedian Amy Schumer found herself in the midst of a storm after jesting about Ashton Kutcher and Mila Kunis’ support for Danny Masterson, recently convicted of rape. The incident began when Schumer, attempting to apologize for a post seen as “cyberbullying” towards actress Nicole Kidman, made a sarcastic reference to Kutcher and Kunis’ letters of support for Masterson. These letters were sent to a judge prior to Masterson’s sentencing hearing. Amy’s apology read, “I want to apologize to all the people I hurt posting a photo of Nicole Kidman and alluding to her being an alien. I will be asking the cast of that ’70s show to write letters advocating for my forgiveness.” She appended her message with the hashtag “#takingtimetoheal.” However, this joke did not land well with the online audience. Comments poured in from fans and critics alike, denouncing Schumer for making light of such a grave issue. Reactions varied from accusing Schumer of being “tasteless” to questioning her decision to jest about a sensitive matter. Adding to the complexity of the situation is the fact that Masterson was recently sentenced to a rigorous 30 years to life in prison, post his conviction on two counts of forcible rape. Kutcher and Kunis’ letters were among nearly 50 submitted to the court in support of Masterson. Astonishingly, in Kutcher’s letter, he praised Masterson as a “role model” and credited him for keeping him away from drugs. Both Kutcher and Kunis later took to Instagram, expressing regret for their letters, clarifying that they were not meant to belittle Masterson’s victims in any way. “We support victims,” Kunis asserted, reiterating their dedication to supporting victims through their philanthropic endeavors. Masterson’s legal journey isn’t over yet. His legal team has expressed their intent to appeal the guilty verdict. Shawn Holley, Masterson’s attorney, stated, “Mr. Masterson did not commit the crimes for which he has been convicted… we are confident that these convictions will be overturned.” This tangled web of celebrity opinions, legal ramifications, and public sentiment showcases the ever-blurring lines between personal opinions, public images, and the weight of social media in today’s age.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Tennessee Tycoon Under Fire - Allegations, Innocence, and Controversy</title><link href="/news/2023/09/13/Tennessee-Scandal/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tennessee Tycoon Under Fire - Allegations, Innocence, and Controversy" /><published>2023-09-13T13:45:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-13T13:45:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/13/Tennessee-Scandal</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/13/Tennessee-Scandal/">&lt;p&gt;In an unfolding saga rife with accusations, controversy, and vehement declarations of innocence, Sean Williams, a once-renowned Tennessee businessman, finds himself at the heart of a growing firestorm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Allegations and Arrests&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ten women have levelled charges against Williams, accusing him of drugging and sexually assaulting them at high-profile gatherings held in his opulent downtown apartment. Responding to these claims, Williams, in written correspondence from the Laurel County Jail, mocked the notion of him drugging anyone. He emphasized his newfound popularity due to his lavish lifestyle and flashy parties, insisting that many were eager to be part of these soirées.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Williams was on the lam for two years before North Carolina police nabbed him this April, uncovering on his electronic devices videos purportedly showing him sexually assaulting 52 different women. In a startling discovery, a thumb drive in his possession allegedly contained over 5,000 images of child pornography.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Law Enforcement in Question&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further muddying the waters, the Johnson City Police Department (JCPD) has also come under scrutiny. The lawsuit alleges the department grossly mishandled several complaints against Williams, essentially turning a blind eye. Reports suggest that between 2019 and 2020, at least six complaints alleging Williams’ nefarious activities reached the JCPD. Rather than apprehending Williams, officers allegedly regarded him as “untouchable.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Seeking Justice&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kateri Dahl, a former Assistant U.S. Attorney, played a crucial role in shining a light on Williams’ alleged transgressions. Dahl claims she was dismissed from her position after voicing concerns regarding Williams. In a bid to ensure justice, Dahl has now donned the role of a whistleblower, highlighting the JCPD’s purported lapses in handling victims’ cases.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An independent audit commissioned by the city corroborates many of Dahl’s claims, revealing “material deficiencies” in JCPD’s handling of sexual assaults. With such lapses, the ability to gather essential evidence for thorough investigations is severely hampered. The audit found the department’s reporting process to be “inconsistent, ineffective, and incomplete.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Williams’ Rebuttal&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Firm in his denial, Williams accuses law enforcement of fabricating evidence, alleging his money was stolen, and illicit drugs were “planted” on him. He asserts that all the images and videos acquired by the police merely depict consensual interactions with friends. As for the ten women pressing charges, Williams suggests each has a personal vendetta against him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amid this web of allegations, the narrative remains contentious. What seems evident, however, is that this case will continue to dominate headlines as the quest for truth, and justice presses on.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In an unfolding saga rife with accusations, controversy, and vehement declarations of innocence, Sean Williams, a once-renowned Tennessee businessman, finds himself at the heart of a growing firestorm. Allegations and Arrests Ten women have levelled charges against Williams, accusing him of drugging and sexually assaulting them at high-profile gatherings held in his opulent downtown apartment. Responding to these claims, Williams, in written correspondence from the Laurel County Jail, mocked the notion of him drugging anyone. He emphasized his newfound popularity due to his lavish lifestyle and flashy parties, insisting that many were eager to be part of these soirées. Williams was on the lam for two years before North Carolina police nabbed him this April, uncovering on his electronic devices videos purportedly showing him sexually assaulting 52 different women. In a startling discovery, a thumb drive in his possession allegedly contained over 5,000 images of child pornography. Law Enforcement in Question Further muddying the waters, the Johnson City Police Department (JCPD) has also come under scrutiny. The lawsuit alleges the department grossly mishandled several complaints against Williams, essentially turning a blind eye. Reports suggest that between 2019 and 2020, at least six complaints alleging Williams’ nefarious activities reached the JCPD. Rather than apprehending Williams, officers allegedly regarded him as “untouchable.” Seeking Justice Kateri Dahl, a former Assistant U.S. Attorney, played a crucial role in shining a light on Williams’ alleged transgressions. Dahl claims she was dismissed from her position after voicing concerns regarding Williams. In a bid to ensure justice, Dahl has now donned the role of a whistleblower, highlighting the JCPD’s purported lapses in handling victims’ cases. An independent audit commissioned by the city corroborates many of Dahl’s claims, revealing “material deficiencies” in JCPD’s handling of sexual assaults. With such lapses, the ability to gather essential evidence for thorough investigations is severely hampered. The audit found the department’s reporting process to be “inconsistent, ineffective, and incomplete.” Williams’ Rebuttal Firm in his denial, Williams accuses law enforcement of fabricating evidence, alleging his money was stolen, and illicit drugs were “planted” on him. He asserts that all the images and videos acquired by the police merely depict consensual interactions with friends. As for the ten women pressing charges, Williams suggests each has a personal vendetta against him. Amid this web of allegations, the narrative remains contentious. What seems evident, however, is that this case will continue to dominate headlines as the quest for truth, and justice presses on.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Cotton Throws Weight Behind Biden Impeachment - Allies and Accusations Emerge</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/13/Cotton-Backs-Biden-Impeachment/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Cotton Throws Weight Behind Biden Impeachment - Allies and Accusations Emerge" /><published>2023-09-13T12:39:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-13T12:39:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/13/Cotton-Backs-Biden-Impeachment</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/13/Cotton-Backs-Biden-Impeachment/">&lt;p&gt;In a notable political development, Senator Tom Cotton (R-AR) declared his endorsement of the House of Representatives’ impeachment inquiry into President Joe Biden’s purported corrupt affiliations. This decision puts the Senator firmly behind a growing cohort within the GOP actively probing Biden’s alleged misconduct.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cotton, in a stark rebuke, articulated his concerns, asserting that Biden “lied repeatedly about his business dealings with Hunter.” He also claimed that the President allowed his son, Hunter Biden, to “sell access to our enemies, including China.” This has added another dimension to an already tense political climate, given Cotton’s influential standing within the Republican party.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This controversy traces back to claims made about Hunter Biden’s supposed request for ‘half’ of his ‘shady, ill-gotten foreign income.’ Echoing Cotton’s sentiments, House Speaker Kevin McCarthy (R-CA) unveiled an impeachment inquiry accusing the President of “abuse of power, obstruction, and corruption.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;House Speaker Kevin McCarthy cited four pivotal pieces of evidence that have cast doubt on Biden’s integrity:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Joe Biden’s alleged lies concerning his participation in the family business.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bank statements purportedly pointing to funds channeled to Biden family members through concealed entities.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;An FBI informant’s file that insinuates Joe Biden was on the receiving end of a bribe from a Ukrainian energy executive.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Allegations of Joe Biden providing “special treatment” to Hunter amidst the Justice Department’s tax probe targeting him.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;McCarthy, on addressing these claims, stated, “Taken together, these allegations paint a picture of a culture of corruption.” He believes they warrant a deeper investigation by the House of Representatives into the severity and validity of the claims.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To navigate these treacherous political waters, House Oversight Chairman James Comer (KY), Judiciary Committee Chairman Jim Jordan (OH), and Ways and Means Committee Chairman Jason Smith (MO) will spearhead the impeachment inquiry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the political tectonic plates shift with these revelations, it remains to be seen how this investigation will impact the Biden administration and the broader political landscape.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a notable political development, Senator Tom Cotton (R-AR) declared his endorsement of the House of Representatives’ impeachment inquiry into President Joe Biden’s purported corrupt affiliations. This decision puts the Senator firmly behind a growing cohort within the GOP actively probing Biden’s alleged misconduct. Cotton, in a stark rebuke, articulated his concerns, asserting that Biden “lied repeatedly about his business dealings with Hunter.” He also claimed that the President allowed his son, Hunter Biden, to “sell access to our enemies, including China.” This has added another dimension to an already tense political climate, given Cotton’s influential standing within the Republican party. This controversy traces back to claims made about Hunter Biden’s supposed request for ‘half’ of his ‘shady, ill-gotten foreign income.’ Echoing Cotton’s sentiments, House Speaker Kevin McCarthy (R-CA) unveiled an impeachment inquiry accusing the President of “abuse of power, obstruction, and corruption.” House Speaker Kevin McCarthy cited four pivotal pieces of evidence that have cast doubt on Biden’s integrity: Joe Biden’s alleged lies concerning his participation in the family business. Bank statements purportedly pointing to funds channeled to Biden family members through concealed entities. An FBI informant’s file that insinuates Joe Biden was on the receiving end of a bribe from a Ukrainian energy executive. Allegations of Joe Biden providing “special treatment” to Hunter amidst the Justice Department’s tax probe targeting him. McCarthy, on addressing these claims, stated, “Taken together, these allegations paint a picture of a culture of corruption.” He believes they warrant a deeper investigation by the House of Representatives into the severity and validity of the claims. To navigate these treacherous political waters, House Oversight Chairman James Comer (KY), Judiciary Committee Chairman Jim Jordan (OH), and Ways and Means Committee Chairman Jason Smith (MO) will spearhead the impeachment inquiry. As the political tectonic plates shift with these revelations, it remains to be seen how this investigation will impact the Biden administration and the broader political landscape.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Missouri Prioritizes Child Safety - Restricts Risky Transgender Treatments for Minors</title><link href="/news/2023/09/13/Child-Safety-Victory-Missouri/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Missouri Prioritizes Child Safety - Restricts Risky Transgender Treatments for Minors" /><published>2023-09-13T11:40:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-13T11:40:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/13/Child-Safety-Victory-Missouri</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/13/Child-Safety-Victory-Missouri/">&lt;p&gt;In a landmark decision championing the safety of children, the state of Missouri has enacted a law that sets stricter regulations on medical treatments for transgender minors. Recognizing the potential long-term implications of certain medical interventions, institutions like Washington University in St. Louis and the University of Missouri Health have proactively stopped prescribing puberty blockers and cross-sex hormones to young patients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Taking effect from Aug. 28, the law serves as a beacon of prudence in medical practices, ensuring that the welfare of children remains paramount. While the Attorney General of Missouri, Andrew Bailey, clarified that ongoing treatments initiated before the law’s enforcement can continue, the top-tier universities chose a cautious path. The legal landscape created by the law’s provisions, which allow patients to sue their doctors for malpractice years after undergoing treatment, underscored the gravity of such irreversible decisions made in one’s youth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The drive behind these healthcare institutions’ decisions is rooted in a part of the statute that grants individuals the right to challenge their earlier treatments. Specifically, those who underwent treatments like puberty blockers or cross-sex hormones during their minor years can take legal action against their doctors either after their 21st birthday or 15 years following the treatment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although the law places certain restrictions, it doesn’t entirely shut doors on support for transgender minors. Washington University and the University of Missouri Health have pledged to continue offering essential services such as mental health and educational assistance to these youths. Moreover, adult transgender individuals retain their access to treatments at these medical centers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The initiative to regulate transgender interventions was not without its share of legal battles. Even though organizations like the ACLU of Missouri sought legal measures against the statute, the court upheld the law, emphasizing the ambiguity surrounding the scientific and medical aspects of transgender treatments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earlier this year, Washington University’s transgender center had come under scrutiny following a whistleblower’s allegations, suggesting potential oversight in the center’s practices. Although the university’s investigations didn’t affirm these claims, the incident did trigger a series of state and federal evaluations. This collective momentum played a pivotal role in the drafting and implementation of the legislation that is today safeguarding the interests and wellbeing of Missouri’s youth.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a landmark decision championing the safety of children, the state of Missouri has enacted a law that sets stricter regulations on medical treatments for transgender minors. Recognizing the potential long-term implications of certain medical interventions, institutions like Washington University in St. Louis and the University of Missouri Health have proactively stopped prescribing puberty blockers and cross-sex hormones to young patients. Taking effect from Aug. 28, the law serves as a beacon of prudence in medical practices, ensuring that the welfare of children remains paramount. While the Attorney General of Missouri, Andrew Bailey, clarified that ongoing treatments initiated before the law’s enforcement can continue, the top-tier universities chose a cautious path. The legal landscape created by the law’s provisions, which allow patients to sue their doctors for malpractice years after undergoing treatment, underscored the gravity of such irreversible decisions made in one’s youth. The drive behind these healthcare institutions’ decisions is rooted in a part of the statute that grants individuals the right to challenge their earlier treatments. Specifically, those who underwent treatments like puberty blockers or cross-sex hormones during their minor years can take legal action against their doctors either after their 21st birthday or 15 years following the treatment. Although the law places certain restrictions, it doesn’t entirely shut doors on support for transgender minors. Washington University and the University of Missouri Health have pledged to continue offering essential services such as mental health and educational assistance to these youths. Moreover, adult transgender individuals retain their access to treatments at these medical centers. The initiative to regulate transgender interventions was not without its share of legal battles. Even though organizations like the ACLU of Missouri sought legal measures against the statute, the court upheld the law, emphasizing the ambiguity surrounding the scientific and medical aspects of transgender treatments. Earlier this year, Washington University’s transgender center had come under scrutiny following a whistleblower’s allegations, suggesting potential oversight in the center’s practices. Although the university’s investigations didn’t affirm these claims, the incident did trigger a series of state and federal evaluations. This collective momentum played a pivotal role in the drafting and implementation of the legislation that is today safeguarding the interests and wellbeing of Missouri’s youth.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Beshear’s Decision Backfires - Early Release of Convicted Child Molester Ignites Controversy</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/13/Beshear-Prisoner-Release/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Beshear’s Decision Backfires - Early Release of Convicted Child Molester Ignites Controversy" /><published>2023-09-13T10:25:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-13T10:25:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/13/Beshear-Prisoner-Release</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/13/Beshear-Prisoner-Release/">&lt;p&gt;As the Kentucky gubernatorial election looms closer, incumbent Democratic Governor Andy Beshear finds himself at the center of a scathing new television advertisement campaign. The ad, released by the conservative-aligned School Freedom Fund, sharply criticizes Beshear for his decision to potentially release certain prisoners at the onset of the coronavirus pandemic. Among these prisoners was James Hamlin, who was accused and later convicted of sodomizing a six-year-old child.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-details&quot;&gt;The Details&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the early stages of the pandemic, amidst concerns of virus spread in crowded facilities, Governor Beshear signed an order titled “Conditional Commutation of Sentence.” The order aimed at reducing the inmate population in Kentucky’s overcrowded prisons. This action was taken in response to the heightened risk presented by the COVID-19 pandemic. The order detailed a list of 697 inmates convicted of “non-violent, non-sexual offenses” whose sentences were set to expire by the end of September 2020. However, included in this list was James Hamlin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hamlin, whose Facebook page contained disturbing comments about minors, was rearrested shortly after the order and subsequently convicted of heinous charges. He is now slated to remain behind bars until 2044, with a possibility for parole in 2039.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;broader-implications&quot;&gt;Broader Implications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The advertisement equates the decision to release such prisoners as putting “deviant predators before innocent kids” and describes such choices as “not just wrong, it’s unforgivable.” Drawing parallels to the controversial Willie Horton ads from the 1988 presidential election, this new campaign against Beshear has the potential to drastically affect the outcome of the upcoming election.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Current public polls suggest a favorable leaning towards Beshear, but the provocative nature of the advertisement might sway public opinion. Governor Beshear’s potential missteps during the early days of the pandemic have previously been highlighted by the School Freedom Fund in another advertisement, spotlighting criminals with “means and motive.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A 2021 report from Kentucky’s Administrative Office of Courts added more fuel to the fire. It pointed out that of the 1,704 individuals who had their sentences commuted by Beshear, 553 were later charged with felonies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-larger-picture&quot;&gt;The Larger Picture&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This controversy comes at a crucial time, with only three major gubernatorial elections slated for 2023. Apart from Kentucky, Louisiana and Mississippi are the other states headed for a gubernatorial showdown. With the Republicans eager to turn the tables after a lackluster 2022 midterm, flipping Kentucky’s and Louisiana’s governor’s mansions from blue to red would offer a significant boost.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Insiders believe that this is just the beginning and that more such ads can be expected as election day nears, raising the stakes in an already high-voltage political atmosphere.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">As the Kentucky gubernatorial election looms closer, incumbent Democratic Governor Andy Beshear finds himself at the center of a scathing new television advertisement campaign. The ad, released by the conservative-aligned School Freedom Fund, sharply criticizes Beshear for his decision to potentially release certain prisoners at the onset of the coronavirus pandemic. Among these prisoners was James Hamlin, who was accused and later convicted of sodomizing a six-year-old child. The Details In the early stages of the pandemic, amidst concerns of virus spread in crowded facilities, Governor Beshear signed an order titled “Conditional Commutation of Sentence.” The order aimed at reducing the inmate population in Kentucky’s overcrowded prisons. This action was taken in response to the heightened risk presented by the COVID-19 pandemic. The order detailed a list of 697 inmates convicted of “non-violent, non-sexual offenses” whose sentences were set to expire by the end of September 2020. However, included in this list was James Hamlin. Hamlin, whose Facebook page contained disturbing comments about minors, was rearrested shortly after the order and subsequently convicted of heinous charges. He is now slated to remain behind bars until 2044, with a possibility for parole in 2039. Broader Implications The advertisement equates the decision to release such prisoners as putting “deviant predators before innocent kids” and describes such choices as “not just wrong, it’s unforgivable.” Drawing parallels to the controversial Willie Horton ads from the 1988 presidential election, this new campaign against Beshear has the potential to drastically affect the outcome of the upcoming election. Current public polls suggest a favorable leaning towards Beshear, but the provocative nature of the advertisement might sway public opinion. Governor Beshear’s potential missteps during the early days of the pandemic have previously been highlighted by the School Freedom Fund in another advertisement, spotlighting criminals with “means and motive.” A 2021 report from Kentucky’s Administrative Office of Courts added more fuel to the fire. It pointed out that of the 1,704 individuals who had their sentences commuted by Beshear, 553 were later charged with felonies. The Larger Picture This controversy comes at a crucial time, with only three major gubernatorial elections slated for 2023. Apart from Kentucky, Louisiana and Mississippi are the other states headed for a gubernatorial showdown. With the Republicans eager to turn the tables after a lackluster 2022 midterm, flipping Kentucky’s and Louisiana’s governor’s mansions from blue to red would offer a significant boost. Insiders believe that this is just the beginning and that more such ads can be expected as election day nears, raising the stakes in an already high-voltage political atmosphere.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Aerosmith’s Farewell Tour Hits a Snag - Steven Tyler’s Vocal Cord Injury</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/13/Aerosmith-Tour-Postponement/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Aerosmith’s Farewell Tour Hits a Snag - Steven Tyler’s Vocal Cord Injury" /><published>2023-09-13T09:14:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-13T09:14:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/13/Aerosmith-Tour-Postponement</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/13/Aerosmith-Tour-Postponement/">&lt;p&gt;The rock world was met with a jolt of concern after legendary Aerosmith frontman, Steven Tyler, revealed that he had suffered from vocal cord damage during a recent concert in New York. This has subsequently led to the postponement of several shows from their much-anticipated “Peace Out” farewell tour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sharing his distress over the situation, Tyler took to the band’s social media platforms, stating, “I’m heartbroken to say I have received strict doctor’s orders not to sing for the next thirty days… We’ll need to postpone a few dates so that we can come back and give you the performance you deserve.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aerosmith’s “Peace Out” tour, marking a capstone for the band’s illustrious 50-year career in the industry, commenced earlier this month in Philadelphia. The tour was set to feature 40 shows, bringing the iconic band’s journey to a close.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In light of Tyler’s injury, concert dates in cities including Detroit, Chicago, Washington, D.C., Toronto, Raleigh, and Cleveland will be rescheduled. The band has assured fans that all previously acquired tickets will be valid for the rearranged dates. Additionally, for those fans unable to adjust to the new dates, refunds have been made available.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This isn’t the first time concerns surrounding Tyler’s health have come to the forefront. In December 2022, Aerosmith had to cancel the concluding shows of their Las Vegas residency. As per the band’s statement at the time, “On the advice of doctors, Steven has to sit these out.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, a few months ago, the band’s Las Vegas residency shows scheduled for June and July were also canceled due to a concerning relapse by Tyler following a foot surgery. The band had then expressed their unwavering support for Tyler’s focus on his health and recovery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the band grapples with the current setback, Steven Tyler is also presently contending with legal issues. He is dealing with a sexual assault lawsuit, an allegation he has vehemently denied.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For now, fans worldwide send their well wishes to Tyler for a swift recovery, hoping to see him back on stage, delivering those iconic performances that have made Aerosmith a global rock phenomenon.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">The rock world was met with a jolt of concern after legendary Aerosmith frontman, Steven Tyler, revealed that he had suffered from vocal cord damage during a recent concert in New York. This has subsequently led to the postponement of several shows from their much-anticipated “Peace Out” farewell tour. Sharing his distress over the situation, Tyler took to the band’s social media platforms, stating, “I’m heartbroken to say I have received strict doctor’s orders not to sing for the next thirty days… We’ll need to postpone a few dates so that we can come back and give you the performance you deserve.” Aerosmith’s “Peace Out” tour, marking a capstone for the band’s illustrious 50-year career in the industry, commenced earlier this month in Philadelphia. The tour was set to feature 40 shows, bringing the iconic band’s journey to a close. In light of Tyler’s injury, concert dates in cities including Detroit, Chicago, Washington, D.C., Toronto, Raleigh, and Cleveland will be rescheduled. The band has assured fans that all previously acquired tickets will be valid for the rearranged dates. Additionally, for those fans unable to adjust to the new dates, refunds have been made available. This isn’t the first time concerns surrounding Tyler’s health have come to the forefront. In December 2022, Aerosmith had to cancel the concluding shows of their Las Vegas residency. As per the band’s statement at the time, “On the advice of doctors, Steven has to sit these out.” Furthermore, a few months ago, the band’s Las Vegas residency shows scheduled for June and July were also canceled due to a concerning relapse by Tyler following a foot surgery. The band had then expressed their unwavering support for Tyler’s focus on his health and recovery. While the band grapples with the current setback, Steven Tyler is also presently contending with legal issues. He is dealing with a sexual assault lawsuit, an allegation he has vehemently denied. For now, fans worldwide send their well wishes to Tyler for a swift recovery, hoping to see him back on stage, delivering those iconic performances that have made Aerosmith a global rock phenomenon.</summary></entry></feed>