<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-09-22T12:20:08-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/09/22/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-09-22T12:20:08-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-22T12:20:08-04:00</updated><id>/2023/09/22/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/22/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Battle over Free Speech - Rumble Resists Calls to Demonetize Russell Brand</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/22/Rumble-Russell-Brand-Controversy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Battle over Free Speech - Rumble Resists Calls to Demonetize Russell Brand" /><published>2023-09-22T12:04:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-22T12:04:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/22/Rumble-Russell-Brand-Controversy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/22/Rumble-Russell-Brand-Controversy/">&lt;p&gt;Streaming platform Rumble is facing intense scrutiny and pressure from the UK Parliament but is choosing to stand its ground. A formal letter from the UK Parliament’s Culture, Media, and Sports Committee Chairwoman, Conservative MP Caroline Dinenage, asked Rumble whether it planned to demonetize comedian and commentator Russell Brand’s channel following serious allegations of rape and sexual assault against him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;parliaments-appeal-and-rumbles-stance&quot;&gt;Parliament’s Appeal and Rumble’s Stance&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The appeal to Rumble came in the wake of YouTube’s decision to demonetize Brand’s account. The UK Parliament expressed concerns over Brand profiting from content on Rumble amidst the grave accusations and inquired about Rumble’s intentions regarding Brand’s ability to earn money on the platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, Rumble issued a staunch response, refusing to demonetize Brand’s channel and labelled the Parliament’s letter as “disturbing”. They defended their stance on the grounds of upholding free speech and the principle that every individual is entitled to a full and serious investigation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Rumble stands for very different values. We have devoted ourselves to the vital cause of defending a free internet – meaning an internet where no one arbitrarily dictates which ideas can or cannot be heard, or which citizens may or may not be entitled to a platform,” Rumble said in a statement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-allegations-against-brand&quot;&gt;The Allegations Against Brand&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Multiple women have accused Russell Brand of rape and sexual assault, as reported by Channel 4 news network and the Sunday Times in Britain. Brand, however, has vehemently denied all the allegations against him. These serious accusations have led various platforms to review their relationships with Brand, and some, like YouTube, to take decisive action against him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;wider-implications-and-repercussions&quot;&gt;Wider Implications and Repercussions&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rumble argues that the allegations against Brand, which are yet to be proven in a court of law, are not related to his video content, and it is “deeply inappropriate and dangerous” for the UK Parliament to attempt to control who is allowed to speak on their platform or to earn a living from doing so. They highlighted the absence of any connection between the allegations and his content on Rumble as a significant factor in their decision.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TikTok and other media outlets, including the BBC, Channel 4, and GB News, have also been approached by the committee for clarification on their positions regarding Brand and his ability to monetize his posts, especially those related to the allegations against him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;reflecting-on-freedom-of-speech-and-accountability&quot;&gt;Reflecting on Freedom of Speech and Accountability&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This ongoing situation brings to the forefront the delicate balance between freedom of speech and accountability. Rumble’s refusal to bend to the pressure from Parliament underscores the debate around the extent of control and influence governmental bodies should have over content on internet platforms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a world where the lines between free speech, censorship, and accountability are continually being redrawn, situations like these serve as crucial talking points and reflections on the values we uphold and the lengths we are willing to go to defend them.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Streaming platform Rumble is facing intense scrutiny and pressure from the UK Parliament but is choosing to stand its ground. A formal letter from the UK Parliament’s Culture, Media, and Sports Committee Chairwoman, Conservative MP Caroline Dinenage, asked Rumble whether it planned to demonetize comedian and commentator Russell Brand’s channel following serious allegations of rape and sexual assault against him. Parliament’s Appeal and Rumble’s Stance The appeal to Rumble came in the wake of YouTube’s decision to demonetize Brand’s account. The UK Parliament expressed concerns over Brand profiting from content on Rumble amidst the grave accusations and inquired about Rumble’s intentions regarding Brand’s ability to earn money on the platform. However, Rumble issued a staunch response, refusing to demonetize Brand’s channel and labelled the Parliament’s letter as “disturbing”. They defended their stance on the grounds of upholding free speech and the principle that every individual is entitled to a full and serious investigation. “Rumble stands for very different values. We have devoted ourselves to the vital cause of defending a free internet – meaning an internet where no one arbitrarily dictates which ideas can or cannot be heard, or which citizens may or may not be entitled to a platform,” Rumble said in a statement. The Allegations Against Brand Multiple women have accused Russell Brand of rape and sexual assault, as reported by Channel 4 news network and the Sunday Times in Britain. Brand, however, has vehemently denied all the allegations against him. These serious accusations have led various platforms to review their relationships with Brand, and some, like YouTube, to take decisive action against him. Wider Implications and Repercussions Rumble argues that the allegations against Brand, which are yet to be proven in a court of law, are not related to his video content, and it is “deeply inappropriate and dangerous” for the UK Parliament to attempt to control who is allowed to speak on their platform or to earn a living from doing so. They highlighted the absence of any connection between the allegations and his content on Rumble as a significant factor in their decision. TikTok and other media outlets, including the BBC, Channel 4, and GB News, have also been approached by the committee for clarification on their positions regarding Brand and his ability to monetize his posts, especially those related to the allegations against him. Reflecting on Freedom of Speech and Accountability This ongoing situation brings to the forefront the delicate balance between freedom of speech and accountability. Rumble’s refusal to bend to the pressure from Parliament underscores the debate around the extent of control and influence governmental bodies should have over content on internet platforms. In a world where the lines between free speech, censorship, and accountability are continually being redrawn, situations like these serve as crucial talking points and reflections on the values we uphold and the lengths we are willing to go to defend them.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Rising Tide - Kari Lake Amplifies GOP Stature</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/22/Kari-Lake-Profile-Boost/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rising Tide - Kari Lake Amplifies GOP Stature" /><published>2023-09-22T11:02:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-22T11:02:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/22/Kari-Lake-Profile-Boost</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/22/Kari-Lake-Profile-Boost/">&lt;p&gt;In a series of moves that have shaken up the political landscape, former Arizona gubernatorial candidate Kari Lake has significantly increased her national profile as a steadfast surrogate for former President Donald Trump and a fervent supporter of Republican candidates. This transformation comes ahead of her anticipated declaration to contest a U.S. Senate seat, furthering the battle for control in the region.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-potential-political-maverick&quot;&gt;A Potential Political Maverick&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lake, a conservative emblem and former news anchor, has been traversing the country, participating in numerous events and speaking engagements to back Republican candidates. Her vigorous efforts are particularly focused on advocating for Trump’s presidential campaign, along with endorsing other GOP candidates across different states. With this aggressive strategy, Lake is likely preparing the ground for her rumored Senate run, scheduled to be announced in the second week of October.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;paving-the-road-for-republicans&quot;&gt;Paving the Road for Republicans&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lake’s impassioned campaigning isn’t limited to Arizona; she has journeyed through 14 states over the past three months to lead events and support Republican organizations on various levels. She has endorsed several candidates in Senate races and even thrown her weight behind Mayor Trent Staggs of Riverton, Utah, and businessman Bernie Moreno in Ohio, portraying her as a significant figure in the Republican realm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;in-trumps-corner&quot;&gt;In Trump’s Corner&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lake has been fervently supporting Trump on the campaign trail, emphasizing her alignment with the former President’s policies and visions. Sources intimate that she will continue this trajectory, appearing in California as Trump’s surrogate for the second Republican presidential debate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-fight-for-arizona&quot;&gt;The Fight for Arizona&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Early polls suggest Lake could be a leading contender in a hypothetical Republican primary. She faces potential competition from figures like Pinal County Sheriff Mark Lamb and businessman Blake Masters. On the Democrat side, Congressman Ruben Gallego is considered the front-runner, with current independent Arizona Senator Kyrsten Sinema’s intentions still unclear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;controversy-and-allegations&quot;&gt;Controversy and Allegations&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lake’s earlier gubernatorial run was marked by controversy, as she maintained the presence of significant voter fraud which favored the Democrats. Her stance on such contentious issues and her alignment with Trump’s viewpoints might impact her appeal to the moderate voters in the critical swing state of Arizona.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;lakes-national-ascendancy&quot;&gt;Lake’s National Ascendancy&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The strategic endeavors of Kari Lake reflect her ambitious goals and the broader Republican objective to regain control over both the Senate and the White House. Her increasing national presence and her alignment with Donald Trump underscore her determination to elevate the conservative agenda. The anticipation surrounding her potential Senate run is soaring, and the political circuits are abuzz, waiting to see how her strategies and alliances shape the course of the upcoming electoral battles.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a series of moves that have shaken up the political landscape, former Arizona gubernatorial candidate Kari Lake has significantly increased her national profile as a steadfast surrogate for former President Donald Trump and a fervent supporter of Republican candidates. This transformation comes ahead of her anticipated declaration to contest a U.S. Senate seat, furthering the battle for control in the region. A Potential Political Maverick Lake, a conservative emblem and former news anchor, has been traversing the country, participating in numerous events and speaking engagements to back Republican candidates. Her vigorous efforts are particularly focused on advocating for Trump’s presidential campaign, along with endorsing other GOP candidates across different states. With this aggressive strategy, Lake is likely preparing the ground for her rumored Senate run, scheduled to be announced in the second week of October. Paving the Road for Republicans Lake’s impassioned campaigning isn’t limited to Arizona; she has journeyed through 14 states over the past three months to lead events and support Republican organizations on various levels. She has endorsed several candidates in Senate races and even thrown her weight behind Mayor Trent Staggs of Riverton, Utah, and businessman Bernie Moreno in Ohio, portraying her as a significant figure in the Republican realm. In Trump’s Corner Lake has been fervently supporting Trump on the campaign trail, emphasizing her alignment with the former President’s policies and visions. Sources intimate that she will continue this trajectory, appearing in California as Trump’s surrogate for the second Republican presidential debate. The Fight for Arizona Early polls suggest Lake could be a leading contender in a hypothetical Republican primary. She faces potential competition from figures like Pinal County Sheriff Mark Lamb and businessman Blake Masters. On the Democrat side, Congressman Ruben Gallego is considered the front-runner, with current independent Arizona Senator Kyrsten Sinema’s intentions still unclear. Controversy and Allegations Lake’s earlier gubernatorial run was marked by controversy, as she maintained the presence of significant voter fraud which favored the Democrats. Her stance on such contentious issues and her alignment with Trump’s viewpoints might impact her appeal to the moderate voters in the critical swing state of Arizona. Lake’s National Ascendancy The strategic endeavors of Kari Lake reflect her ambitious goals and the broader Republican objective to regain control over both the Senate and the White House. Her increasing national presence and her alignment with Donald Trump underscore her determination to elevate the conservative agenda. The anticipation surrounding her potential Senate run is soaring, and the political circuits are abuzz, waiting to see how her strategies and alliances shape the course of the upcoming electoral battles.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Surge in the Race - Sen. Scott Bags a Cool Million</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/22/Scott-Fundraising-Momentum/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Surge in the Race - Sen. Scott Bags a Cool Million" /><published>2023-09-22T10:07:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-22T10:07:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/22/Scott-Fundraising-Momentum</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/22/Scott-Fundraising-Momentum/">&lt;p&gt;In a powerful display of political momentum, Sen. Tim Scott of South Carolina, a hopeful candidate for the White House from the Republican party, has managed to amass an impressive $1 million in campaign contributions within a mere 24 hours. This substantial windfall was revealed by a spokesperson from Scott’s campaign during his speaking engagements in New York City and Charleston, South Carolina.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;newfound-momentum&quot;&gt;Newfound Momentum&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This fundraising achievement could indicate a possible surge in momentum for Sen. Scott, who, until now, had been trailing behind some of his fellow competitors in national polling data. Scott’s campaign is seemingly catching speed, and his performance in the polls in Iowa—a state known for its pivotal role in determining the fate of presidential candidates—is promising.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;eyes-on-the-prize&quot;&gt;Eyes on the Prize&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the second Republican debate looming, this spike in contributions is particularly crucial. The debate is seen as a golden opportunity for GOP presidential aspirants to position themselves as the alternative to former President Donald Trump, who is currently the front-runner by a significant margin. Trump, however, has chosen not to participate in this debate, opting instead to speak at an event in Detroit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Scott’s spokesperson, Matt Gorman, emphasized that Scott is ready to return to the debate stage to highlight the serious policy distinctions between the candidates, conveying that, “Tim is prepared to have a conversation with voters, be the adult in the room, and demonstrate why he is the strongest candidate to beat Joe Biden.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;against-the-odds&quot;&gt;Against the Odds&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite the efforts of all the contenders, surpassing Trump’s dominance in the polls remains a considerable challenge. While the Iowa caucuses are still a few months away, giving candidates ample time to strategize and gain traction, how and when the field will narrow down in the lead-up to this crucial event is still uncertain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;scotts-strategy&quot;&gt;Scott’s Strategy&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sen. Scott is gearing up to leverage this debate to showcase his viewpoints on various pressing issues like the economy and parental rights and to present his vision for the country. He aims to engage with the voters effectively and demonstrate why he is the ideal candidate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-road-ahead&quot;&gt;The Road Ahead&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This million-dollar boost is certainly a beacon of hope for Sen. Scott’s campaign. As the debate nears, all eyes will be on how he and his fellow candidates capitalize on this opportunity to present themselves as viable contenders and how they will strategize to gain an edge in the race against the dominant presence of Trump. The political arena is buzzing with anticipation as the Republican candidates brace themselves for the challenges and opportunities that lie ahead in the race to the White House.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a powerful display of political momentum, Sen. Tim Scott of South Carolina, a hopeful candidate for the White House from the Republican party, has managed to amass an impressive $1 million in campaign contributions within a mere 24 hours. This substantial windfall was revealed by a spokesperson from Scott’s campaign during his speaking engagements in New York City and Charleston, South Carolina. Newfound Momentum This fundraising achievement could indicate a possible surge in momentum for Sen. Scott, who, until now, had been trailing behind some of his fellow competitors in national polling data. Scott’s campaign is seemingly catching speed, and his performance in the polls in Iowa—a state known for its pivotal role in determining the fate of presidential candidates—is promising. Eyes on the Prize With the second Republican debate looming, this spike in contributions is particularly crucial. The debate is seen as a golden opportunity for GOP presidential aspirants to position themselves as the alternative to former President Donald Trump, who is currently the front-runner by a significant margin. Trump, however, has chosen not to participate in this debate, opting instead to speak at an event in Detroit. Scott’s spokesperson, Matt Gorman, emphasized that Scott is ready to return to the debate stage to highlight the serious policy distinctions between the candidates, conveying that, “Tim is prepared to have a conversation with voters, be the adult in the room, and demonstrate why he is the strongest candidate to beat Joe Biden.” Against the Odds Despite the efforts of all the contenders, surpassing Trump’s dominance in the polls remains a considerable challenge. While the Iowa caucuses are still a few months away, giving candidates ample time to strategize and gain traction, how and when the field will narrow down in the lead-up to this crucial event is still uncertain. Scott’s Strategy Sen. Scott is gearing up to leverage this debate to showcase his viewpoints on various pressing issues like the economy and parental rights and to present his vision for the country. He aims to engage with the voters effectively and demonstrate why he is the ideal candidate. The Road Ahead This million-dollar boost is certainly a beacon of hope for Sen. Scott’s campaign. As the debate nears, all eyes will be on how he and his fellow candidates capitalize on this opportunity to present themselves as viable contenders and how they will strategize to gain an edge in the race against the dominant presence of Trump. The political arena is buzzing with anticipation as the Republican candidates brace themselves for the challenges and opportunities that lie ahead in the race to the White House.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Baltimore’s Educational Crisis - Zero Proficiency in Math across 13 High Schools</title><link href="/news/2023/09/22/Educational-Crisis-Baltimore/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Baltimore’s Educational Crisis - Zero Proficiency in Math across 13 High Schools" /><published>2023-09-22T09:15:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-22T09:15:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/22/Educational-Crisis-Baltimore</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/22/Educational-Crisis-Baltimore/">&lt;p&gt;In a shocking revelation, state math exams have found that not a single student from 13 high schools in Baltimore, Maryland, demonstrated proficiency in math. This alarming statistic has triggered severe concern over the state of education in the region, with officials and experts calling it “educational homicide.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-grave-scenario&quot;&gt;A Grave Scenario&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The 13 schools in question, including renowned names like Patterson High School and Frederick Douglass, are part of 33 city schools in Baltimore. This implies a whopping 40% of the city schools are entangled in this educational crisis. Jason Rodriguez, deputy director of a local non-profit People Empowered by the Struggle, called out the rampant system, emphasizing a dire need for accountability rather than funding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;numbers-speak-volumes&quot;&gt;Numbers Speak Volumes&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of the 1,736 students who took the test in these 13 schools, a staggering 1,295 students, making up 74.5%, scored one out of four— the lowest possible score. This situation is especially startling considering the substantial financial resources invested in the district. Last school year, Baltimore City Schools received a record $1.6 billion from taxpayers, and an additional $799 million in Covid relief funding from the federal government.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-recurring-issue&quot;&gt;A Recurring Issue&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This isn’t the first time Baltimore City Schools have been under the scanner for such dismal educational outcomes. A comparable report by Project Baltimore in 2017 also highlighted zero math proficiency in 13 schools, some of which continue to struggle with the same issue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-response&quot;&gt;The Response&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;City Schools attribute these results to years of underfunding and the recent pandemic. They argue that recent increments in funds don’t nullify the damage caused by chronic underfunding over the years, and that improvement in such a situation would require significant time and effort.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;beyond-the-tests&quot;&gt;Beyond the Tests&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This predicament goes beyond mere numbers and test scores, shedding light on deeper, systemic issues in education. The reality of these alarming scores opens up urgent discussions on the structure, functionality, and effectiveness of the educational systems in place and raises critical questions about the future of the students affected by it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The consistent educational crisis in Baltimore, marked by zero proficiency in math across several high schools, is a disturbing indicator of deep-rooted issues in the educational landscape. This situation demands immediate attention, thorough investigation, and robust reforms to ensure that every student has access to quality education, which is essential for shaping a prosperous and equitable future.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a shocking revelation, state math exams have found that not a single student from 13 high schools in Baltimore, Maryland, demonstrated proficiency in math. This alarming statistic has triggered severe concern over the state of education in the region, with officials and experts calling it “educational homicide.” A Grave Scenario The 13 schools in question, including renowned names like Patterson High School and Frederick Douglass, are part of 33 city schools in Baltimore. This implies a whopping 40% of the city schools are entangled in this educational crisis. Jason Rodriguez, deputy director of a local non-profit People Empowered by the Struggle, called out the rampant system, emphasizing a dire need for accountability rather than funding. Numbers Speak Volumes Of the 1,736 students who took the test in these 13 schools, a staggering 1,295 students, making up 74.5%, scored one out of four— the lowest possible score. This situation is especially startling considering the substantial financial resources invested in the district. Last school year, Baltimore City Schools received a record $1.6 billion from taxpayers, and an additional $799 million in Covid relief funding from the federal government. A Recurring Issue This isn’t the first time Baltimore City Schools have been under the scanner for such dismal educational outcomes. A comparable report by Project Baltimore in 2017 also highlighted zero math proficiency in 13 schools, some of which continue to struggle with the same issue. The Response City Schools attribute these results to years of underfunding and the recent pandemic. They argue that recent increments in funds don’t nullify the damage caused by chronic underfunding over the years, and that improvement in such a situation would require significant time and effort. Beyond the Tests This predicament goes beyond mere numbers and test scores, shedding light on deeper, systemic issues in education. The reality of these alarming scores opens up urgent discussions on the structure, functionality, and effectiveness of the educational systems in place and raises critical questions about the future of the students affected by it. Conclusion The consistent educational crisis in Baltimore, marked by zero proficiency in math across several high schools, is a disturbing indicator of deep-rooted issues in the educational landscape. This situation demands immediate attention, thorough investigation, and robust reforms to ensure that every student has access to quality education, which is essential for shaping a prosperous and equitable future.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Tragedy Unveiled - The Untimely Passing of Angus Cloud</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/22/Tragic-Passing-of-Angus-Cloud/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tragedy Unveiled - The Untimely Passing of Angus Cloud" /><published>2023-09-22T08:05:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-22T08:05:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/22/Tragic-Passing-of-Angus-Cloud</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/22/Tragic-Passing-of-Angus-Cloud/">&lt;p&gt;The entertainment world is still coming to terms with the tragic loss of Angus Cloud, who shot to fame with his breakout role in the hit HBO series ‘Euphoria’. Angus, also known as Conor Hickey, passed away on July 31 at the tender age of 25, leaving fans and fellow cast members grieving.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;accidental-overdose-and-unanswered-questions&quot;&gt;Accidental Overdose and Unanswered Questions&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fox News Digital has confirmed that Angus’s untimely death was the result of an accidental overdose. The Alameda County Coroner’s office revealed a mix of methamphetamine, cocaine, fentanyl, and benzodiazepines as the cause of death, opening up discussions surrounding the pressing issue of drug use and mental health struggles among artists and young people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Angus’s family released a statement expressing their profound grief and shared their hope that Angus’s battle with mental health would serve as a reminder to others that they are not alone in their struggles. “Angus was open about his battle with mental health and we hope that his passing can be a reminder to others that they are not alone and should not fight this on their own in silence,” the statement read.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-star-with-a-special-presence&quot;&gt;A Star with a Special Presence&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Angus Cloud’s portrayal of Fezco, a high school dropout and drug dealer, was praised for its depth and authenticity. Despite the character’s rough exterior, Angus imbued Fezco with a sense of vulnerability and relatability, earning him adoration from fans and respect from colleagues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cloud’s sudden rise to fame began when he was “plucked off the street” and cast in ‘Euphoria’. He had discussed the complexities of playing such a role and had been open about bringing a lot of his own experiences and emotions to the character of Fezco. The show’s casting director, Jennifer Venditti, remarked that Angus did not “get enough credit” for the work he put into his role.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;tributes-pour-in&quot;&gt;Tributes Pour In&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Angus’s passing saw an outpour of grief and love from co-stars, especially Zendaya, the lead actress of ‘Euphoria’. Zendaya, in a heartfelt Instagram post, described Angus as a person of “infinite beauty” and expressed her gratitude for having known him. “I’m so grateful I got the chance to know him in this life, to call him a brother, to see his warm kind eyes and bright smile, or hear his infectious cackle of a laugh,” she wrote.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;remembering-angus&quot;&gt;Remembering Angus&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Angus Cloud leaves behind a legacy marked by talent, resilience, and an undeniable presence. His struggles underscore the pressing need for open discussions surrounding mental health and substance abuse, especially among young people in the limelight. In these moments of loss and reflection, the hope remains that society can move towards greater understanding and support for those battling their inner demons, and in doing so, honor the memory of artists like Angus.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">The entertainment world is still coming to terms with the tragic loss of Angus Cloud, who shot to fame with his breakout role in the hit HBO series ‘Euphoria’. Angus, also known as Conor Hickey, passed away on July 31 at the tender age of 25, leaving fans and fellow cast members grieving. Accidental Overdose and Unanswered Questions Fox News Digital has confirmed that Angus’s untimely death was the result of an accidental overdose. The Alameda County Coroner’s office revealed a mix of methamphetamine, cocaine, fentanyl, and benzodiazepines as the cause of death, opening up discussions surrounding the pressing issue of drug use and mental health struggles among artists and young people. Angus’s family released a statement expressing their profound grief and shared their hope that Angus’s battle with mental health would serve as a reminder to others that they are not alone in their struggles. “Angus was open about his battle with mental health and we hope that his passing can be a reminder to others that they are not alone and should not fight this on their own in silence,” the statement read. A Star with a Special Presence Angus Cloud’s portrayal of Fezco, a high school dropout and drug dealer, was praised for its depth and authenticity. Despite the character’s rough exterior, Angus imbued Fezco with a sense of vulnerability and relatability, earning him adoration from fans and respect from colleagues. Cloud’s sudden rise to fame began when he was “plucked off the street” and cast in ‘Euphoria’. He had discussed the complexities of playing such a role and had been open about bringing a lot of his own experiences and emotions to the character of Fezco. The show’s casting director, Jennifer Venditti, remarked that Angus did not “get enough credit” for the work he put into his role. Tributes Pour In Angus’s passing saw an outpour of grief and love from co-stars, especially Zendaya, the lead actress of ‘Euphoria’. Zendaya, in a heartfelt Instagram post, described Angus as a person of “infinite beauty” and expressed her gratitude for having known him. “I’m so grateful I got the chance to know him in this life, to call him a brother, to see his warm kind eyes and bright smile, or hear his infectious cackle of a laugh,” she wrote. Remembering Angus Angus Cloud leaves behind a legacy marked by talent, resilience, and an undeniable presence. His struggles underscore the pressing need for open discussions surrounding mental health and substance abuse, especially among young people in the limelight. In these moments of loss and reflection, the hope remains that society can move towards greater understanding and support for those battling their inner demons, and in doing so, honor the memory of artists like Angus.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Sahel’s Power Play - Former French Colonies Forge New Defense Alliance</title><link href="/news/2023/09/22/Sahel-Defense-Alliance/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sahel’s Power Play - Former French Colonies Forge New Defense Alliance" /><published>2023-09-22T07:01:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-22T07:01:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/22/Sahel-Defense-Alliance</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/22/Sahel-Defense-Alliance/">&lt;p&gt;Amidst a backdrop of political upheavals and security concerns, the landlocked West African nations of Mali, Niger, and Burkina Faso have announced the formation of the Alliance of Sahel States. This alliance comes as a bold move from nations previously aligned with the G5 Sahel Alliance, a group significantly supported by France, aiming to combat terrorism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-strategic-alliance-in-the-sahel&quot;&gt;A Strategic Alliance in the Sahel&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The countries involved have witnessed military coups overturning their elected governments: Mali in 2021, Burkina Faso in 2022, and Niger in July 2023. Now, under military regimes, these nations have inked a mutual defense pact on September 16, 2023, in Bamako, known as the Liptako-Gourma Charter, which could shape regional dynamics significantly. This alliance mandates mutual defense and suppression of armed uprisings in each other’s territories.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;sahel-states-vs-france&quot;&gt;Sahel States vs. France&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This defense pact appears as a definitive step following the deteriorating relations between these nations and France. Niger, especially, has expressed substantial concern over French involvement in the region and has compelled France to withdraw all forces from its territory, impacting the counterterrorism agreements profoundly. This development has sparked protests, with the local populace demanding the exit of French forces.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;why-the-alliance-matters&quot;&gt;Why the Alliance Matters&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This alliance is not just a military arrangement; it intertwines the economic and political futures of the involved nations and stresses the importance of political independence, human dignity, and economic emancipation for the African people and countries. The pact appears crucial for Mali, dealing with external military intervention fears and internal insurgencies, and offers Burkina Faso an opportunity to assume a leadership role, being relatively stable compared to its allies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;addressing-regional-turmoil&quot;&gt;Addressing Regional Turmoil&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Liptako-Gourma region, where the borders of Mali, Burkina Faso, and Niger converge, has been a hotspot for Islamist extremist violence for over a decade. This alliance seems to be a response to ongoing regional strife and is aimed at establishing a cohesive front against terrorism, symbolizing a united effort for regional stability and security.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-new-chapter-in-regional-dynamics&quot;&gt;A New Chapter in Regional Dynamics&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The formation of the Alliance of Sahel States is a pivotal move that has the potential to reshape the geopolitical and security landscape of the Sahel region. It marks a departure from previous alignments and sets the stage for a new era of regional cooperation and conflict. Whether this alliance will prove to be a bastion of stability or a precursor to further tension remains to be seen, but it undoubtedly signals a new trajectory in the intricate tapestry of Sahel’s geopolitics.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Amidst a backdrop of political upheavals and security concerns, the landlocked West African nations of Mali, Niger, and Burkina Faso have announced the formation of the Alliance of Sahel States. This alliance comes as a bold move from nations previously aligned with the G5 Sahel Alliance, a group significantly supported by France, aiming to combat terrorism. A Strategic Alliance in the Sahel The countries involved have witnessed military coups overturning their elected governments: Mali in 2021, Burkina Faso in 2022, and Niger in July 2023. Now, under military regimes, these nations have inked a mutual defense pact on September 16, 2023, in Bamako, known as the Liptako-Gourma Charter, which could shape regional dynamics significantly. This alliance mandates mutual defense and suppression of armed uprisings in each other’s territories. Sahel States vs. France This defense pact appears as a definitive step following the deteriorating relations between these nations and France. Niger, especially, has expressed substantial concern over French involvement in the region and has compelled France to withdraw all forces from its territory, impacting the counterterrorism agreements profoundly. This development has sparked protests, with the local populace demanding the exit of French forces. Why the Alliance Matters This alliance is not just a military arrangement; it intertwines the economic and political futures of the involved nations and stresses the importance of political independence, human dignity, and economic emancipation for the African people and countries. The pact appears crucial for Mali, dealing with external military intervention fears and internal insurgencies, and offers Burkina Faso an opportunity to assume a leadership role, being relatively stable compared to its allies. Addressing Regional Turmoil The Liptako-Gourma region, where the borders of Mali, Burkina Faso, and Niger converge, has been a hotspot for Islamist extremist violence for over a decade. This alliance seems to be a response to ongoing regional strife and is aimed at establishing a cohesive front against terrorism, symbolizing a united effort for regional stability and security. A New Chapter in Regional Dynamics The formation of the Alliance of Sahel States is a pivotal move that has the potential to reshape the geopolitical and security landscape of the Sahel region. It marks a departure from previous alignments and sets the stage for a new era of regional cooperation and conflict. Whether this alliance will prove to be a bastion of stability or a precursor to further tension remains to be seen, but it undoubtedly signals a new trajectory in the intricate tapestry of Sahel’s geopolitics.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Era of the Media Titan - Rupert Murdoch Steps Back, But Not Out</title><link href="/media/2023/09/22/Media-Mogul-Transition/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Era of the Media Titan - Rupert Murdoch Steps Back, But Not Out" /><published>2023-09-22T06:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-22T06:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/media/2023/09/22/Media-Mogul-Transition</id><content type="html" xml:base="/media/2023/09/22/Media-Mogul-Transition/">&lt;p&gt;Rupert Murdoch, the powerful and transformative media mogul, has decided to step back from the leadership roles he held in his illustrious companies, Fox Corporation and News Corp. The iconic figure announced he is transitioning to the role of Chairman Emeritus, a change set to be formalized in November.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-new-chapter&quot;&gt;A New Chapter&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the age of 92, Murdoch reassured his colleagues through a letter that he remains in good health and his engagement with news and ideas will persist. His son, Lachlan Murdoch, is slated to take up the mantle as the sole chairman of both companies. Rupert Murdoch’s enduring engagement with the fields of news and ideas underscores his commitment to the companies he nurtured, and this new role allows him to stay connected, albeit from a distance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-legacy-of-influence-and-innovation&quot;&gt;A Legacy of Influence and Innovation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rupert Murdoch’s journey started in the 1950s in Australia, evolving over the decades to leave an indelible mark on the media landscapes across continents. From taking control of News Limited in his mid-20s to establishing the internationally consolidated News Corporation in 1980, Murdoch’s impact has been both expansive and transformative.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Murdoch’s innovations in media and his relentless pursuit of a diversified media empire, including television networks, newspapers, and magazines, have reshaped media consumption globally. With acquisitions like Twentieth Century Fox and the launch of the FOX Broadcasting Company, Murdoch established precedents and set high standards in the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;staunch-defender-of-freedoms&quot;&gt;Staunch Defender of Freedoms&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Murdoch emphasized that his commitment to the cause of freedom of speech and thought would remain unswerving. He critiqued the contemptuous elites and some media entities, asserting that they have been pushing narratives rather than pursuing truth. In his newly announced role, he guaranteed his everyday involvement in the “contest of ideas.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;lachlan-steps-up&quot;&gt;Lachlan Steps Up&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lachlan Murdoch, who will lead both companies, conveyed his admiration and gratitude to his father for his visionary approach, pioneering spirit, and the enduring legacy he established. He expressed his excitement about having his father continue to serve as Chairman Emeritus, offering valuable counsel to both companies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-journey-of-impact&quot;&gt;A Journey of Impact&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rupert Murdoch’s career is a testament to a passion for media and a vision that spanned and connected the world. The accolades he received, including the Companion of the Order of Australia and induction into the Television Academy Hall of Fame, are acknowledgments of his lasting influence in the media industry. His philanthropic contributions across various domains, including education, culture, and medical research, underscore his multifaceted impact on societies around the globe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-continuing-journey&quot;&gt;A Continuing Journey&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even as he transitions into a new phase, Murdoch’s influence in the field of media is set to endure. His new role as Chairman Emeritus ensures his continued involvement in the companies he built and the ideas he championed. The media landscape, marked indelibly by his innovations and standards, watches as a new chapter in Rupert Murdoch’s journey unfolds.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Media" /><summary type="html">Rupert Murdoch, the powerful and transformative media mogul, has decided to step back from the leadership roles he held in his illustrious companies, Fox Corporation and News Corp. The iconic figure announced he is transitioning to the role of Chairman Emeritus, a change set to be formalized in November. A New Chapter At the age of 92, Murdoch reassured his colleagues through a letter that he remains in good health and his engagement with news and ideas will persist. His son, Lachlan Murdoch, is slated to take up the mantle as the sole chairman of both companies. Rupert Murdoch’s enduring engagement with the fields of news and ideas underscores his commitment to the companies he nurtured, and this new role allows him to stay connected, albeit from a distance. A Legacy of Influence and Innovation Rupert Murdoch’s journey started in the 1950s in Australia, evolving over the decades to leave an indelible mark on the media landscapes across continents. From taking control of News Limited in his mid-20s to establishing the internationally consolidated News Corporation in 1980, Murdoch’s impact has been both expansive and transformative. Murdoch’s innovations in media and his relentless pursuit of a diversified media empire, including television networks, newspapers, and magazines, have reshaped media consumption globally. With acquisitions like Twentieth Century Fox and the launch of the FOX Broadcasting Company, Murdoch established precedents and set high standards in the industry. Staunch Defender of Freedoms Murdoch emphasized that his commitment to the cause of freedom of speech and thought would remain unswerving. He critiqued the contemptuous elites and some media entities, asserting that they have been pushing narratives rather than pursuing truth. In his newly announced role, he guaranteed his everyday involvement in the “contest of ideas.” Lachlan Steps Up Lachlan Murdoch, who will lead both companies, conveyed his admiration and gratitude to his father for his visionary approach, pioneering spirit, and the enduring legacy he established. He expressed his excitement about having his father continue to serve as Chairman Emeritus, offering valuable counsel to both companies. A Journey of Impact Rupert Murdoch’s career is a testament to a passion for media and a vision that spanned and connected the world. The accolades he received, including the Companion of the Order of Australia and induction into the Television Academy Hall of Fame, are acknowledgments of his lasting influence in the media industry. His philanthropic contributions across various domains, including education, culture, and medical research, underscore his multifaceted impact on societies around the globe. A Continuing Journey Even as he transitions into a new phase, Murdoch’s influence in the field of media is set to endure. His new role as Chairman Emeritus ensures his continued involvement in the companies he built and the ideas he championed. The media landscape, marked indelibly by his innovations and standards, watches as a new chapter in Rupert Murdoch’s journey unfolds.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Connection Between Trident DMG and Democrats Takes Center Stage</title><link href="/news/2023/09/21/Democrat-Linked-PR-Firm/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Connection Between Trident DMG and Democrats Takes Center Stage" /><published>2023-09-21T17:21:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-21T17:21:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/21/Democrat-Linked-PR-Firm</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/21/Democrat-Linked-PR-Firm/">&lt;p&gt;Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu’s recent encounters with protestors in cities like California and New York over his proposed judicial reforms have raised eyebrows. The protests, although seemingly grassroots, might have more intricate ties, namely to Trident DMG, a PR firm based in Washington with known affiliations to the Democratic Party.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trident DMG’s connections to the Democratic Party are no secret in the corridors of power in Washington. And now, with reports suggesting their potential role in organizing opposition against Netanyahu on U.S. soil, these ties are receiving greater scrutiny. Their association with Blue and White Future, an organization from Israel that stands against Netanyahu, has only fueled these speculations. Reports highlight a three-month contract worth $75,000 between Trident DMG and the Israeli organization, putting the PR firm’s Democrat links under the spotlight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eleanor McManus, co-founder and partner of Trident DMG, while emphasizing the company’s role in promoting awareness about the so-called “democracy crisis” in Israel, stopped short of confirming or denying their direct involvement in the U.S. protests against Netanyahu. However, her statement did little to dissuade discussions about the firm’s connections to Democratic power players and their possible influence in international political issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The growing concerns in the Jewish community, fearing an amplification of anti-Israel narratives due to these protests, adds another layer to this unfolding drama. With Trident DMG at the crosshairs, and their Democratic links being examined closely, the tale of foreign influences shaping domestic protests gains yet another chapter.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu’s recent encounters with protestors in cities like California and New York over his proposed judicial reforms have raised eyebrows. The protests, although seemingly grassroots, might have more intricate ties, namely to Trident DMG, a PR firm based in Washington with known affiliations to the Democratic Party. Trident DMG’s connections to the Democratic Party are no secret in the corridors of power in Washington. And now, with reports suggesting their potential role in organizing opposition against Netanyahu on U.S. soil, these ties are receiving greater scrutiny. Their association with Blue and White Future, an organization from Israel that stands against Netanyahu, has only fueled these speculations. Reports highlight a three-month contract worth $75,000 between Trident DMG and the Israeli organization, putting the PR firm’s Democrat links under the spotlight. Eleanor McManus, co-founder and partner of Trident DMG, while emphasizing the company’s role in promoting awareness about the so-called “democracy crisis” in Israel, stopped short of confirming or denying their direct involvement in the U.S. protests against Netanyahu. However, her statement did little to dissuade discussions about the firm’s connections to Democratic power players and their possible influence in international political issues. The growing concerns in the Jewish community, fearing an amplification of anti-Israel narratives due to these protests, adds another layer to this unfolding drama. With Trident DMG at the crosshairs, and their Democratic links being examined closely, the tale of foreign influences shaping domestic protests gains yet another chapter.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Serious Felony Charges - Hunter Biden’s Virtual Court Appearance Disputed</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/21/Hunter-Biden-Felony-Charges/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Serious Felony Charges - Hunter Biden’s Virtual Court Appearance Disputed" /><published>2023-09-21T16:10:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-21T16:10:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/21/Hunter-Biden-Felony-Charges</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/21/Hunter-Biden-Felony-Charges/">&lt;p&gt;In an unfolding legal saga, Special Counsel David Weiss is contesting Hunter Biden’s wish to make his court appearance virtually regarding the significant felony gun charges he faces.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-virtual-tug-of-war&quot;&gt;A Virtual Tug-of-War&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hunter Biden, the son of President Joe Biden, has found himself in hot water with the law. He has been slapped with charges, including making false statements during a firearm purchase and possessing a gun while being an unlawful user or addicted to controlled substances. These accusations have come to the limelight amidst the broader controversies surrounding his past actions and decisions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Biden’s legal team, led by attorney Abbe Lowell, sent out a request for the preliminary court appearance to be held virtually. However, this request isn’t sitting well with some, notably Special Counsel David Weiss.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-grounds-of-opposition&quot;&gt;The Grounds of Opposition&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Weiss has made his stance clear by objecting to this request. His reasoning? The charges are of a “serious” nature, and it’s essential for the court to assess Hunter in person, especially when determining conditions of release. The emphasis here is on the gravity of the charges and the need for the court to make accurate evaluations without the limitations of a video call.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The counter-argument from Biden’s legal team is that they’re not asking for any special treatment. Lowell argues that Hunter is trying to minimize unnecessary strains on government resources, given the logistical challenges of a Secret Service-protected individual traveling cross-country and the subsequent disruptions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-backstory&quot;&gt;The Backstory&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This isn’t the first time Hunter Biden’s activities have made the news. Fox News highlighted an incident from 2018 where a firearm owned by him was discarded in a trash bin near a school in Delaware. This event adds another layer of complexity to the current charges and the surrounding narrative.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, Hunter Biden’s past has been brought to light with his discharge from the Navy in 2014, following a positive cocaine test.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-challenge-to-the-system&quot;&gt;A Challenge to the System?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Abbe Lowell is not backing down without a fight. He’s raised concerns over the nature of the charges and argues that they may be influenced by political pressure. Lowell believes that Hunter’s brief possession of an unloaded gun did not pose a public safety risk. In contrast, a prosecutor succumbing to political influences could threaten the justice system’s integrity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the case progresses, many await to see how this chapter in Hunter Biden’s tumultuous life will conclude. Whether the court appearance will be virtual or in-person remains undecided, but one thing is clear: this legal battle has only just begun.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In an unfolding legal saga, Special Counsel David Weiss is contesting Hunter Biden’s wish to make his court appearance virtually regarding the significant felony gun charges he faces. A Virtual Tug-of-War Hunter Biden, the son of President Joe Biden, has found himself in hot water with the law. He has been slapped with charges, including making false statements during a firearm purchase and possessing a gun while being an unlawful user or addicted to controlled substances. These accusations have come to the limelight amidst the broader controversies surrounding his past actions and decisions. Biden’s legal team, led by attorney Abbe Lowell, sent out a request for the preliminary court appearance to be held virtually. However, this request isn’t sitting well with some, notably Special Counsel David Weiss. The Grounds of Opposition Weiss has made his stance clear by objecting to this request. His reasoning? The charges are of a “serious” nature, and it’s essential for the court to assess Hunter in person, especially when determining conditions of release. The emphasis here is on the gravity of the charges and the need for the court to make accurate evaluations without the limitations of a video call. The counter-argument from Biden’s legal team is that they’re not asking for any special treatment. Lowell argues that Hunter is trying to minimize unnecessary strains on government resources, given the logistical challenges of a Secret Service-protected individual traveling cross-country and the subsequent disruptions. The Backstory This isn’t the first time Hunter Biden’s activities have made the news. Fox News highlighted an incident from 2018 where a firearm owned by him was discarded in a trash bin near a school in Delaware. This event adds another layer of complexity to the current charges and the surrounding narrative. Furthermore, Hunter Biden’s past has been brought to light with his discharge from the Navy in 2014, following a positive cocaine test. A Challenge to the System? Abbe Lowell is not backing down without a fight. He’s raised concerns over the nature of the charges and argues that they may be influenced by political pressure. Lowell believes that Hunter’s brief possession of an unloaded gun did not pose a public safety risk. In contrast, a prosecutor succumbing to political influences could threaten the justice system’s integrity. As the case progresses, many await to see how this chapter in Hunter Biden’s tumultuous life will conclude. Whether the court appearance will be virtual or in-person remains undecided, but one thing is clear: this legal battle has only just begun.</summary></entry></feed>