<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-09-20T14:20:24-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/09/20/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-09-20T14:20:24-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-20T14:20:24-04:00</updated><id>/2023/09/20/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/20/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Innovative or Controversial? - AI Chatbot Assists with Abortion Information</title><link href="/news/2023/09/20/AI-Abortion-Chatbot/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Innovative or Controversial? - AI Chatbot Assists with Abortion Information" /><published>2023-09-20T14:02:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-20T14:02:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/20/AI-Abortion-Chatbot</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/20/AI-Abortion-Chatbot/">&lt;p&gt;In a tech-meets-healthcare development, a new AI chatbot named “Charley, The Abortion Chatbot” is designed to guide pregnant women and teens towards abortion services. Developed by Cecile Richards and Tom Subak, two former officials from Planned Parenthood, the chatbot aims to offer private and precise information about abortion, but not without its share of criticisms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Upon visiting the National Women’s Health Network website, users are greeted by Charley saying, “Hi, my name’s Charley. I can help you get an abortion. Let’s get started.” The platform ensures user privacy, requesting only the date of the user’s last menstrual cycle and their state of residence. In its guidance, it covers topics like nearest abortion providers, how minors can seek an abortion without parental consent, and details about mail-order abortion drugs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, not everyone views Charley as a helpful tool. E.V. Osment, the vice president of SBA Pro-Life America, expressed concerns to the Washington Examiner, stating that such platforms could endanger lives and potentially promote illegal activities. A run-through of Charley by the Examiner revealed that it provided out-of-state options with fewer restrictions for users based in Virginia. For Mississippi users, the chatbot even suggested leaving the country or heading to Puerto Rico, a U.S. territory where passports aren’t needed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Co-founders Richards and Subak envision Charley being integrated into various medical and abortion clinic websites across the nation. Nicole Cushman, the content manager for Charley, shed light on their motivation: “Our research showed that people were turning primarily to Google for information about abortion options in the post-Roe landscape and that it was very challenging for abortion seekers to connect to available options.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The rise of Charley underscores a growing intersection of technology and healthcare, with the ongoing debate around abortion only intensifying the scrutiny of such platforms. As with many tools of this nature, the line between empowerment and controversy remains thin.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a tech-meets-healthcare development, a new AI chatbot named “Charley, The Abortion Chatbot” is designed to guide pregnant women and teens towards abortion services. Developed by Cecile Richards and Tom Subak, two former officials from Planned Parenthood, the chatbot aims to offer private and precise information about abortion, but not without its share of criticisms. Upon visiting the National Women’s Health Network website, users are greeted by Charley saying, “Hi, my name’s Charley. I can help you get an abortion. Let’s get started.” The platform ensures user privacy, requesting only the date of the user’s last menstrual cycle and their state of residence. In its guidance, it covers topics like nearest abortion providers, how minors can seek an abortion without parental consent, and details about mail-order abortion drugs. However, not everyone views Charley as a helpful tool. E.V. Osment, the vice president of SBA Pro-Life America, expressed concerns to the Washington Examiner, stating that such platforms could endanger lives and potentially promote illegal activities. A run-through of Charley by the Examiner revealed that it provided out-of-state options with fewer restrictions for users based in Virginia. For Mississippi users, the chatbot even suggested leaving the country or heading to Puerto Rico, a U.S. territory where passports aren’t needed. Co-founders Richards and Subak envision Charley being integrated into various medical and abortion clinic websites across the nation. Nicole Cushman, the content manager for Charley, shed light on their motivation: “Our research showed that people were turning primarily to Google for information about abortion options in the post-Roe landscape and that it was very challenging for abortion seekers to connect to available options.” The rise of Charley underscores a growing intersection of technology and healthcare, with the ongoing debate around abortion only intensifying the scrutiny of such platforms. As with many tools of this nature, the line between empowerment and controversy remains thin.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Vanna White Secures Her Spot - Ryan Seacrest Set to Spin the “Wheel”</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/20/Wheel-of-Fortune/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Vanna White Secures Her Spot - Ryan Seacrest Set to Spin the “Wheel”" /><published>2023-09-20T13:09:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-20T13:09:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/20/Wheel-of-Fortune</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/20/Wheel-of-Fortune/">&lt;p&gt;Vanna White is not leaving her letters just yet! She has renewed her contract with “Wheel of Fortune” for another two years. This extension ensures fans will see her light up the screen until the 2025-26 season.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, Pat Sajak, who’s been charming us with his hosting prowess since 1981, is set to retire in 2024. With his departure, Ryan Seacrest will step in to fill those big shoes, starting from fall 2024. Seacrest, who’s made waves co-hosting “Live with Kelly and Ryan,” expressed his disbelief and excitement about joining this legacy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sajak and White, a duo that has become synonymous with “Wheel of Fortune,” began their journey together in 1982. As Season 41 unfolds, viewers are in for a treat as they’ll see Maggie Sajak, Pat’s daughter, featuring the “Word of the Day” on her European tour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maggie is also upping the ante for the show’s fans. As the show’s Social Media Correspondent, she’s rolling out the “Fan Fridays” sweepstakes, giving fans opportunities to win exciting prizes every week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For Seacrest, joining “Wheel of Fortune” is like a dream come true. He recently shared his enthusiasm and gratitude, mentioning how he looked up to Sajak and is eagerly waiting to meet the contestants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All these new shifts and updates spell out an exciting future for “Wheel of Fortune.” As the show gears up for its next chapter, fans worldwide are ready and waiting to spin into the new era!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Vanna White is not leaving her letters just yet! She has renewed her contract with “Wheel of Fortune” for another two years. This extension ensures fans will see her light up the screen until the 2025-26 season. Meanwhile, Pat Sajak, who’s been charming us with his hosting prowess since 1981, is set to retire in 2024. With his departure, Ryan Seacrest will step in to fill those big shoes, starting from fall 2024. Seacrest, who’s made waves co-hosting “Live with Kelly and Ryan,” expressed his disbelief and excitement about joining this legacy. Sajak and White, a duo that has become synonymous with “Wheel of Fortune,” began their journey together in 1982. As Season 41 unfolds, viewers are in for a treat as they’ll see Maggie Sajak, Pat’s daughter, featuring the “Word of the Day” on her European tour. Maggie is also upping the ante for the show’s fans. As the show’s Social Media Correspondent, she’s rolling out the “Fan Fridays” sweepstakes, giving fans opportunities to win exciting prizes every week. For Seacrest, joining “Wheel of Fortune” is like a dream come true. He recently shared his enthusiasm and gratitude, mentioning how he looked up to Sajak and is eagerly waiting to meet the contestants. All these new shifts and updates spell out an exciting future for “Wheel of Fortune.” As the show gears up for its next chapter, fans worldwide are ready and waiting to spin into the new era!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Biden Under Fire - Voters See Evidence in Impeachment Inquiry</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/20/Biden-Impeachment-Evidence/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Biden Under Fire - Voters See Evidence in Impeachment Inquiry" /><published>2023-09-20T12:03:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-20T12:03:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/20/Biden-Impeachment-Evidence</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/20/Biden-Impeachment-Evidence/">&lt;p&gt;A recent poll has unveiled a startling revelation regarding the ongoing impeachment inquiry into President Joe Biden. Contrary to the assertions of several Democrats and media outlets that there’s no basis for the inquiry, a plurality of voters believe there’s indeed evidence pointing to Biden’s wrongdoing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Public Opinion Speaks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a Morning Consult poll released on Tuesday, a plurality of respondents (43-41 percent) stated that the main thrust behind the impeachment inquiry stems from genuine evidence of Biden’s transgressions. This sentiment isn’t limited to any one demographic; a plurality of independent voters (40-39 percent) share the same viewpoint. Notably, a significant 74 percent of Republican voters agree with the rationale behind the impeachment inquiry, even if just 16 percent of Democrats feel the same way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The findings seem to showcase a predominant narrative – that the GOP is successfully making a case for Biden’s impeachment in the court of public opinion. Statements from the White House, numerous Democrats, and media allies have been outright dismissive of the inquiry, emphasizing a lack of evidence. Yet, House Republicans have spotlighted various alleged pieces of evidence, including photos, videos, texts, and testimonies, implicating Biden in the controversy surrounding his family’s business dealings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Broader Consensus on Impeachment Inquiry&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further dissecting the poll’s data reveals another telling aspect: nearly half of the surveyed voters (48 percent) are in favor of the impeachment inquiry. Meanwhile, 42 percent are against it, and 10 percent remain on the fence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you break it down:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;47 percent of independent voters back the inquiry.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;36 percent of Democrats are in support.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A mere 31 percent of Republicans oppose the inquiry.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The findings indicate a general consensus, even among Democrats, that the impeachment inquiry is at the very least warranted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Implications for Biden and the Democrats&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Morning Consult’s analysis suggests that these findings should ring alarm bells for Biden and the Democratic party. For comparison, Democrats were less resistant to the idea of impeaching President Donald Trump in 2019 regarding his approach to Ukraine. Almost half of the Democrats believe either Biden committed an impeachable offense or he has demonstrated unfitness to serve.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Additionally, the ongoing saga seems to be benefiting Kevin McCarthy, the House speaker, who, despite facing challenges within the GOP, is now in the limelight due to the impeachment proceedings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In summary, the perception of Biden’s impeachment inquiry underscores the prevailing sentiment among voters. While many within the media and the Democratic party may downplay the legitimacy of the inquiry, a significant portion of the electorate feels otherwise. As the proceedings unfold, it remains to be seen how this perception might shape Biden’s presidency and the broader political landscape.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">A recent poll has unveiled a startling revelation regarding the ongoing impeachment inquiry into President Joe Biden. Contrary to the assertions of several Democrats and media outlets that there’s no basis for the inquiry, a plurality of voters believe there’s indeed evidence pointing to Biden’s wrongdoing. Public Opinion Speaks In a Morning Consult poll released on Tuesday, a plurality of respondents (43-41 percent) stated that the main thrust behind the impeachment inquiry stems from genuine evidence of Biden’s transgressions. This sentiment isn’t limited to any one demographic; a plurality of independent voters (40-39 percent) share the same viewpoint. Notably, a significant 74 percent of Republican voters agree with the rationale behind the impeachment inquiry, even if just 16 percent of Democrats feel the same way. The findings seem to showcase a predominant narrative – that the GOP is successfully making a case for Biden’s impeachment in the court of public opinion. Statements from the White House, numerous Democrats, and media allies have been outright dismissive of the inquiry, emphasizing a lack of evidence. Yet, House Republicans have spotlighted various alleged pieces of evidence, including photos, videos, texts, and testimonies, implicating Biden in the controversy surrounding his family’s business dealings. Broader Consensus on Impeachment Inquiry Further dissecting the poll’s data reveals another telling aspect: nearly half of the surveyed voters (48 percent) are in favor of the impeachment inquiry. Meanwhile, 42 percent are against it, and 10 percent remain on the fence. When you break it down: 47 percent of independent voters back the inquiry. 36 percent of Democrats are in support. A mere 31 percent of Republicans oppose the inquiry. The findings indicate a general consensus, even among Democrats, that the impeachment inquiry is at the very least warranted. Implications for Biden and the Democrats Morning Consult’s analysis suggests that these findings should ring alarm bells for Biden and the Democratic party. For comparison, Democrats were less resistant to the idea of impeaching President Donald Trump in 2019 regarding his approach to Ukraine. Almost half of the Democrats believe either Biden committed an impeachable offense or he has demonstrated unfitness to serve. Additionally, the ongoing saga seems to be benefiting Kevin McCarthy, the House speaker, who, despite facing challenges within the GOP, is now in the limelight due to the impeachment proceedings. In summary, the perception of Biden’s impeachment inquiry underscores the prevailing sentiment among voters. While many within the media and the Democratic party may downplay the legitimacy of the inquiry, a significant portion of the electorate feels otherwise. As the proceedings unfold, it remains to be seen how this perception might shape Biden’s presidency and the broader political landscape.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Sudden Loss - Temple University’s Acting President Dies on Stage</title><link href="/news/2023/09/20/Temple-University-Tragedy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sudden Loss - Temple University’s Acting President Dies on Stage" /><published>2023-09-20T11:05:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-20T11:05:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/20/Temple-University-Tragedy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/20/Temple-University-Tragedy/">&lt;p&gt;In a deeply tragic turn of events, JoAnne A. Epps, the acting president of Temple University, collapsed on stage during a memorial service on Tuesday. She was immediately rushed to the hospital but was sadly pronounced dead upon arrival.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Epps, 72, was attending a service in honor of Charles L. Blockson, a significant figure associated with the Blockson Collection at the university. The unexpected incident has sent shockwaves through the Temple University community and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a heartfelt statement released by the university, the extent of her impact was clear. “President Epps was a devoted servant and friend who represented the best parts of Temple. She spent nearly 40 years of her life serving this university, and her loss will reverberate through the community for years to come.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The exact cause of her demise has not been disclosed yet. Temple University Provost, Gregory Mandel, visibly shaken by the event, commented on Epps, saying, “We are all in deep grief and at a loss for words. To know Joanne is to be her friend. She was one of the most remarkably compassionate and caring individuals I’ve ever known.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Epps had a longstanding and influential role within Temple University. Prior to her position as acting president, she served as the dean of the university’s law school and later as provost. Her rise to the role of acting president came in the wake of the resignation of Jason Wingard, Temple’s first Black president. Reflecting on her journey, Epps had shared with local news, “I would never have imagined even becoming a professor at Temple, let alone being in this position.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pennsylvania’s Governor, Josh Shapiro, paid his respects by referring to Epps as a “powerful force and constant ambassador for Temple University for nearly four decades.” Expressing his grief on X (previously known as Twitter), he mentioned how this loss deeply impacts not just the university, but the entire city of Philadelphia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As acting president, Epps had been actively addressing vital concerns, notably focusing on the university’s enrollment and challenges tied to rising crime near the campus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As Temple University, Philadelphia, and the broader academic community grapple with this tragic loss, the legacy and contributions of JoAnne A. Epps will undoubtedly be remembered and cherished.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a deeply tragic turn of events, JoAnne A. Epps, the acting president of Temple University, collapsed on stage during a memorial service on Tuesday. She was immediately rushed to the hospital but was sadly pronounced dead upon arrival. Epps, 72, was attending a service in honor of Charles L. Blockson, a significant figure associated with the Blockson Collection at the university. The unexpected incident has sent shockwaves through the Temple University community and beyond. In a heartfelt statement released by the university, the extent of her impact was clear. “President Epps was a devoted servant and friend who represented the best parts of Temple. She spent nearly 40 years of her life serving this university, and her loss will reverberate through the community for years to come.” The exact cause of her demise has not been disclosed yet. Temple University Provost, Gregory Mandel, visibly shaken by the event, commented on Epps, saying, “We are all in deep grief and at a loss for words. To know Joanne is to be her friend. She was one of the most remarkably compassionate and caring individuals I’ve ever known.” Epps had a longstanding and influential role within Temple University. Prior to her position as acting president, she served as the dean of the university’s law school and later as provost. Her rise to the role of acting president came in the wake of the resignation of Jason Wingard, Temple’s first Black president. Reflecting on her journey, Epps had shared with local news, “I would never have imagined even becoming a professor at Temple, let alone being in this position.” Pennsylvania’s Governor, Josh Shapiro, paid his respects by referring to Epps as a “powerful force and constant ambassador for Temple University for nearly four decades.” Expressing his grief on X (previously known as Twitter), he mentioned how this loss deeply impacts not just the university, but the entire city of Philadelphia. As acting president, Epps had been actively addressing vital concerns, notably focusing on the university’s enrollment and challenges tied to rising crime near the campus. As Temple University, Philadelphia, and the broader academic community grapple with this tragic loss, the legacy and contributions of JoAnne A. Epps will undoubtedly be remembered and cherished.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Seven GOP Contenders Set Eyes on 2nd Debate Stage</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/20/GOP-Debate-Candidates/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Seven GOP Contenders Set Eyes on 2nd Debate Stage" /><published>2023-09-20T10:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-20T10:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/20/GOP-Debate-Candidates</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/20/GOP-Debate-Candidates/">&lt;p&gt;As the Republican primaries heat up, seven GOP candidates have apparently secured their spots for the second presidential debate, slated for September 27. However, all eyes are on former President Donald Trump, who’s choosing to skip the event in favor of addressing striking autoworkers in Michigan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who’s In and Who’s Out?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The debate, hosted at the Ronald Reagan Presidential Library in Simi Valley, California, will likely include a mix of familiar faces and emerging leaders:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Gov. Ron DeSantis (R-FL)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Entrepreneur Vivek Ramaswamy&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Former Gov. Nikki Haley (R-SC)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Former Vice President Mike Pence&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sen. Tim Scott (R-SC)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Former Gov. Chris Christie (R-NJ)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to CBS News politics reporter Aaron Navarro, these candidates have likely satisfied the Republican National Committee’s updated polling and donor prerequisites. However, Gov. Doug Burgum (R-ND) and former Gov. Asa Hutchinson (R-AR), both participants in the first debate, seem to be trailing behind in their bid to join the next round.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Debate Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Candidates looking to step onto the debate stage need to hit certain benchmarks:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Secure three percent or more in two national polls&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Alternatively, obtain at least three percent in one national poll and three percent in two of the initial four early voting states&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All polls considered must be dated August 1 or later. Additionally, hopefuls must also rally a total of 50,000 unique donors, a 10,000 donor increase from the first debate’s requirements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trump’s Counter-Move&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While these candidates are gearing up for a lively debate, Trump is charting his own course. Sources have confirmed that during the debate, Trump plans to engage with members of the United Auto Workers in Detroit, Michigan, who are currently striking against major automakers like General Motors, Ford, and Stellantis. The New York Times has indicated that Trump is set to give a “prime-time speech” to these union members.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This isn’t the first time Trump has opted for a counter-programming strategy. During the first debate, he rivaled the event with a gripping 45-minute interview with Tucker Carlson, which quickly went viral.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the third debate expected in Miami, Florida, in November, it’ll be intriguing to see how the political strategies evolve and what surprises lie ahead in this gripping election season.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">As the Republican primaries heat up, seven GOP candidates have apparently secured their spots for the second presidential debate, slated for September 27. However, all eyes are on former President Donald Trump, who’s choosing to skip the event in favor of addressing striking autoworkers in Michigan. Who’s In and Who’s Out? The debate, hosted at the Ronald Reagan Presidential Library in Simi Valley, California, will likely include a mix of familiar faces and emerging leaders: Gov. Ron DeSantis (R-FL) Entrepreneur Vivek Ramaswamy Former Gov. Nikki Haley (R-SC) Former Vice President Mike Pence Sen. Tim Scott (R-SC) Former Gov. Chris Christie (R-NJ) According to CBS News politics reporter Aaron Navarro, these candidates have likely satisfied the Republican National Committee’s updated polling and donor prerequisites. However, Gov. Doug Burgum (R-ND) and former Gov. Asa Hutchinson (R-AR), both participants in the first debate, seem to be trailing behind in their bid to join the next round. The Debate Requirements Candidates looking to step onto the debate stage need to hit certain benchmarks: Secure three percent or more in two national polls Alternatively, obtain at least three percent in one national poll and three percent in two of the initial four early voting states All polls considered must be dated August 1 or later. Additionally, hopefuls must also rally a total of 50,000 unique donors, a 10,000 donor increase from the first debate’s requirements. Trump’s Counter-Move While these candidates are gearing up for a lively debate, Trump is charting his own course. Sources have confirmed that during the debate, Trump plans to engage with members of the United Auto Workers in Detroit, Michigan, who are currently striking against major automakers like General Motors, Ford, and Stellantis. The New York Times has indicated that Trump is set to give a “prime-time speech” to these union members. This isn’t the first time Trump has opted for a counter-programming strategy. During the first debate, he rivaled the event with a gripping 45-minute interview with Tucker Carlson, which quickly went viral. With the third debate expected in Miami, Florida, in November, it’ll be intriguing to see how the political strategies evolve and what surprises lie ahead in this gripping election season.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A Wrong Turn - Arkansas Trooper Retires After Dramatic Mistake</title><link href="/news/2023/09/20/Arkansas-Trooper-Controversy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Wrong Turn - Arkansas Trooper Retires After Dramatic Mistake" /><published>2023-09-20T09:07:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-20T09:07:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/20/Arkansas-Trooper-Controversy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/20/Arkansas-Trooper-Controversy/">&lt;p&gt;While high-speed pursuits often make for thrilling movie scenes, real-life chases can have dire consequences - especially when mistakes are made. Arkansas recently witnessed such an incident when a state trooper mistakenly targeted the wrong vehicle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On a regular Sunday evening on Interstate 40, an Arkansas State Trooper was in hot pursuit of two vehicles reportedly speeding over 100 mph. One of these was a white sedan. In the midst of this chase, Trooper Cpl. Thomas Hubbard, possibly overwhelmed by the speed and intensity, misidentified a completely unrelated white sedan as the suspect’s car.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Without a moment’s hesitation, Hubbard executed a PIT (precision immobilization technique) maneuver on the innocent vehicle. For those unfamiliar, a PIT maneuver is a tactic used by police to force a fleeing car to lose control and stop. This involves a controlled hit by the police vehicle to the side near a rear wheel of the pursued vehicle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The unsuspecting white sedan, taken off guard, was sent spiraling to the shoulder of the interstate. Dashcam footage vividly captured this entire sequence: the rapid chase, the sedan flashing its brakes, and the subsequent collision.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But what about the occupants of the car? Miraculously, both the driver and the passenger emerged from the crash unscathed. They both declined medical treatment, demonstrating the resilience humans sometimes show in the face of sudden adversity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The aftermath of the incident has led to swift action. Hubbard has since submitted his retirement and remains off duty. The Arkansas State Police initiated an immediate internal review.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet, this isn’t the first time the Arkansas State Police have found themselves under scrutiny for PIT maneuvers. Back in 2021, a woman took legal action against another trooper who “negligently performed” a PIT maneuver, causing her car to overturn at 60 mph. Further investigations by local news revealed that between January 2017 and December 2020, the technique was used a staggering 306 times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But with such a powerful tactic comes grave responsibility. The Washington Post reported that since 2016, at least 30 people have lost their lives due to PIT maneuvers. Eighteen of these were for minor traffic violations, such as speeding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the wake of such statistics and recent incidents, it begs the question: Is it time for a thorough review and possible revision of this pursuit technique?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">While high-speed pursuits often make for thrilling movie scenes, real-life chases can have dire consequences - especially when mistakes are made. Arkansas recently witnessed such an incident when a state trooper mistakenly targeted the wrong vehicle. On a regular Sunday evening on Interstate 40, an Arkansas State Trooper was in hot pursuit of two vehicles reportedly speeding over 100 mph. One of these was a white sedan. In the midst of this chase, Trooper Cpl. Thomas Hubbard, possibly overwhelmed by the speed and intensity, misidentified a completely unrelated white sedan as the suspect’s car. Without a moment’s hesitation, Hubbard executed a PIT (precision immobilization technique) maneuver on the innocent vehicle. For those unfamiliar, a PIT maneuver is a tactic used by police to force a fleeing car to lose control and stop. This involves a controlled hit by the police vehicle to the side near a rear wheel of the pursued vehicle. The unsuspecting white sedan, taken off guard, was sent spiraling to the shoulder of the interstate. Dashcam footage vividly captured this entire sequence: the rapid chase, the sedan flashing its brakes, and the subsequent collision. But what about the occupants of the car? Miraculously, both the driver and the passenger emerged from the crash unscathed. They both declined medical treatment, demonstrating the resilience humans sometimes show in the face of sudden adversity. The aftermath of the incident has led to swift action. Hubbard has since submitted his retirement and remains off duty. The Arkansas State Police initiated an immediate internal review. Yet, this isn’t the first time the Arkansas State Police have found themselves under scrutiny for PIT maneuvers. Back in 2021, a woman took legal action against another trooper who “negligently performed” a PIT maneuver, causing her car to overturn at 60 mph. Further investigations by local news revealed that between January 2017 and December 2020, the technique was used a staggering 306 times. But with such a powerful tactic comes grave responsibility. The Washington Post reported that since 2016, at least 30 people have lost their lives due to PIT maneuvers. Eighteen of these were for minor traffic violations, such as speeding. In the wake of such statistics and recent incidents, it begs the question: Is it time for a thorough review and possible revision of this pursuit technique?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">When Freedom of Speech Faces Jail - The Lira Case in Ukraine</title><link href="/news/2023/09/20/Free-Speech-In-Ukraine/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="When Freedom of Speech Faces Jail - The Lira Case in Ukraine" /><published>2023-09-20T08:03:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-20T08:03:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/20/Free-Speech-In-Ukraine</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/20/Free-Speech-In-Ukraine/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Freedom Under Fire&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As Washington D.C.’s lawmakers debate over funneling billions of taxpayer dollars into Ukraine, the nation hailed for its democratic values, a controversial situation unfolds in the shadows. Gonzalo Lira, an American citizen journalist, remains behind bars in Ukraine. His supposed crime? Allegedly spreading Russian propaganda.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Billions on the Table&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;President Joe Biden’s administration is in talks to sanction another $24 billion for Ukraine. This is in addition to the massive $113 billion that Congress has already greenlit for the country since the onset of its conflict with Russia. While supporting Ukraine, Biden emphasized that such investment aids “the future of every country that seeks a world governed by basic rules.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet, one crucial issue remained absent from the president’s discourse, especially at the United Nations. The matter of Gonzalo Lira, the American-Chilean dual citizen jailed in Ukraine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lira’s Contentious Arrest&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gonzalo Lira, living in Ukraine’s Kharkiv city when Russia invaded, faces a potential prison term of five to eight years under Ukraine’s wartime propaganda regulations. He was apprehended in May, with Ukrainian authorities accusing him of producing content favoring Russia on his YouTube channel. Here, he challenged the mainstream narratives about the war, even suggesting provocations from the Ukrainian side and concerns about NATO’s eastward expansion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lira’s attempts to cross the Ukrainian-Hungarian border to claim asylum after a bail release led to his sudden social media silence. His chilling last words in a video hinted at a potential re-arrest and the grim prospect of “dying in prison.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Real Story Behind the Charges?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ukraine’s government alleges that Lira intended to legitimize Russia’s aggression against their nation. However, the charge sheet makes no mention of Lira ever collaborating with the Russian government or committing any tangible crimes beyond his social media statements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lira’s defense is simple: he shared his opinions on the conflict without causing harm to anyone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moreover, during his initial incarceration, Lira claims he faced physical abuse from fellow prisoners, indirectly facilitated by prison guards. He expressed disappointment, feeling the Chilean embassy showed more concern for his well-being than the U.S. State Department.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a response, a State Department spokesperson affirmed their knowledge of Lira’s detention and vowed to assist U.S. citizens abroad. However, the depth of this assistance remains unclear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Greater Implications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ukrainian military spokesperson Sarah Ashton-Cirillo, recently in the limelight for her bold statements against supposed Russian propagandists, testified against Lira, but asserted he was in good health during their encounter. U.S. Senator J.D. Vance has meanwhile raised concerns over Ukraine’s stance on free speech, questioning the measures they might take against it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ironically, while Lira remains detained, the Biden administration negotiated with Iran, leading to the release of five Americans in exchange for a $6 billion deal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As dollars continue flowing into Ukraine, it’s crucial to ask: At what cost to freedom and democratic values?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Freedom Under Fire As Washington D.C.’s lawmakers debate over funneling billions of taxpayer dollars into Ukraine, the nation hailed for its democratic values, a controversial situation unfolds in the shadows. Gonzalo Lira, an American citizen journalist, remains behind bars in Ukraine. His supposed crime? Allegedly spreading Russian propaganda. Billions on the Table President Joe Biden’s administration is in talks to sanction another $24 billion for Ukraine. This is in addition to the massive $113 billion that Congress has already greenlit for the country since the onset of its conflict with Russia. While supporting Ukraine, Biden emphasized that such investment aids “the future of every country that seeks a world governed by basic rules.” Yet, one crucial issue remained absent from the president’s discourse, especially at the United Nations. The matter of Gonzalo Lira, the American-Chilean dual citizen jailed in Ukraine. Lira’s Contentious Arrest Gonzalo Lira, living in Ukraine’s Kharkiv city when Russia invaded, faces a potential prison term of five to eight years under Ukraine’s wartime propaganda regulations. He was apprehended in May, with Ukrainian authorities accusing him of producing content favoring Russia on his YouTube channel. Here, he challenged the mainstream narratives about the war, even suggesting provocations from the Ukrainian side and concerns about NATO’s eastward expansion. Lira’s attempts to cross the Ukrainian-Hungarian border to claim asylum after a bail release led to his sudden social media silence. His chilling last words in a video hinted at a potential re-arrest and the grim prospect of “dying in prison.” The Real Story Behind the Charges? Ukraine’s government alleges that Lira intended to legitimize Russia’s aggression against their nation. However, the charge sheet makes no mention of Lira ever collaborating with the Russian government or committing any tangible crimes beyond his social media statements. Lira’s defense is simple: he shared his opinions on the conflict without causing harm to anyone. Moreover, during his initial incarceration, Lira claims he faced physical abuse from fellow prisoners, indirectly facilitated by prison guards. He expressed disappointment, feeling the Chilean embassy showed more concern for his well-being than the U.S. State Department. In a response, a State Department spokesperson affirmed their knowledge of Lira’s detention and vowed to assist U.S. citizens abroad. However, the depth of this assistance remains unclear. The Greater Implications Ukrainian military spokesperson Sarah Ashton-Cirillo, recently in the limelight for her bold statements against supposed Russian propagandists, testified against Lira, but asserted he was in good health during their encounter. U.S. Senator J.D. Vance has meanwhile raised concerns over Ukraine’s stance on free speech, questioning the measures they might take against it. Ironically, while Lira remains detained, the Biden administration negotiated with Iran, leading to the release of five Americans in exchange for a $6 billion deal. As dollars continue flowing into Ukraine, it’s crucial to ask: At what cost to freedom and democratic values?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">High-Profile Split - Bijou Phillips Seeks Divorce From Convicted Actor Danny Masterson</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/20/Bijou-Divorce/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="High-Profile Split - Bijou Phillips Seeks Divorce From Convicted Actor Danny Masterson" /><published>2023-09-20T07:12:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-20T07:12:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/20/Bijou-Divorce</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/20/Bijou-Divorce/">&lt;p&gt;In a turn of events that’s captured the attention of Hollywood and fans worldwide, Bijou Phillips, model and actress, has filed for divorce from her husband, actor Danny Masterson, best known for his role in the popular sitcom “That ’70s Show.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-marriage-under-the-spotlight&quot;&gt;A Marriage Under the Spotlight&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Phillips, 43, has cited “irreconcilable differences” in her official court documents. The couple, who got married in 2011, shares a daughter. Phillips’ petition notably seeks full legal and physical custody of their child, proposing visitation rights for Masterson.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While many knew them as a vibrant pair, especially after seeing them in matching outfits at various events, the shadows of recent events loomed large over their relationship. Just two weeks ago, Masterson, 47, received a sentence of 30 years to life in prison on two counts of forcible rape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-trials-and-emotional-rollercoaster&quot;&gt;The Trials and Emotional Rollercoaster&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The charges and subsequent conviction shook Hollywood. Masterson was on trial twice, with the first ending in a mistrial last November. He had faced accusations related to events occurring between 2001 and 2003 at his Hollywood Hills residence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Throughout the legal ordeals, Phillips remained a steadfast presence, supporting her husband in court. Sketches from the courtroom even captured a poignant moment where Masterson blew a kiss to his wife after his sentencing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This unwavering support might be why the news of their divorce has come as a surprise to many. Just last week, sources claimed Phillips had “no plans” to leave Masterson, even expressing her heartbreak and urging the court to consider his pivotal role in their family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-look-back-at-their-journey&quot;&gt;A Look Back at Their Journey&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The duo first crossed paths at a celebrity poker game in 2004. Their connection was instantaneous, leading to a 19-year journey together filled with ups and downs. They celebrated their union in 2011 and welcomed their daughter in 2014. Phillips once wrote about their bond, saying, “Danny and I have been together for 19 years… I can say that Danny has literally been a life-saving partner to me.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Masterson’s legal team has already signaled plans to appeal the court’s decision, citing alleged mistakes during the trial. On a related note, when the Church of Scientology was asked for a comment on Masterson’s case, they reaffirmed their policy urging members to adhere to the laws and denied any accusations of harassment towards the accusers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As this chapter ends and new ones begin for both Phillips and Masterson, fans and the entertainment world will be keenly watching and hoping for healing and closure for all involved.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">In a turn of events that’s captured the attention of Hollywood and fans worldwide, Bijou Phillips, model and actress, has filed for divorce from her husband, actor Danny Masterson, best known for his role in the popular sitcom “That ’70s Show.” A Marriage Under the Spotlight Phillips, 43, has cited “irreconcilable differences” in her official court documents. The couple, who got married in 2011, shares a daughter. Phillips’ petition notably seeks full legal and physical custody of their child, proposing visitation rights for Masterson. While many knew them as a vibrant pair, especially after seeing them in matching outfits at various events, the shadows of recent events loomed large over their relationship. Just two weeks ago, Masterson, 47, received a sentence of 30 years to life in prison on two counts of forcible rape. The Trials and Emotional Rollercoaster The charges and subsequent conviction shook Hollywood. Masterson was on trial twice, with the first ending in a mistrial last November. He had faced accusations related to events occurring between 2001 and 2003 at his Hollywood Hills residence. Throughout the legal ordeals, Phillips remained a steadfast presence, supporting her husband in court. Sketches from the courtroom even captured a poignant moment where Masterson blew a kiss to his wife after his sentencing. This unwavering support might be why the news of their divorce has come as a surprise to many. Just last week, sources claimed Phillips had “no plans” to leave Masterson, even expressing her heartbreak and urging the court to consider his pivotal role in their family. A Look Back at Their Journey The duo first crossed paths at a celebrity poker game in 2004. Their connection was instantaneous, leading to a 19-year journey together filled with ups and downs. They celebrated their union in 2011 and welcomed their daughter in 2014. Phillips once wrote about their bond, saying, “Danny and I have been together for 19 years… I can say that Danny has literally been a life-saving partner to me.” Masterson’s legal team has already signaled plans to appeal the court’s decision, citing alleged mistakes during the trial. On a related note, when the Church of Scientology was asked for a comment on Masterson’s case, they reaffirmed their policy urging members to adhere to the laws and denied any accusations of harassment towards the accusers. As this chapter ends and new ones begin for both Phillips and Masterson, fans and the entertainment world will be keenly watching and hoping for healing and closure for all involved.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump Calls Out Empty Seats at Biden’s UN Address</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/20/Trump-UN-Response/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump Calls Out Empty Seats at Biden’s UN Address" /><published>2023-09-20T06:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-20T06:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/20/Trump-UN-Response</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/20/Trump-UN-Response/">&lt;p&gt;In a recent post on Truth Social, former President Donald Trump pulled no punches when he highlighted the noticeably empty seats at President Joe Biden’s address to the United Nations General Assembly in New York. Trump’s assertion was clear: under Biden’s administration, America seems to have lost a measure of international respect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Biden Speaks to Half-Filled Hall&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Biden just finished his surrender (‘speech’) at the United Nations, and nobody, despite all we give them, showed up. No respect for America any longer!” Trump’s message on Truth Social stated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This observation was further underscored by the conspicuous absence of several world leaders. Notably missing were French President Emmanuel Macron, U.K. Prime Minister Rishi Sunak, India’s Prime Minister Narendra Modi, Chinese President Xi Jinping, and Russian President Vladimir Putin. With these key players absent, the U.S. was the only member of the five permanent members of the U.N. Security Council in attendance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Richard Gowan, U.N. director for the International Crisis Group, expressed his views to CBS News, noting the significance of the absence of Sunak and Macron.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Biden’s Appeal Amidst a Hollowed Audience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In his address, President Biden made passionate pleas to those present, emphasizing the importance of supporting Ukraine against Russia’s invasion. “Russia believes that the world will grow weary and allow it to brutalize Ukraine without consequence,” Biden remarked, urging the world to act.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In stark contrast, Trump has offered a decisive approach, stating his intention to resolve the Ukraine crisis within 24 hours should he be re-elected in 2024.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Questionable Choices on Iran&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adding to the list of criticisms, Biden’s recent dealings with Iran have come under severe scrutiny. A prisoner swap agreement, which allowed Iran to tap into $6 billion of previously frozen oil revenue, has been slammed by Republicans, including Trump.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The former President expressed his incredulity on Truth Social, questioning the wisdom of releasing funds while securing a mere trade of detainees. “How much of a kickback does Crooked Joe Biden get? Does anyone realize how much money 6 Billion Dollars is?” Trump asked pointedly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The White House countered by emphasizing that the funds would be strictly monitored and used only for humanitarian purposes. However, this response hasn’t silenced critics, including Trump, who see this move as a reflection of a broader theme of perceived weakness in Biden’s administration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With Biden’s recent actions raising eyebrows both at home and on the international stage, one can’t help but ponder if America’s position on the world stage is truly waning.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a recent post on Truth Social, former President Donald Trump pulled no punches when he highlighted the noticeably empty seats at President Joe Biden’s address to the United Nations General Assembly in New York. Trump’s assertion was clear: under Biden’s administration, America seems to have lost a measure of international respect. Biden Speaks to Half-Filled Hall “Biden just finished his surrender (‘speech’) at the United Nations, and nobody, despite all we give them, showed up. No respect for America any longer!” Trump’s message on Truth Social stated. This observation was further underscored by the conspicuous absence of several world leaders. Notably missing were French President Emmanuel Macron, U.K. Prime Minister Rishi Sunak, India’s Prime Minister Narendra Modi, Chinese President Xi Jinping, and Russian President Vladimir Putin. With these key players absent, the U.S. was the only member of the five permanent members of the U.N. Security Council in attendance. Richard Gowan, U.N. director for the International Crisis Group, expressed his views to CBS News, noting the significance of the absence of Sunak and Macron. Biden’s Appeal Amidst a Hollowed Audience In his address, President Biden made passionate pleas to those present, emphasizing the importance of supporting Ukraine against Russia’s invasion. “Russia believes that the world will grow weary and allow it to brutalize Ukraine without consequence,” Biden remarked, urging the world to act. In stark contrast, Trump has offered a decisive approach, stating his intention to resolve the Ukraine crisis within 24 hours should he be re-elected in 2024. Questionable Choices on Iran Adding to the list of criticisms, Biden’s recent dealings with Iran have come under severe scrutiny. A prisoner swap agreement, which allowed Iran to tap into $6 billion of previously frozen oil revenue, has been slammed by Republicans, including Trump. The former President expressed his incredulity on Truth Social, questioning the wisdom of releasing funds while securing a mere trade of detainees. “How much of a kickback does Crooked Joe Biden get? Does anyone realize how much money 6 Billion Dollars is?” Trump asked pointedly. The White House countered by emphasizing that the funds would be strictly monitored and used only for humanitarian purposes. However, this response hasn’t silenced critics, including Trump, who see this move as a reflection of a broader theme of perceived weakness in Biden’s administration. With Biden’s recent actions raising eyebrows both at home and on the international stage, one can’t help but ponder if America’s position on the world stage is truly waning.</summary></entry></feed>