<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-10-30T16:16:05-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/30/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-30T16:16:05-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-30T16:16:05-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/30/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/30/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/30/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-30T16:16:05-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-30T16:16:05-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/30/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/30/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/">&lt;p&gt;Recent surprise attacks by Hamas on Israel has fueled ongoing tensions between staunchly conservative commentators and the progressive “Squad” Democrats known for criticizing Israel. The intensity of the backlash highlights the deep political divide over foreign policy in the Middle East.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Hamas’ shocking attack, several members of the “Squad,” including Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.), called for a “ceasefire and de-escalation,” condemning the violence. The absence of a statement from Rep. Rashida Tlaib (D-Mich.) was notably called out by conservative media outlets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;South Carolina GOP Rep. Nancy Mace quickly labeled Ocasio-Cortez a “Hamas apologist” in response to her call for peace and de-escalation. Rep. Ilhan Omar (D-Minn.), no stranger to controversy surrounding her views on Israel, echoed the call for de-escalation and ceasefire. Omar’s prior statements comparing the US and Israel to terrorist groups like Hamas and the Taliban resurfaced in the debate, fueling more criticisms. Omar’s 2019 tweet, where she opined that “Israel has hypnotized the world,” also continues to haunt her political career, often cited by critics to challenge her stance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conservative commentators have been especially vocal. “FOX &amp;amp; Friends Weekend” co-host Rachel Campos-Duffy took aim at Omar, saying she fails to recognize the peace in the Middle East under Trump’s administration. Conservative pundit John Hasson also called out Omar, claiming she insinuated that attacks on IDF forces were acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Massachusetts Democrat Rep. Ayanna Pressley’s concerns over the “devastating attacks on Israelis” were met with skepticism. A prominent conservative online personality, Comfortably Smug, accused the “Squad” of advising Israel to back down after the nation suffered massive attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Jamaal Bowman’s call for an end to the Gaza blockade, in addition to condemning the Hamas attacks, was met with criticism from conservative radio host Jason Rantz. He accused Bowman of pairing his condemnation of terrorism with unwarranted criticisms of Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Cori Bush emphasized the urgent need for a ceasefire, while pushing for an end to “U.S. support for Israeli military occupation and apartheid.” Defense attorney Marina Medvin criticized Bush, suggesting that she equates the death of Palestinian terrorists to the horrific acts committed against Jewish civilians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amidst the political turmoil and intense debate, the attacks have taken a heavy toll. Israeli media report over 300 dead due to the wide-ranging assault. Gaza health officials note that at least 200 Palestinians have perished in the retaliatory Israeli air strikes following the initial Hamas attack. As the situation remains volatile, both sides continue to count their casualties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This divisive issue showcases the challenge America faces in crafting a unified approach to foreign policy, with deeply entrenched political divides at play. As the situation develops, the debate is bound to intensify, shedding light on the complexities of U.S. politics in the global arena.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Pentagon’s Unprecedented Power Play: A Bomb 24 Times Stronger than Hiroshima</title><link href="/news/2023/10/30/Nuclear-Bomb-Power-Increase/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Pentagon’s Unprecedented Power Play: A Bomb 24 Times Stronger than Hiroshima" /><published>2023-10-30T13:54:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-30T13:54:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/30/Nuclear-Bomb-Power-Increase</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/30/Nuclear-Bomb-Power-Increase/">&lt;p&gt;The Pentagon’s recent announcement of its intention to develop a nuclear bomb 24 times more powerful than the one dropped on Hiroshima has sent shockwaves around the globe, stirring a pot of controversial debate and critical reflection. This move marks a significant escalation in the country’s military capabilities, but it also raises important questions about the world’s future in terms of nuclear armament and security.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a press release issued earlier this week, the Department of Defense outlined their plans for the B61-13, a modern iteration of the B61 nuclear gravity bomb. John Plumb, Assistant Secretary of Defense for Space Policy, emphasized that this development is a direct response to a changing security environment and the emerging threats posed by potential adversaries. He underscored the United States’ obligation to continually assess and adapt its capabilities to ensure a credible deterrence strategy, as well as to uphold its commitments to allied nations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The B61-13 is projected to have a similar yield to the B61-7, boasting a maximum yield of 360 kilotons. To put this in perspective, the bomb dropped on Hiroshima during World War II had a yield of approximately 15 kilotons, making the B61-13 about 24 times more powerful. Furthermore, it would be approximately 14 times larger than the bomb dropped on Nagasaki. Despite its formidable power, the Pentagon assures that the B61-13 will incorporate the latest safety, security, and accuracy features, akin to those found in the B61-12.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This news comes amid escalating global tensions and following a high-explosive experiment conducted by the U.S. at a nuclear test site in Nevada. Officials state that these tests are integral to advancing nuclear nonproliferation goals and enhancing the country’s ability to detect underground nuclear explosive tests. However, the timing of this announcement, coupled with Russia’s anticipated withdrawal from the 1966 Comprehensive Nuclear Test Ban Treaty, has reignited fears of a potential nuclear arms race.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Pentagon is clear in its statement that, if approved, the B61-13 would not result in an increase in the overall number of nuclear weapons in the U.S. stockpile; instead, it would serve to replace some of the existing B61-7s. Plumb reiterated that this development represents a measured and necessary step in addressing the challenges of an increasingly unpredictable and dynamic security environment, providing the U.S. with greater flexibility while maintaining a responsible approach to nuclear armament.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the world grapples with the implications of this development, the debate continues over the necessity, ethics, and potential risks associated with possessing such an unparalleled level of destructive power. The path forward remains uncertain, and the discourse on global security and the future of nuclear weaponry is more crucial than ever.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">The Pentagon’s recent announcement of its intention to develop a nuclear bomb 24 times more powerful than the one dropped on Hiroshima has sent shockwaves around the globe, stirring a pot of controversial debate and critical reflection. This move marks a significant escalation in the country’s military capabilities, but it also raises important questions about the world’s future in terms of nuclear armament and security. In a press release issued earlier this week, the Department of Defense outlined their plans for the B61-13, a modern iteration of the B61 nuclear gravity bomb. John Plumb, Assistant Secretary of Defense for Space Policy, emphasized that this development is a direct response to a changing security environment and the emerging threats posed by potential adversaries. He underscored the United States’ obligation to continually assess and adapt its capabilities to ensure a credible deterrence strategy, as well as to uphold its commitments to allied nations. The B61-13 is projected to have a similar yield to the B61-7, boasting a maximum yield of 360 kilotons. To put this in perspective, the bomb dropped on Hiroshima during World War II had a yield of approximately 15 kilotons, making the B61-13 about 24 times more powerful. Furthermore, it would be approximately 14 times larger than the bomb dropped on Nagasaki. Despite its formidable power, the Pentagon assures that the B61-13 will incorporate the latest safety, security, and accuracy features, akin to those found in the B61-12. This news comes amid escalating global tensions and following a high-explosive experiment conducted by the U.S. at a nuclear test site in Nevada. Officials state that these tests are integral to advancing nuclear nonproliferation goals and enhancing the country’s ability to detect underground nuclear explosive tests. However, the timing of this announcement, coupled with Russia’s anticipated withdrawal from the 1966 Comprehensive Nuclear Test Ban Treaty, has reignited fears of a potential nuclear arms race. The Pentagon is clear in its statement that, if approved, the B61-13 would not result in an increase in the overall number of nuclear weapons in the U.S. stockpile; instead, it would serve to replace some of the existing B61-7s. Plumb reiterated that this development represents a measured and necessary step in addressing the challenges of an increasingly unpredictable and dynamic security environment, providing the U.S. with greater flexibility while maintaining a responsible approach to nuclear armament. As the world grapples with the implications of this development, the debate continues over the necessity, ethics, and potential risks associated with possessing such an unparalleled level of destructive power. The path forward remains uncertain, and the discourse on global security and the future of nuclear weaponry is more crucial than ever.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Kim Kardashian’s Latest Stunt: A Step Too Far?</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/30/Kardashian-Faux-Nipple-Controversy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Kim Kardashian’s Latest Stunt: A Step Too Far?" /><published>2023-10-30T12:41:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-30T12:41:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/30/Kardashian-Faux-Nipple-Controversy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/30/Kardashian-Faux-Nipple-Controversy/">&lt;p&gt;Kim Kardashian, a name synonymous with controversy and boundary-pushing, is once again at the center of public discourse. This time, it’s due to her clothing brand SKIMS’ latest product – a faux-nipple bra. While Kardashian is no stranger to making bold statements through fashion, many are questioning whether this latest stunt has taken things a step too far.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a promotional video laden with cheeky commentary and a nod to global warming, Kardashian introduces “The SKIMS Ultimate Nipple Bra,” a bra designed to make women appear as though they are perpetually cold. The bra features built-in faux nipples, ensuring visibility regardless of the weather. “Some days are hard. But these nipples are harder. And unlike the icebergs, these aren’t going anywhere,” Kardashian quips in the video.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Kardashian may view this as a bold and innovative fashion statement, it’s hard to ignore the potential negative implications. The product has been criticized for objectifying women, reducing them to body parts for shock value and attention. Additionally, the tasteless humor surrounding a global crisis like climate change has left many shaking their heads, wondering if there are no longer any boundaries left to cross.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The decision to launch the product on Halloween also adds a layer of skepticism. Is this just a seasonal stunt, aimed at capturing attention during a time known for costumes and risqué attire? Or is it a genuine attempt at innovation in the fashion industry?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, Kardashian’s decision to tie the product to global warming seems misplaced and opportunistic. In the video, she states, “I’m not a scientist, but I do believe everyone can use their skill set to do their part.” However, many are questioning how selling a faux-nipple bra contributes to the fight against climate change, or if it’s simply a ploy to draw attention and controversy – something Kardashian is all too familiar with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Critics argue that this latest move by Kardashian and SKIMS is indicative of a larger issue within celebrity culture, where shock value and controversy often trump taste and social responsibility. The faux-nipple bra, while certainly attention-grabbing, raises questions about the lengths to which celebrities will go to stay relevant, and the impact of such stunts on societal standards and expectations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the product prepares to hit the shelves, the court of public opinion is in session. Whether the SKIMS Ultimate Nipple Bra will be seen as a bold fashion statement or a tasteless stunt remains to be seen. However, one thing is clear – Kardashian has once again ignited a conversation, though perhaps not for the reasons she intended.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Kim Kardashian, a name synonymous with controversy and boundary-pushing, is once again at the center of public discourse. This time, it’s due to her clothing brand SKIMS’ latest product – a faux-nipple bra. While Kardashian is no stranger to making bold statements through fashion, many are questioning whether this latest stunt has taken things a step too far. In a promotional video laden with cheeky commentary and a nod to global warming, Kardashian introduces “The SKIMS Ultimate Nipple Bra,” a bra designed to make women appear as though they are perpetually cold. The bra features built-in faux nipples, ensuring visibility regardless of the weather. “Some days are hard. But these nipples are harder. And unlike the icebergs, these aren’t going anywhere,” Kardashian quips in the video. While Kardashian may view this as a bold and innovative fashion statement, it’s hard to ignore the potential negative implications. The product has been criticized for objectifying women, reducing them to body parts for shock value and attention. Additionally, the tasteless humor surrounding a global crisis like climate change has left many shaking their heads, wondering if there are no longer any boundaries left to cross. The decision to launch the product on Halloween also adds a layer of skepticism. Is this just a seasonal stunt, aimed at capturing attention during a time known for costumes and risqué attire? Or is it a genuine attempt at innovation in the fashion industry? Furthermore, Kardashian’s decision to tie the product to global warming seems misplaced and opportunistic. In the video, she states, “I’m not a scientist, but I do believe everyone can use their skill set to do their part.” However, many are questioning how selling a faux-nipple bra contributes to the fight against climate change, or if it’s simply a ploy to draw attention and controversy – something Kardashian is all too familiar with. Critics argue that this latest move by Kardashian and SKIMS is indicative of a larger issue within celebrity culture, where shock value and controversy often trump taste and social responsibility. The faux-nipple bra, while certainly attention-grabbing, raises questions about the lengths to which celebrities will go to stay relevant, and the impact of such stunts on societal standards and expectations. As the product prepares to hit the shelves, the court of public opinion is in session. Whether the SKIMS Ultimate Nipple Bra will be seen as a bold fashion statement or a tasteless stunt remains to be seen. However, one thing is clear – Kardashian has once again ignited a conversation, though perhaps not for the reasons she intended.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Biden’s Blunders: A Tale of Weakness on the World Stage</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/30/Biden-Failure-International/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Biden’s Blunders: A Tale of Weakness on the World Stage" /><published>2023-10-30T07:08:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-30T07:08:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/30/Biden-Failure-International</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/30/Biden-Failure-International/">&lt;p&gt;In a no-holds-barred critique, Rep. Rob Estes, a Kansas Republican, took President Joe Biden to task for what he views as a series of critical failures in international relations, tying them directly to a trifecta of global crises. Estes, in his candid conversation on Newsmax’s “Saturday Agenda,” did not mince words, painting a picture of an administration fraught with weakness and a lack of strategic foresight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Afghanistan debacle stands as a glaring testament to Biden’s incapacity to lead, according to Estes. The chaotic withdrawal, he argues, broadcasted a message of vulnerability that reverberated across the globe, emboldening the likes of Russia and Iran, and resulting in devastating humanitarian crises.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Biden’s mismanagement in Afghanistan was a clear signal to world leaders like Putin that the U.S. was retreating from its position of strength,” Estes declared, connecting the dots between the administration’s blunders and the emboldened stance of adversarial nations. He underscored the severity of these blunders, pointing out the direct line between Biden’s failures and the atrocities unfolding before the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Estes’ criticism extended beyond the international arena, as he also tackled the dysfunction evident in domestic politics. He described the election of Speaker Mike Johnson as a “messy process,” a symptom of the broader disarray within the government. Despite acknowledging Johnson’s commitment to doing the right thing, Estes could not help but highlight the ways in which the administration’s failures have permeated every level of governance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In his call to action, Estes underscored the dire need for strong, decisive leadership, the kind that seems to be sorely lacking in the current administration. He pinpointed inflation, government overspending, border insecurity, and the need to stand with Israel as pressing issues that require immediate and unwavering attention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For conservative readers and those frustrated with the direction in which the country is headed, Estes’ words resonate deeply. His critique of Biden is not just a denunciation of past actions; it is a rallying cry for a return to strength, accountability, and principled leadership. The Biden administration’s failures on the world stage are not just abstract policies gone awry; they are, as Estes highlights, a direct threat to American security and global stability.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a no-holds-barred critique, Rep. Rob Estes, a Kansas Republican, took President Joe Biden to task for what he views as a series of critical failures in international relations, tying them directly to a trifecta of global crises. Estes, in his candid conversation on Newsmax’s “Saturday Agenda,” did not mince words, painting a picture of an administration fraught with weakness and a lack of strategic foresight. The Afghanistan debacle stands as a glaring testament to Biden’s incapacity to lead, according to Estes. The chaotic withdrawal, he argues, broadcasted a message of vulnerability that reverberated across the globe, emboldening the likes of Russia and Iran, and resulting in devastating humanitarian crises. “Biden’s mismanagement in Afghanistan was a clear signal to world leaders like Putin that the U.S. was retreating from its position of strength,” Estes declared, connecting the dots between the administration’s blunders and the emboldened stance of adversarial nations. He underscored the severity of these blunders, pointing out the direct line between Biden’s failures and the atrocities unfolding before the world. Estes’ criticism extended beyond the international arena, as he also tackled the dysfunction evident in domestic politics. He described the election of Speaker Mike Johnson as a “messy process,” a symptom of the broader disarray within the government. Despite acknowledging Johnson’s commitment to doing the right thing, Estes could not help but highlight the ways in which the administration’s failures have permeated every level of governance. In his call to action, Estes underscored the dire need for strong, decisive leadership, the kind that seems to be sorely lacking in the current administration. He pinpointed inflation, government overspending, border insecurity, and the need to stand with Israel as pressing issues that require immediate and unwavering attention. For conservative readers and those frustrated with the direction in which the country is headed, Estes’ words resonate deeply. His critique of Biden is not just a denunciation of past actions; it is a rallying cry for a return to strength, accountability, and principled leadership. The Biden administration’s failures on the world stage are not just abstract policies gone awry; they are, as Estes highlights, a direct threat to American security and global stability.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A Major Shift in the GOP Race: Predicting the Next Candidate to Exit</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/30/Shake-Up-GOP-Race/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Major Shift in the GOP Race: Predicting the Next Candidate to Exit" /><published>2023-10-30T06:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-30T06:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/30/Shake-Up-GOP-Race</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/30/Shake-Up-GOP-Race/">&lt;p&gt;The 2024 GOP presidential race has entered a new phase of intensity following former Vice President Mike Pence’s unexpected departure, leaving political enthusiasts and insiders speculating about the next big shake-up in the Republican field. The withdrawal of such a major player has undoubtedly sent ripples across the political landscape, leading many to wonder: who will be the next to exit the stage?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pence’s decision to suspend his campaign came as a shock to many, leaving a void in the race and prompting immediate speculation on the future of other contenders. “This field will shrink,” predicts Ari Fleischer, a veteran Republican consultant, pointing to the inevitable consolidation in the coming months.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The battle for the GOP nomination has been fierce, with candidates navigating through a crowded field and stiff competition. With the exit of Pence, who has long held sway among social conservatives, the dynamics of the race are poised for a significant shift. The remaining candidates are now scrambling to court Pence’s base, particularly in influential early voting states like Iowa and New Hampshire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Iowa, with its outsized influence in the nominating process, has been a key battleground for candidates looking to gain momentum. Evangelicals play a critical role in the state’s politics, and Pence had been making concerted efforts to connect with this crucial voting bloc. With his exit, candidates like Tim Scott, with his strong appeal to social conservatives, and Ron DeSantis, known for his solid pro-life record, are well-positioned to make gains among former Pence supporters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the race is far from decided. The next few months will be crucial as candidates seek to differentiate themselves and gain traction among Republican voters. The upcoming GOP debates will serve as a critical platform for candidates to showcase their policies, connect with voters, and prove their mettle in a crowded field.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet, not all candidates are guaranteed a spot on the debate stage. The Republican National Committee’s polling and donor thresholds have proven to be a significant hurdle, with several candidates struggling to qualify. The failure to make the debate stage could spell the end of the road for some campaigns, further consolidating the field.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Florida Governor Ron DeSantis, former South Carolina Governor Nikki Haley, biotech entrepreneur Vivek Ramaswamy, and former New Jersey Governor Chris Christie have all announced that they have met the necessary criteria for the upcoming debate. However, North Dakota Governor Doug Burgum and former Arkansas Governor Asa Hutchinson have yet to qualify, placing their campaigns on precarious ground.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the race heats up, the pressure is on for candidates to deliver strong performances, secure funding, and connect with key voting blocs. The 2024 GOP presidential race is proving to be one of the most competitive and unpredictable in recent memory, with plenty of twists and turns still to come.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the stage set for a fierce battle, all eyes are on the GOP field as it navigates through this period of transition and uncertainty. The next few weeks and months will be critical in shaping the trajectory of the race, determining who will stay, who will go, and who will ultimately secure the Republican nomination.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">The 2024 GOP presidential race has entered a new phase of intensity following former Vice President Mike Pence’s unexpected departure, leaving political enthusiasts and insiders speculating about the next big shake-up in the Republican field. The withdrawal of such a major player has undoubtedly sent ripples across the political landscape, leading many to wonder: who will be the next to exit the stage? Pence’s decision to suspend his campaign came as a shock to many, leaving a void in the race and prompting immediate speculation on the future of other contenders. “This field will shrink,” predicts Ari Fleischer, a veteran Republican consultant, pointing to the inevitable consolidation in the coming months. The battle for the GOP nomination has been fierce, with candidates navigating through a crowded field and stiff competition. With the exit of Pence, who has long held sway among social conservatives, the dynamics of the race are poised for a significant shift. The remaining candidates are now scrambling to court Pence’s base, particularly in influential early voting states like Iowa and New Hampshire. Iowa, with its outsized influence in the nominating process, has been a key battleground for candidates looking to gain momentum. Evangelicals play a critical role in the state’s politics, and Pence had been making concerted efforts to connect with this crucial voting bloc. With his exit, candidates like Tim Scott, with his strong appeal to social conservatives, and Ron DeSantis, known for his solid pro-life record, are well-positioned to make gains among former Pence supporters. However, the race is far from decided. The next few months will be crucial as candidates seek to differentiate themselves and gain traction among Republican voters. The upcoming GOP debates will serve as a critical platform for candidates to showcase their policies, connect with voters, and prove their mettle in a crowded field. Yet, not all candidates are guaranteed a spot on the debate stage. The Republican National Committee’s polling and donor thresholds have proven to be a significant hurdle, with several candidates struggling to qualify. The failure to make the debate stage could spell the end of the road for some campaigns, further consolidating the field. Florida Governor Ron DeSantis, former South Carolina Governor Nikki Haley, biotech entrepreneur Vivek Ramaswamy, and former New Jersey Governor Chris Christie have all announced that they have met the necessary criteria for the upcoming debate. However, North Dakota Governor Doug Burgum and former Arkansas Governor Asa Hutchinson have yet to qualify, placing their campaigns on precarious ground. As the race heats up, the pressure is on for candidates to deliver strong performances, secure funding, and connect with key voting blocs. The 2024 GOP presidential race is proving to be one of the most competitive and unpredictable in recent memory, with plenty of twists and turns still to come. With the stage set for a fierce battle, all eyes are on the GOP field as it navigates through this period of transition and uncertainty. The next few weeks and months will be critical in shaping the trajectory of the race, determining who will stay, who will go, and who will ultimately secure the Republican nomination.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Democratic Heavyweights Concerned Over Biden’s 2024 Prospects</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/29/Bidens-2024-Weaknesses/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Democratic Heavyweights Concerned Over Biden’s 2024 Prospects" /><published>2023-10-29T18:12:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-29T18:12:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/29/Bidens-2024-Weaknesses</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/29/Bidens-2024-Weaknesses/">&lt;p&gt;Prominent Democratic strategist James Carville is breaking the silence on what many in the party are thinking but are too afraid to say: President Joe Biden’s chances of re-election in 2024 are looking bleak. Carville, known for his straight-shooting and often controversial commentary, has revealed that top Democrats are urging him to keep quiet about the President’s potential weaknesses heading into the next election cycle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This revelation comes amid a storm of concerns regarding Biden’s poll numbers and his age, which some believe could hinder his ability to lead the nation effectively for another term. In a candid interview with The Atlantic, Carville expressed his concerns, highlighting that the president’s numbers “are not good” and showing no signs of improvement. His commentary echoes the sentiment of a growing number of Democrats who are becoming increasingly vocal about their apprehensions for the 2024 election.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite his stark warning, Carville notes that when he brings up these issues with Democratic leaders, they do not disagree with his assessment. Instead, they request him to remain silent. “Nobody is saying, ‘James, you’re wrong,’” he pointed out. “They’re saying, ‘James, you can’t say that.’”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The recent announcement of Rep. Dean Phillips’, D-Minn., primary campaign against Biden adds another layer of complexity to the situation. Phillips echoes Carville’s concerns, openly questioning Biden’s ability to defeat Donald Trump if he decides to run again. He criticized the silence within the Democratic party, expressing his frustration and alarm at the lack of open dialogue regarding Biden’s chances.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This growing dissent within the Democratic ranks raises questions about the party’s unity and readiness for the 2024 election. While some, like former Obama 2012 campaign manager Jim Messina, are attempting to quell these concerns by reminding the party of Biden’s previous victory over Trump, others like Carville remain unconvinced.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The strategist pointed out the under-reported issue of declining Black voter turnout since 2020, a critical demographic for Democratic success. He emphasized the need for the party to acknowledge and address these challenges openly rather than sweeping them under the rug.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the 2024 election looms closer, the Democratic party finds itself at a crossroads. Will they continue to maintain a united front, ignoring the warning signs, or will they engage in an open and honest dialogue about their potential weaknesses? Only time will tell, but one thing is for certain: voices like Carville’s will not be easily silenced, and the pressure on Biden to prove his viability as a candidate will only intensify.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Prominent Democratic strategist James Carville is breaking the silence on what many in the party are thinking but are too afraid to say: President Joe Biden’s chances of re-election in 2024 are looking bleak. Carville, known for his straight-shooting and often controversial commentary, has revealed that top Democrats are urging him to keep quiet about the President’s potential weaknesses heading into the next election cycle. This revelation comes amid a storm of concerns regarding Biden’s poll numbers and his age, which some believe could hinder his ability to lead the nation effectively for another term. In a candid interview with The Atlantic, Carville expressed his concerns, highlighting that the president’s numbers “are not good” and showing no signs of improvement. His commentary echoes the sentiment of a growing number of Democrats who are becoming increasingly vocal about their apprehensions for the 2024 election. Despite his stark warning, Carville notes that when he brings up these issues with Democratic leaders, they do not disagree with his assessment. Instead, they request him to remain silent. “Nobody is saying, ‘James, you’re wrong,’” he pointed out. “They’re saying, ‘James, you can’t say that.’” The recent announcement of Rep. Dean Phillips’, D-Minn., primary campaign against Biden adds another layer of complexity to the situation. Phillips echoes Carville’s concerns, openly questioning Biden’s ability to defeat Donald Trump if he decides to run again. He criticized the silence within the Democratic party, expressing his frustration and alarm at the lack of open dialogue regarding Biden’s chances. This growing dissent within the Democratic ranks raises questions about the party’s unity and readiness for the 2024 election. While some, like former Obama 2012 campaign manager Jim Messina, are attempting to quell these concerns by reminding the party of Biden’s previous victory over Trump, others like Carville remain unconvinced. The strategist pointed out the under-reported issue of declining Black voter turnout since 2020, a critical demographic for Democratic success. He emphasized the need for the party to acknowledge and address these challenges openly rather than sweeping them under the rug. As the 2024 election looms closer, the Democratic party finds itself at a crossroads. Will they continue to maintain a united front, ignoring the warning signs, or will they engage in an open and honest dialogue about their potential weaknesses? Only time will tell, but one thing is for certain: voices like Carville’s will not be easily silenced, and the pressure on Biden to prove his viability as a candidate will only intensify.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Pumpkin Farmers Under Pressure: Water Scarcity, Soaring Heat, and Rising Labor Costs</title><link href="/news/2023/10/29/Pumpkin-Farming-Woes/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Pumpkin Farmers Under Pressure: Water Scarcity, Soaring Heat, and Rising Labor Costs" /><published>2023-10-29T16:57:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-29T16:57:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/29/Pumpkin-Farming-Woes</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/29/Pumpkin-Farming-Woes/">&lt;p&gt;Pumpkin farmers in the Western regions of the United States are navigating through a storm of challenges, including unrelenting heat, scarce water supplies, and escalating labor costs. Alan Mazzotti, a farmer in northeast Colorado, has firsthand experience with these issues, witnessing the snow-capped Rocky Mountains on clear days, yet struggling with insufficient water supplies for his pumpkin crops.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The environmental challenges are compounded by financial strains. Rising labor costs and inflation are cutting into profits, squeezing the viability of pumpkin farming. Mazzotti had to make the tough decision to plant only half of his usual pumpkin crop due to water delivery being cut by half. The unexpected heavy rains that followed were too late to save the season, illustrating the unpredictable nature of farming in today’s climate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Farmers across Texas, New Mexico, and Colorado are experiencing similar predicaments. Climate change is intensifying drought conditions and heat extremes, resulting in reduced yields and barren lands. Some farmers have reported losses of 20% or more in predicted yields, showcasing the severe impact of these environmental challenges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The financial aspect of pumpkin farming is becoming increasingly precarious. Soaring labor costs, propelled by new laws ensuring overtime pay for farmworkers, are narrowing profit margins. Lindsey Pyle, a North Texas farmer, highlights the surge in expenses, from seeds and fuel to supplies and chemicals, resulting in a 20% yield loss. The cost of irrigation is skyrocketing as groundwater levels drop, driving energy bills into the thousands of dollars each month for some farmers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The uncertain future of pumpkin farming is a growing concern. Groundwater scarcity is a critical issue, with aquifers being depleted at an alarming rate. Climate change is reducing the precipitation needed to recharge these water sources, threatening the long-term sustainability of pumpkin farming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Farmers are forced to make tough choices about which crops to plant and how to allocate their dwindling water resources. The rising cost and availability of labor are additional challenges, creating a financial burden that may be unsustainable in the long run.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, the myriad of challenges faced by pumpkin farmers in the Western US paints a stark picture of the agricultural industry’s future. The intersection of environmental, financial, and labor-related issues requires urgent attention and innovative solutions to ensure the sustainability of pumpkin farming and the broader agricultural sector.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Pumpkin farmers in the Western regions of the United States are navigating through a storm of challenges, including unrelenting heat, scarce water supplies, and escalating labor costs. Alan Mazzotti, a farmer in northeast Colorado, has firsthand experience with these issues, witnessing the snow-capped Rocky Mountains on clear days, yet struggling with insufficient water supplies for his pumpkin crops. The environmental challenges are compounded by financial strains. Rising labor costs and inflation are cutting into profits, squeezing the viability of pumpkin farming. Mazzotti had to make the tough decision to plant only half of his usual pumpkin crop due to water delivery being cut by half. The unexpected heavy rains that followed were too late to save the season, illustrating the unpredictable nature of farming in today’s climate. Farmers across Texas, New Mexico, and Colorado are experiencing similar predicaments. Climate change is intensifying drought conditions and heat extremes, resulting in reduced yields and barren lands. Some farmers have reported losses of 20% or more in predicted yields, showcasing the severe impact of these environmental challenges. The financial aspect of pumpkin farming is becoming increasingly precarious. Soaring labor costs, propelled by new laws ensuring overtime pay for farmworkers, are narrowing profit margins. Lindsey Pyle, a North Texas farmer, highlights the surge in expenses, from seeds and fuel to supplies and chemicals, resulting in a 20% yield loss. The cost of irrigation is skyrocketing as groundwater levels drop, driving energy bills into the thousands of dollars each month for some farmers. The uncertain future of pumpkin farming is a growing concern. Groundwater scarcity is a critical issue, with aquifers being depleted at an alarming rate. Climate change is reducing the precipitation needed to recharge these water sources, threatening the long-term sustainability of pumpkin farming. Farmers are forced to make tough choices about which crops to plant and how to allocate their dwindling water resources. The rising cost and availability of labor are additional challenges, creating a financial burden that may be unsustainable in the long run. In conclusion, the myriad of challenges faced by pumpkin farmers in the Western US paints a stark picture of the agricultural industry’s future. The intersection of environmental, financial, and labor-related issues requires urgent attention and innovative solutions to ensure the sustainability of pumpkin farming and the broader agricultural sector.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Unity in the Ranks: GOP Leaders Call for Consolidation Behind Trump</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/29/GOP-Unification-Behind-Trump/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Unity in the Ranks: GOP Leaders Call for Consolidation Behind Trump" /><published>2023-10-29T15:41:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-29T15:41:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/29/GOP-Unification-Behind-Trump</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/29/GOP-Unification-Behind-Trump/">&lt;p&gt;National Republican Senatorial Committee (NRSC) Chairman Sen. Steve Daines (R-MT) has made a powerful call for unity within the Republican party, urging his fellow GOP members to rally behind former President Donald Trump for the 2024 Presidential election.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This move, seen by many as a decisive attempt to consolidate the party’s power, comes at a crucial time when the political landscape is fraught with division and uncertainty. Sen. Daines, a significant figure in the Republican party and a fervent supporter of Trump, believes that this is the strategic move that the GOP needs to ensure victory in the upcoming election.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His call for unity follows the recent withdrawal of former Vice President Mike Pence from the presidential race, a move that Daines praised and saw as a step in the right direction. “I was surprised, but I think that’s the right move,” Daines commented, emphasizing the need for the party to coalesce around Trump as the clear front-runner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This plea for consolidation is not just a simple endorsement of Trump; it represents a major push by a top-tier GOP leader to shape the direction of the party’s future. As NRSC chairman, Daines plays a pivotal role in determining party spending and resource allocation for U.S. Senate races, and his influence is crucial in rallying support for key Senate candidates across the nation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The call for unity goes beyond mere political posturing; it is a calculated effort to streamline the party’s resources and focus, aiming to solidify support behind Trump and avoid a prolonged and potentially divisive primary battle. Daines’s statement reflects a growing sentiment within the party that Trump’s nomination is inevitable, and that the sooner the party unites behind him, the stronger their position will be in the general election.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Polls have consistently shown Trump as the clear favorite among Republican voters, with a commanding lead over other potential GOP candidates. His popularity and influence within the party remain strong, and his ability to mobilize the Republican base is unparalleled. This makes him a formidable opponent for any Democratic candidate, including incumbent President Joe Biden.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By urging his fellow Republicans to unite behind Trump, Sen. Daines is sending a clear message that the time for internal party squabbles is over. The GOP needs to focus on the bigger picture, and that means consolidating their support behind the candidate who has the best chance of leading them to victory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the 2024 Presidential election draws nearer, the Republican party finds itself at a crossroads. Sen. Daines’s call for unity is a bold move that has the potential to shape the future of the GOP and solidify their position as a united front ready to take on the challenges of the election season. Only time will tell if his fellow Republicans will heed his call and rally behind Trump, but one thing is certain: the stakes have never been higher, and the need for unity has never been more urgent.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">National Republican Senatorial Committee (NRSC) Chairman Sen. Steve Daines (R-MT) has made a powerful call for unity within the Republican party, urging his fellow GOP members to rally behind former President Donald Trump for the 2024 Presidential election. This move, seen by many as a decisive attempt to consolidate the party’s power, comes at a crucial time when the political landscape is fraught with division and uncertainty. Sen. Daines, a significant figure in the Republican party and a fervent supporter of Trump, believes that this is the strategic move that the GOP needs to ensure victory in the upcoming election. His call for unity follows the recent withdrawal of former Vice President Mike Pence from the presidential race, a move that Daines praised and saw as a step in the right direction. “I was surprised, but I think that’s the right move,” Daines commented, emphasizing the need for the party to coalesce around Trump as the clear front-runner. This plea for consolidation is not just a simple endorsement of Trump; it represents a major push by a top-tier GOP leader to shape the direction of the party’s future. As NRSC chairman, Daines plays a pivotal role in determining party spending and resource allocation for U.S. Senate races, and his influence is crucial in rallying support for key Senate candidates across the nation. The call for unity goes beyond mere political posturing; it is a calculated effort to streamline the party’s resources and focus, aiming to solidify support behind Trump and avoid a prolonged and potentially divisive primary battle. Daines’s statement reflects a growing sentiment within the party that Trump’s nomination is inevitable, and that the sooner the party unites behind him, the stronger their position will be in the general election. Polls have consistently shown Trump as the clear favorite among Republican voters, with a commanding lead over other potential GOP candidates. His popularity and influence within the party remain strong, and his ability to mobilize the Republican base is unparalleled. This makes him a formidable opponent for any Democratic candidate, including incumbent President Joe Biden. By urging his fellow Republicans to unite behind Trump, Sen. Daines is sending a clear message that the time for internal party squabbles is over. The GOP needs to focus on the bigger picture, and that means consolidating their support behind the candidate who has the best chance of leading them to victory. As the 2024 Presidential election draws nearer, the Republican party finds itself at a crossroads. Sen. Daines’s call for unity is a bold move that has the potential to shape the future of the GOP and solidify their position as a united front ready to take on the challenges of the election season. Only time will tell if his fellow Republicans will heed his call and rally behind Trump, but one thing is certain: the stakes have never been higher, and the need for unity has never been more urgent.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Halloween Horror: Tragic Shooting Unfolds in Florida</title><link href="/news/2023/10/29/Florida-Shooting-Halloween/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Halloween Horror: Tragic Shooting Unfolds in Florida" /><published>2023-10-29T14:32:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-29T14:32:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/29/Florida-Shooting-Halloween</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/29/Florida-Shooting-Halloween/">&lt;p&gt;In the early hours of Sunday morning, what should have been a festive Halloween celebration turned tragic as gunfire erupted on the streets of Tampa’s Ybor City neighborhood. At least two people were killed, and 18 others were left injured in a chaotic scene filled with revelers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The incident occurred just before 3 a.m. near a popular strip of bars and clubs located on the 1600 block of East 7th Avenue. According to Tampa Police Chief Lee Bercaw, a fight broke out between two groups amidst hundreds of innocent bystanders who were caught in the crossfire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The violence quickly escalated, leading to an exchange of gunfire that left the crowded street in disarray. Video footage captured at the scene reveals the moment of panic as shots rang out, causing partygoers in elaborate Halloween costumes to flee for safety.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The aftermath showed a scene of devastation, with injured victims on the ground receiving urgent medical attention from police officers. In the wake of the tragedy, the police taped off an extensive area spanning four to five blocks in downtown Ybor, conducting a thorough investigation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Emmitt Wilson, a devastated parent who lost his 14-year-old son Elijah in the shooting, described the young victim as a “good child” who was simply “at the wrong place at the wrong time.” The sorrowful father also mentioned his efforts in advising his son to avoid certain company, a plea that tragically went unheeded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Tampa Police Department reported that one male suspect had turned himself in, and investigations are underway to identify and locate a second shooter believed to be involved in the incident. The health conditions of the 18 hospitalized victims remain undisclosed at this time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The police are actively seeking information and video footage from the public to aid in their ongoing investigation. Authorities encourage anyone with relevant information to come forward and contact the Tampa Police Department at 813-231-6130.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In these difficult times, the city of Tampa is grappling with the aftermath of this horrifying incident, reminding us all of the need for vigilance, community solidarity, and a collective effort to prevent such tragedies in the future. As the investigation continues, our thoughts are with the victims and their families, hoping for swift justice and healing.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In the early hours of Sunday morning, what should have been a festive Halloween celebration turned tragic as gunfire erupted on the streets of Tampa’s Ybor City neighborhood. At least two people were killed, and 18 others were left injured in a chaotic scene filled with revelers. The incident occurred just before 3 a.m. near a popular strip of bars and clubs located on the 1600 block of East 7th Avenue. According to Tampa Police Chief Lee Bercaw, a fight broke out between two groups amidst hundreds of innocent bystanders who were caught in the crossfire. The violence quickly escalated, leading to an exchange of gunfire that left the crowded street in disarray. Video footage captured at the scene reveals the moment of panic as shots rang out, causing partygoers in elaborate Halloween costumes to flee for safety. The aftermath showed a scene of devastation, with injured victims on the ground receiving urgent medical attention from police officers. In the wake of the tragedy, the police taped off an extensive area spanning four to five blocks in downtown Ybor, conducting a thorough investigation. Emmitt Wilson, a devastated parent who lost his 14-year-old son Elijah in the shooting, described the young victim as a “good child” who was simply “at the wrong place at the wrong time.” The sorrowful father also mentioned his efforts in advising his son to avoid certain company, a plea that tragically went unheeded. The Tampa Police Department reported that one male suspect had turned himself in, and investigations are underway to identify and locate a second shooter believed to be involved in the incident. The health conditions of the 18 hospitalized victims remain undisclosed at this time. The police are actively seeking information and video footage from the public to aid in their ongoing investigation. Authorities encourage anyone with relevant information to come forward and contact the Tampa Police Department at 813-231-6130. In these difficult times, the city of Tampa is grappling with the aftermath of this horrifying incident, reminding us all of the need for vigilance, community solidarity, and a collective effort to prevent such tragedies in the future. As the investigation continues, our thoughts are with the victims and their families, hoping for swift justice and healing.</summary></entry></feed>