<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-09-11T02:20:29-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/09/11/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-09-11T02:20:29-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-11T02:20:29-04:00</updated><id>/2023/09/11/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/11/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Holding the Line in Texas - Cruz’s Fiery Re-election Bid Amidst Blue Ambitions</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/10/Texas-Red-Fortress/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Holding the Line in Texas - Cruz’s Fiery Re-election Bid Amidst Blue Ambitions" /><published>2023-09-10T17:04:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-10T17:04:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/10/Texas-Red-Fortress</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/10/Texas-Red-Fortress/">&lt;p&gt;Sen. Ted Cruz, an unwavering voice for conservative values, faces his 2024 re-election bid with fierce determination. Recognizing the sizeable group of Democrats eager to challenge his seat, Cruz prepares to defend the GOP’s long-held stronghold in Texas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With his victory over then-Rep. Beto O’Rourke in 2018, Cruz showed that Texans remain committed to their Republican roots, even in the face of immense Democratic funding and campaign efforts. As Cruz aptly noted, following former President Donald Trump, “there is no Republican in the country that Democrats would more ardently like to unseat.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, Democrats are coming in with all guns blazing, with Rep. Colin Allred leading the charge. Allred’s fundraising efforts managed to exceed Cruz’s by almost $2 million in Q2 2023, showing the extent of the Democrats’ fervor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet, history remains on the GOP’s side. Texas, a beacon of conservative governance, continues to resist turning blue, regardless of Democrats’ efforts. Cal Jillson, a renowned political science professor at Southern Methodist University, reinforced this sentiment, noting, “It’s probably not ruby red, but it’s still a red state.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Democrats, once dominant in Texas from the post-Civil War era through the 1970s, have been repeatedly challenged since the 1980s. With stalwarts like the Bush family frequently representing the state, Texas has stayed red in presidential, senate, and gubernatorial elections for decades.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recent election results further underscore Texas’ conservative leanings. Although Cruz’s 2018 race and Trump’s 2020 results hinted at closer margins, the GOP has continued to triumph. For instance, in 2022, Gov. Greg Abbott asserted GOP dominance, defeating O’Rourke with a decisive near-11 point lead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jillson points to the evolving nature of the GOP electorate in Texas. While the party once leaned heavily toward business-friendly conservatism, today’s GOP in Texas boasts a robust mix of social conservatives and populists, advocating more vehemently for conservative principles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In an ever-changing political landscape, the GOP remains focused on rallying Hispanic voters, a demographic pivotal to future elections. While Democrats may tout their hold on two out of three heavily Latino districts, Republicans have begun making strides with male Hispanic voters in the Rio Grande Valley. This trend could shape future GOP campaigns in the state.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With Cruz leading the charge and the unwavering spirit of Texas conservatives, the state remains a resilient red fortress, even amidst Democrats’ fervent dreams of turning it blue.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Sen. Ted Cruz, an unwavering voice for conservative values, faces his 2024 re-election bid with fierce determination. Recognizing the sizeable group of Democrats eager to challenge his seat, Cruz prepares to defend the GOP’s long-held stronghold in Texas. With his victory over then-Rep. Beto O’Rourke in 2018, Cruz showed that Texans remain committed to their Republican roots, even in the face of immense Democratic funding and campaign efforts. As Cruz aptly noted, following former President Donald Trump, “there is no Republican in the country that Democrats would more ardently like to unseat.” However, Democrats are coming in with all guns blazing, with Rep. Colin Allred leading the charge. Allred’s fundraising efforts managed to exceed Cruz’s by almost $2 million in Q2 2023, showing the extent of the Democrats’ fervor. Yet, history remains on the GOP’s side. Texas, a beacon of conservative governance, continues to resist turning blue, regardless of Democrats’ efforts. Cal Jillson, a renowned political science professor at Southern Methodist University, reinforced this sentiment, noting, “It’s probably not ruby red, but it’s still a red state.” The Democrats, once dominant in Texas from the post-Civil War era through the 1970s, have been repeatedly challenged since the 1980s. With stalwarts like the Bush family frequently representing the state, Texas has stayed red in presidential, senate, and gubernatorial elections for decades. Recent election results further underscore Texas’ conservative leanings. Although Cruz’s 2018 race and Trump’s 2020 results hinted at closer margins, the GOP has continued to triumph. For instance, in 2022, Gov. Greg Abbott asserted GOP dominance, defeating O’Rourke with a decisive near-11 point lead. Jillson points to the evolving nature of the GOP electorate in Texas. While the party once leaned heavily toward business-friendly conservatism, today’s GOP in Texas boasts a robust mix of social conservatives and populists, advocating more vehemently for conservative principles. In an ever-changing political landscape, the GOP remains focused on rallying Hispanic voters, a demographic pivotal to future elections. While Democrats may tout their hold on two out of three heavily Latino districts, Republicans have begun making strides with male Hispanic voters in the Rio Grande Valley. This trend could shape future GOP campaigns in the state. With Cruz leading the charge and the unwavering spirit of Texas conservatives, the state remains a resilient red fortress, even amidst Democrats’ fervent dreams of turning it blue.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump Tackles Iowa - From Frat Parties to Football Throws</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/10/Trump-Iowa-Game/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump Tackles Iowa - From Frat Parties to Football Throws" /><published>2023-09-10T16:02:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-10T16:02:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/10/Trump-Iowa-Game</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/10/Trump-Iowa-Game/">&lt;p&gt;Iowa witnessed an exuberant political spectacle on Saturday as former President Donald Trump turned a college football game into an informal campaign rally. Demonstrating his trademark charisma, Trump partied with an Iowa State fraternity, showcased his grill skills, and engaged with the crowd by throwing footballs, further underlining his dominant position in the 2024 GOP nomination race.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a spirited pre-game event, Trump visited the Alpha Gamma Rho (AGR) agriculture fraternity house at Iowa State University in Ames. Not one to stick to convention, the former president threw footballs from a beer pong table into the waiting crowd. These candid moments were interspersed with Trump flipping burgers and posing for photographs with fraternity members, all of which undoubtedly added to his ever-growing allure among supporters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The vivacity carried over to the game, with the crowd erupting into cheers upon Trump’s arrival.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the backdrop of these events, Trump’s stronghold on the GOP nomination seems increasingly unassailable. Recent polling by Civiqs in association with Iowa State reveals Trump holding a majority with 51% support. This places him well ahead of competitors, notably Florida Governor Ron DeSantis who stands at a mere 14% support in Iowa, despite his team’s prior emphasis on the state’s significance for his campaign. DeSantis’ team, recalibrating their stance, suggested that even a “strong second” in Iowa might suffice, with a campaign official even stating, “&lt;em&gt;I don’t think there’s a single state we have to win&lt;/em&gt;.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adding to Trump’s momentum is the recent endorsement from South Dakota Governor Kristi Noem. Once seen as a potential rival for the 2024 nomination, Noem’s endorsement further solidifies Trump’s status as the frontrunner in the GOP race.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In what was ostensibly a day of sport, Trump adeptly blended politics and entertainment, leaving an indelible impression on Iowa’s electorate and amplifying his message for 2024.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Iowa witnessed an exuberant political spectacle on Saturday as former President Donald Trump turned a college football game into an informal campaign rally. Demonstrating his trademark charisma, Trump partied with an Iowa State fraternity, showcased his grill skills, and engaged with the crowd by throwing footballs, further underlining his dominant position in the 2024 GOP nomination race. In a spirited pre-game event, Trump visited the Alpha Gamma Rho (AGR) agriculture fraternity house at Iowa State University in Ames. Not one to stick to convention, the former president threw footballs from a beer pong table into the waiting crowd. These candid moments were interspersed with Trump flipping burgers and posing for photographs with fraternity members, all of which undoubtedly added to his ever-growing allure among supporters. The vivacity carried over to the game, with the crowd erupting into cheers upon Trump’s arrival. In the backdrop of these events, Trump’s stronghold on the GOP nomination seems increasingly unassailable. Recent polling by Civiqs in association with Iowa State reveals Trump holding a majority with 51% support. This places him well ahead of competitors, notably Florida Governor Ron DeSantis who stands at a mere 14% support in Iowa, despite his team’s prior emphasis on the state’s significance for his campaign. DeSantis’ team, recalibrating their stance, suggested that even a “strong second” in Iowa might suffice, with a campaign official even stating, “I don’t think there’s a single state we have to win.” Adding to Trump’s momentum is the recent endorsement from South Dakota Governor Kristi Noem. Once seen as a potential rival for the 2024 nomination, Noem’s endorsement further solidifies Trump’s status as the frontrunner in the GOP race. In what was ostensibly a day of sport, Trump adeptly blended politics and entertainment, leaving an indelible impression on Iowa’s electorate and amplifying his message for 2024.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump’s Resilience Shines - Despite Legal Onslaughts, Support Soars</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/10/Trump-Resilience/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump’s Resilience Shines - Despite Legal Onslaughts, Support Soars" /><published>2023-09-10T15:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-10T15:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/10/Trump-Resilience</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/10/Trump-Resilience/">&lt;p&gt;Donald Trump’s political journey has always been emblematic of resilience. Facing an array of legal challenges, including four recent indictments, the former president’s popularity within the Republican party not only remains unshaken but appears to be surging.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Former Arkansas Governor Mike Huckabee is among those marveling at Trump’s capacity to navigate political storms with unique charisma. Huckabee expressed his admiration on Newsmax’s “The Count,” stating, “&lt;em&gt;It’s what I love about Donald Trump. It rolls right off of [him]&lt;/em&gt;.” The former governor emphasizes that Trump’s resilience is an asset for the Republicans, especially since any other potential nominee would likely face similar challenges from Democrats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Indeed, Trump’s magnetism has been a subject of political discourse since his 2016 presidential bid. A testament to his appeal came from the man himself when he remarked, “&lt;em&gt;I could stand in the middle of Fifth Avenue and shoot somebody, and I wouldn’t lose any voters.&lt;/em&gt;” Such brazen confidence, backed by unwavering support from his base, has reinforced Trump’s “Teflon Don” moniker, making him appear impervious to the usual political pitfalls.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Throughout his presidential tenure, Trump successfully weathered two impeachments, a feat unparalleled in U.S. history. These events, coupled with the current legal challenges, seem to only amplify his political might. Polling data indicates that with every indictment, Trump’s favorability among Republicans climbs. Each legal challenge appears to fortify his image as a political maverick who consistently defies conventional political norms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adding to this perception, Trump’s active engagement on his social media platform, Truth Social, reveals a deep-seated belief in his path back to the White House. A telling post to his 6 million followers read, “&lt;em&gt;I NEED ONE MORE INDICTMENT TO ENSURE MY ELECTION!&lt;/em&gt;”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This uncanny ability to transform adversity into advantage defines Trump’s political legacy. As the 2024 elections loom, Trump’s resilience and unyielding support base position him as a formidable force in the political arena, challenging both allies and adversaries to take heed.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Donald Trump’s political journey has always been emblematic of resilience. Facing an array of legal challenges, including four recent indictments, the former president’s popularity within the Republican party not only remains unshaken but appears to be surging. Former Arkansas Governor Mike Huckabee is among those marveling at Trump’s capacity to navigate political storms with unique charisma. Huckabee expressed his admiration on Newsmax’s “The Count,” stating, “It’s what I love about Donald Trump. It rolls right off of [him].” The former governor emphasizes that Trump’s resilience is an asset for the Republicans, especially since any other potential nominee would likely face similar challenges from Democrats. Indeed, Trump’s magnetism has been a subject of political discourse since his 2016 presidential bid. A testament to his appeal came from the man himself when he remarked, “I could stand in the middle of Fifth Avenue and shoot somebody, and I wouldn’t lose any voters.” Such brazen confidence, backed by unwavering support from his base, has reinforced Trump’s “Teflon Don” moniker, making him appear impervious to the usual political pitfalls. Throughout his presidential tenure, Trump successfully weathered two impeachments, a feat unparalleled in U.S. history. These events, coupled with the current legal challenges, seem to only amplify his political might. Polling data indicates that with every indictment, Trump’s favorability among Republicans climbs. Each legal challenge appears to fortify his image as a political maverick who consistently defies conventional political norms. Adding to this perception, Trump’s active engagement on his social media platform, Truth Social, reveals a deep-seated belief in his path back to the White House. A telling post to his 6 million followers read, “I NEED ONE MORE INDICTMENT TO ENSURE MY ELECTION!” This uncanny ability to transform adversity into advantage defines Trump’s political legacy. As the 2024 elections loom, Trump’s resilience and unyielding support base position him as a formidable force in the political arena, challenging both allies and adversaries to take heed.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Dramatic Twist in 23-Year Cold Case Kidnapping</title><link href="/news/2023/09/10/Kidnapping-Case-Turn/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dramatic Twist in 23-Year Cold Case Kidnapping" /><published>2023-09-10T14:02:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-10T14:02:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/10/Kidnapping-Case-Turn</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/10/Kidnapping-Case-Turn/">&lt;p&gt;In an unforeseen twist to a heart-rending 23-year-old kidnapping cold case, the primary suspect is now believed to be an innocent missing individual, just like her own daughter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;West Virginia’s decades-old narrative pivots around the mysterious disappearance of 10-year-old Natasha “Alex” Carter in 2000. Initial suspicions, fueled by FBI wanted posters and a $10,000 reward, landed heavily on Susan Gail Carter, her mother. Susan was believed to have abducted her daughter amidst a strained custody dispute. Evidence for these suspicions included Susan’s purported declaration to her husband, Rick Lafferty, that he’d never again see their daughter. Further, the child’s grandmother’s testimony indicated that young Natasha was fearful of her own mother.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the investigation’s entire trajectory shifted recently. Fresh evidence unearthed by the West Virginia State Police suggests that both mother and daughter may have vanished simultaneously.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;State police, along with the FBI, acted on new intelligence to execute search warrants at the Carter family’s last known Raleigh County residence. The FBI has confirmed the acquisition of “additional forensic evidence,” but details remain closely guarded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Larry Dell Webb owned the property under investigation. Post the police’s sweep, Terry Lilly, Webb’s caretaker, allowed journalists access to the premises. The Register Herald’s accounts highlighted removed sections of drywall and extracted tile flooring, possibly hinting at concealed evidence or a grisly scene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Susan was 41 when she vanished, while Natasha, known by her middle name “Alex,” was only 10. The duo’s disappearance took place shortly after moving in with Susan’s new spouse. West Virginia State Police’s statement clarified that what started as an alleged kidnapping by Susan Carter has now morphed into a dual missing persons case since August 8, 2000.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Desperate for leads, law enforcement has doubled the previous reward, now offering $20,000 for crucial information leading to the whereabouts of the Carters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Highlighting the case’s national significance, “In Pursuit with John Walsh” featured it in a 2022 episode. Calls to action urge anyone with pertinent information to step forward and contact the West Virginia State Police Beckley Detachment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This chilling tale underscores the complexities and often unforeseen turns in long-standing cold cases. The quest for truth continues.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In an unforeseen twist to a heart-rending 23-year-old kidnapping cold case, the primary suspect is now believed to be an innocent missing individual, just like her own daughter. West Virginia’s decades-old narrative pivots around the mysterious disappearance of 10-year-old Natasha “Alex” Carter in 2000. Initial suspicions, fueled by FBI wanted posters and a $10,000 reward, landed heavily on Susan Gail Carter, her mother. Susan was believed to have abducted her daughter amidst a strained custody dispute. Evidence for these suspicions included Susan’s purported declaration to her husband, Rick Lafferty, that he’d never again see their daughter. Further, the child’s grandmother’s testimony indicated that young Natasha was fearful of her own mother. However, the investigation’s entire trajectory shifted recently. Fresh evidence unearthed by the West Virginia State Police suggests that both mother and daughter may have vanished simultaneously. State police, along with the FBI, acted on new intelligence to execute search warrants at the Carter family’s last known Raleigh County residence. The FBI has confirmed the acquisition of “additional forensic evidence,” but details remain closely guarded. Larry Dell Webb owned the property under investigation. Post the police’s sweep, Terry Lilly, Webb’s caretaker, allowed journalists access to the premises. The Register Herald’s accounts highlighted removed sections of drywall and extracted tile flooring, possibly hinting at concealed evidence or a grisly scene. Susan was 41 when she vanished, while Natasha, known by her middle name “Alex,” was only 10. The duo’s disappearance took place shortly after moving in with Susan’s new spouse. West Virginia State Police’s statement clarified that what started as an alleged kidnapping by Susan Carter has now morphed into a dual missing persons case since August 8, 2000. Desperate for leads, law enforcement has doubled the previous reward, now offering $20,000 for crucial information leading to the whereabouts of the Carters. Highlighting the case’s national significance, “In Pursuit with John Walsh” featured it in a 2022 episode. Calls to action urge anyone with pertinent information to step forward and contact the West Virginia State Police Beckley Detachment. This chilling tale underscores the complexities and often unforeseen turns in long-standing cold cases. The quest for truth continues.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ashton Kutcher and Mila Kunis Express Regret - Support Letters for Convicted Rapist Danny Masterson Cause Uproar</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/10/Kutcher-Kunis-Apology/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ashton Kutcher and Mila Kunis Express Regret - Support Letters for Convicted Rapist Danny Masterson Cause Uproar" /><published>2023-09-10T13:01:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-10T13:01:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/10/Kutcher-Kunis-Apology</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/10/Kutcher-Kunis-Apology/">&lt;p&gt;In a recent turn of events, renowned actors and couple, Ashton Kutcher and Mila Kunis, have publicly retracted their previous endorsement for their former “That ’70s Show” co-star, Danny Masterson, after his conviction for rape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Apology Through the Lens of Social Media&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A video uploaded to Instagram witnessed both Kutcher and Kunis expressing their remorse. The pair clarified that their intention was solely to support a friend they had known for 25 years, without any thought of causing harm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Being aware of the pain the character letters have inflicted, we sincerely apologize,” Kutcher voiced.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reiterating their commitment to supporting victims of abuse, Kunis added, “Our past endeavors prove our dedication to supporting victims. This will continue to be a focus for us.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The letters were composed in response to a plea from Masterson’s family, hoping their influence would have a bearing on the sentencing phase. Masterson was ultimately sentenced to 30 years to life for the rape of two women.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kunis emphasized that the letters were never meant to question the judicial system’s legitimacy or cast doubt on the jury’s decision.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both actors expressed deep sorrow for any harm their actions may have inadvertently caused, especially if it led to the re-traumatization of victims. “We deeply regret the hurt caused and extend our sympathy to every victim of sexual assault, abuse, or rape,” the couple concluded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Polarizing Figure Amongst Co-stars&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Breitbart News highlighted that Kutcher and Kunis’s letter to the judge praised Masterson as an “exceptional role model” and a beacon against drug abuse in Hollywood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kutcher wrote, “Attributing my distance from the common Hollywood trap of drugs directly to Danny, he has consistently demonstrated exemplary behavior.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further, Kunis lauded Masterson’s influence, describing him as a guiding light against drug abuse, emphasizing his impact on her well-being and decision-making in the entertainment realm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, not all co-stars from “That ’70s Show” shared the couple’s sentiment. While Kurtwood Smith, Debra Rupp, and David Trainer expressed their support for Masterson, Topher Grace distinctly distanced himself. Grace’s wife, Ashley Hinshaw, posted a potent statement on Instagram, shedding light on the trauma survivors endure in such circumstances, “To every rape victim retraumatized by societal debates over the rapist’s fate, we see and recognize your pain,” she articulated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the dust settles on this episode, it serves as a poignant reminder of the responsibility public figures carry and the far-reaching consequences of their actions.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">In a recent turn of events, renowned actors and couple, Ashton Kutcher and Mila Kunis, have publicly retracted their previous endorsement for their former “That ’70s Show” co-star, Danny Masterson, after his conviction for rape. Apology Through the Lens of Social Media A video uploaded to Instagram witnessed both Kutcher and Kunis expressing their remorse. The pair clarified that their intention was solely to support a friend they had known for 25 years, without any thought of causing harm. “Being aware of the pain the character letters have inflicted, we sincerely apologize,” Kutcher voiced. Reiterating their commitment to supporting victims of abuse, Kunis added, “Our past endeavors prove our dedication to supporting victims. This will continue to be a focus for us.” The letters were composed in response to a plea from Masterson’s family, hoping their influence would have a bearing on the sentencing phase. Masterson was ultimately sentenced to 30 years to life for the rape of two women. Kunis emphasized that the letters were never meant to question the judicial system’s legitimacy or cast doubt on the jury’s decision. Both actors expressed deep sorrow for any harm their actions may have inadvertently caused, especially if it led to the re-traumatization of victims. “We deeply regret the hurt caused and extend our sympathy to every victim of sexual assault, abuse, or rape,” the couple concluded. A Polarizing Figure Amongst Co-stars Breitbart News highlighted that Kutcher and Kunis’s letter to the judge praised Masterson as an “exceptional role model” and a beacon against drug abuse in Hollywood. Kutcher wrote, “Attributing my distance from the common Hollywood trap of drugs directly to Danny, he has consistently demonstrated exemplary behavior.” Further, Kunis lauded Masterson’s influence, describing him as a guiding light against drug abuse, emphasizing his impact on her well-being and decision-making in the entertainment realm. However, not all co-stars from “That ’70s Show” shared the couple’s sentiment. While Kurtwood Smith, Debra Rupp, and David Trainer expressed their support for Masterson, Topher Grace distinctly distanced himself. Grace’s wife, Ashley Hinshaw, posted a potent statement on Instagram, shedding light on the trauma survivors endure in such circumstances, “To every rape victim retraumatized by societal debates over the rapist’s fate, we see and recognize your pain,” she articulated. As the dust settles on this episode, it serves as a poignant reminder of the responsibility public figures carry and the far-reaching consequences of their actions.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Alarming Algos - News Corp CEO Highlights AI’s Left-Wing Bias in Journalism</title><link href="/news/2023/09/10/AI-Left-Wing-Bias/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Alarming Algos - News Corp CEO Highlights AI’s Left-Wing Bias in Journalism" /><published>2023-09-10T12:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-10T12:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/10/AI-Left-Wing-Bias</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/10/AI-Left-Wing-Bias/">&lt;p&gt;The realm of Artificial Intelligence (AI) in journalism is not devoid of controversy. At the recent Goldman Sachs Communacopia and Technology Conference, News Corp CEO Robert Thomson dropped a bombshell, warning of the growing left-wing bias embedded within AI’s content generation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In today’s fast-paced media environment, the objectivity and quality of news are of paramount importance. However, Thomson raised concerns, painting a picture of an industry where AI’s “rubbish in, rubbish out” approach could further entrench existing biases, especially the left-leaning slant observed in certain media giants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AI, with its capacity to sift through and regenerate vast amounts of pre-existing content, can inadvertently proliferate and magnify any inherent biases. The CEO’s vivid depiction of the potential fallout is that of an “ever-shrinking circle of sanity surrounded by a reservoir of rubbish.” In essence, instead of embracing the potential insights AI could bring, the media landscape is at risk of turning into what he evocatively described as “maggot-ridden mind mold.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But beyond the bias, Thomson shed light on the broader implications of AI in journalism. He highlighted the disturbing decline in newsroom employment, indicating a drop of nearly 57% between 2008 to 2020. With AI poised to take a more substantial role, the livelihoods of thousands more are under threat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thomson’s solution? Accountability. He asserted that companies training generative AI using archived materials should compensate the original publishers appropriately. “If you derive benefit from our content, we should derive a benefit or else you’re in danger of undermining the creation of that content,” he stated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The discourse around AI’s role in journalism, especially its political bias, is a pressing concern. As the lines between human-led journalism and AI-generated content blur, Thomson’s cautionary note is a clarion call for the industry to tread carefully, ensuring technology enhances rather than skews the narrative.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">The realm of Artificial Intelligence (AI) in journalism is not devoid of controversy. At the recent Goldman Sachs Communacopia and Technology Conference, News Corp CEO Robert Thomson dropped a bombshell, warning of the growing left-wing bias embedded within AI’s content generation. In today’s fast-paced media environment, the objectivity and quality of news are of paramount importance. However, Thomson raised concerns, painting a picture of an industry where AI’s “rubbish in, rubbish out” approach could further entrench existing biases, especially the left-leaning slant observed in certain media giants. AI, with its capacity to sift through and regenerate vast amounts of pre-existing content, can inadvertently proliferate and magnify any inherent biases. The CEO’s vivid depiction of the potential fallout is that of an “ever-shrinking circle of sanity surrounded by a reservoir of rubbish.” In essence, instead of embracing the potential insights AI could bring, the media landscape is at risk of turning into what he evocatively described as “maggot-ridden mind mold.” But beyond the bias, Thomson shed light on the broader implications of AI in journalism. He highlighted the disturbing decline in newsroom employment, indicating a drop of nearly 57% between 2008 to 2020. With AI poised to take a more substantial role, the livelihoods of thousands more are under threat. Thomson’s solution? Accountability. He asserted that companies training generative AI using archived materials should compensate the original publishers appropriately. “If you derive benefit from our content, we should derive a benefit or else you’re in danger of undermining the creation of that content,” he stated. The discourse around AI’s role in journalism, especially its political bias, is a pressing concern. As the lines between human-led journalism and AI-generated content blur, Thomson’s cautionary note is a clarion call for the industry to tread carefully, ensuring technology enhances rather than skews the narrative.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Tim Scott Denounces California Bill - Calls Punishing Non-Affirming Parents ‘Evil’</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/10/Tim-Scott-Reacts/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tim Scott Denounces California Bill - Calls Punishing Non-Affirming Parents ‘Evil’" /><published>2023-09-10T11:06:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-10T11:06:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/10/Tim-Scott-Reacts</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/10/Tim-Scott-Reacts/">&lt;p&gt;In a fierce rebuke of California’s recent legislative move, Republican presidential candidate Tim Scott labeled a bill penalizing parents who do not affirm their transgender children as “evil.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The contentious bill, AB 957, freshly passed by the California State Assembly, has come under intense scrutiny. This legislation obliges judges in child custody cases to evaluate if a parent has recognized and affirmed their child’s transgender identity. The core proposition of the bill originally intended courts to see whether parents were gender-affirming. A subsequent amendment further tightened these stipulations. It laid down that to be adjudged as fit parents in a court of law, acknowledgment and affirmation of a child’s gender identity become essential.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tim Scott, a stalwart defender of parental rights, voiced his profound dismay at this measure. He articulated, “&lt;em&gt;The radical Left is on a mission to make parents less important. They believe your kids belong to them.&lt;/em&gt;” He further pledged his unwavering commitment to reversing this narrative by emphatically stating, “&lt;em&gt;I will fight back, put parents back in charge, and shield the next generation of children from such overreach.&lt;/em&gt;”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Previously, Senator Scott unveiled an extensive plan aimed at safeguarding children and empowering families. Central to his “Empower Parents Plan” is the establishment of a robust family-first culture. Scott, the Senate’s only Black Republican, is resolute in championing traditional values. He stresses the significance of allowing children to grow naturally, free from societal pressures about their gender identities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to this, Scott demands that parents be granted unrestricted access to their children’s educational content, ensuring they are privy to all materials their children are exposed to in schools. A fervent advocate for school choice, Scott envisions weakening the stranglehold of teachers’ unions. He ardently supports granting parents a more substantial say in choosing the educational path best suited for their children, whether that’s public, private, charter, STEM schools, or homeschooling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a succinct summation of his educational vision, Scott declared his intent to “&lt;em&gt;replace indoctrination with education. ABC, not CRT.&lt;/em&gt;” With unwavering dedication to parental rights and a clear vision for America’s educational future, Senator Tim Scott continues to shape the discourse on this critical issue.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a fierce rebuke of California’s recent legislative move, Republican presidential candidate Tim Scott labeled a bill penalizing parents who do not affirm their transgender children as “evil.” The contentious bill, AB 957, freshly passed by the California State Assembly, has come under intense scrutiny. This legislation obliges judges in child custody cases to evaluate if a parent has recognized and affirmed their child’s transgender identity. The core proposition of the bill originally intended courts to see whether parents were gender-affirming. A subsequent amendment further tightened these stipulations. It laid down that to be adjudged as fit parents in a court of law, acknowledgment and affirmation of a child’s gender identity become essential. Tim Scott, a stalwart defender of parental rights, voiced his profound dismay at this measure. He articulated, “The radical Left is on a mission to make parents less important. They believe your kids belong to them.” He further pledged his unwavering commitment to reversing this narrative by emphatically stating, “I will fight back, put parents back in charge, and shield the next generation of children from such overreach.” Previously, Senator Scott unveiled an extensive plan aimed at safeguarding children and empowering families. Central to his “Empower Parents Plan” is the establishment of a robust family-first culture. Scott, the Senate’s only Black Republican, is resolute in championing traditional values. He stresses the significance of allowing children to grow naturally, free from societal pressures about their gender identities. In addition to this, Scott demands that parents be granted unrestricted access to their children’s educational content, ensuring they are privy to all materials their children are exposed to in schools. A fervent advocate for school choice, Scott envisions weakening the stranglehold of teachers’ unions. He ardently supports granting parents a more substantial say in choosing the educational path best suited for their children, whether that’s public, private, charter, STEM schools, or homeschooling. In a succinct summation of his educational vision, Scott declared his intent to “replace indoctrination with education. ABC, not CRT.” With unwavering dedication to parental rights and a clear vision for America’s educational future, Senator Tim Scott continues to shape the discourse on this critical issue.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Rapper’s Lyrics Lead to Arrest - Kenjuan McDaniel Faces Murder Charges</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/10/Rapper-Charged-With-Murder/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rapper’s Lyrics Lead to Arrest - Kenjuan McDaniel Faces Murder Charges" /><published>2023-09-10T10:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-10T10:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/10/Rapper-Charged-With-Murder</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/10/Rapper-Charged-With-Murder/">&lt;p&gt;In a shocking twist of events, Nevada-based rapper Kenjuan McDaniel is currently behind bars after being arrested on a murder charge. The Las Vegas Metropolitan Police Department claims that McDaniel’s own song lyrics serve as a confession to the crime.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Song that Spoke Too Much&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On August 29, the 25-year-old rapper was apprehended and is now facing an open murder charge involving a deadly weapon. The charge stems from a crime that occurred in 2021, where 32-year-old Randall Wallace was tragically shot dead in an apartment complex. It was previously noted that Wallace had been involved in a heated dispute with three then-unidentified individuals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;McDaniel’s song, “Fadee Free”, has been pinpointed by the authorities as the piece that contains incriminating evidence. Not only does the song, which was released on YouTube, allude to the homicide, but certain details highlighted in the lyrics weren’t public knowledge, making the police even more suspicious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Las Vegas Review-Journal unveiled a part of the police arrest report that dissects specific lyrics from “Fadee Free”. One particular line: “Brought it with that fire, hear that ‘ah’, see your body twitching,” was associated with Wallace’s unfortunate demise, especially given accounts of Wallace twitching before succumbing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another lyric, as highlighted by 8 News Now, reads: “Parked the car, doubled back on feet, the smartest way to slide.” The police found correlations between this line and the modus operandi of the murder. Additionally, McDaniel’s song allegedly includes a reference to a nickname familiar to Wallace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A High-Stakes Legal Battle Awaits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the preliminary hearing for McDaniel scheduled on September 14, the rapper’s fate hangs in the balance. His bail is currently set at a hefty $1 million, with mandated electronic monitoring, as indicated by the court records.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The case not only illuminates the dangerous line between art and real life but also prompts artists to ponder the implications of their work. As McDaniel’s story unfolds, the music industry and fans worldwide are left to grapple with the complexities of music’s power to both inspire and incriminate.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">In a shocking twist of events, Nevada-based rapper Kenjuan McDaniel is currently behind bars after being arrested on a murder charge. The Las Vegas Metropolitan Police Department claims that McDaniel’s own song lyrics serve as a confession to the crime. The Song that Spoke Too Much On August 29, the 25-year-old rapper was apprehended and is now facing an open murder charge involving a deadly weapon. The charge stems from a crime that occurred in 2021, where 32-year-old Randall Wallace was tragically shot dead in an apartment complex. It was previously noted that Wallace had been involved in a heated dispute with three then-unidentified individuals. McDaniel’s song, “Fadee Free”, has been pinpointed by the authorities as the piece that contains incriminating evidence. Not only does the song, which was released on YouTube, allude to the homicide, but certain details highlighted in the lyrics weren’t public knowledge, making the police even more suspicious. The Las Vegas Review-Journal unveiled a part of the police arrest report that dissects specific lyrics from “Fadee Free”. One particular line: “Brought it with that fire, hear that ‘ah’, see your body twitching,” was associated with Wallace’s unfortunate demise, especially given accounts of Wallace twitching before succumbing. Another lyric, as highlighted by 8 News Now, reads: “Parked the car, doubled back on feet, the smartest way to slide.” The police found correlations between this line and the modus operandi of the murder. Additionally, McDaniel’s song allegedly includes a reference to a nickname familiar to Wallace. A High-Stakes Legal Battle Awaits With the preliminary hearing for McDaniel scheduled on September 14, the rapper’s fate hangs in the balance. His bail is currently set at a hefty $1 million, with mandated electronic monitoring, as indicated by the court records. The case not only illuminates the dangerous line between art and real life but also prompts artists to ponder the implications of their work. As McDaniel’s story unfolds, the music industry and fans worldwide are left to grapple with the complexities of music’s power to both inspire and incriminate.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Unmasked - Scientist Admits to Sidestepping Whole Truth on Climate Study</title><link href="/news/2023/09/10/Climate-Truth-Revelation/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Unmasked - Scientist Admits to Sidestepping Whole Truth on Climate Study" /><published>2023-09-10T09:04:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-10T09:04:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/10/Climate-Truth-Revelation</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/10/Climate-Truth-Revelation/">&lt;p&gt;California’s wildfire crisis has long been a contentious point of debate. But now, the spotlight shines not on the fires themselves, but on the academic transparency surrounding research into their causes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Patrick T. Brown, a renowned earth and climate scientist from Johns Hopkins University, stirred the pot by admitting he “left out the full truth” in his research published in the distinguished science journal, Nature. He attributed this decision to pressures scientists face in getting their work published in esteemed journals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a candid confession, Brown shared that his study on the correlation between climate change and extreme wildfire behavior was “narrowly focused”. He concentrated predominantly on the human influence on wildfires, neglecting other crucial factors, such as poor forest management, that significantly impact fire behavior.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a compelling statement in The Free Press, Brown explained, “And the editors of these journals have made it abundantly clear… they want climate papers that support certain preapproved narratives—even when those narratives come at the expense of broader knowledge for society.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Brown’s revelations have significant implications. Not only do they raise questions about the objectivity of prestigious journals, but they also challenge the depth and authenticity of the discourse on climate change. As Brown himself emphasized, such skewed representations “misinform the public” and hinder the identification of real solutions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;California Assembly leader, James Gallagher, a Republican, was swift in his condemnation. He criticized liberals for manipulating data to fit a preconceived narrative, consequently pushing radical policies. “Patrick Brown is saying the quiet part out loud - liberals are cherry-picking data to fit an agenda and push radical policies that drive up the cost of living,” Gallagher conveyed to Fox News Digital.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Republican Assembly member Joe Patterson further stressed the issue, accusing Governor Gavin Newsom of pressuring scientists to ignore significant factors responsible for wildfires. “Republicans want scientists to consider all causes of massive wildfires, including climate change,” Patterson noted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As debate rages, one thing is crystal clear: the quest for academic and journalistic integrity in the climate debate remains as fiery as the wildfires themselves.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">California’s wildfire crisis has long been a contentious point of debate. But now, the spotlight shines not on the fires themselves, but on the academic transparency surrounding research into their causes. Patrick T. Brown, a renowned earth and climate scientist from Johns Hopkins University, stirred the pot by admitting he “left out the full truth” in his research published in the distinguished science journal, Nature. He attributed this decision to pressures scientists face in getting their work published in esteemed journals. In a candid confession, Brown shared that his study on the correlation between climate change and extreme wildfire behavior was “narrowly focused”. He concentrated predominantly on the human influence on wildfires, neglecting other crucial factors, such as poor forest management, that significantly impact fire behavior. In a compelling statement in The Free Press, Brown explained, “And the editors of these journals have made it abundantly clear… they want climate papers that support certain preapproved narratives—even when those narratives come at the expense of broader knowledge for society.” Brown’s revelations have significant implications. Not only do they raise questions about the objectivity of prestigious journals, but they also challenge the depth and authenticity of the discourse on climate change. As Brown himself emphasized, such skewed representations “misinform the public” and hinder the identification of real solutions. California Assembly leader, James Gallagher, a Republican, was swift in his condemnation. He criticized liberals for manipulating data to fit a preconceived narrative, consequently pushing radical policies. “Patrick Brown is saying the quiet part out loud - liberals are cherry-picking data to fit an agenda and push radical policies that drive up the cost of living,” Gallagher conveyed to Fox News Digital. Republican Assembly member Joe Patterson further stressed the issue, accusing Governor Gavin Newsom of pressuring scientists to ignore significant factors responsible for wildfires. “Republicans want scientists to consider all causes of massive wildfires, including climate change,” Patterson noted. As debate rages, one thing is crystal clear: the quest for academic and journalistic integrity in the climate debate remains as fiery as the wildfires themselves.</summary></entry></feed>