<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-09-21T13:13:54-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/09/21/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-09-21T13:13:54-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-21T13:13:54-04:00</updated><id>/2023/09/21/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/21/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">A Cry for Help - Sacramento’s Growing Homeless Struggle</title><link href="/news/2023/09/21/Sacramento-Crisis/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Cry for Help - Sacramento’s Growing Homeless Struggle" /><published>2023-09-21T13:02:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-21T13:02:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/21/Sacramento-Crisis</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/21/Sacramento-Crisis/">&lt;p&gt;Sacramento, California’s capital, is often bustling with politicians and city leaders. But recently, it’s the growing number of tents and makeshift shelters that are stealing headlines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;from-the-golden-state-to-a-homeless-crisis&quot;&gt;From the Golden State to a Homeless Crisis&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Democratic District Attorney Thien Ho of Sacramento County is up in arms against his city. Why? It’s over the homeless conditions which, according to him, resemble those of a “Third World country.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Tuesday, Ho announced a civil lawsuit against Sacramento. The lawsuit accuses the city of allowing a public safety crisis concerning its homeless population. And the numbers back his claim: In just seven years, the unhoused population in Sacramento has skyrocketed by over 250%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Our community is on the edge,” the lawsuit reads. “We have homeless folks living in conditions you’d find in severely underdeveloped countries. Meanwhile, the rest of us are caught between wanting to help and dealing with the chaos.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-tipping-point&quot;&gt;The Tipping Point&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ho lamented the repetitive cycle the city seems to be stuck in. “It’s like Groundhog’s Day,” he said, “where the situation remains grim, and nothing improves.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Problems stemming from the increasing homelessness are becoming hard to ignore. Both Judge Michael Bowman and District Attorney Ho have voiced concerns about growing homeless encampments near the courthouse. These settlements are not just an eyesore but also pose genuine threats. Reports include instances of assault, public misconduct, and other disturbances which, according to Ho, compromise the safety of jurors, victims, and witnesses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-plea-for-change&quot;&gt;A Plea for Change&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The city’s response to this escalating crisis has been, to many, unsatisfactory. Mayor Darrell Steinberg promised the initiation of the “Miller Park Safe Camping” to alleviate the situation, but three months on, conditions appear to have only deteriorated. Instances of assault and harassment linked to the homeless population have surged, further deepening the divide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A survey conducted by Ho’s office in July asked locals how the 16 main homeless encampments across Sacramento affected their lives. Out of nearly 3,000 responses, many recounted harrowing experiences. Residents reported assaults, disruptions to community events, and continuous harassment by homeless individuals. Some even stated that their pleas for help from City Hall either went unanswered or were met with dismissive remarks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, in response to the lawsuit, City Attorney Susana Alcala Wood expressed disappointment, stating the DA seems more keen on laying blame than seeking solutions. Mayor Steinberg termed Ho’s actions a “performative distraction,” yet acknowledged the frustrations faced by residents due to the ongoing crisis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sacramento’s struggle highlights the broader challenges many California cities face with their growing homeless populations. While solutions may be complex and multifaceted, the need for actionable change is evident.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Sacramento, California’s capital, is often bustling with politicians and city leaders. But recently, it’s the growing number of tents and makeshift shelters that are stealing headlines. From the Golden State to a Homeless Crisis Democratic District Attorney Thien Ho of Sacramento County is up in arms against his city. Why? It’s over the homeless conditions which, according to him, resemble those of a “Third World country.” On Tuesday, Ho announced a civil lawsuit against Sacramento. The lawsuit accuses the city of allowing a public safety crisis concerning its homeless population. And the numbers back his claim: In just seven years, the unhoused population in Sacramento has skyrocketed by over 250%. “Our community is on the edge,” the lawsuit reads. “We have homeless folks living in conditions you’d find in severely underdeveloped countries. Meanwhile, the rest of us are caught between wanting to help and dealing with the chaos.” The Tipping Point Ho lamented the repetitive cycle the city seems to be stuck in. “It’s like Groundhog’s Day,” he said, “where the situation remains grim, and nothing improves.” Problems stemming from the increasing homelessness are becoming hard to ignore. Both Judge Michael Bowman and District Attorney Ho have voiced concerns about growing homeless encampments near the courthouse. These settlements are not just an eyesore but also pose genuine threats. Reports include instances of assault, public misconduct, and other disturbances which, according to Ho, compromise the safety of jurors, victims, and witnesses. A Plea for Change The city’s response to this escalating crisis has been, to many, unsatisfactory. Mayor Darrell Steinberg promised the initiation of the “Miller Park Safe Camping” to alleviate the situation, but three months on, conditions appear to have only deteriorated. Instances of assault and harassment linked to the homeless population have surged, further deepening the divide. A survey conducted by Ho’s office in July asked locals how the 16 main homeless encampments across Sacramento affected their lives. Out of nearly 3,000 responses, many recounted harrowing experiences. Residents reported assaults, disruptions to community events, and continuous harassment by homeless individuals. Some even stated that their pleas for help from City Hall either went unanswered or were met with dismissive remarks. However, in response to the lawsuit, City Attorney Susana Alcala Wood expressed disappointment, stating the DA seems more keen on laying blame than seeking solutions. Mayor Steinberg termed Ho’s actions a “performative distraction,” yet acknowledged the frustrations faced by residents due to the ongoing crisis. Sacramento’s struggle highlights the broader challenges many California cities face with their growing homeless populations. While solutions may be complex and multifaceted, the need for actionable change is evident.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">McConaughey and Harrelson’s DNA Test Drama - Maury Povich Steps In!</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/21/DNA-Test-Proposal/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="McConaughey and Harrelson’s DNA Test Drama - Maury Povich Steps In!" /><published>2023-09-21T12:09:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-21T12:09:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/21/DNA-Test-Proposal</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/21/DNA-Test-Proposal/">&lt;p&gt;It’s a storyline that sounds like it’s straight out of Hollywood: two leading men, Matthew McConaughey and Woody Harrelson, discovering that they might be half-brothers. But it’s not a movie – it’s real life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The buzz around this surprising possibility grew louder after McConaughey shared some revelations about his family’s past. During a podcast interview, he disclosed that Harrelson’s father might have had a connection with his mother during her divorce. This set off waves of speculation – are the two superstar actors related by blood?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enter Maury Povich, a retired television host, best known for his dramatic on-screen DNA test reveals. In a light-hearted twist, Povich offered to step in and conduct a DNA test for the two stars, even proposing a prime-time TV special. “I would come out of retirement. We could do primetime, ‘DNA, Maury’s back with Woody and Matthew,’” Povich said in a video to E! News.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Harrelson seemed intrigued by the idea when he appeared on “The Late Show with Stephen Colbert,” musing about the implications of such a test. “For [McConaughey], it’s a big deal. He feels like he’s losing a father. But I’m like, no, you’re gaining a different father and a brother.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The two have been friends for over two decades, showcasing their camaraderie in projects such as “True Detective.” Fans are eagerly awaiting their reunion onscreen in the upcoming series, “Brother From Another Mother,” which, given the current rumors, holds an uncanny relevance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, will they take the test? The world waits with bated breath. Whatever the outcome, it’s clear that the bond between McConaughey and Harrelson is stronger than ever. The story of their potential shared heritage adds another layer of intrigue to their already storied friendship.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">It’s a storyline that sounds like it’s straight out of Hollywood: two leading men, Matthew McConaughey and Woody Harrelson, discovering that they might be half-brothers. But it’s not a movie – it’s real life. The buzz around this surprising possibility grew louder after McConaughey shared some revelations about his family’s past. During a podcast interview, he disclosed that Harrelson’s father might have had a connection with his mother during her divorce. This set off waves of speculation – are the two superstar actors related by blood? Enter Maury Povich, a retired television host, best known for his dramatic on-screen DNA test reveals. In a light-hearted twist, Povich offered to step in and conduct a DNA test for the two stars, even proposing a prime-time TV special. “I would come out of retirement. We could do primetime, ‘DNA, Maury’s back with Woody and Matthew,’” Povich said in a video to E! News. Harrelson seemed intrigued by the idea when he appeared on “The Late Show with Stephen Colbert,” musing about the implications of such a test. “For [McConaughey], it’s a big deal. He feels like he’s losing a father. But I’m like, no, you’re gaining a different father and a brother.” The two have been friends for over two decades, showcasing their camaraderie in projects such as “True Detective.” Fans are eagerly awaiting their reunion onscreen in the upcoming series, “Brother From Another Mother,” which, given the current rumors, holds an uncanny relevance. So, will they take the test? The world waits with bated breath. Whatever the outcome, it’s clear that the bond between McConaughey and Harrelson is stronger than ever. The story of their potential shared heritage adds another layer of intrigue to their already storied friendship.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Train Travels - Migrants’ New Path to Texas</title><link href="/news/2023/09/21/Migrant-Journey/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Train Travels - Migrants’ New Path to Texas" /><published>2023-09-21T11:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-21T11:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/21/Migrant-Journey</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/21/Migrant-Journey/">&lt;p&gt;The path to a new life can be hard. For thousands of migrants from Venezuela and Caribbean countries, it’s now taking them on a train journey towards the US border.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;all-aboard-the-migrant-express&quot;&gt;All Aboard the Migrant Express&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Migrants, in search of a brighter future, have turned to trains as their way into Piedras Negras, Coahuila. This city shares its borders with Texas. From here, many hope to enter the US.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Starting their trip in the bustling industrial city of Monterrey, Nuevo Leon, these determined individuals rode in and on the rail cars, moving towards their destination.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But things didn’t always go as planned. Mexican authorities caught wind of their journey and brought their train to a halt. Despite this hiccup, these migrants pressed on, eventually making their way to Piedras Negras.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;piedras-negras---a-gateway-city&quot;&gt;Piedras Negras - A Gateway City&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why Piedras Negras? This city has become a significant spot for migrants. Nearly 4,000 migrants began their crossing into Texas just this past Wednesday. The city’s appeal? The area lacks the extensive border barriers and fencing seen in other regions, making it an attractive point of entry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://media.breitbart.com/media/2023/09/Migrant-Trains-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Migrants at Piedras Negras&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;A crowd of migrants gather at Piedras Negras, looking for an opportunity to cross into Texas.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-bigger-picture&quot;&gt;The Bigger Picture&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The train-riding migrants shared stories of their long journey. Many mentioned that they began in Mexico City with travel permits in hand. But the path wasn’t easy. Along the way, these migrants faced challenges from Mexican immigration agents (known as INM) and police forces. Some even claimed they were extorted by these officials.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the story of these migrants is just one of many, it highlights the lengths people will go to for a chance at a better life. As the situation at the border evolves, the world watches, waiting to see how both sides will respond.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">The path to a new life can be hard. For thousands of migrants from Venezuela and Caribbean countries, it’s now taking them on a train journey towards the US border. All Aboard the Migrant Express Migrants, in search of a brighter future, have turned to trains as their way into Piedras Negras, Coahuila. This city shares its borders with Texas. From here, many hope to enter the US. Starting their trip in the bustling industrial city of Monterrey, Nuevo Leon, these determined individuals rode in and on the rail cars, moving towards their destination. But things didn’t always go as planned. Mexican authorities caught wind of their journey and brought their train to a halt. Despite this hiccup, these migrants pressed on, eventually making their way to Piedras Negras. Piedras Negras - A Gateway City Why Piedras Negras? This city has become a significant spot for migrants. Nearly 4,000 migrants began their crossing into Texas just this past Wednesday. The city’s appeal? The area lacks the extensive border barriers and fencing seen in other regions, making it an attractive point of entry. A crowd of migrants gather at Piedras Negras, looking for an opportunity to cross into Texas. The Bigger Picture The train-riding migrants shared stories of their long journey. Many mentioned that they began in Mexico City with travel permits in hand. But the path wasn’t easy. Along the way, these migrants faced challenges from Mexican immigration agents (known as INM) and police forces. Some even claimed they were extorted by these officials. While the story of these migrants is just one of many, it highlights the lengths people will go to for a chance at a better life. As the situation at the border evolves, the world watches, waiting to see how both sides will respond.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hunter Biden’s Unusual DOJ Treatment Raises Eyebrows</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/21/Hunter-Biden-Justice-Treatment/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hunter Biden’s Unusual DOJ Treatment Raises Eyebrows" /><published>2023-09-21T10:06:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-21T10:06:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/21/Hunter-Biden-Justice-Treatment</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/21/Hunter-Biden-Justice-Treatment/">&lt;p&gt;Hunter Biden’s recent indictment has taken the nation by storm. However, what’s capturing even more attention is the seemingly lenient approach the Department of Justice (DOJ) is taking toward his case, especially when considering its historical hard stance on similar matters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-surprising-treatment-of-a-presidents-son&quot;&gt;The Surprising Treatment of a President’s Son&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hunter Biden’s case isn’t just any case. He’s the first son of a sitting U.S. president to face criminal indictment. While it’s big news, insiders suggest that there’s more to come in this unfolding saga.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A former federal prosecutor has expressed deep concern over how the DOJ has been conducting a five-year investigation into Hunter Biden’s case. The evidence pointing toward corruption and severe criminal actions appears evident.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;comparing-hunters-case-to-traditional-doj-action&quot;&gt;Comparing Hunter’s Case to Traditional DOJ Action&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Historically, the DOJ has been strict, particularly when dealing with firearms offenses. This approach is in line with the Project Safe Neighborhoods (PSN), an initiative established over two decades ago to address such offenses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The program has seen every attorney general’s support, even the current one, Merrick Garland. Through this initiative, countless Americans have been sentenced to an average of 40 months in federal prison for similar gun charges. However, Hunter Biden’s treatment seems to diverge from these typical outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In his role, the former federal prosecutor has dealt with numerous firearms cases. Never has he seen a case with such compelling evidence being settled without charges. After sifting through data of over 189,000 illegal firearms possession cases, not one was found to be given an offer of diversion by the DOJ.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-controversial-sweetheart-deal&quot;&gt;The Controversial Sweetheart Deal&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It caused quite a stir when the DOJ tried to settle Hunter Biden’s case without bringing any charges and even proposed immunity for unrelated charges. But, thanks to a vigilant federal judge, that deal was stopped in its tracks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, weeks later, three indictments were filed against Hunter. These were for allegedly making false statements when buying a gun and for possessing a gun while being addicted to drugs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;more-evidence-awaiting-in-the-wings&quot;&gt;More Evidence Awaiting in the Wings?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There seems to be a treasure trove of evidence against Hunter Biden. An abandoned laptop, containing compromising emails, pictures, and videos, seems to point toward serious criminal activity. This, combined with testimony from a former business associate and revelations from House committee investigations, paints a grim picture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The available evidence seems to indicate the creation of fake companies, collaboration of co-conspirators, and a grand scheme to earn millions from foreign entities. Yet, the DOJ’s investigation seems to overlook these potential charges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-big-question&quot;&gt;The Big Question&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the evidence is as compelling as it appears, why aren’t Hunter and Joe Biden facing the level of scrutiny that others in similar situations have encountered? Many feel that there’s a false sense of security that they will never face serious consequences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Only time will tell if justice will prevail in its true form, or if a different set of rules applies to those in power.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Hunter Biden’s recent indictment has taken the nation by storm. However, what’s capturing even more attention is the seemingly lenient approach the Department of Justice (DOJ) is taking toward his case, especially when considering its historical hard stance on similar matters. The Surprising Treatment of a President’s Son Hunter Biden’s case isn’t just any case. He’s the first son of a sitting U.S. president to face criminal indictment. While it’s big news, insiders suggest that there’s more to come in this unfolding saga. A former federal prosecutor has expressed deep concern over how the DOJ has been conducting a five-year investigation into Hunter Biden’s case. The evidence pointing toward corruption and severe criminal actions appears evident. Comparing Hunter’s Case to Traditional DOJ Action Historically, the DOJ has been strict, particularly when dealing with firearms offenses. This approach is in line with the Project Safe Neighborhoods (PSN), an initiative established over two decades ago to address such offenses. The program has seen every attorney general’s support, even the current one, Merrick Garland. Through this initiative, countless Americans have been sentenced to an average of 40 months in federal prison for similar gun charges. However, Hunter Biden’s treatment seems to diverge from these typical outcomes. In his role, the former federal prosecutor has dealt with numerous firearms cases. Never has he seen a case with such compelling evidence being settled without charges. After sifting through data of over 189,000 illegal firearms possession cases, not one was found to be given an offer of diversion by the DOJ. The Controversial Sweetheart Deal It caused quite a stir when the DOJ tried to settle Hunter Biden’s case without bringing any charges and even proposed immunity for unrelated charges. But, thanks to a vigilant federal judge, that deal was stopped in its tracks. However, weeks later, three indictments were filed against Hunter. These were for allegedly making false statements when buying a gun and for possessing a gun while being addicted to drugs. More Evidence Awaiting in the Wings? There seems to be a treasure trove of evidence against Hunter Biden. An abandoned laptop, containing compromising emails, pictures, and videos, seems to point toward serious criminal activity. This, combined with testimony from a former business associate and revelations from House committee investigations, paints a grim picture. The available evidence seems to indicate the creation of fake companies, collaboration of co-conspirators, and a grand scheme to earn millions from foreign entities. Yet, the DOJ’s investigation seems to overlook these potential charges. The Big Question If the evidence is as compelling as it appears, why aren’t Hunter and Joe Biden facing the level of scrutiny that others in similar situations have encountered? Many feel that there’s a false sense of security that they will never face serious consequences. Only time will tell if justice will prevail in its true form, or if a different set of rules applies to those in power.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump Dominates New Hampshire, DeSantis Drops to Fifth</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/21/Trump-Leads-NH/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump Dominates New Hampshire, DeSantis Drops to Fifth" /><published>2023-09-21T09:07:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-21T09:07:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/21/Trump-Leads-NH</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/21/Trump-Leads-NH/">&lt;p&gt;In a twist of political fate, Former President Donald Trump has taken a strong lead in New Hampshire, while Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis has dramatically fallen to fifth place. This surprising turn was found in a recent CNN New Hampshire Primary Poll.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;trump-towers-in-the-granite-state&quot;&gt;Trump Towers in the Granite State&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to the poll, Trump leads the GOP primary race with an impressive 39% support. This places him a whopping 26 points ahead of the second contender, businessman Vivek Ramaswamy, who gathered 13% of the votes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nikki Haley, the former South Carolina Governor, wasn’t far behind Ramaswamy with 12% support. Former New Jersey Governor Chris Christie was next in line with 11%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;desantis-faces-a-setback&quot;&gt;DeSantis Faces a Setback&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perhaps the biggest news from the poll was DeSantis’s decline. After announcing earlier this summer that his campaign would focus on the first three states, including New Hampshire, the latest poll reveals he has only managed to garner 10% support, placing him fifth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This represents a significant 13-point dip from a survey conducted in July, where DeSantis was shown to have 23% support in New Hampshire. Changes in his campaign strategy, staff layoffs, and a change in campaign management may have contributed to this sharp decline.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-deeper-dive-into-voter-sentiments&quot;&gt;A Deeper Dive into Voter Sentiments&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The survey also shed light on the commitment of the voter base. A substantial 69% of Trump supporters stated they’re sure about supporting him, while only 18% of DeSantis supporters felt the same conviction for their candidate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When participants were questioned about which candidate they felt had the best chance to win the 2024 presidential general election, over half (51%) vouched for Trump. DeSantis lagged far behind with only 16% believing in his chances.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;in-conclusion&quot;&gt;In Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the political landscape can be unpredictable, this recent survey clearly indicates a shift in the wind. With DeSantis’s position dwindling in both national and state-wide polls, and Trump’s strong presence in New Hampshire, the 2024 GOP primary race is shaping up to be an intriguing one.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a twist of political fate, Former President Donald Trump has taken a strong lead in New Hampshire, while Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis has dramatically fallen to fifth place. This surprising turn was found in a recent CNN New Hampshire Primary Poll. Trump Towers in the Granite State According to the poll, Trump leads the GOP primary race with an impressive 39% support. This places him a whopping 26 points ahead of the second contender, businessman Vivek Ramaswamy, who gathered 13% of the votes. Nikki Haley, the former South Carolina Governor, wasn’t far behind Ramaswamy with 12% support. Former New Jersey Governor Chris Christie was next in line with 11%. DeSantis Faces a Setback Perhaps the biggest news from the poll was DeSantis’s decline. After announcing earlier this summer that his campaign would focus on the first three states, including New Hampshire, the latest poll reveals he has only managed to garner 10% support, placing him fifth. This represents a significant 13-point dip from a survey conducted in July, where DeSantis was shown to have 23% support in New Hampshire. Changes in his campaign strategy, staff layoffs, and a change in campaign management may have contributed to this sharp decline. A Deeper Dive into Voter Sentiments The survey also shed light on the commitment of the voter base. A substantial 69% of Trump supporters stated they’re sure about supporting him, while only 18% of DeSantis supporters felt the same conviction for their candidate. When participants were questioned about which candidate they felt had the best chance to win the 2024 presidential general election, over half (51%) vouched for Trump. DeSantis lagged far behind with only 16% believing in his chances. In Conclusion While the political landscape can be unpredictable, this recent survey clearly indicates a shift in the wind. With DeSantis’s position dwindling in both national and state-wide polls, and Trump’s strong presence in New Hampshire, the 2024 GOP primary race is shaping up to be an intriguing one.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Defending Gibson - Director Speaks Out on Casting Controversy</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/21/Defending-Gibson/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Defending Gibson - Director Speaks Out on Casting Controversy" /><published>2023-09-21T08:05:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-21T08:05:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/21/Defending-Gibson</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/21/Defending-Gibson/">&lt;p&gt;Amidst a wave of mixed reactions, Albert Hughes, the director of the new TV series “The Continental: From the World of John Wick”, is defending his choice to cast Mel Gibson. The series, a prequel to the successful “John Wick” films, features Gibson in the role of Cormac, the manager of the New York Continental.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;why-gibson&quot;&gt;Why Gibson?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I cast [Gibson] based on his past work that I grew up on,” Hughes said in a recent interview with the New York Post. He believes that fans will understand the casting decision once they see Gibson’s performance. “The personal stuff is not my business to talk about,” Hughes emphasized.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, not everyone is thrilled about the casting. Social media has been buzzing with reactions from fans, many of whom have strong opinions on Gibson due to his past controversies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2023/09/672/378/Mel_Gibson.jpg?ve=1&amp;amp;tl=1&quot; alt=&quot;Mel Gibson&quot; /&gt;(Kevin Winter/Getty Images)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“john wick without keanu (and with mel gibson) is not john wick at all,” shared one user on X, formerly known as Twitter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another added, “I can’t stomach watching Mel Gibson ever again.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But Hughes isn’t fazed by the social media chatter. He explained that the casting process in Hollywood often involves narrowing down from a list of big names, based on availability and response from agents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-controversial-past&quot;&gt;A Controversial Past&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gibson has been a contentious figure in Hollywood since his 2006 arrest for DUI. The incident became even more controversial due to Gibson’s antisemitic remarks during the arrest. Tapes from 2010 further tarnished his image, showcasing Gibson using racist language towards his then-girlfriend, Oksana Grigorieva.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the actor-director has since apologized, particularly for the antisemitic comments, saying, “There is no excuse, nor should there be any tolerance, for anyone who thinks or expresses any kind of antisemitic remark.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2023/09/672/378/Mel_Gibson_2.jpg?ve=1&amp;amp;tl=1&quot; alt=&quot;Mel Gibson&quot; /&gt;(Murray Close/Getty Images)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;whats-next&quot;&gt;What’s Next?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chad Stahelski, the director behind the “John Wick” films, serves as the executive producer for the new series. Though the show shares a universe with the films, Hughes assures fans that it offers a different perspective.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gibson’s presence in the series will undoubtedly continue to be a topic of debate among fans. But as the premiere date draws near, it remains to be seen whether the actor’s involvement will affect the show’s success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you plan on tuning in to “The Continental: From the World of John Wick”? Let us know your thoughts!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Amidst a wave of mixed reactions, Albert Hughes, the director of the new TV series “The Continental: From the World of John Wick”, is defending his choice to cast Mel Gibson. The series, a prequel to the successful “John Wick” films, features Gibson in the role of Cormac, the manager of the New York Continental. Why Gibson? “I cast [Gibson] based on his past work that I grew up on,” Hughes said in a recent interview with the New York Post. He believes that fans will understand the casting decision once they see Gibson’s performance. “The personal stuff is not my business to talk about,” Hughes emphasized. However, not everyone is thrilled about the casting. Social media has been buzzing with reactions from fans, many of whom have strong opinions on Gibson due to his past controversies. (Kevin Winter/Getty Images) “john wick without keanu (and with mel gibson) is not john wick at all,” shared one user on X, formerly known as Twitter. Another added, “I can’t stomach watching Mel Gibson ever again.” But Hughes isn’t fazed by the social media chatter. He explained that the casting process in Hollywood often involves narrowing down from a list of big names, based on availability and response from agents. A Controversial Past Gibson has been a contentious figure in Hollywood since his 2006 arrest for DUI. The incident became even more controversial due to Gibson’s antisemitic remarks during the arrest. Tapes from 2010 further tarnished his image, showcasing Gibson using racist language towards his then-girlfriend, Oksana Grigorieva. However, the actor-director has since apologized, particularly for the antisemitic comments, saying, “There is no excuse, nor should there be any tolerance, for anyone who thinks or expresses any kind of antisemitic remark.” (Murray Close/Getty Images) What’s Next? Chad Stahelski, the director behind the “John Wick” films, serves as the executive producer for the new series. Though the show shares a universe with the films, Hughes assures fans that it offers a different perspective. Gibson’s presence in the series will undoubtedly continue to be a topic of debate among fans. But as the premiere date draws near, it remains to be seen whether the actor’s involvement will affect the show’s success. Do you plan on tuning in to “The Continental: From the World of John Wick”? Let us know your thoughts!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Senator Cruz Foresees Michelle Obama’s Entry in 2024 Race</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/21/Cruz-Predicts/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Senator Cruz Foresees Michelle Obama’s Entry in 2024 Race" /><published>2023-09-21T07:02:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-21T07:02:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/21/Cruz-Predicts</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/21/Cruz-Predicts/">&lt;p&gt;Texas Senator Ted Cruz has sparked conversations with a bold prediction: the Democrats might opt for former First Lady Michelle Obama to replace President Joe Biden for the 2024 elections. According to Cruz, the Dems are getting increasingly “nervous” about Biden’s potential run.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-big-prediction&quot;&gt;The Big Prediction&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On his podcast, “Verdict with Ted Cruz”, the Senator voiced that the odds of Biden not getting the Democrat nomination have “risen significantly.” Citing reasons, he pointed to polling numbers indicating two-thirds of Americans believe Biden might be too old for presidency and emerging concerns about Biden’s connections and possible corruptions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cruz did not shy away from pointing fingers at the media. According to him, their changing stance on Biden signifies the Democrats’ contemplation of a potential change in leadership.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;michelle-obama---the-unexpected-game-changer&quot;&gt;Michelle Obama - The Unexpected Game-Changer?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the Democratic National Convention sees Biden’s “mental diminishment” become more evident, Cruz believes the platform will serve as a launching pad for Michelle Obama. His reasoning? Bringing in Michelle Obama would not alienate African American women voters - a significant constituent for the Democrats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Having served as the First Lady, Cruz argues that Michelle has the leverage to bypass other top Democratic contenders and could be viewed as the Obamas’ attempt to “save the day.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;behind-the-scenes&quot;&gt;Behind The Scenes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moreover, Cruz opined that former President Barack Obama might already be the unseen hand guiding the Biden administration. “I don’t think Joe Biden is the decision maker,” Cruz stated, suggesting Barack’s influential role. He warns that if media sentiment continues to turn on Biden, the chances of seeing Michelle Obama in the 2024 race could increase.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Considering a hypothetical scenario where Biden willingly steps down, Cruz joked that the Democrats might herald him as the “biggest hero” in their history.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;final-thoughts&quot;&gt;Final Thoughts&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Positioning Democrats as being “dynastic” and “command and control”, Cruz believes Michelle already holds a superior position within the Democratic hierarchy than most contenders. He concludes by suggesting that her nomination might be the “only solution” that doesn’t lead to internal strife within the party.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the political arena is unpredictable, Cruz’s observations offer an intriguing perspective on the potential future of American politics.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Texas Senator Ted Cruz has sparked conversations with a bold prediction: the Democrats might opt for former First Lady Michelle Obama to replace President Joe Biden for the 2024 elections. According to Cruz, the Dems are getting increasingly “nervous” about Biden’s potential run. The Big Prediction On his podcast, “Verdict with Ted Cruz”, the Senator voiced that the odds of Biden not getting the Democrat nomination have “risen significantly.” Citing reasons, he pointed to polling numbers indicating two-thirds of Americans believe Biden might be too old for presidency and emerging concerns about Biden’s connections and possible corruptions. Cruz did not shy away from pointing fingers at the media. According to him, their changing stance on Biden signifies the Democrats’ contemplation of a potential change in leadership. Michelle Obama - The Unexpected Game-Changer? If the Democratic National Convention sees Biden’s “mental diminishment” become more evident, Cruz believes the platform will serve as a launching pad for Michelle Obama. His reasoning? Bringing in Michelle Obama would not alienate African American women voters - a significant constituent for the Democrats. Having served as the First Lady, Cruz argues that Michelle has the leverage to bypass other top Democratic contenders and could be viewed as the Obamas’ attempt to “save the day.” Behind The Scenes Moreover, Cruz opined that former President Barack Obama might already be the unseen hand guiding the Biden administration. “I don’t think Joe Biden is the decision maker,” Cruz stated, suggesting Barack’s influential role. He warns that if media sentiment continues to turn on Biden, the chances of seeing Michelle Obama in the 2024 race could increase. Considering a hypothetical scenario where Biden willingly steps down, Cruz joked that the Democrats might herald him as the “biggest hero” in their history. Final Thoughts Positioning Democrats as being “dynastic” and “command and control”, Cruz believes Michelle already holds a superior position within the Democratic hierarchy than most contenders. He concludes by suggesting that her nomination might be the “only solution” that doesn’t lead to internal strife within the party. While the political arena is unpredictable, Cruz’s observations offer an intriguing perspective on the potential future of American politics.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Future Generations at Risk? The Potential Effects of Aspartame</title><link href="/news/2023/09/21/Aspartame-Study-Effects/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Future Generations at Risk? The Potential Effects of Aspartame" /><published>2023-09-21T06:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-21T06:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/21/Aspartame-Study-Effects</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/21/Aspartame-Study-Effects/">&lt;p&gt;Aspartame, a widespread zero-calorie sweetener, is making headlines again. A study from Florida State University (FSU) College of Medicine indicates potential links between the sweetener and memory or learning challenges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;unpacking-the-study&quot;&gt;Unpacking the Study&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Researchers from FSU carried out a 16-week experiment on mice. Three groups were set up:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;One consumed 15% of the FDA’s daily recommended maximum intake of aspartame (like drinking four 8-oz. sodas).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The second group had 7% of the recommended maximum (equivalent to two 8-oz. sodas daily).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A control group only drank water.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Throughout the experiment, the mice underwent maze tests. The results? Mice that consumed water found their way out much quicker than their aspartame-drinking counterparts. Those consuming aspartame did finish, but they struggled and often needed extra assistance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2023/09/672/378/mice-in-maze.jpg?ve=1&amp;amp;tl=1&quot; alt=&quot;Mice in a Maze&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Mice navigating through a maze. The aspartame consumers had a tougher time.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;findings-and-concerns&quot;&gt;Findings and Concerns&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The study’s co-author, Pradeep Bhide, shed light on the emotional connection between memory and learning. He emphasized the unique nature of the findings, pointing out that only the children (and not the grandchildren) of the male mice showed these effects. This suggests epigenetic changes in the sperm might be responsible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With these results in mind, Bhide proposed a more in-depth, multi-generational investigation of aspartame by the FDA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earlier in June, the World Health Organization made waves by categorizing aspartame as “possibly carcinogenic to humans”. While industry experts refuted this claim, the WHO hasn’t touched on the cognitive implications highlighted by FSU’s recent findings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dr. Kelly Johnson-Arbor, a Washington, D.C.-based medical toxicology physician, weighed in. She remarked on the study’s implications: potential hereditary memory and learning problems stemming from even minimal aspartame consumption. But she also added a note of caution, stating more research is necessary to firmly establish this connection.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;to-drink-or-not-to-drink&quot;&gt;To Drink or Not to Drink?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Industry leaders have stepped forward to defend aspartame. The Calorie Control Council’s president, Robert Rankin, emphasized that the study’s results should not be generalized to humans. He cited the vast body of evidence and global health organizations that deem aspartame safe after rigorous evaluations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the debate rages on, the FSU study has certainly added a new layer to the conversation surrounding artificial sweeteners and their potential effects. As research continues, consumers might consider limiting their intake or staying updated with the latest findings to make informed choices.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Aspartame, a widespread zero-calorie sweetener, is making headlines again. A study from Florida State University (FSU) College of Medicine indicates potential links between the sweetener and memory or learning challenges. Unpacking the Study Researchers from FSU carried out a 16-week experiment on mice. Three groups were set up: One consumed 15% of the FDA’s daily recommended maximum intake of aspartame (like drinking four 8-oz. sodas). The second group had 7% of the recommended maximum (equivalent to two 8-oz. sodas daily). A control group only drank water. Throughout the experiment, the mice underwent maze tests. The results? Mice that consumed water found their way out much quicker than their aspartame-drinking counterparts. Those consuming aspartame did finish, but they struggled and often needed extra assistance. Mice navigating through a maze. The aspartame consumers had a tougher time. Findings and Concerns The study’s co-author, Pradeep Bhide, shed light on the emotional connection between memory and learning. He emphasized the unique nature of the findings, pointing out that only the children (and not the grandchildren) of the male mice showed these effects. This suggests epigenetic changes in the sperm might be responsible. With these results in mind, Bhide proposed a more in-depth, multi-generational investigation of aspartame by the FDA. Earlier in June, the World Health Organization made waves by categorizing aspartame as “possibly carcinogenic to humans”. While industry experts refuted this claim, the WHO hasn’t touched on the cognitive implications highlighted by FSU’s recent findings. Dr. Kelly Johnson-Arbor, a Washington, D.C.-based medical toxicology physician, weighed in. She remarked on the study’s implications: potential hereditary memory and learning problems stemming from even minimal aspartame consumption. But she also added a note of caution, stating more research is necessary to firmly establish this connection. To Drink or Not to Drink? Industry leaders have stepped forward to defend aspartame. The Calorie Control Council’s president, Robert Rankin, emphasized that the study’s results should not be generalized to humans. He cited the vast body of evidence and global health organizations that deem aspartame safe after rigorous evaluations. While the debate rages on, the FSU study has certainly added a new layer to the conversation surrounding artificial sweeteners and their potential effects. As research continues, consumers might consider limiting their intake or staying updated with the latest findings to make informed choices.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Texas Representative Takes Stand Against Gun Restrictions</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/20/Protecting-Gun-Rights/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Texas Representative Takes Stand Against Gun Restrictions" /><published>2023-09-20T17:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-20T17:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/20/Protecting-Gun-Rights</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/20/Protecting-Gun-Rights/">&lt;p&gt;In response to what some are calling aggressive moves by the left, Texas Representative Michael Cloud is stepping up to safeguard the rights of gun owners. On Tuesday, he reintroduced the “Protecting the Right To Keep and Bear Arms Act”. This legislation, if passed, would restrict the president and the Department of Health and Human Services (HHS) from using public health emergencies as a means to enforce gun control measures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;second-amendment-under-fire&quot;&gt;Second Amendment Under Fire?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vice President Kamala Harris recently expressed her support for the Second Amendment on “The Jennifer Hudson Show”. However, her endorsement for an assault weapons ban in the same conversation has raised eyebrows among conservatives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, Michael Cloud has expressed concern over the strategies of the ‘radical left’. “For a long time, radical left politicians have been open about their willingness to use executive authority and rob Americans of their Second Amendment rights,” Cloud stated, pointing out the need for his reintroduced bill.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The catalyst for such statements and actions is clear. Last week, New Mexico’s Democratic Governor, Michelle Lujan Grisham, declared gun violence as a public health crisis and attempted to implement a 30-day prohibition on carrying firearms in public spaces and on state-owned properties in Albuquerque. Cloud did not hold back in his criticism, “The Biden administration, Gov. Grisham, and others have exercised extraordinary executive power to push their liberal agenda and expand the power of the government.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-response&quot;&gt;The Response&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Grisham’s bold move faced swift resistance. A judge promptly blocked the proposed 30-day gun ban. In turn, Grisham adjusted her rule to limit firearms at public parks or playgrounds, specifically mentioning areas “where we know we have high risk of kids and families.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many, including Aidan Johnston, director of federal affairs for Gun Owners of America, have voiced their concerns. Johnston noted that Grisham’s utilization of a ‘public health emergency’ to suspend the Second Amendment is a troubling instance of officials potentially misusing ‘emergency powers’ to infringe on constitutional rights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In light of these concerns, Rep. Pete Sessions and Rep. Mary Miller have also shown their support for Cloud’s bill, emphasizing the importance of preserving the rights of gun owners.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-bigger-picture&quot;&gt;The Bigger Picture&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This isn’t the first time gun violence has been referred to as a “public health crisis.” Earlier this year, Health and Human Services Secretary Xavier Becerra used the term after a mass shooting in Atlanta. Prior to that, officials in California had made similar appeals to label gun violence as a public health emergency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a polarized political climate, the debate over gun rights and gun control continues to intensify. With representatives like Michael Cloud taking a stand, the future of the Second Amendment remains a fiercely contested topic in the United States.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In response to what some are calling aggressive moves by the left, Texas Representative Michael Cloud is stepping up to safeguard the rights of gun owners. On Tuesday, he reintroduced the “Protecting the Right To Keep and Bear Arms Act”. This legislation, if passed, would restrict the president and the Department of Health and Human Services (HHS) from using public health emergencies as a means to enforce gun control measures. Second Amendment Under Fire? Vice President Kamala Harris recently expressed her support for the Second Amendment on “The Jennifer Hudson Show”. However, her endorsement for an assault weapons ban in the same conversation has raised eyebrows among conservatives. Meanwhile, Michael Cloud has expressed concern over the strategies of the ‘radical left’. “For a long time, radical left politicians have been open about their willingness to use executive authority and rob Americans of their Second Amendment rights,” Cloud stated, pointing out the need for his reintroduced bill. The catalyst for such statements and actions is clear. Last week, New Mexico’s Democratic Governor, Michelle Lujan Grisham, declared gun violence as a public health crisis and attempted to implement a 30-day prohibition on carrying firearms in public spaces and on state-owned properties in Albuquerque. Cloud did not hold back in his criticism, “The Biden administration, Gov. Grisham, and others have exercised extraordinary executive power to push their liberal agenda and expand the power of the government.” The Response Grisham’s bold move faced swift resistance. A judge promptly blocked the proposed 30-day gun ban. In turn, Grisham adjusted her rule to limit firearms at public parks or playgrounds, specifically mentioning areas “where we know we have high risk of kids and families.” Many, including Aidan Johnston, director of federal affairs for Gun Owners of America, have voiced their concerns. Johnston noted that Grisham’s utilization of a ‘public health emergency’ to suspend the Second Amendment is a troubling instance of officials potentially misusing ‘emergency powers’ to infringe on constitutional rights. In light of these concerns, Rep. Pete Sessions and Rep. Mary Miller have also shown their support for Cloud’s bill, emphasizing the importance of preserving the rights of gun owners. The Bigger Picture This isn’t the first time gun violence has been referred to as a “public health crisis.” Earlier this year, Health and Human Services Secretary Xavier Becerra used the term after a mass shooting in Atlanta. Prior to that, officials in California had made similar appeals to label gun violence as a public health emergency. In a polarized political climate, the debate over gun rights and gun control continues to intensify. With representatives like Michael Cloud taking a stand, the future of the Second Amendment remains a fiercely contested topic in the United States.</summary></entry></feed>