<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-11-09T01:20:14-05:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/11/09/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-11-09T01:20:14-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-09T01:20:14-05:00</updated><id>/2023/11/09/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/11/09/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/11/09/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-11-09T01:20:14-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-09T01:20:14-05:00</updated><id>/2023/11/09/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/11/09/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/">&lt;p&gt;Recent surprise attacks by Hamas on Israel has fueled ongoing tensions between staunchly conservative commentators and the progressive “Squad” Democrats known for criticizing Israel. The intensity of the backlash highlights the deep political divide over foreign policy in the Middle East.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Hamas’ shocking attack, several members of the “Squad,” including Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.), called for a “ceasefire and de-escalation,” condemning the violence. The absence of a statement from Rep. Rashida Tlaib (D-Mich.) was notably called out by conservative media outlets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;South Carolina GOP Rep. Nancy Mace quickly labeled Ocasio-Cortez a “Hamas apologist” in response to her call for peace and de-escalation. Rep. Ilhan Omar (D-Minn.), no stranger to controversy surrounding her views on Israel, echoed the call for de-escalation and ceasefire. Omar’s prior statements comparing the US and Israel to terrorist groups like Hamas and the Taliban resurfaced in the debate, fueling more criticisms. Omar’s 2019 tweet, where she opined that “Israel has hypnotized the world,” also continues to haunt her political career, often cited by critics to challenge her stance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conservative commentators have been especially vocal. “FOX &amp;amp; Friends Weekend” co-host Rachel Campos-Duffy took aim at Omar, saying she fails to recognize the peace in the Middle East under Trump’s administration. Conservative pundit John Hasson also called out Omar, claiming she insinuated that attacks on IDF forces were acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Massachusetts Democrat Rep. Ayanna Pressley’s concerns over the “devastating attacks on Israelis” were met with skepticism. A prominent conservative online personality, Comfortably Smug, accused the “Squad” of advising Israel to back down after the nation suffered massive attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Jamaal Bowman’s call for an end to the Gaza blockade, in addition to condemning the Hamas attacks, was met with criticism from conservative radio host Jason Rantz. He accused Bowman of pairing his condemnation of terrorism with unwarranted criticisms of Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Cori Bush emphasized the urgent need for a ceasefire, while pushing for an end to “U.S. support for Israeli military occupation and apartheid.” Defense attorney Marina Medvin criticized Bush, suggesting that she equates the death of Palestinian terrorists to the horrific acts committed against Jewish civilians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amidst the political turmoil and intense debate, the attacks have taken a heavy toll. Israeli media report over 300 dead due to the wide-ranging assault. Gaza health officials note that at least 200 Palestinians have perished in the retaliatory Israeli air strikes following the initial Hamas attack. As the situation remains volatile, both sides continue to count their casualties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This divisive issue showcases the challenge America faces in crafting a unified approach to foreign policy, with deeply entrenched political divides at play. As the situation develops, the debate is bound to intensify, shedding light on the complexities of U.S. politics in the global arena.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">House GOP Votes to Slash Transportation Secretary’s Paycheck to a Single Dollar</title><link href="/news/2023/11/08/Buttigieg-Salary-Cut/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="House GOP Votes to Slash Transportation Secretary’s Paycheck to a Single Dollar" /><published>2023-11-08T19:45:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-08T19:45:00-05:00</updated><id>/news/2023/11/08/Buttigieg-Salary-Cut</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/11/08/Buttigieg-Salary-Cut/">&lt;p&gt;In a bold statement of disapproval, House Republicans have taken a swipe at Transportation Secretary Pete Buttigieg by pushing forward an amendment to trim his salary down to a mere dollar. The measure, led by Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene of Georgia, reflects growing Republican discontent with Buttigieg’s handling of transportation issues and use of public funds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Greene, known for her fiery rhetoric and no-holds-barred approach, spearheaded the initiative as part of the 2024 Transportation, Housing, and Urban Development Appropriations Act. The amendment, which passed through a voice vote, has been framed as a means to effectively “fire” Buttigieg from his position, an outcome Greene suggests is warranted due to his alleged misuse of taxpayer dollars.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Republican lawmaker took to social media to air her grievances, where she criticized Buttigieg for what she perceives as staged photo ops and the misuse of government aircraft for personal travel, including attending events for LGBTQ rights awards. Greene’s assertion is that Buttigieg’s actions are an undue financial burden on American taxpayers who should not be responsible for funding these trips or his salary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The vote to cut Buttigieg’s salary to one dollar is largely symbolic, reflecting the House GOP’s dissatisfaction with what they see as failures and mismanagement during his tenure as transportation secretary. One of the most contentious issues is Buttigieg’s response to the toxic train derailment in East Palestine, Ohio. His delayed response to the crisis drew ire from the public and lawmakers alike, raising questions about his leadership in managing the nation’s transportation challenges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Buttigieg’s use of private jets has also come under scrutiny. Reports indicate that he has used government-managed private aircraft for travel numerous times since assuming office, drawing criticism for opting for private flights amidst widespread commercial flight cancellations and delays.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s worth noting, however, that the amendment’s passage does not guarantee a change in Buttigieg’s salary. The House GOP’s spending bills, laden with partisan goals, must contend with a Democratic-controlled Senate and an executive branch unlikely to endorse a pay cut for one of its cabinet members. Thus, while the move reflects House Republicans’ stance, it faces an uphill battle to materialize into actual policy change.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the debate over Buttigieg’s salary unfolds, it underscores the broader political tensions between the current administration and Republican lawmakers who are eager to reverse policies and decisions they deem ineffective or extravagant. The symbolic dollar salary is a sharp critique from the GOP, illustrating their intent to hold Cabinet members accountable for their performance and fiscal responsibility.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a bold statement of disapproval, House Republicans have taken a swipe at Transportation Secretary Pete Buttigieg by pushing forward an amendment to trim his salary down to a mere dollar. The measure, led by Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene of Georgia, reflects growing Republican discontent with Buttigieg’s handling of transportation issues and use of public funds. Greene, known for her fiery rhetoric and no-holds-barred approach, spearheaded the initiative as part of the 2024 Transportation, Housing, and Urban Development Appropriations Act. The amendment, which passed through a voice vote, has been framed as a means to effectively “fire” Buttigieg from his position, an outcome Greene suggests is warranted due to his alleged misuse of taxpayer dollars. The Republican lawmaker took to social media to air her grievances, where she criticized Buttigieg for what she perceives as staged photo ops and the misuse of government aircraft for personal travel, including attending events for LGBTQ rights awards. Greene’s assertion is that Buttigieg’s actions are an undue financial burden on American taxpayers who should not be responsible for funding these trips or his salary. The vote to cut Buttigieg’s salary to one dollar is largely symbolic, reflecting the House GOP’s dissatisfaction with what they see as failures and mismanagement during his tenure as transportation secretary. One of the most contentious issues is Buttigieg’s response to the toxic train derailment in East Palestine, Ohio. His delayed response to the crisis drew ire from the public and lawmakers alike, raising questions about his leadership in managing the nation’s transportation challenges. Buttigieg’s use of private jets has also come under scrutiny. Reports indicate that he has used government-managed private aircraft for travel numerous times since assuming office, drawing criticism for opting for private flights amidst widespread commercial flight cancellations and delays. It’s worth noting, however, that the amendment’s passage does not guarantee a change in Buttigieg’s salary. The House GOP’s spending bills, laden with partisan goals, must contend with a Democratic-controlled Senate and an executive branch unlikely to endorse a pay cut for one of its cabinet members. Thus, while the move reflects House Republicans’ stance, it faces an uphill battle to materialize into actual policy change. As the debate over Buttigieg’s salary unfolds, it underscores the broader political tensions between the current administration and Republican lawmakers who are eager to reverse policies and decisions they deem ineffective or extravagant. The symbolic dollar salary is a sharp critique from the GOP, illustrating their intent to hold Cabinet members accountable for their performance and fiscal responsibility.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Kat Von D’s Awakening: Celebrity Tattoo Artist Speaks Out on Extremism</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/11/08/Reflections-of-Kat-Von-D/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Kat Von D’s Awakening: Celebrity Tattoo Artist Speaks Out on Extremism" /><published>2023-11-08T17:53:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-08T17:53:00-05:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/11/08/Reflections-of-Kat-Von-D</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/11/08/Reflections-of-Kat-Von-D/">&lt;p&gt;Celebrity tattoo artist Kat Von D has shared a candid look into the personal transformation that led her to re-evaluate her beliefs amidst the race riots of 2020. Witnessing firsthand the tumult caused by Black Lives Matter and Antifa in Los Angeles, Von D confided that the reality of these events was “much worse” than the broadcasted narratives, prompting a significant shift in her religious and political convictions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During a heartfelt interview on the “Relatable” podcast with host Allie Beth Stuckey, Von D reflected on her life in the epicenter of the violent, left-wing riots that rocked the city. The artist, who lived a stone’s throw away from the mayor’s residence, experienced Antifa’s threats up close. The gravity of these moments pierced through the veil of media representation, revealing a harsher truth that spurred her to question the path she was on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The journey of self-discovery and spiritual awakening saw Von D turn away from her former occult practices and find solace in a Baptist church in Indiana. Last month, she took to social media to share the profound moment of her baptism, signaling a new chapter in her life. Her transformative experiences have not only altered her personal views but have also reshaped her role as a wife and mother, as she distances herself from past allurements that now repulse her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kat Von D’s revelations strike a chord with many who have found themselves disillusioned by extreme ideologies. Her story is a testament to the power of personal transformation and the courage it takes to break free from the echo chambers that often cloud judgment. As she embraces her newfound path, Von D expresses a heartfelt wish to articulate the depth of the positive changes she’s undergone, changes that have redefined her identity and purpose.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her candid discussion provides a stark reminder of the complex layers behind public figures and the pivotal experiences that can lead to profound personal evolutions. As Von D steps forward in her journey, she not only sheds the ink of her past but also the ideological bindings, emerging with a fresh perspective that celebrates growth, change, and the pursuit of authenticity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those watching, Kat Von D’s metamorphosis is not just a tale of personal rebirth but a narrative that challenges perceptions, urging others to look beyond the screen and question the world around them. As she continues to navigate her path, her story of reclamation and redemption is set to inspire others to seek their own truths in an ever-changing landscape.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Celebrity tattoo artist Kat Von D has shared a candid look into the personal transformation that led her to re-evaluate her beliefs amidst the race riots of 2020. Witnessing firsthand the tumult caused by Black Lives Matter and Antifa in Los Angeles, Von D confided that the reality of these events was “much worse” than the broadcasted narratives, prompting a significant shift in her religious and political convictions. During a heartfelt interview on the “Relatable” podcast with host Allie Beth Stuckey, Von D reflected on her life in the epicenter of the violent, left-wing riots that rocked the city. The artist, who lived a stone’s throw away from the mayor’s residence, experienced Antifa’s threats up close. The gravity of these moments pierced through the veil of media representation, revealing a harsher truth that spurred her to question the path she was on. The journey of self-discovery and spiritual awakening saw Von D turn away from her former occult practices and find solace in a Baptist church in Indiana. Last month, she took to social media to share the profound moment of her baptism, signaling a new chapter in her life. Her transformative experiences have not only altered her personal views but have also reshaped her role as a wife and mother, as she distances herself from past allurements that now repulse her. Kat Von D’s revelations strike a chord with many who have found themselves disillusioned by extreme ideologies. Her story is a testament to the power of personal transformation and the courage it takes to break free from the echo chambers that often cloud judgment. As she embraces her newfound path, Von D expresses a heartfelt wish to articulate the depth of the positive changes she’s undergone, changes that have redefined her identity and purpose. Her candid discussion provides a stark reminder of the complex layers behind public figures and the pivotal experiences that can lead to profound personal evolutions. As Von D steps forward in her journey, she not only sheds the ink of her past but also the ideological bindings, emerging with a fresh perspective that celebrates growth, change, and the pursuit of authenticity. For those watching, Kat Von D’s metamorphosis is not just a tale of personal rebirth but a narrative that challenges perceptions, urging others to look beyond the screen and question the world around them. As she continues to navigate her path, her story of reclamation and redemption is set to inspire others to seek their own truths in an ever-changing landscape.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Susanna Gibson’s Controversial Campaign Ends in Defeat in Virginia</title><link href="/politics/2023/11/08/Virginia-Election-Outcome/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Susanna Gibson’s Controversial Campaign Ends in Defeat in Virginia" /><published>2023-11-08T16:33:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-08T16:33:00-05:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/11/08/Virginia-Election-Outcome</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/11/08/Virginia-Election-Outcome/">&lt;p&gt;In a victory for traditional values and a rebuke of scandal-plagued politics, Republican David Owen has clinched a narrow win over Democrat Susanna Gibson in the race for Virginia House District 57. The election was marked by the controversy that enveloped Gibson’s campaign after reports of her involvement in online sexual content came to light.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Susanna Gibson’s campaign, overshadowed by her own actions on livestreaming platforms, ended not with the triumph she had hoped for, but with the electorate decisively turning their backs on her bid for office. Despite Gibson’s attempts to deflect the scandal as a political attack, it was her decisions that ultimately led voters to question her judgment and suitability for public office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Associated Press called the race for Owen, signaling a clear preference for a candidate who steered clear of the personal controversies that plagued his opponent. Gibson, a 40-year-old nurse practitioner and mother of two, found herself at the center of a media storm after The Washington Post’s report on her participation in explicit livestreams.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gibson’s attempt to remain in the race, even after the revelations, sparked intense debate within the district. Her insistence that the scandal was an “illegal invasion” of her privacy and a tactic to “silence women” did little to sway public opinion in her favor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Republican Party of Virginia took a firm stance on reminding voters of Gibson’s choices, distributing mailers that highlighted the issue. Their strategy was clear: to ensure that voters were fully informed about the character and conduct of the Democratic candidate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a district that the nonpartisan Virginia Public Access Project had rated as highly competitive, the outcome of this election sends a strong message about the values and expectations voters hold for their elected officials. The electorate’s decision suggests a repudiation of behavior they deemed unbecoming of a public servant, choosing instead to support a candidate who maintained a focus on policy and public service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gibson’s defeat in this closely watched race may serve as a cautionary tale for future candidates, underscoring the importance of personal conduct in the public’s evaluation of their potential leaders. As the dust settles on this contentious campaign, the voters of Virginia House District 57 have made their stance clear, opting for a representative who embodies the principles they wish to see in their government.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the Republican victor prepares to take office, the community looks forward to leadership that can move beyond the tumult of the campaign and focus on addressing the pressing issues facing Virginians today.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a victory for traditional values and a rebuke of scandal-plagued politics, Republican David Owen has clinched a narrow win over Democrat Susanna Gibson in the race for Virginia House District 57. The election was marked by the controversy that enveloped Gibson’s campaign after reports of her involvement in online sexual content came to light. Susanna Gibson’s campaign, overshadowed by her own actions on livestreaming platforms, ended not with the triumph she had hoped for, but with the electorate decisively turning their backs on her bid for office. Despite Gibson’s attempts to deflect the scandal as a political attack, it was her decisions that ultimately led voters to question her judgment and suitability for public office. The Associated Press called the race for Owen, signaling a clear preference for a candidate who steered clear of the personal controversies that plagued his opponent. Gibson, a 40-year-old nurse practitioner and mother of two, found herself at the center of a media storm after The Washington Post’s report on her participation in explicit livestreams. Gibson’s attempt to remain in the race, even after the revelations, sparked intense debate within the district. Her insistence that the scandal was an “illegal invasion” of her privacy and a tactic to “silence women” did little to sway public opinion in her favor. The Republican Party of Virginia took a firm stance on reminding voters of Gibson’s choices, distributing mailers that highlighted the issue. Their strategy was clear: to ensure that voters were fully informed about the character and conduct of the Democratic candidate. In a district that the nonpartisan Virginia Public Access Project had rated as highly competitive, the outcome of this election sends a strong message about the values and expectations voters hold for their elected officials. The electorate’s decision suggests a repudiation of behavior they deemed unbecoming of a public servant, choosing instead to support a candidate who maintained a focus on policy and public service. Gibson’s defeat in this closely watched race may serve as a cautionary tale for future candidates, underscoring the importance of personal conduct in the public’s evaluation of their potential leaders. As the dust settles on this contentious campaign, the voters of Virginia House District 57 have made their stance clear, opting for a representative who embodies the principles they wish to see in their government. As the Republican victor prepares to take office, the community looks forward to leadership that can move beyond the tumult of the campaign and focus on addressing the pressing issues facing Virginians today.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump Cites McConnell’s ‘Stench’ in Cameron’s Kentucky Loss</title><link href="/politics/2023/11/08/Trump-McConnell-Stench/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump Cites McConnell’s ‘Stench’ in Cameron’s Kentucky Loss" /><published>2023-11-08T14:35:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-08T14:35:00-05:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/11/08/Trump-McConnell-Stench</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/11/08/Trump-McConnell-Stench/">&lt;p&gt;In the wake of the Republican Daniel Cameron’s defeat in Kentucky’s gubernatorial race, former President Donald Trump has pointed the finger at Senate Minority Leader Mitch McConnell’s influence as the pivotal factor that tipped the scales against the GOP candidate. Trump’s remarks have stirred the pot within Republican circles, as the party grapples with the unexpected loss in a state that has shown strong Republican leanings in recent elections.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump, who had endorsed Cameron, took to social media to express his views on the election’s outcome, stating, “Daniel Cameron lost because he couldn’t alleviate the stench of Mitch McConnell. I told him early that’s a big burden to overcome.” The former President’s assertion is that Cameron’s association with McConnell, who has faced growing dissatisfaction from the Republican base, significantly hampered his campaign.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The loss has sent shockwaves through the Republican establishment, with some party members calling for a leadership shuffle, including the resignation of Republican National Committee (RNC) Chairwoman Ronna McDaniel. Others within the party, notably those aligned with the Never Trump movement, have suggested that the Kentucky race signals a broader shift away from the MAGA brand within the GOP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, Trump remains steadfast in his belief that McConnell’s negative reputation among the conservative base was the albatross around Cameron’s neck, rather than any reflection on Trump’s influence or the strength of the MAGA movement. Trump emphasized this by contrasting Cameron’s loss with the victory of Mississippi Gov. Tate Reeves, whom Trump also supported. “I moved him up 25 Points, but the McConnell relationship was ‘too much to bear,’” Trump commented on Reeves’ successful re-election.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the GOP navigates this post-election landscape, Trump’s comments underscore the intra-party tensions and the ongoing debate over the direction of the Republican Party. With the 2024 presidential election on the horizon, how the party responds to these internal challenges could shape its strategy and identity in the lead-up to the next electoral cycle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, McConnell, a long-serving figure in the Senate and a key architect of the party’s legislative strategy, has yet to respond to Trump’s remarks. As Republican leaders and voters reflect on the Kentucky election results, the conversation about McConnell’s role and influence within the party is likely to intensify, potentially impacting future endorsements and campaign strategies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For now, the GOP faces a moment of introspection as it seeks to unite its factions and prepare for the next round of political contests, with Trump’s voice remaining a powerful force in shaping the narrative and direction of the party.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In the wake of the Republican Daniel Cameron’s defeat in Kentucky’s gubernatorial race, former President Donald Trump has pointed the finger at Senate Minority Leader Mitch McConnell’s influence as the pivotal factor that tipped the scales against the GOP candidate. Trump’s remarks have stirred the pot within Republican circles, as the party grapples with the unexpected loss in a state that has shown strong Republican leanings in recent elections. Trump, who had endorsed Cameron, took to social media to express his views on the election’s outcome, stating, “Daniel Cameron lost because he couldn’t alleviate the stench of Mitch McConnell. I told him early that’s a big burden to overcome.” The former President’s assertion is that Cameron’s association with McConnell, who has faced growing dissatisfaction from the Republican base, significantly hampered his campaign. The loss has sent shockwaves through the Republican establishment, with some party members calling for a leadership shuffle, including the resignation of Republican National Committee (RNC) Chairwoman Ronna McDaniel. Others within the party, notably those aligned with the Never Trump movement, have suggested that the Kentucky race signals a broader shift away from the MAGA brand within the GOP. However, Trump remains steadfast in his belief that McConnell’s negative reputation among the conservative base was the albatross around Cameron’s neck, rather than any reflection on Trump’s influence or the strength of the MAGA movement. Trump emphasized this by contrasting Cameron’s loss with the victory of Mississippi Gov. Tate Reeves, whom Trump also supported. “I moved him up 25 Points, but the McConnell relationship was ‘too much to bear,’” Trump commented on Reeves’ successful re-election. As the GOP navigates this post-election landscape, Trump’s comments underscore the intra-party tensions and the ongoing debate over the direction of the Republican Party. With the 2024 presidential election on the horizon, how the party responds to these internal challenges could shape its strategy and identity in the lead-up to the next electoral cycle. Meanwhile, McConnell, a long-serving figure in the Senate and a key architect of the party’s legislative strategy, has yet to respond to Trump’s remarks. As Republican leaders and voters reflect on the Kentucky election results, the conversation about McConnell’s role and influence within the party is likely to intensify, potentially impacting future endorsements and campaign strategies. For now, the GOP faces a moment of introspection as it seeks to unite its factions and prepare for the next round of political contests, with Trump’s voice remaining a powerful force in shaping the narrative and direction of the party.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Supreme Court Leans Toward Upholding Gun Ban for Domestic Violence Restraining Orders</title><link href="/politics/2023/11/08/Supreme-Court-Gun-Law/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Supreme Court Leans Toward Upholding Gun Ban for Domestic Violence Restraining Orders" /><published>2023-11-08T06:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-08T06:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/11/08/Supreme-Court-Gun-Law</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/11/08/Supreme-Court-Gun-Law/">&lt;p&gt;The Supreme Court signaled support for maintaining a federal law that restricts gun ownership for individuals with domestic violence restraining orders. This stance emerged during a session where justices engaged in a rigorous oral argument, dissecting the intricacies of the Second Amendment and its application in contemporary society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The case in question, U.S. v. Rahimi, could have extensive repercussions, stretching its influence to various gun rights legislations and potentially affecting the ongoing legal battle faced by Hunter Biden. The son of the President, Biden is gearing up to challenge a federal indictment which alleges he lied about his drug addiction when acquiring a firearm in 2018.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Texas man central to the Supreme Court case, Zackey Rahimi, faced charges stemming from multiple incidents involving firearms, leading to a restraining order that prohibited him from possessing a gun. His appeal put into question the constitutionality of such federal restrictions, arguing that they contravene his right to self-defense as afforded by the Second Amendment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the discussions, Justice Elena Kagan and others stressed the government’s rationale that history has shown the necessity of keeping firearms from individuals deemed dangerous. Such a viewpoint finds support across the Court’s ideological spectrum, including the more conservative justices, suggesting a potential consensus for upholding the existing ban.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chief Justice John Roberts, however, expressed concerns over the breadth of the term “irresponsible” when applied to gun ownership, hinting at the subjective nature of deeming someone unfit to bear arms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The background of the case paints a troubling picture of Rahimi’s repeated violations of the protective order, including brandishing weapons and threatening behavior. These actions did not escape the Court’s attention, with even the conservative justices questioning Rahimi’s suitability to possess firearms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the courthouse steps, demonstrators rallied, with the majority advocating for stricter gun control, reflecting the national conversation on gun violence following recent tragic events.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Supreme Court’s eventual decision will likely be nuanced, focusing narrowly on the legitimacy of denying guns to those with a documented history of violence. Yet, it will set a critical precedent for future Second Amendment challenges and provide guidance for lower courts currently navigating the complex legal landscape post the landmark 2022 ruling, which expanded gun rights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The outcome will be closely watched by all, from legal scholars to policymakers to everyday citizens, as it will not only impact public safety and individual rights but also resonate through the ongoing societal debate about the balance between liberty and protection.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the nation awaits the Court’s ruling, due by the summer of 2024, the significance of this case extends beyond the legal arguments presented—it embodies the enduring struggle to reconcile the foundational principles of the Constitution with the pressing demands of modern governance.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">The Supreme Court signaled support for maintaining a federal law that restricts gun ownership for individuals with domestic violence restraining orders. This stance emerged during a session where justices engaged in a rigorous oral argument, dissecting the intricacies of the Second Amendment and its application in contemporary society. The case in question, U.S. v. Rahimi, could have extensive repercussions, stretching its influence to various gun rights legislations and potentially affecting the ongoing legal battle faced by Hunter Biden. The son of the President, Biden is gearing up to challenge a federal indictment which alleges he lied about his drug addiction when acquiring a firearm in 2018. The Texas man central to the Supreme Court case, Zackey Rahimi, faced charges stemming from multiple incidents involving firearms, leading to a restraining order that prohibited him from possessing a gun. His appeal put into question the constitutionality of such federal restrictions, arguing that they contravene his right to self-defense as afforded by the Second Amendment. During the discussions, Justice Elena Kagan and others stressed the government’s rationale that history has shown the necessity of keeping firearms from individuals deemed dangerous. Such a viewpoint finds support across the Court’s ideological spectrum, including the more conservative justices, suggesting a potential consensus for upholding the existing ban. Chief Justice John Roberts, however, expressed concerns over the breadth of the term “irresponsible” when applied to gun ownership, hinting at the subjective nature of deeming someone unfit to bear arms. The background of the case paints a troubling picture of Rahimi’s repeated violations of the protective order, including brandishing weapons and threatening behavior. These actions did not escape the Court’s attention, with even the conservative justices questioning Rahimi’s suitability to possess firearms. On the courthouse steps, demonstrators rallied, with the majority advocating for stricter gun control, reflecting the national conversation on gun violence following recent tragic events. The Supreme Court’s eventual decision will likely be nuanced, focusing narrowly on the legitimacy of denying guns to those with a documented history of violence. Yet, it will set a critical precedent for future Second Amendment challenges and provide guidance for lower courts currently navigating the complex legal landscape post the landmark 2022 ruling, which expanded gun rights. The outcome will be closely watched by all, from legal scholars to policymakers to everyday citizens, as it will not only impact public safety and individual rights but also resonate through the ongoing societal debate about the balance between liberty and protection. As the nation awaits the Court’s ruling, due by the summer of 2024, the significance of this case extends beyond the legal arguments presented—it embodies the enduring struggle to reconcile the foundational principles of the Constitution with the pressing demands of modern governance.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump Campaign Confidently Counters DeSantis’ Two-Man Race Claim</title><link href="/politics/2023/11/07/Trump-Campaign-Strategics/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump Campaign Confidently Counters DeSantis’ Two-Man Race Claim" /><published>2023-11-07T18:20:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-07T18:20:00-05:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/11/07/Trump-Campaign-Strategics</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/11/07/Trump-Campaign-Strategics/">&lt;p&gt;Former President Donald Trump’s campaign has boldly dismissed the notion that the 2024 primary is merely a two-man contest. Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis’ strategy to portray himself as the sole viable challenger to Trump has been met with skepticism from the Trump team, indicating a growing confidence in their frontrunner status.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump’s spokesperson, Steven Cheung, threw a sharp jab at DeSantis by referring to him as “DeSanctimonious” and criticizing his campaign’s focus on attacking fellow GOP contender Nikki Haley. The Trump campaign’s rhetoric suggests a belief that DeSantis is losing his footing in the primary race, as indicated by Cheung’s metaphor of a “wounded bird” plummeting from the political skies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The unfolding dynamics underscore the heated competition that characterizes the Republican field. While DeSantis’ campaign has worked diligently to frame the race as a direct face-off with Trump, Trump’s camp remains unfazed, bolstered by consistent polling leads. The endorsement from Iowa Gov. Kim Reynolds, a significant political figure, has added fuel to DeSantis’ campaign fire. However, Trump’s team remains confident that their candidate’s broad appeal and political track record will continue to resonate with Republican voters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nikki Haley’s rising poll numbers in key primary states such as New Hampshire and South Carolina have prompted the Trump campaign to question DeSantis’ assertion of a two-man race. It’s a clear indicator of the fluid nature of the primary landscape and the potential for other candidates to disrupt the perceived duopoly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump’s enduring popularity among the GOP base has been further reinforced by his unprecedented situation as a former president who has been indicted. Far from diminishing his political capital, the indictments have seemingly galvanized his support within the party. His campaign has adeptly turned these legal challenges into a rallying cry for his supporters, who view him as a political fighter undeterred by opposition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the campaign trail heats up, Trump’s team is poised to capitalize on their candidate’s dominant position. They are prepared to leverage his strong poll numbers and loyal base to fend off challenges from DeSantis and other GOP rivals. With the primary season fast approaching, the Trump campaign’s latest moves indicate a strategy of assertive confidence and readiness to take on all comers in the quest to reclaim the presidency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Republican primary race continues to be a captivating political spectacle, with Trump’s campaign at the center of the action, exuding the boldness and combativeness that have become hallmarks of his political brand.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Former President Donald Trump’s campaign has boldly dismissed the notion that the 2024 primary is merely a two-man contest. Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis’ strategy to portray himself as the sole viable challenger to Trump has been met with skepticism from the Trump team, indicating a growing confidence in their frontrunner status. Trump’s spokesperson, Steven Cheung, threw a sharp jab at DeSantis by referring to him as “DeSanctimonious” and criticizing his campaign’s focus on attacking fellow GOP contender Nikki Haley. The Trump campaign’s rhetoric suggests a belief that DeSantis is losing his footing in the primary race, as indicated by Cheung’s metaphor of a “wounded bird” plummeting from the political skies. The unfolding dynamics underscore the heated competition that characterizes the Republican field. While DeSantis’ campaign has worked diligently to frame the race as a direct face-off with Trump, Trump’s camp remains unfazed, bolstered by consistent polling leads. The endorsement from Iowa Gov. Kim Reynolds, a significant political figure, has added fuel to DeSantis’ campaign fire. However, Trump’s team remains confident that their candidate’s broad appeal and political track record will continue to resonate with Republican voters. Nikki Haley’s rising poll numbers in key primary states such as New Hampshire and South Carolina have prompted the Trump campaign to question DeSantis’ assertion of a two-man race. It’s a clear indicator of the fluid nature of the primary landscape and the potential for other candidates to disrupt the perceived duopoly. Trump’s enduring popularity among the GOP base has been further reinforced by his unprecedented situation as a former president who has been indicted. Far from diminishing his political capital, the indictments have seemingly galvanized his support within the party. His campaign has adeptly turned these legal challenges into a rallying cry for his supporters, who view him as a political fighter undeterred by opposition. As the campaign trail heats up, Trump’s team is poised to capitalize on their candidate’s dominant position. They are prepared to leverage his strong poll numbers and loyal base to fend off challenges from DeSantis and other GOP rivals. With the primary season fast approaching, the Trump campaign’s latest moves indicate a strategy of assertive confidence and readiness to take on all comers in the quest to reclaim the presidency. The Republican primary race continues to be a captivating political spectacle, with Trump’s campaign at the center of the action, exuding the boldness and combativeness that have become hallmarks of his political brand.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Quick Action by Capitol Police Thwarts Potential Threat Near U.S. Capitol</title><link href="/news/2023/11/07/AR-15-Arrest-Capitol/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Quick Action by Capitol Police Thwarts Potential Threat Near U.S. Capitol" /><published>2023-11-07T17:05:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-07T17:05:00-05:00</updated><id>/news/2023/11/07/AR-15-Arrest-Capitol</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/11/07/AR-15-Arrest-Capitol/">&lt;p&gt;U.S. Capitol Police swiftly arrested a man armed with an AR-15 near the U.S. Capitol on Tuesday afternoon, eliminating any potential threat to public safety. The individual was detained in the park opposite Union Station, a bustling hub adjacent to the Capitol complex.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The arrest came amid heightened alertness as Capitol Police officers responded to reports of a suspicious vehicle parked in the vicinity. The suspect’s swift apprehension speaks to the readiness and efficiency of law enforcement in securing the area, a reminder of the constant surveillance that protects the nation’s legislative center.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Authorities have assured the public that there appears to be no ongoing danger, as initial investigations suggest the individual was acting alone. This incident underscores the importance of continuous security measures and the need for prompt action in the face of potential risks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the Capitol Police worked to gather more information, they issued a cautionary notice, advising staff and visitors to steer clear of the area during the operation. The park was thoroughly searched, and the suspect’s belongings are being examined to ensure no additional threats remain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Capitol Police’s effective management of the situation averted disruptions to the congressional proceedings and maintained the sanctity of the Capitol grounds. The incident, while isolated, serves as a stark reminder of the challenges faced by security forces in today’s unpredictable environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the suspect securely in custody and the area deemed safe, Capitol Police continue their investigation to ascertain the motives behind the suspect’s presence and any potential connections to larger threats. Their proactive approach and transparent communication via social media provided timely updates, keeping the community informed and engaged.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The incident near the Capitol, though resolved without harm, highlights the critical role of law enforcement in maintaining peace and preventing potential crises. It exemplifies the dedication of the Capitol Police to the safety of all who work within and visit this key symbol of American democracy.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">U.S. Capitol Police swiftly arrested a man armed with an AR-15 near the U.S. Capitol on Tuesday afternoon, eliminating any potential threat to public safety. The individual was detained in the park opposite Union Station, a bustling hub adjacent to the Capitol complex. The arrest came amid heightened alertness as Capitol Police officers responded to reports of a suspicious vehicle parked in the vicinity. The suspect’s swift apprehension speaks to the readiness and efficiency of law enforcement in securing the area, a reminder of the constant surveillance that protects the nation’s legislative center. Authorities have assured the public that there appears to be no ongoing danger, as initial investigations suggest the individual was acting alone. This incident underscores the importance of continuous security measures and the need for prompt action in the face of potential risks. As the Capitol Police worked to gather more information, they issued a cautionary notice, advising staff and visitors to steer clear of the area during the operation. The park was thoroughly searched, and the suspect’s belongings are being examined to ensure no additional threats remain. Capitol Police’s effective management of the situation averted disruptions to the congressional proceedings and maintained the sanctity of the Capitol grounds. The incident, while isolated, serves as a stark reminder of the challenges faced by security forces in today’s unpredictable environment. With the suspect securely in custody and the area deemed safe, Capitol Police continue their investigation to ascertain the motives behind the suspect’s presence and any potential connections to larger threats. Their proactive approach and transparent communication via social media provided timely updates, keeping the community informed and engaged. The incident near the Capitol, though resolved without harm, highlights the critical role of law enforcement in maintaining peace and preventing potential crises. It exemplifies the dedication of the Capitol Police to the safety of all who work within and visit this key symbol of American democracy.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump’s Fortune Soars: A $500 Million Surge Since White House Departure</title><link href="/news/2023/11/07/Trump-Fortune-Growth/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump’s Fortune Soars: A $500 Million Surge Since White House Departure" /><published>2023-11-07T15:53:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-07T15:53:00-05:00</updated><id>/news/2023/11/07/Trump-Fortune-Growth</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/11/07/Trump-Fortune-Growth/">&lt;p&gt;In a striking testament to his enduring business savvy, former President Donald Trump’s net worth has seen a significant uptick, swelling by an impressive $500 million since he bid farewell to the Oval Office. According to the Bloomberg Billionaires Index, Trump’s financial clout now stands at a robust $3.1 billion, an ascension attributed largely to the surging real estate market in the Sunshine State.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The value of Trump’s iconic Mar-a-Lago in Palm Beach and the prestigious Doral golf resort in Miami have both benefitted from Florida’s property boom, contributing substantially to his wealth’s upward trajectory. With the sale of his storied Washington hotel and a strategic reduction of liabilities, Trump boasts a stronger cash position and a lighter debt load than he’s held over the past decade.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet, Bloomberg hints that Trump’s wealth could eclipse the current estimate of $3.1 billion. It concedes that factors such as the Trump brand’s influence, the historical significance of his holdings, and potential redevelopment or rezoning opportunities may significantly inflate property valuations. These considerations, in tandem with Trump’s strategic real estate moves, underscore his acumen as a property mogul with an unparalleled understanding of the market’s nuances.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s no secret that estimates of Trump’s wealth have been a point of contention, often diverging between his own assessments and those of external appraisers. While the New York Attorney General’s lawsuit against the former president pegs his wealth at a lower figure, real estate professionals in Palm Beach have voiced surprise at the undervaluation of Mar-a-Lago, suggesting it could command a market price well into the hundreds of millions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The debate extends to the valuation of Trump’s penthouse in Trump Tower, with Trump’s company asserting a value of $131.3 million in contrast to Bloomberg’s $40 million estimate and the lack of an official court assessment. The intricacies of New York real estate law allow for a broader interpretation of square footage, potentially inflating the size and worth of such a unique and iconic property.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adding to the complexity, any potential sale of Trump’s penthouse could fetch a premium, not solely due to its luxury but also the prestige associated with the Trump name. Trump supporters, in particular, might be willing to pay top dollar for a piece of the former president’s legacy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the Bloomberg Billionaires Index grapples with the fluid nature of real estate valuations, influenced by factors like interest rates and market trends, it acknowledges the possibility that Trump’s wealth could indeed align with his own claims — or even surpass them. This financial narrative is not just a reflection of numbers but also of Trump’s indelible mark on the real estate sector, a legacy that began reshaping New York’s skyline as early as the 1970s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the landscape of American entrepreneurship and real estate development, Trump’s increasing fortune is more than a figure — it’s a chapter in the storied history of a businessman who rose to the pinnacle of political power and continues to command a towering presence in both arenas.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a striking testament to his enduring business savvy, former President Donald Trump’s net worth has seen a significant uptick, swelling by an impressive $500 million since he bid farewell to the Oval Office. According to the Bloomberg Billionaires Index, Trump’s financial clout now stands at a robust $3.1 billion, an ascension attributed largely to the surging real estate market in the Sunshine State. The value of Trump’s iconic Mar-a-Lago in Palm Beach and the prestigious Doral golf resort in Miami have both benefitted from Florida’s property boom, contributing substantially to his wealth’s upward trajectory. With the sale of his storied Washington hotel and a strategic reduction of liabilities, Trump boasts a stronger cash position and a lighter debt load than he’s held over the past decade. Yet, Bloomberg hints that Trump’s wealth could eclipse the current estimate of $3.1 billion. It concedes that factors such as the Trump brand’s influence, the historical significance of his holdings, and potential redevelopment or rezoning opportunities may significantly inflate property valuations. These considerations, in tandem with Trump’s strategic real estate moves, underscore his acumen as a property mogul with an unparalleled understanding of the market’s nuances. It’s no secret that estimates of Trump’s wealth have been a point of contention, often diverging between his own assessments and those of external appraisers. While the New York Attorney General’s lawsuit against the former president pegs his wealth at a lower figure, real estate professionals in Palm Beach have voiced surprise at the undervaluation of Mar-a-Lago, suggesting it could command a market price well into the hundreds of millions. The debate extends to the valuation of Trump’s penthouse in Trump Tower, with Trump’s company asserting a value of $131.3 million in contrast to Bloomberg’s $40 million estimate and the lack of an official court assessment. The intricacies of New York real estate law allow for a broader interpretation of square footage, potentially inflating the size and worth of such a unique and iconic property. Adding to the complexity, any potential sale of Trump’s penthouse could fetch a premium, not solely due to its luxury but also the prestige associated with the Trump name. Trump supporters, in particular, might be willing to pay top dollar for a piece of the former president’s legacy. As the Bloomberg Billionaires Index grapples with the fluid nature of real estate valuations, influenced by factors like interest rates and market trends, it acknowledges the possibility that Trump’s wealth could indeed align with his own claims — or even surpass them. This financial narrative is not just a reflection of numbers but also of Trump’s indelible mark on the real estate sector, a legacy that began reshaping New York’s skyline as early as the 1970s. In the landscape of American entrepreneurship and real estate development, Trump’s increasing fortune is more than a figure — it’s a chapter in the storied history of a businessman who rose to the pinnacle of political power and continues to command a towering presence in both arenas.</summary></entry></feed>