<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-10-28T02:18:58-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/28/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-28T02:18:58-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-28T02:18:58-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/28/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/28/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/28/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-28T02:18:58-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-28T02:18:58-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/28/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/28/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/">&lt;p&gt;Recent surprise attacks by Hamas on Israel has fueled ongoing tensions between staunchly conservative commentators and the progressive “Squad” Democrats known for criticizing Israel. The intensity of the backlash highlights the deep political divide over foreign policy in the Middle East.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Hamas’ shocking attack, several members of the “Squad,” including Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.), called for a “ceasefire and de-escalation,” condemning the violence. The absence of a statement from Rep. Rashida Tlaib (D-Mich.) was notably called out by conservative media outlets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;South Carolina GOP Rep. Nancy Mace quickly labeled Ocasio-Cortez a “Hamas apologist” in response to her call for peace and de-escalation. Rep. Ilhan Omar (D-Minn.), no stranger to controversy surrounding her views on Israel, echoed the call for de-escalation and ceasefire. Omar’s prior statements comparing the US and Israel to terrorist groups like Hamas and the Taliban resurfaced in the debate, fueling more criticisms. Omar’s 2019 tweet, where she opined that “Israel has hypnotized the world,” also continues to haunt her political career, often cited by critics to challenge her stance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conservative commentators have been especially vocal. “FOX &amp;amp; Friends Weekend” co-host Rachel Campos-Duffy took aim at Omar, saying she fails to recognize the peace in the Middle East under Trump’s administration. Conservative pundit John Hasson also called out Omar, claiming she insinuated that attacks on IDF forces were acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Massachusetts Democrat Rep. Ayanna Pressley’s concerns over the “devastating attacks on Israelis” were met with skepticism. A prominent conservative online personality, Comfortably Smug, accused the “Squad” of advising Israel to back down after the nation suffered massive attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Jamaal Bowman’s call for an end to the Gaza blockade, in addition to condemning the Hamas attacks, was met with criticism from conservative radio host Jason Rantz. He accused Bowman of pairing his condemnation of terrorism with unwarranted criticisms of Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Cori Bush emphasized the urgent need for a ceasefire, while pushing for an end to “U.S. support for Israeli military occupation and apartheid.” Defense attorney Marina Medvin criticized Bush, suggesting that she equates the death of Palestinian terrorists to the horrific acts committed against Jewish civilians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amidst the political turmoil and intense debate, the attacks have taken a heavy toll. Israeli media report over 300 dead due to the wide-ranging assault. Gaza health officials note that at least 200 Palestinians have perished in the retaliatory Israeli air strikes following the initial Hamas attack. As the situation remains volatile, both sides continue to count their casualties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This divisive issue showcases the challenge America faces in crafting a unified approach to foreign policy, with deeply entrenched political divides at play. As the situation develops, the debate is bound to intensify, shedding light on the complexities of U.S. politics in the global arena.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Heroic Rescue: Michigan Police Save Kidnapped Man from Gruesome Fate</title><link href="/news/2023/10/27/Kidnapping-Michigan/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Heroic Rescue: Michigan Police Save Kidnapped Man from Gruesome Fate" /><published>2023-10-27T16:09:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-27T16:09:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/27/Kidnapping-Michigan</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/27/Kidnapping-Michigan/">&lt;p&gt;In a harrowing incident that unfolded in Michigan, police managed to save a man from a terrifying fate after he was kidnapped and found bound and injured inside his own vehicle. The Shelby Township Police Department sprang into action after learning about the incident, which took place in the parking lot of a Lifetime Fitness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 24-year-old male victim found himself in the clutches of four armed and masked assailants, resulting in an immediate and large-scale investigation by local law enforcement. With the assistance of the Sterling Heights Police Department, the police were able to track down the suspect’s vehicle at the victim’s home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What ensued was a high-stakes chase, as the suspect attempted to flee in the vehicle before ultimately crashing. Despite his efforts to escape on foot, he was quickly apprehended by a police officer, bringing an end to the terrifying ordeal for the kidnapped man.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The suspect, identified as 33-year-old Antonio Andujar-Ruiz from Tampa, Florida, was found to have an extensive and violent criminal history, including a previous conviction of assault with intent to murder. Detectives believe that he traveled all the way to Michigan with the sole purpose of committing this violent crime, underlining the premeditated nature of the attack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“This does not appear to be a random act,” the police stated, highlighting the targeted nature of the incident.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The victim, thankfully rescued, was found in a dire state, “bound and tortured” inside his GMC pickup truck, with the suspect’s assault rifle also recovered from the scene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Andujar-Ruiz now faces a slew of serious charges including carjacking, conspiracy to commit carjacking, armed robbery, torture, unlawful imprisonment, home invasion in the 1st degree, and related weapons charges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Shelby Township Police Department emphasized the collaborative effort involved in the investigation and rescue, with multiple federal agencies including the Coast Guard, U.S. Customs and Border Protection, and the Federal Bureau of Investigation playing crucial roles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Police Chief Robert Shelide expressed his gratitude towards all the law enforcement agencies involved, commending them for their quick response and tenacity. He also took a moment to criticize the justice system, stating that this incident could have been prevented if a “career violent criminal” had not been given the opportunity to reoffend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This story serves as a stark reminder of the importance of vigilance, the bravery of law enforcement, and the critical need for reform in the justice system to ensure the safety of our communities.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a harrowing incident that unfolded in Michigan, police managed to save a man from a terrifying fate after he was kidnapped and found bound and injured inside his own vehicle. The Shelby Township Police Department sprang into action after learning about the incident, which took place in the parking lot of a Lifetime Fitness. The 24-year-old male victim found himself in the clutches of four armed and masked assailants, resulting in an immediate and large-scale investigation by local law enforcement. With the assistance of the Sterling Heights Police Department, the police were able to track down the suspect’s vehicle at the victim’s home. What ensued was a high-stakes chase, as the suspect attempted to flee in the vehicle before ultimately crashing. Despite his efforts to escape on foot, he was quickly apprehended by a police officer, bringing an end to the terrifying ordeal for the kidnapped man. The suspect, identified as 33-year-old Antonio Andujar-Ruiz from Tampa, Florida, was found to have an extensive and violent criminal history, including a previous conviction of assault with intent to murder. Detectives believe that he traveled all the way to Michigan with the sole purpose of committing this violent crime, underlining the premeditated nature of the attack. “This does not appear to be a random act,” the police stated, highlighting the targeted nature of the incident. The victim, thankfully rescued, was found in a dire state, “bound and tortured” inside his GMC pickup truck, with the suspect’s assault rifle also recovered from the scene. Andujar-Ruiz now faces a slew of serious charges including carjacking, conspiracy to commit carjacking, armed robbery, torture, unlawful imprisonment, home invasion in the 1st degree, and related weapons charges. The Shelby Township Police Department emphasized the collaborative effort involved in the investigation and rescue, with multiple federal agencies including the Coast Guard, U.S. Customs and Border Protection, and the Federal Bureau of Investigation playing crucial roles. Police Chief Robert Shelide expressed his gratitude towards all the law enforcement agencies involved, commending them for their quick response and tenacity. He also took a moment to criticize the justice system, stating that this incident could have been prevented if a “career violent criminal” had not been given the opportunity to reoffend. This story serves as a stark reminder of the importance of vigilance, the bravery of law enforcement, and the critical need for reform in the justice system to ensure the safety of our communities.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">High-Speed Chase and Gunfire: A Shocking Incident at Texas Air Force Base</title><link href="/news/2023/10/27/Air-Force-Police-Texas-Base/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="High-Speed Chase and Gunfire: A Shocking Incident at Texas Air Force Base" /><published>2023-10-27T14:34:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-27T14:34:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/27/Air-Force-Police-Texas-Base</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/27/Air-Force-Police-Texas-Base/">&lt;p&gt;Air Force police at Joint Base San Antonio-Camp Bullis in Texas were compelled to open fire on a vehicle that breached the base’s gates at an excessive speed this weekend. The unidentified driver aggressively sped towards the Air Force guards, breaking through the access control point and momentarily gaining access to the installation before attempting to exit back through the gate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to Angela Casarez, a spokesperson for Joint Base San Antonio-Camp Bullis, the security forces had no choice but to take defensive measures. “Security forces pursued the driver and took defensive measures when the suspected gate runner attempted to exit the installation via the inbound lane traveling at an excessive rate of speed,” she explained. The situation was tense and rapid, with the base’s Air Force police acting swiftly to neutralize the threat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the vehicle’s quick penetration of the base, the driver was unable to reach any of the training areas located on the expansive, more than 27,000-acre installation. Remarkably, no injuries were reported from the incident, either to the Air Force personnel or the driver.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The San Antonio Police Department later apprehended the suspect, approximately nine miles from the base, following his involvement in a separate incident. The base, primarily used for training Army, Air Force, and Marine Corps combat troops, is a part of the larger Joint Base San Antonio, which includes other major installations like Joint Base-Fort Sam Houston, Joint Base-Randolph, and Joint Base-Lackland.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This incident comes on the heels of another security scare at Joint Base-Fort Sam Houston, where a gate was temporarily closed, and several buildings were placed on lockdown following reports of gunshots from a nearby wooded area. According to an Air Force spokesperson, there is no evidence to suggest that these two incidents are connected. Both the gate and buildings were reopened hours after the incidents, with no reported injuries to military personnel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The spokesperson for Joint Base San Antonio confirmed to Fox News Digital that the Air Force Security Forces did indeed open fire in self-defense when the driver posed an imminent threat to their safety. Fortunately, no injuries or damage to Air Force property were reported. The incident remains under thorough investigation as officials work to piece together the events of that alarming day and ensure the safety and security of military installations.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Air Force police at Joint Base San Antonio-Camp Bullis in Texas were compelled to open fire on a vehicle that breached the base’s gates at an excessive speed this weekend. The unidentified driver aggressively sped towards the Air Force guards, breaking through the access control point and momentarily gaining access to the installation before attempting to exit back through the gate. According to Angela Casarez, a spokesperson for Joint Base San Antonio-Camp Bullis, the security forces had no choice but to take defensive measures. “Security forces pursued the driver and took defensive measures when the suspected gate runner attempted to exit the installation via the inbound lane traveling at an excessive rate of speed,” she explained. The situation was tense and rapid, with the base’s Air Force police acting swiftly to neutralize the threat. Despite the vehicle’s quick penetration of the base, the driver was unable to reach any of the training areas located on the expansive, more than 27,000-acre installation. Remarkably, no injuries were reported from the incident, either to the Air Force personnel or the driver. The San Antonio Police Department later apprehended the suspect, approximately nine miles from the base, following his involvement in a separate incident. The base, primarily used for training Army, Air Force, and Marine Corps combat troops, is a part of the larger Joint Base San Antonio, which includes other major installations like Joint Base-Fort Sam Houston, Joint Base-Randolph, and Joint Base-Lackland. This incident comes on the heels of another security scare at Joint Base-Fort Sam Houston, where a gate was temporarily closed, and several buildings were placed on lockdown following reports of gunshots from a nearby wooded area. According to an Air Force spokesperson, there is no evidence to suggest that these two incidents are connected. Both the gate and buildings were reopened hours after the incidents, with no reported injuries to military personnel. The spokesperson for Joint Base San Antonio confirmed to Fox News Digital that the Air Force Security Forces did indeed open fire in self-defense when the driver posed an imminent threat to their safety. Fortunately, no injuries or damage to Air Force property were reported. The incident remains under thorough investigation as officials work to piece together the events of that alarming day and ensure the safety and security of military installations.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Tumultuous Road to Electing a House Speaker: Gaetz Calls McCarthy a ‘Saboteur’</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/27/Speaker-Election-House/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Tumultuous Road to Electing a House Speaker: Gaetz Calls McCarthy a ‘Saboteur’" /><published>2023-10-27T12:12:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-27T12:12:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/27/Speaker-Election-House</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/27/Speaker-Election-House/">&lt;p&gt;Rep. Matt Gaetz, R-Fla., has publicly accused former Speaker hopeful Kevin McCarthy of sabotaging the election process for the House Speaker position, alleging that McCarthy’s machinations delayed the appointment of Mike Johnson, R-La., to the speakership. Gaetz’s comments add a dramatic chapter to the already intense race for one of the most significant positions in American politics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just a month after Gaetz played a crucial role in McCarthy’s ousting, the Florida Congressman has shifted the spotlight back onto McCarthy, accusing him of being a “saboteur” and blaming him for the delay in electing a House Speaker. According to Gaetz, McCarthy undermined the candidacies of Reps. Steve Scalise, R-La., Jim Jordan, R-Ohio, and Tom Emmer, R-Minn., ultimately prolonging the process and creating turmoil within the Republican Party.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The eventual election of Mike Johnson as House Speaker marked the end of a tumultuous period for the Republicans, but Gaetz insists that the delay could have been avoided. He alleges that McCarthy actively worked against his fellow Republicans, hindering their chances of securing the speakership. “What Tom Emmer, Steve Scalise and Jim Jordan all saw was that the actual saboteur of their candidacies was Kevin McCarthy,” Gaetz declared, casting a shadow of doubt over McCarthy’s actions during the election.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, former President Donald Trump weighed in on the matter, taking credit for derailing Emmer’s candidacy and stating bluntly, “I killed him.” McCarthy, for his part, publicly supported Jordan, referring to him as a “great ally” during the three floor votes. However, Gaetz remains adamant that McCarthy’s intentions were not as straightforward as they seemed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to Gaetz, McCarthy’s true colors were revealed during a closed-door GOP conference meeting, where freshman Rep. Marc Molinaro, R-N.Y., proposed polling the Republicans on Johnson’s candidacy. “Kevin McCarthy objected,” Gaetz stated, “Because at that point he hadn’t figured out a way yet how to scuttle Mike Johnson the way he scuttled Tom Emmer, Steve Scalise and Jim Jordan before.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gaetz concluded his accusations by contrasting Johnson with McCarthy, painting Johnson as a leader free from obligations to lobbyists and special interests, while suggesting that McCarthy was indebted to these groups. “Mike Johnson answers to God and the Constitution,” Gaetz proclaimed, firmly placing his support behind the new Speaker.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the dust settles on this high-stakes political showdown, questions linger about the true dynamics of the Speaker election and the role McCarthy played in it. Gaetz’s accusations have undoubtedly added a layer of intrigue to the proceedings, casting a long shadow over McCarthy’s actions and intentions during this critical period in American politics.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Rep. Matt Gaetz, R-Fla., has publicly accused former Speaker hopeful Kevin McCarthy of sabotaging the election process for the House Speaker position, alleging that McCarthy’s machinations delayed the appointment of Mike Johnson, R-La., to the speakership. Gaetz’s comments add a dramatic chapter to the already intense race for one of the most significant positions in American politics. Just a month after Gaetz played a crucial role in McCarthy’s ousting, the Florida Congressman has shifted the spotlight back onto McCarthy, accusing him of being a “saboteur” and blaming him for the delay in electing a House Speaker. According to Gaetz, McCarthy undermined the candidacies of Reps. Steve Scalise, R-La., Jim Jordan, R-Ohio, and Tom Emmer, R-Minn., ultimately prolonging the process and creating turmoil within the Republican Party. The eventual election of Mike Johnson as House Speaker marked the end of a tumultuous period for the Republicans, but Gaetz insists that the delay could have been avoided. He alleges that McCarthy actively worked against his fellow Republicans, hindering their chances of securing the speakership. “What Tom Emmer, Steve Scalise and Jim Jordan all saw was that the actual saboteur of their candidacies was Kevin McCarthy,” Gaetz declared, casting a shadow of doubt over McCarthy’s actions during the election. Interestingly, former President Donald Trump weighed in on the matter, taking credit for derailing Emmer’s candidacy and stating bluntly, “I killed him.” McCarthy, for his part, publicly supported Jordan, referring to him as a “great ally” during the three floor votes. However, Gaetz remains adamant that McCarthy’s intentions were not as straightforward as they seemed. According to Gaetz, McCarthy’s true colors were revealed during a closed-door GOP conference meeting, where freshman Rep. Marc Molinaro, R-N.Y., proposed polling the Republicans on Johnson’s candidacy. “Kevin McCarthy objected,” Gaetz stated, “Because at that point he hadn’t figured out a way yet how to scuttle Mike Johnson the way he scuttled Tom Emmer, Steve Scalise and Jim Jordan before.” Gaetz concluded his accusations by contrasting Johnson with McCarthy, painting Johnson as a leader free from obligations to lobbyists and special interests, while suggesting that McCarthy was indebted to these groups. “Mike Johnson answers to God and the Constitution,” Gaetz proclaimed, firmly placing his support behind the new Speaker. As the dust settles on this high-stakes political showdown, questions linger about the true dynamics of the Speaker election and the role McCarthy played in it. Gaetz’s accusations have undoubtedly added a layer of intrigue to the proceedings, casting a long shadow over McCarthy’s actions and intentions during this critical period in American politics.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Battleground in the Tar Heel State: Republicans Defend North Carolina’s New Election Law</title><link href="/news/2023/10/27/Election-Law-North-Carolina/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Battleground in the Tar Heel State: Republicans Defend North Carolina’s New Election Law" /><published>2023-10-27T10:35:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-27T10:35:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/27/Election-Law-North-Carolina</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/27/Election-Law-North-Carolina/">&lt;p&gt;In the face of a Democrat-backed legal challenge, the Republican National Committee (RNC) and the North Carolina Republican Party (NCGOP) are taking a stand to defend the state’s newly established election law. Senate Bill 747, the focal point of this legal battleground, represents a significant effort to enhance election integrity in the Tar Heel State, with Republicans emphasizing its role in promoting transparency, voter ID strength, and safeguarding poll watchers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enacted on October 10th, following a Republican-led override of Democratic Governor Roy Cooper’s veto, Senate Bill 747 has become a flashpoint in the ongoing debate over voting rights and election security. The law’s provisions, aimed at tightening the deadline for mail-in ballots, ensuring robust voter ID requirements, and protecting the role of poll watchers, have garnered praise from Republicans for their potential to secure the election process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, this legislative move was swiftly met with opposition from the Democratic National Committee (DNC) and the North Carolina Democratic Party, who filed a lawsuit alleging that the law suppresses voters’ rights and violates both the U.S. Constitution and the Voting Rights Act. In their legal challenge, the Democrats accuse the law of being “a direct assault on the ‘most fundamental’ right to vote.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Responding to these accusations, the RNC and NCGOP have decided to intervene, expressing their intent to defend the law’s provisions and highlight their importance in maintaining a secure and transparent election process. RNC Chairwoman Ronna McDaniel, in a statement to Fox News Digital, criticized President Biden for his administration’s legal actions against state voting laws, urging him to focus on addressing the nation’s pressing issues instead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Republicans’ legal filing counters the Democrats’ allegations, emphasizing the need for “fair election-litigation procedures” and defending the law’s measures as “common-sense” safeguards supported by the majority of American voters. Citing a 2021 Axis Research study, the filing highlights broad public support for stronger voter ID requirements and the belief that state legislatures should dictate voting rules and regulations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With North Carolina positioned as a crucial battleground state for the 2024 presidential election, the outcome of this legal challenge holds significant implications. The state, which has predominantly leaned Republican in recent presidential elections, saw former President Donald Trump secure victory by a narrow margin in 2020, underscoring the importance of election laws and voter mobilization efforts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As both parties prepare for the 2024 electoral showdown, the battle over Senate Bill 747 exemplifies the broader national debate over voting rights and election integrity. With Republicans resolute in their defense of the law, and Democrats equally determined in their legal challenge, North Carolina becomes a key arena in the fight to shape the future of American democracy.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In the face of a Democrat-backed legal challenge, the Republican National Committee (RNC) and the North Carolina Republican Party (NCGOP) are taking a stand to defend the state’s newly established election law. Senate Bill 747, the focal point of this legal battleground, represents a significant effort to enhance election integrity in the Tar Heel State, with Republicans emphasizing its role in promoting transparency, voter ID strength, and safeguarding poll watchers. Enacted on October 10th, following a Republican-led override of Democratic Governor Roy Cooper’s veto, Senate Bill 747 has become a flashpoint in the ongoing debate over voting rights and election security. The law’s provisions, aimed at tightening the deadline for mail-in ballots, ensuring robust voter ID requirements, and protecting the role of poll watchers, have garnered praise from Republicans for their potential to secure the election process. However, this legislative move was swiftly met with opposition from the Democratic National Committee (DNC) and the North Carolina Democratic Party, who filed a lawsuit alleging that the law suppresses voters’ rights and violates both the U.S. Constitution and the Voting Rights Act. In their legal challenge, the Democrats accuse the law of being “a direct assault on the ‘most fundamental’ right to vote.” Responding to these accusations, the RNC and NCGOP have decided to intervene, expressing their intent to defend the law’s provisions and highlight their importance in maintaining a secure and transparent election process. RNC Chairwoman Ronna McDaniel, in a statement to Fox News Digital, criticized President Biden for his administration’s legal actions against state voting laws, urging him to focus on addressing the nation’s pressing issues instead. The Republicans’ legal filing counters the Democrats’ allegations, emphasizing the need for “fair election-litigation procedures” and defending the law’s measures as “common-sense” safeguards supported by the majority of American voters. Citing a 2021 Axis Research study, the filing highlights broad public support for stronger voter ID requirements and the belief that state legislatures should dictate voting rules and regulations. With North Carolina positioned as a crucial battleground state for the 2024 presidential election, the outcome of this legal challenge holds significant implications. The state, which has predominantly leaned Republican in recent presidential elections, saw former President Donald Trump secure victory by a narrow margin in 2020, underscoring the importance of election laws and voter mobilization efforts. As both parties prepare for the 2024 electoral showdown, the battle over Senate Bill 747 exemplifies the broader national debate over voting rights and election integrity. With Republicans resolute in their defense of the law, and Democrats equally determined in their legal challenge, North Carolina becomes a key arena in the fight to shape the future of American democracy.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Energizing America: Republicans Leap into Action with New Leadership and Key Legislation</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/27/Energizing-America/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Energizing America: Republicans Leap into Action with New Leadership and Key Legislation" /><published>2023-10-27T09:25:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-27T09:25:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/27/Energizing-America</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/27/Energizing-America/">&lt;p&gt;With Rep. Mike Johnson now firmly in place as the U.S. House Speaker, the Republicans are showing the American people that they are ready to get back to work and make significant legislative progress. The recent passage of the Energy and Water Appropriations Act is a prime example of their dedication to serving the nation and improving governmental efficiency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In his new role, Speaker Johnson, a Louisiana Republican with a deep commitment to conservative values, has hit the ground running with a clear vision for the future and a comprehensive plan to challenge the status quo. His election has ended weeks of anticipation and set the stage for a Republican-led initiative to push congressional Democrats and President Joe Biden to engage in meaningful negotiations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Energy and Water Appropriations Act, known as H.R. 4394, is just the first in a series of 12 appropriations bills that the Republicans plan to pass in their effort to apply pressure on their Democratic counterparts and the Biden administration. The swift passage of this bill is a testament to the Republicans’ ability to mobilize quickly and work efficiently, showcasing their commitment to fulfilling their promises to the American people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaker Johnson is no stranger to fighting for traditional values and principles. With a history of advocating for religious liberty and conservative ideals, he represents a type of leadership that many believe is necessary to restore integrity and accountability to Congress. His ascent to the Speakership has been met with widespread praise from his fellow Republicans, including former Speaker Kevin McCarthy and House Judiciary Committee Chairman Jim Jordan, both of whom have expressed their full support and confidence in Johnson’s ability to lead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking ahead, Speaker Johnson has laid out an ambitious legislative schedule, pinpointing key appropriations bills to be tackled in the coming weeks. His forward-thinking plan reflects a commitment to fiscal responsibility, proper governance, and the overall betterment of the nation. With his readiness to address challenging issues and his dedication to principle, Johnson has earned respect and admiration from his colleagues, positioning himself as a leader capable of steering the Republican party towards success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As Republicans celebrate the election of Speaker Mike Johnson and the successful passage of the Energy and Water Appropriations Act, there is a palpable sense of hope and determination within the party. With a clear agenda and a committed leader at the helm, the Republicans are demonstrating their readiness to work diligently for the American people, uphold traditional values, and drive positive change. The message is clear: under Speaker Mike Johnson’s leadership, the Republicans are energized, back to work, and ready to make America thrive once again.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">With Rep. Mike Johnson now firmly in place as the U.S. House Speaker, the Republicans are showing the American people that they are ready to get back to work and make significant legislative progress. The recent passage of the Energy and Water Appropriations Act is a prime example of their dedication to serving the nation and improving governmental efficiency. In his new role, Speaker Johnson, a Louisiana Republican with a deep commitment to conservative values, has hit the ground running with a clear vision for the future and a comprehensive plan to challenge the status quo. His election has ended weeks of anticipation and set the stage for a Republican-led initiative to push congressional Democrats and President Joe Biden to engage in meaningful negotiations. The Energy and Water Appropriations Act, known as H.R. 4394, is just the first in a series of 12 appropriations bills that the Republicans plan to pass in their effort to apply pressure on their Democratic counterparts and the Biden administration. The swift passage of this bill is a testament to the Republicans’ ability to mobilize quickly and work efficiently, showcasing their commitment to fulfilling their promises to the American people. Speaker Johnson is no stranger to fighting for traditional values and principles. With a history of advocating for religious liberty and conservative ideals, he represents a type of leadership that many believe is necessary to restore integrity and accountability to Congress. His ascent to the Speakership has been met with widespread praise from his fellow Republicans, including former Speaker Kevin McCarthy and House Judiciary Committee Chairman Jim Jordan, both of whom have expressed their full support and confidence in Johnson’s ability to lead. Looking ahead, Speaker Johnson has laid out an ambitious legislative schedule, pinpointing key appropriations bills to be tackled in the coming weeks. His forward-thinking plan reflects a commitment to fiscal responsibility, proper governance, and the overall betterment of the nation. With his readiness to address challenging issues and his dedication to principle, Johnson has earned respect and admiration from his colleagues, positioning himself as a leader capable of steering the Republican party towards success. As Republicans celebrate the election of Speaker Mike Johnson and the successful passage of the Energy and Water Appropriations Act, there is a palpable sense of hope and determination within the party. With a clear agenda and a committed leader at the helm, the Republicans are demonstrating their readiness to work diligently for the American people, uphold traditional values, and drive positive change. The message is clear: under Speaker Mike Johnson’s leadership, the Republicans are energized, back to work, and ready to make America thrive once again.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Preserving Integrity in Education: A Critical Look at Scholastic’s ‘Inclusive’ Policy</title><link href="/education/2023/10/27/Conservative-Response-School-Fairs/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Preserving Integrity in Education: A Critical Look at Scholastic’s ‘Inclusive’ Policy" /><published>2023-10-27T08:32:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-27T08:32:00-04:00</updated><id>/education/2023/10/27/Conservative-Response-School-Fairs</id><content type="html" xml:base="/education/2023/10/27/Conservative-Response-School-Fairs/">&lt;p&gt;Scholastic Inc., a well-known children’s publisher, recently found itself at the center of controversy following its decision to segregate books with racial, disability, and LGBTQ+ themes at school book fairs. This move, intended as a response to the growing number of content restrictions in various states, has sparked a significant backlash and raised questions about the role of education in today’s politically charged climate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The publisher created a separate package of books, titled “Share Every Story, Celebrate Every Voice,” giving schools the option to include these titles in their book fairs. While some have criticized this move as exclusionary, it is crucial to examine the broader context and consider the importance of upholding traditional values in education.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In an era where ‘woke’ ideologies are increasingly prevalent, infiltrating various aspects of society including education, it is essential to stand firm in our commitment to preserve the integrity of our educational content. The term ‘woke’ has come to represent a set of beliefs that emphasize political correctness and social justice, often at the expense of free speech and diverse perspectives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Scholastic’s decision to segregate these books, while controversial, can also be seen as a response to the concerns of parents and educators who wish to protect their children from indoctrination and ensure that they receive a balanced education. The inclusion of books that promote particular ideologies should not be done at the expense of academic rigor and intellectual diversity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In their statement, Scholastic acknowledged the backlash and announced the discontinuation of the “Share Every Story, Celebrate Every Voice” collection starting in January. However, they failed to provide a clear strategy for the future, leaving many wondering about their commitment to upholding educational standards and resisting the pressures of political correctness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is vital for educators, parents, and students to remain engaged and vigilant in the face of challenges to our educational system. We must strive to provide our children with an education that is grounded in tradition, promotes critical thinking, and prepares them to navigate the complexities of the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Publishers like Scholastic play a significant role in shaping the minds of future generations, and they must be held accountable for their decisions. It is our responsibility to ensure that our education system remains a bastion of learning, free from the influence of political agendas and focused on the intellectual development of all students.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The controversy surrounding Scholastic’s policy is a reminder of the importance of standing firm in our values and advocating for an education system that upholds the principles of intellectual freedom, academic excellence, and traditional values.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Education" /><summary type="html">Scholastic Inc., a well-known children’s publisher, recently found itself at the center of controversy following its decision to segregate books with racial, disability, and LGBTQ+ themes at school book fairs. This move, intended as a response to the growing number of content restrictions in various states, has sparked a significant backlash and raised questions about the role of education in today’s politically charged climate. The publisher created a separate package of books, titled “Share Every Story, Celebrate Every Voice,” giving schools the option to include these titles in their book fairs. While some have criticized this move as exclusionary, it is crucial to examine the broader context and consider the importance of upholding traditional values in education. In an era where ‘woke’ ideologies are increasingly prevalent, infiltrating various aspects of society including education, it is essential to stand firm in our commitment to preserve the integrity of our educational content. The term ‘woke’ has come to represent a set of beliefs that emphasize political correctness and social justice, often at the expense of free speech and diverse perspectives. Scholastic’s decision to segregate these books, while controversial, can also be seen as a response to the concerns of parents and educators who wish to protect their children from indoctrination and ensure that they receive a balanced education. The inclusion of books that promote particular ideologies should not be done at the expense of academic rigor and intellectual diversity. In their statement, Scholastic acknowledged the backlash and announced the discontinuation of the “Share Every Story, Celebrate Every Voice” collection starting in January. However, they failed to provide a clear strategy for the future, leaving many wondering about their commitment to upholding educational standards and resisting the pressures of political correctness. It is vital for educators, parents, and students to remain engaged and vigilant in the face of challenges to our educational system. We must strive to provide our children with an education that is grounded in tradition, promotes critical thinking, and prepares them to navigate the complexities of the world. Publishers like Scholastic play a significant role in shaping the minds of future generations, and they must be held accountable for their decisions. It is our responsibility to ensure that our education system remains a bastion of learning, free from the influence of political agendas and focused on the intellectual development of all students. The controversy surrounding Scholastic’s policy is a reminder of the importance of standing firm in our values and advocating for an education system that upholds the principles of intellectual freedom, academic excellence, and traditional values.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">End of the Manhunt: Maryland Judge’s Alleged Killer Discovered Deceased</title><link href="/news/2023/10/27/Maryland-Judge-Killer-Found/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="End of the Manhunt: Maryland Judge’s Alleged Killer Discovered Deceased" /><published>2023-10-27T07:10:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-27T07:10:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/27/Maryland-Judge-Killer-Found</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/27/Maryland-Judge-Killer-Found/">&lt;p&gt;The state of Maryland has been holding its breath since October 19, when Circuit Court Judge Andrew Wilkinson was shot and killed in his own driveway, a tragic event that shook the community to its core. The prime suspect, Pedro Argote, has been the subject of an intense manhunt since the incident, a search that has finally come to an end.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the morning of October 26, Argote’s lifeless body was discovered in a secluded, wooded area near Williamsport, Maryland, approximately a mile from where he had abandoned his vehicle post-crime. The discovery was made around 11 a.m., according to the Washington County Sheriff’s Office, which quickly issued a press release to inform the public and bring a measure of closure to this harrowing case.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sheriff Brian Albert addressed the media in a brief press conference later in the afternoon, revealing that Argote’s remains would be sent to Baltimore for an autopsy. This procedure will hopefully shed light on the circumstances of his death, including the cause, manner, and exact time of his passing. Sheriff Albert remained tight-lipped about whether a weapon was found near Argote’s body, choosing not to comment on that specific detail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The death of Judge Wilkinson was a result of a targeted attack, rooted in a bitter divorce and custody battle that had culminated just days before the shooting. Argote, facing allegations of prolonged abuse toward his family, had lost custody of his four children, aged 3 to 12, and was barred from any contact with them. The judge’s ruling was a decisive move to protect the children and their mother from further harm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wilkinson’s family, reeling from the loss, has found a semblance of peace in the wake of Argote’s death. “The family was relieved that we brought this to a little bit of closure,” shared Sheriff Albert, acknowledging the profound impact this resolution has had on the judge’s loved ones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The incident has raised questions and concerns about the safety of legal professionals, particularly judges, who make impactful and sometimes controversial decisions as part of their duties. Sheriff Albert hinted at future discussions aimed at enhancing protective measures for judges, ensuring that they can serve justice without fearing for their lives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As Maryland comes to terms with these tragic events, the community looks to heal and move forward, knowing that the manhunt has come to an end. The focus now shifts to remembering Judge Wilkinson for his commitment to justice and the safety of those he served, as well as supporting his grieving family in their time of need.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">The state of Maryland has been holding its breath since October 19, when Circuit Court Judge Andrew Wilkinson was shot and killed in his own driveway, a tragic event that shook the community to its core. The prime suspect, Pedro Argote, has been the subject of an intense manhunt since the incident, a search that has finally come to an end. On the morning of October 26, Argote’s lifeless body was discovered in a secluded, wooded area near Williamsport, Maryland, approximately a mile from where he had abandoned his vehicle post-crime. The discovery was made around 11 a.m., according to the Washington County Sheriff’s Office, which quickly issued a press release to inform the public and bring a measure of closure to this harrowing case. Sheriff Brian Albert addressed the media in a brief press conference later in the afternoon, revealing that Argote’s remains would be sent to Baltimore for an autopsy. This procedure will hopefully shed light on the circumstances of his death, including the cause, manner, and exact time of his passing. Sheriff Albert remained tight-lipped about whether a weapon was found near Argote’s body, choosing not to comment on that specific detail. The death of Judge Wilkinson was a result of a targeted attack, rooted in a bitter divorce and custody battle that had culminated just days before the shooting. Argote, facing allegations of prolonged abuse toward his family, had lost custody of his four children, aged 3 to 12, and was barred from any contact with them. The judge’s ruling was a decisive move to protect the children and their mother from further harm. Wilkinson’s family, reeling from the loss, has found a semblance of peace in the wake of Argote’s death. “The family was relieved that we brought this to a little bit of closure,” shared Sheriff Albert, acknowledging the profound impact this resolution has had on the judge’s loved ones. The incident has raised questions and concerns about the safety of legal professionals, particularly judges, who make impactful and sometimes controversial decisions as part of their duties. Sheriff Albert hinted at future discussions aimed at enhancing protective measures for judges, ensuring that they can serve justice without fearing for their lives. As Maryland comes to terms with these tragic events, the community looks to heal and move forward, knowing that the manhunt has come to an end. The focus now shifts to remembering Judge Wilkinson for his commitment to justice and the safety of those he served, as well as supporting his grieving family in their time of need.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Controversy Erupts as ‘Squad’ Democrats Refuse to Condemn Hamas Terrorism</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/27/Squad-Democrats-Hamas-Condemnation/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Controversy Erupts as ‘Squad’ Democrats Refuse to Condemn Hamas Terrorism" /><published>2023-10-27T06:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-27T06:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/27/Squad-Democrats-Hamas-Condemnation</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/27/Squad-Democrats-Hamas-Condemnation/">&lt;p&gt;The political atmosphere in Congress took a tense turn as a group of House Democrats, predominantly from the far-left “Squad,” voted against a resolution condemning the October 7 attack on Israel by Hamas terrorists. The resolution, H.R. 771, which also reaffirmed America’s unwavering support for Israel, witnessed overwhelming bipartisan approval but faced resistance from these members, sparking outrage and condemnation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Republican Representative Jason Smith of Missouri did not hold back his criticisms, lambasting the “Squad” members and other Democrats for their refusal to back the resolution. Speaking on “The Brian Kilmeade Show,” Smith labeled their actions as a “complete disgrace” and questioned their fitness to serve in Congress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Those nine Democrats are a complete disgrace,” Smith remarked vehemently. He pointed out that Cori Bush, a member of the “Squad” from his home state, has advocated for defunding the police while representing a city that, per capita, experiences more murders than any other in the United States. Smith argued that these members are irrational, accusing them of wishing to destroy society and of promoting propaganda that is as misleading as possible. He emphasized, “The fact that they’re harboring and supporting terrorists who have killed more Jewish people since the Holocaust is absolutely unacceptable and these people do not deserve to serve in the halls of Congress.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 10 members who voted against the resolution included six of the eight “Squad” members: Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez of New York, Ilhan Omar of Minnesota, Rashida Tlaib of Michigan, Jamaal Bowman of New York, Summer Lee of Pennsylvania, and Cori Bush of Missouri. They were joined by André Carson of Indiana, Al Green of Texas, and Delia Ramirez of Illinois.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the other side, two “Squad” members, Greg Casar of Texas and Ayanna Pressley of Massachusetts, chose to vote present, alongside Joaquin Castro of Texas, Nydia Velázquez of New York, Jesús “Chuy” Garcia of Illinois, and Pramila Jayapal of Washington.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Republican Representative Thomas Massie of Kentucky also voted against the resolution, but he explicitly condemned the Hamas attack and affirmed Israel’s right to defend itself, unlike some members of the “Squad.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The resolution’s passage with an overwhelming majority of 412-10, despite the notable dissenting votes, sends a clear message of America’s solidarity with Israel. However, the “Squad” members’ refusal to condemn Hamas, a designated terrorist organization, has ignited a fiery debate about their stance on Israel and their commitment to combating terrorism, placing them under intense scrutiny and criticism.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">The political atmosphere in Congress took a tense turn as a group of House Democrats, predominantly from the far-left “Squad,” voted against a resolution condemning the October 7 attack on Israel by Hamas terrorists. The resolution, H.R. 771, which also reaffirmed America’s unwavering support for Israel, witnessed overwhelming bipartisan approval but faced resistance from these members, sparking outrage and condemnation. Republican Representative Jason Smith of Missouri did not hold back his criticisms, lambasting the “Squad” members and other Democrats for their refusal to back the resolution. Speaking on “The Brian Kilmeade Show,” Smith labeled their actions as a “complete disgrace” and questioned their fitness to serve in Congress. “Those nine Democrats are a complete disgrace,” Smith remarked vehemently. He pointed out that Cori Bush, a member of the “Squad” from his home state, has advocated for defunding the police while representing a city that, per capita, experiences more murders than any other in the United States. Smith argued that these members are irrational, accusing them of wishing to destroy society and of promoting propaganda that is as misleading as possible. He emphasized, “The fact that they’re harboring and supporting terrorists who have killed more Jewish people since the Holocaust is absolutely unacceptable and these people do not deserve to serve in the halls of Congress.” The 10 members who voted against the resolution included six of the eight “Squad” members: Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez of New York, Ilhan Omar of Minnesota, Rashida Tlaib of Michigan, Jamaal Bowman of New York, Summer Lee of Pennsylvania, and Cori Bush of Missouri. They were joined by André Carson of Indiana, Al Green of Texas, and Delia Ramirez of Illinois. On the other side, two “Squad” members, Greg Casar of Texas and Ayanna Pressley of Massachusetts, chose to vote present, alongside Joaquin Castro of Texas, Nydia Velázquez of New York, Jesús “Chuy” Garcia of Illinois, and Pramila Jayapal of Washington. Republican Representative Thomas Massie of Kentucky also voted against the resolution, but he explicitly condemned the Hamas attack and affirmed Israel’s right to defend itself, unlike some members of the “Squad.” The resolution’s passage with an overwhelming majority of 412-10, despite the notable dissenting votes, sends a clear message of America’s solidarity with Israel. However, the “Squad” members’ refusal to condemn Hamas, a designated terrorist organization, has ignited a fiery debate about their stance on Israel and their commitment to combating terrorism, placing them under intense scrutiny and criticism.</summary></entry></feed>