<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-09-28T18:14:38-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/09/28/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-09-28T18:14:38-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-28T18:14:38-04:00</updated><id>/2023/09/28/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/28/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Unraveling the Gilgo Beach Mystery - DNA Clue Unearths Shocking Suspect</title><link href="/news/2023/09/28/Breaking-Gilgo-Beach-Murder/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Unraveling the Gilgo Beach Mystery - DNA Clue Unearths Shocking Suspect" /><published>2023-09-28T17:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-28T17:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/28/Breaking-Gilgo-Beach-Murder</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/28/Breaking-Gilgo-Beach-Murder/">&lt;p&gt;In a startling development in the unresolved Gilgo Beach slayings, &lt;strong&gt;Rex Heuermann&lt;/strong&gt;, a New York City architect, now faces murder charges, after a cheek swab DNA matched a sample found on a discarded pizza box outside his Manhattan firm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-disconcerting-revelation&quot;&gt;A Disconcerting Revelation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The picturesque sands of Gilgo Beach have been overshadowed by the macabre discovery of multiple bodies, linking to the allegedly sinister actions of Heuermann. For years, the grim events at the beach have left locals and the nation in anticipation of justice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;pizza-box-becomes-a-key-evidence&quot;&gt;Pizza Box Becomes a Key Evidence&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The pizza box, an unlikely piece of evidence, was discarded by Heuermann before his arrest in July and subsequently seized by the FBI. This seemingly mundane object became the lynchpin in connecting him to the gruesome crimes at Gilgo Beach, showcasing that sometimes justice has unconventional allies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The revelation came to light on a Wednesday morning in court, where Suffolk County District Attorney Ray Tierney confirmed that the DNA evidence is consistent with their expectations. In reaction to this breakthrough, defense attorneys, Danielle Coysh and Mike Brown, who had initially objected to the cheek swab, have been left to reconsider their defense strategy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;victims-of-the-beach&quot;&gt;Victims of the Beach&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Megan Waterman, 22, vanished in 2010, leaving behind only snippets of her presence on security videos from a hotel in Hauppauge, New York. Along with her, Amber Costello, 27, and Melissa Barthelemy, 24, also met their tragic ends at the beach, their remains discovered in chilling proximity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;investigative-trails-and-more-victims&quot;&gt;Investigative Trails and More Victims&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The relentless pursuit of justice by investigators involved correlating phone records, descriptions from acquaintances of the victims, and unraveling the connection to Heuermann. His notoriety might extend further as he is the prime suspect in the death of another woman, Maureen Brainard-Barnes, 25, discovered near the initial crime scene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Investigations commenced with the search for another missing woman, Shannan Gilbert, leading to the uncovering of the horrifying scenes at the beach. The coastal area has unveiled six other bodies, adding more grim chapters to the Gilgo Beach mystery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;awaiting-justice&quot;&gt;Awaiting Justice&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Heuermann has refuted the six counts of murder charged against him, maintaining his stance of not guilty. If convicted, a life sentence without the prospect of parole looms over him, and he remains in custody without bail at the Suffolk County Jail in Yaphank.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This journey of justice, from an abandoned pizza box to courtrooms, echoes the persistent clamor for answers and resolution for the victims of the Gilgo Beach horror. It’s a gruesome reminder that sometimes, justice and revelation lie in the most unexpected places. The developments in this case could finally bring solace to the haunted sands of Gilgo Beach and the lingering souls seeking peace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Heuermann is due back in court on Nov. 15, and the world watches, hoping for the curtains to fall on this long-standing mystery. The startling revelations and ongoing investigations continue to hold the nation in suspense, as we collectively hope for clarity and justice in the unsettling saga of Gilgo Beach.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a startling development in the unresolved Gilgo Beach slayings, Rex Heuermann, a New York City architect, now faces murder charges, after a cheek swab DNA matched a sample found on a discarded pizza box outside his Manhattan firm. A Disconcerting Revelation The picturesque sands of Gilgo Beach have been overshadowed by the macabre discovery of multiple bodies, linking to the allegedly sinister actions of Heuermann. For years, the grim events at the beach have left locals and the nation in anticipation of justice. Pizza Box Becomes a Key Evidence The pizza box, an unlikely piece of evidence, was discarded by Heuermann before his arrest in July and subsequently seized by the FBI. This seemingly mundane object became the lynchpin in connecting him to the gruesome crimes at Gilgo Beach, showcasing that sometimes justice has unconventional allies. The revelation came to light on a Wednesday morning in court, where Suffolk County District Attorney Ray Tierney confirmed that the DNA evidence is consistent with their expectations. In reaction to this breakthrough, defense attorneys, Danielle Coysh and Mike Brown, who had initially objected to the cheek swab, have been left to reconsider their defense strategy. Victims of the Beach Megan Waterman, 22, vanished in 2010, leaving behind only snippets of her presence on security videos from a hotel in Hauppauge, New York. Along with her, Amber Costello, 27, and Melissa Barthelemy, 24, also met their tragic ends at the beach, their remains discovered in chilling proximity. Investigative Trails and More Victims The relentless pursuit of justice by investigators involved correlating phone records, descriptions from acquaintances of the victims, and unraveling the connection to Heuermann. His notoriety might extend further as he is the prime suspect in the death of another woman, Maureen Brainard-Barnes, 25, discovered near the initial crime scene. Investigations commenced with the search for another missing woman, Shannan Gilbert, leading to the uncovering of the horrifying scenes at the beach. The coastal area has unveiled six other bodies, adding more grim chapters to the Gilgo Beach mystery. Awaiting Justice Heuermann has refuted the six counts of murder charged against him, maintaining his stance of not guilty. If convicted, a life sentence without the prospect of parole looms over him, and he remains in custody without bail at the Suffolk County Jail in Yaphank. This journey of justice, from an abandoned pizza box to courtrooms, echoes the persistent clamor for answers and resolution for the victims of the Gilgo Beach horror. It’s a gruesome reminder that sometimes, justice and revelation lie in the most unexpected places. The developments in this case could finally bring solace to the haunted sands of Gilgo Beach and the lingering souls seeking peace. Heuermann is due back in court on Nov. 15, and the world watches, hoping for the curtains to fall on this long-standing mystery. The startling revelations and ongoing investigations continue to hold the nation in suspense, as we collectively hope for clarity and justice in the unsettling saga of Gilgo Beach.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Auto Workers in Uproar - Biden’s Green Policies Fuel Strife</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/28/Auto-Worker-Strike/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Auto Workers in Uproar - Biden’s Green Policies Fuel Strife" /><published>2023-09-28T16:20:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-28T16:20:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/28/Auto-Worker-Strike</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/28/Auto-Worker-Strike/">&lt;p&gt;Doug Burgum, the Republican Governor of North Dakota, takes a stand for auto workers during the recent GOP debate, highlighting the ongoing strikes sparked by President Joe Biden’s stringent green policies, particularly focusing on electric vehicle (EV) mandates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-strife-of-detroits-auto-workers&quot;&gt;The Strife of Detroit’s Auto Workers&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gov. Burgum passionately voiced the grievances of members of the United Auto Workers (UAW) who are striking against major automotive giants—General Motors (GM), Ford, and Stellantis. He pointed out that the uproar in Detroit isn’t just about labor conditions or wages but fundamentally a protest against Biden’s interference with the capital and free markets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Biden’s policies are forcing the production of a particular type of car—we’re particularly subsidizing electric vehicles. This subsidization isn’t just affecting the type of vehicles produced but also where the essential components are sourced,” Burgum asserted during the debate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;chinas-dominance-in-ev-production&quot;&gt;China’s Dominance in EV Production&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;China presently holds the reins of the EV supply chain, manufacturing critical components vital for EV batteries. Their control spans over significant portions of the world’s lithium, manganese, cobalt, graphite, and nickel, elements essential for the production of EVs. Burgum highlighted that this control extends to nearly every facet of an EV battery’s parts, reflecting China’s dominance in this sector.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The batteries for these subsidized cars are predominantly sourced from China, which controls 85 percent of the rare-earth minerals. This dominance ensures that EVs sold in the U.S. market are, in one form or another, produced or sourced in China,” stated Burgum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;bidens-green-policies-and-the-subsequent-fallout&quot;&gt;Biden’s Green Policies and the Subsequent Fallout&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The widespread adoption of Biden’s Inflation Reduction Act is facilitating automakers with extensive tax credits for electric vehicles produced in North America, translating to an economic boon for the manufacturers. However, this act is not just reshaping the automotive landscape but is anticipated to obliterate millions of American auto jobs due to the shift from combustion engines to electric vehicles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The shift to EVs necessitates two-thirds fewer workers to manufacture a car, and Biden’s policies are precipitating this transformation,” explained Burgum. He emphasized that the strikes are a direct consequence of these policies, which are putting the jobs of millions of auto workers at risk, making it imperative to scrutinize and reassess these green mandates closely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;impact-on-american-workers&quot;&gt;Impact on American Workers&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The transition to electric vehicles is not just a simple switch in energy sources; it is a radical transformation in the production processes, labor requirements, and supply chain dynamics, with profound implications for American workers, especially those in the automotive sector.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-call-for-rational-policies&quot;&gt;The Call for Rational Policies&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Burgum’s remarks underline the necessity for rational and worker-friendly policies that don’t just consider environmental aspects but also evaluate the socio-economic repercussions on the American working class. The implications of these policies necessitate a balanced approach to ensure that the transition to greener technologies doesn’t escalate into widespread social and economic upheaval.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ongoing strikes and the distress among the American auto workers mirror the pressing need to refine and reconsider policies, balancing ecological concerns with the well-being and prospects of the American workforce.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Doug Burgum, the Republican Governor of North Dakota, takes a stand for auto workers during the recent GOP debate, highlighting the ongoing strikes sparked by President Joe Biden’s stringent green policies, particularly focusing on electric vehicle (EV) mandates. The Strife of Detroit’s Auto Workers Gov. Burgum passionately voiced the grievances of members of the United Auto Workers (UAW) who are striking against major automotive giants—General Motors (GM), Ford, and Stellantis. He pointed out that the uproar in Detroit isn’t just about labor conditions or wages but fundamentally a protest against Biden’s interference with the capital and free markets. “Biden’s policies are forcing the production of a particular type of car—we’re particularly subsidizing electric vehicles. This subsidization isn’t just affecting the type of vehicles produced but also where the essential components are sourced,” Burgum asserted during the debate. China’s Dominance in EV Production China presently holds the reins of the EV supply chain, manufacturing critical components vital for EV batteries. Their control spans over significant portions of the world’s lithium, manganese, cobalt, graphite, and nickel, elements essential for the production of EVs. Burgum highlighted that this control extends to nearly every facet of an EV battery’s parts, reflecting China’s dominance in this sector. “The batteries for these subsidized cars are predominantly sourced from China, which controls 85 percent of the rare-earth minerals. This dominance ensures that EVs sold in the U.S. market are, in one form or another, produced or sourced in China,” stated Burgum. Biden’s Green Policies and the Subsequent Fallout The widespread adoption of Biden’s Inflation Reduction Act is facilitating automakers with extensive tax credits for electric vehicles produced in North America, translating to an economic boon for the manufacturers. However, this act is not just reshaping the automotive landscape but is anticipated to obliterate millions of American auto jobs due to the shift from combustion engines to electric vehicles. “The shift to EVs necessitates two-thirds fewer workers to manufacture a car, and Biden’s policies are precipitating this transformation,” explained Burgum. He emphasized that the strikes are a direct consequence of these policies, which are putting the jobs of millions of auto workers at risk, making it imperative to scrutinize and reassess these green mandates closely. Impact on American Workers The transition to electric vehicles is not just a simple switch in energy sources; it is a radical transformation in the production processes, labor requirements, and supply chain dynamics, with profound implications for American workers, especially those in the automotive sector. The Call for Rational Policies Burgum’s remarks underline the necessity for rational and worker-friendly policies that don’t just consider environmental aspects but also evaluate the socio-economic repercussions on the American working class. The implications of these policies necessitate a balanced approach to ensure that the transition to greener technologies doesn’t escalate into widespread social and economic upheaval. The ongoing strikes and the distress among the American auto workers mirror the pressing need to refine and reconsider policies, balancing ecological concerns with the well-being and prospects of the American workforce.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Oversight Urgency - Rand Paul Demands Monitoring for Ukraine Aid</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/28/Ukraine-Aid-Inspection/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Oversight Urgency - Rand Paul Demands Monitoring for Ukraine Aid" /><published>2023-09-28T15:19:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-28T15:19:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/28/Ukraine-Aid-Inspection</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/28/Ukraine-Aid-Inspection/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;tightening-the-reins-on-ukraine-aid&quot;&gt;Tightening the Reins on Ukraine Aid&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Republican Senator Rand Paul has brought a pressing matter to the spotlight—&lt;strong&gt;the necessity for rigorous scrutiny over the United States’ security assistance and weapons sent to Ukraine.&lt;/strong&gt; He vocalized this concern on “The Record With Greta Van Susteren” on Newsmax, emphasizing the urgent need to end the sending of billions in unmonitored aid to Ukraine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-need-for-a-watchful-eye&quot;&gt;The Need for a Watchful Eye&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Paul keenly noted that during the final years of the Afghanistan war, a special inspector general was appointed for Afghanistan reconstruction to oversee the expenditures made to the allied government. He reflected on his encounters with John F. Sopko, the executive of the agency since 2012, and his team of experts who have unearthed &lt;strong&gt;billions of dollars wasted and stolen in Afghanistan.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“I think we should have an inspector general monitoring the money. It’s the least we can do,”&lt;/em&gt; he stated, pointing out Ukraine’s reputation as one of the most corrupt nations globally. Senator Paul believes that someone of Sopko’s calibre would be apt to lead a similar investigation into the aid sent to Ukraine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-strenuous-battle-for-accountability&quot;&gt;A Strenuous Battle for Accountability&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Senator Paul’s endeavours to establish an Inspector General (IG) faced a setback in May, despite his assertive attempts to hold up billions in aid. The ongoing issue has escalated, becoming a significant point of contention, as he continues to champion for systematic oversight on the financial assistance sent, insisting that such a measure is crucial given the substantial amounts involved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;delving-into-the-figures&quot;&gt;Delving into the Figures&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to the Council on Foreign Relations, the U.S. has sent a whopping &lt;strong&gt;$46.6 billion to Ukraine&lt;/strong&gt; between January 24, 2022, and July 31, 2023, in addition to $26.4 billion in financial aid and $3.9 billion in humanitarian aid. The senate’s recent proposal also includes an additional $6.1 billion for Ukraine, against which Paul was one of the 19 Republicans who voted, but it was passed 77-19.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;congressional-rush-and-urgency&quot;&gt;Congressional Rush and Urgency&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With Congress hastily trying to enact a temporary spending bill to keep the government running until late November or early December, this would give lawmakers the opportunity to refine a long-term bill, adding a layer of urgency to Senator Paul’s appeal for increased oversight on the aid sent to Ukraine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;final-thoughts-on-enhanced-oversight-for-ukraine-aid-allocation&quot;&gt;Final Thoughts on Enhanced Oversight for Ukraine Aid Allocation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Senator Rand Paul’s call for a Special Inspector General is not just a demand for accountability but a symbol of the urgent reform needed in the allocation and monitoring of aid. It reflects a broader need for transparency and diligence in international aid, especially in regions with a history of corruption, ensuring that the aid provided is utilized effectively and reaches those in genuine need.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Tightening the Reins on Ukraine Aid Republican Senator Rand Paul has brought a pressing matter to the spotlight—the necessity for rigorous scrutiny over the United States’ security assistance and weapons sent to Ukraine. He vocalized this concern on “The Record With Greta Van Susteren” on Newsmax, emphasizing the urgent need to end the sending of billions in unmonitored aid to Ukraine. The Need for a Watchful Eye Paul keenly noted that during the final years of the Afghanistan war, a special inspector general was appointed for Afghanistan reconstruction to oversee the expenditures made to the allied government. He reflected on his encounters with John F. Sopko, the executive of the agency since 2012, and his team of experts who have unearthed billions of dollars wasted and stolen in Afghanistan. “I think we should have an inspector general monitoring the money. It’s the least we can do,” he stated, pointing out Ukraine’s reputation as one of the most corrupt nations globally. Senator Paul believes that someone of Sopko’s calibre would be apt to lead a similar investigation into the aid sent to Ukraine. A Strenuous Battle for Accountability Senator Paul’s endeavours to establish an Inspector General (IG) faced a setback in May, despite his assertive attempts to hold up billions in aid. The ongoing issue has escalated, becoming a significant point of contention, as he continues to champion for systematic oversight on the financial assistance sent, insisting that such a measure is crucial given the substantial amounts involved. Delving into the Figures According to the Council on Foreign Relations, the U.S. has sent a whopping $46.6 billion to Ukraine between January 24, 2022, and July 31, 2023, in addition to $26.4 billion in financial aid and $3.9 billion in humanitarian aid. The senate’s recent proposal also includes an additional $6.1 billion for Ukraine, against which Paul was one of the 19 Republicans who voted, but it was passed 77-19. Congressional Rush and Urgency With Congress hastily trying to enact a temporary spending bill to keep the government running until late November or early December, this would give lawmakers the opportunity to refine a long-term bill, adding a layer of urgency to Senator Paul’s appeal for increased oversight on the aid sent to Ukraine. Final Thoughts on Enhanced Oversight for Ukraine Aid Allocation Senator Rand Paul’s call for a Special Inspector General is not just a demand for accountability but a symbol of the urgent reform needed in the allocation and monitoring of aid. It reflects a broader need for transparency and diligence in international aid, especially in regions with a history of corruption, ensuring that the aid provided is utilized effectively and reaches those in genuine need.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Lights, Camera, Action Again - Hollywood Writers Strike Reaches Resolution!</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/28/Hollywood-Writers-Strike-Ends/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Lights, Camera, Action Again - Hollywood Writers Strike Reaches Resolution!" /><published>2023-09-28T14:26:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-28T14:26:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/28/Hollywood-Writers-Strike-Ends</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/28/Hollywood-Writers-Strike-Ends/">&lt;p&gt;After 148 tension-filled days, Hollywood is set to spring back to life as the Writers Guild of America (WGA) resolves to lift the strike that brought the entertainment industry to a standstill. The official end to this nearly five-month-long disruption means that the wheels of Hollywood’s creation machine are finally starting to turn again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-new-beginning-for-hollywood-writers&quot;&gt;A New Beginning for Hollywood Writers&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Following intense negotiations, the union leadership authorized its 11,500 members to get back to the grind, giving the green light to tasks that had been prohibited due to the strike rules, such as pitching and selling scripts, taking meetings, and responding to notes. Writers’ rooms can also reconvene, marking the end of a period of stagnation and the beginning of new creative endeavors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-road-to-agreement&quot;&gt;The Road to Agreement&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The strike was mainly spurred by disagreements over various aspects like minimum staffing in television writers’ rooms and compensation for the success of projects on streaming platforms. Artificial intelligence also became a point of contention during the discussions. However, a compromise was reached, allowing writers to resume work while the ratification process continues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the end of the WGA strike, Hollywood may still face disruptions due to the ongoing SAG-AFTRA strike, which kicked off in July. Both unions have been manifesting strength, resilience, and solidarity on the picket lines, keeping the hopes of a fair deal alive. SAG-AFTRA has expressed its congratulations to the WGA on reaching a tentative agreement but remains firm in its commitment to achieving necessary terms for its members.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-implications-and-the-future&quot;&gt;The Implications and the Future&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lifting of the strike symbolizes a positive turn for Hollywood, paving the way for the creation of new, diverse, and engaging content. Writers, now free from the constraints of the strike, can once again delve into the world of imagination and storytelling, contributing to the rich tapestry of the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the journey doesn’t end here. The union members have to cast their votes between October 2 and October 9 for the contract to become official for the next three years. Until then, the world waits with bated breath, hoping for a smooth transition to normalcy and a surge in entertainment content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;conclusion---a-collective-sigh-of-relief&quot;&gt;Conclusion - A Collective Sigh of Relief&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As Hollywood slowly starts to rev its engines again, the ending of the WGA strike brings with it a sense of optimism and anticipation. It’s a step towards revitalizing an industry that has been the source of joy, inspiration, and escape for millions around the globe. And while challenges persist, the resolve and unity displayed by the members of the industry herald a promising future, potentially filled with groundbreaking narratives and unforgettable cinematic experiences.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">After 148 tension-filled days, Hollywood is set to spring back to life as the Writers Guild of America (WGA) resolves to lift the strike that brought the entertainment industry to a standstill. The official end to this nearly five-month-long disruption means that the wheels of Hollywood’s creation machine are finally starting to turn again. A New Beginning for Hollywood Writers Following intense negotiations, the union leadership authorized its 11,500 members to get back to the grind, giving the green light to tasks that had been prohibited due to the strike rules, such as pitching and selling scripts, taking meetings, and responding to notes. Writers’ rooms can also reconvene, marking the end of a period of stagnation and the beginning of new creative endeavors. The Road to Agreement The strike was mainly spurred by disagreements over various aspects like minimum staffing in television writers’ rooms and compensation for the success of projects on streaming platforms. Artificial intelligence also became a point of contention during the discussions. However, a compromise was reached, allowing writers to resume work while the ratification process continues. Despite the end of the WGA strike, Hollywood may still face disruptions due to the ongoing SAG-AFTRA strike, which kicked off in July. Both unions have been manifesting strength, resilience, and solidarity on the picket lines, keeping the hopes of a fair deal alive. SAG-AFTRA has expressed its congratulations to the WGA on reaching a tentative agreement but remains firm in its commitment to achieving necessary terms for its members. The Implications and the Future The lifting of the strike symbolizes a positive turn for Hollywood, paving the way for the creation of new, diverse, and engaging content. Writers, now free from the constraints of the strike, can once again delve into the world of imagination and storytelling, contributing to the rich tapestry of the entertainment industry. However, the journey doesn’t end here. The union members have to cast their votes between October 2 and October 9 for the contract to become official for the next three years. Until then, the world waits with bated breath, hoping for a smooth transition to normalcy and a surge in entertainment content. Conclusion - A Collective Sigh of Relief As Hollywood slowly starts to rev its engines again, the ending of the WGA strike brings with it a sense of optimism and anticipation. It’s a step towards revitalizing an industry that has been the source of joy, inspiration, and escape for millions around the globe. And while challenges persist, the resolve and unity displayed by the members of the industry herald a promising future, potentially filled with groundbreaking narratives and unforgettable cinematic experiences.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A Long-awaited Break - Remains of Colorado’s Missing Mom Suzanne Morphew Found</title><link href="/news/2023/09/28/Colorados-Missing-Mom/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Long-awaited Break - Remains of Colorado’s Missing Mom Suzanne Morphew Found" /><published>2023-09-28T13:17:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-28T13:17:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/28/Colorados-Missing-Mom</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/28/Colorados-Missing-Mom/">&lt;p&gt;The mysterious case of Suzanne Morphew, a Colorado mother who disappeared without a trace over three years ago, has haunted the nation and particularly affected the local community. Suzanne vanished during a bike ride on Mother’s Day in 2020, leaving friends, family, and the entire nation in suspense and sorrow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;discovery-in-saguache-county&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Discovery in Saguache County&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After three long and painful years, the Colorado Bureau of Investigation (CBI) revealed that Suzanne’s remains have been positively identified, discovered in the remote Saguache County in the southwestern part of the state. This discovery has provided some closure, albeit sorrowful, to a case that has lingered in the public consciousness since her disappearance, generating theories, rumors, and a myriad of unanswered questions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-community-mourns&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Community Mourns&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chaffee County Sheriff John Spezze expressed the depth of impact Suzanne’s disappearance and death had on the community, emphasizing the continuous efforts by the sheriff’s office in pursuit of justice for Suzanne. Despite the numerous speculations and global attention, the investigation never ceased, with every possible lead pursued fervently. The discovery of Suzanne’s remains may be a significant breakthrough, but it has left the community with more questions than answers, and the pursuit of truth continues relentlessly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;suzanne-and-barry-morphews-troubled-relationship&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Suzanne and Barry Morphew’s Troubled Relationship&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Prosecutors initially accused Barry Morphew, Suzanne’s husband, of murdering her after discovering her intentions to leave him. However, these charges were later dropped in April 2022. Subsequently, text messages surfaced, revealing Suzanne’s affairs and suspicions about Barry’s fidelity, shedding light on the turbulent dynamics between the couple. Suzanne’s messages to her alleged lover, Jeff Libler, exposed her emotional state and her craving for connection, love, and time with him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;legal-repercussions-and-continuous-search-for-justice&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Legal Repercussions and Continuous Search for Justice&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Barry Morphew, following the drop of charges, filed a lawsuit against the prosecutors for the wrongful arrest, claiming innocence and asserting the distress he suffered due to the allegations. The judicial system and law enforcement agencies continue to navigate through this complex and highly scrutinized case, ensuring that justice is served, and the truth unveiled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-journey-to-justice&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Journey to Justice&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The loss of Suzanne Morphew is a tragedy that resonates deeply with people around the world. The ongoing pursuit of justice is not just for Suzanne, but for every missing person whose disappearance remains unsolved. The community, family, friends, and the multitude following the case are left yearning for answers, clinging to hope that justice will be served, and the truth about Suzanne’s untimely demise will finally come to light.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;closure-and-reflection&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Closure and Reflection&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the world reflects on the heartbreaking outcome of Suzanne Morphew’s disappearance, it’s crucial to continue supporting the ongoing investigations and to maintain hope for justice. Suzanne’s story is a poignant reminder of the numerous unsolved disappearances occurring globally, emphasizing the importance of community solidarity, relentless pursuit of the truth, and unwavering hope in the face of tragedy. The discovery of Suzanne’s remains is a step towards closure, but the journey to full understanding and justice is far from over.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">The mysterious case of Suzanne Morphew, a Colorado mother who disappeared without a trace over three years ago, has haunted the nation and particularly affected the local community. Suzanne vanished during a bike ride on Mother’s Day in 2020, leaving friends, family, and the entire nation in suspense and sorrow. Discovery in Saguache County After three long and painful years, the Colorado Bureau of Investigation (CBI) revealed that Suzanne’s remains have been positively identified, discovered in the remote Saguache County in the southwestern part of the state. This discovery has provided some closure, albeit sorrowful, to a case that has lingered in the public consciousness since her disappearance, generating theories, rumors, and a myriad of unanswered questions. A Community Mourns Chaffee County Sheriff John Spezze expressed the depth of impact Suzanne’s disappearance and death had on the community, emphasizing the continuous efforts by the sheriff’s office in pursuit of justice for Suzanne. Despite the numerous speculations and global attention, the investigation never ceased, with every possible lead pursued fervently. The discovery of Suzanne’s remains may be a significant breakthrough, but it has left the community with more questions than answers, and the pursuit of truth continues relentlessly. Suzanne and Barry Morphew’s Troubled Relationship Prosecutors initially accused Barry Morphew, Suzanne’s husband, of murdering her after discovering her intentions to leave him. However, these charges were later dropped in April 2022. Subsequently, text messages surfaced, revealing Suzanne’s affairs and suspicions about Barry’s fidelity, shedding light on the turbulent dynamics between the couple. Suzanne’s messages to her alleged lover, Jeff Libler, exposed her emotional state and her craving for connection, love, and time with him. Legal Repercussions and Continuous Search for Justice Barry Morphew, following the drop of charges, filed a lawsuit against the prosecutors for the wrongful arrest, claiming innocence and asserting the distress he suffered due to the allegations. The judicial system and law enforcement agencies continue to navigate through this complex and highly scrutinized case, ensuring that justice is served, and the truth unveiled. The Journey to Justice The loss of Suzanne Morphew is a tragedy that resonates deeply with people around the world. The ongoing pursuit of justice is not just for Suzanne, but for every missing person whose disappearance remains unsolved. The community, family, friends, and the multitude following the case are left yearning for answers, clinging to hope that justice will be served, and the truth about Suzanne’s untimely demise will finally come to light. Closure and Reflection As the world reflects on the heartbreaking outcome of Suzanne Morphew’s disappearance, it’s crucial to continue supporting the ongoing investigations and to maintain hope for justice. Suzanne’s story is a poignant reminder of the numerous unsolved disappearances occurring globally, emphasizing the importance of community solidarity, relentless pursuit of the truth, and unwavering hope in the face of tragedy. The discovery of Suzanne’s remains is a step towards closure, but the journey to full understanding and justice is far from over.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Triumph and Taunts - Trump Labels GOP Rivals as Mere ‘Job Candidates’</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/28/Trump-GOP-Debate/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Triumph and Taunts - Trump Labels GOP Rivals as Mere ‘Job Candidates’" /><published>2023-09-28T12:09:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-28T12:09:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/28/Trump-GOP-Debate</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/28/Trump-GOP-Debate/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;trumps-triumphant-return&quot;&gt;Trump’s Triumphant Return&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Former President Donald Trump, unabashed and more confident than ever, made a powerful appearance before autoworkers and the working-class citizens of Michigan on Wednesday night. His demeanor and words displayed clear dominance, as he joyously reflected on his substantial lead in the Republican presidential primary polls.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;playful-jabs-at-gop-hopefuls&quot;&gt;Playful Jabs at GOP Hopefuls&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trump’s speech, broadcasted live and in full on Newsmax, was marked by his characteristic blend of humor and daring jabs at his GOP rivals. Speaking to a spirited crowd in Clinton Township at Drake Enterprises, a non-unionized auto parts supplier, he playfully referred to his GOP challengers as mere “job candidates,” aspiring for a role in his administration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“They’re all job candidates, they want to be in the — they’ll do anything. Secretary of something,”&lt;/em&gt; Trump remarked, highlighting the perceived desperation and ambition of his challengers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;vp-possibilities--a-resounding-no&quot;&gt;VP Possibilities – A Resounding ‘No’&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trump was subtle yet impactful in his dismissal of his rivals as potential running mates. He reiterated his commitment to not consider anyone running against him as his next vice president, making it clear that he sees no worthy candidate for the VP role among the group.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“They even say VP, does anybody see any VP in the group?” Trump queried the crowd, adding, “I don’t think so,”&lt;/em&gt; thereby expressing his discerning stance on the caliber of his competition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-statement-of-confidence&quot;&gt;A Statement of Confidence&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trump’s remarks and his casual, yet disparaging references to his rivals are indicative of his confidence in his political journey. His approach, exuding assurance and supremacy, sends a potent message about his stance in the political arena, depicting him as a leader who is secure in his position and unthreatened by his competition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;reflections-on-political-dynamics&quot;&gt;Reflections on Political Dynamics&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The gathering in Michigan was not just about political commentary but also a reflection of the underlying dynamics and competition within the GOP. Trump’s unequivocal expressions and his assertive disposition were a display of the ongoing power play and the intricate relationships within the Republican camp.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;concluding-thoughts&quot;&gt;Concluding Thoughts&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This event, marked by Trump’s triumphant tones and playful yet piercing remarks, unveiled the prevailing sentiments and the vibrant interplay within the GOP. It was a clear representation of Trump’s robust political positioning and his unwavering confidence in his leadership capabilities, underlining the intensifying journey towards the upcoming presidential race.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Trump’s Triumphant Return Former President Donald Trump, unabashed and more confident than ever, made a powerful appearance before autoworkers and the working-class citizens of Michigan on Wednesday night. His demeanor and words displayed clear dominance, as he joyously reflected on his substantial lead in the Republican presidential primary polls. Playful Jabs at GOP Hopefuls Trump’s speech, broadcasted live and in full on Newsmax, was marked by his characteristic blend of humor and daring jabs at his GOP rivals. Speaking to a spirited crowd in Clinton Township at Drake Enterprises, a non-unionized auto parts supplier, he playfully referred to his GOP challengers as mere “job candidates,” aspiring for a role in his administration. “They’re all job candidates, they want to be in the — they’ll do anything. Secretary of something,” Trump remarked, highlighting the perceived desperation and ambition of his challengers. VP Possibilities – A Resounding ‘No’ Trump was subtle yet impactful in his dismissal of his rivals as potential running mates. He reiterated his commitment to not consider anyone running against him as his next vice president, making it clear that he sees no worthy candidate for the VP role among the group. “They even say VP, does anybody see any VP in the group?” Trump queried the crowd, adding, “I don’t think so,” thereby expressing his discerning stance on the caliber of his competition. A Statement of Confidence Trump’s remarks and his casual, yet disparaging references to his rivals are indicative of his confidence in his political journey. His approach, exuding assurance and supremacy, sends a potent message about his stance in the political arena, depicting him as a leader who is secure in his position and unthreatened by his competition. Reflections on Political Dynamics The gathering in Michigan was not just about political commentary but also a reflection of the underlying dynamics and competition within the GOP. Trump’s unequivocal expressions and his assertive disposition were a display of the ongoing power play and the intricate relationships within the Republican camp. Concluding Thoughts This event, marked by Trump’s triumphant tones and playful yet piercing remarks, unveiled the prevailing sentiments and the vibrant interplay within the GOP. It was a clear representation of Trump’s robust political positioning and his unwavering confidence in his leadership capabilities, underlining the intensifying journey towards the upcoming presidential race.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A Fresh Start - How AI is Revolutionizing TV and Diminishing Bias</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/28/AI-Revolutionizing-Television/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Fresh Start - How AI is Revolutionizing TV and Diminishing Bias" /><published>2023-09-28T11:04:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-28T11:04:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/28/AI-Revolutionizing-Television</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/28/AI-Revolutionizing-Television/">&lt;p&gt;In a landscape cluttered with subjective narratives and biased reportage, Artificial Intelligence (AI) emerges as a beacon of transformation, disrupting the conventional television medium and liberating viewers from the entrenched viewpoints of traditional cable TV.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;ai---curtailing-biased-narratives&quot;&gt;AI - Curtailing Biased Narratives&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AI is pioneering a revolutionary shift in television consumption, opening up avenues for diverse and balanced content, thereby mitigating the omnipresence of left-leaning bias prevalent in mainstream cable channels like CNN, Comedy Central, and MTV. This shift not only marks the decline of one-sided narratives but also brings forth a more equitable and balanced media landscape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;personalized-and-viewer-centric-experiences&quot;&gt;Personalized and Viewer-Centric Experiences&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Advanced streaming services such as Netflix, Apple, and Amazon, are employing AI to analyze intricate patterns of viewer habits, preferences, and interactions. This allows them to curate and recommend content that aligns with individual tastes, ensuring an engaging and tailored viewing experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;streaming---a-merit-based-platform&quot;&gt;Streaming - A Merit-Based Platform&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Streaming services, propelled by the precision and intelligence of AI, operate on merit-based frameworks, unlike cable TV which often elevates content not on merit, but on other discretionary and biased parameters. Streaming platforms must earn their keep through direct subscription fees, bringing forth content that genuinely resonates with viewers, free from the artificial sustenance provided by cable networks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the AI-driven streaming domain, the success of content is exclusively determined by its intrinsic quality and viewer appeal. This is in stark contrast to cable TV, where the rigidity and constraints of the medium often lead to the proliferation of subpar content, benefiting from a system that isn’t fully reflective of genuine viewer preference or merit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;dismantling-traditional-media-monoliths&quot;&gt;Dismantling Traditional Media Monoliths&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The innovative intervention of AI is signaling the gradual obsolescence of conventional media outlets that have long thrived on one-dimensional and skewed representations. Channels sustained by cable TV, despite their limited viewership and appeal, are facing an inevitable decline, pressured by the ascendancy of meritocratic streaming services and the equitable media environment enabled by AI.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the emerging landscape, AI is empowering viewers to break free from the monopolistic grip of mainstream cable narratives and to explore a diverse array of content that is more harmonious with their preferences and values. This transition represents not merely a technological advancement but a societal progression towards a more balanced and unbiased media ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;final-thoughts&quot;&gt;Final Thoughts&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As AI continues to redefine the television experience, it’s bringing to light the inherent shortcomings and biases of traditional media outlets, encouraging a move towards more impartial and viewer-centric platforms. The advent of AI is a step towards a future where media is not a tool for propagating singular viewpoints but a diverse and balanced space, echoing the varied voices and perspectives of the global audience.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">In a landscape cluttered with subjective narratives and biased reportage, Artificial Intelligence (AI) emerges as a beacon of transformation, disrupting the conventional television medium and liberating viewers from the entrenched viewpoints of traditional cable TV. AI - Curtailing Biased Narratives AI is pioneering a revolutionary shift in television consumption, opening up avenues for diverse and balanced content, thereby mitigating the omnipresence of left-leaning bias prevalent in mainstream cable channels like CNN, Comedy Central, and MTV. This shift not only marks the decline of one-sided narratives but also brings forth a more equitable and balanced media landscape. Personalized and Viewer-Centric Experiences Advanced streaming services such as Netflix, Apple, and Amazon, are employing AI to analyze intricate patterns of viewer habits, preferences, and interactions. This allows them to curate and recommend content that aligns with individual tastes, ensuring an engaging and tailored viewing experience. Streaming - A Merit-Based Platform Streaming services, propelled by the precision and intelligence of AI, operate on merit-based frameworks, unlike cable TV which often elevates content not on merit, but on other discretionary and biased parameters. Streaming platforms must earn their keep through direct subscription fees, bringing forth content that genuinely resonates with viewers, free from the artificial sustenance provided by cable networks. In the AI-driven streaming domain, the success of content is exclusively determined by its intrinsic quality and viewer appeal. This is in stark contrast to cable TV, where the rigidity and constraints of the medium often lead to the proliferation of subpar content, benefiting from a system that isn’t fully reflective of genuine viewer preference or merit. Dismantling Traditional Media Monoliths The innovative intervention of AI is signaling the gradual obsolescence of conventional media outlets that have long thrived on one-dimensional and skewed representations. Channels sustained by cable TV, despite their limited viewership and appeal, are facing an inevitable decline, pressured by the ascendancy of meritocratic streaming services and the equitable media environment enabled by AI. In the emerging landscape, AI is empowering viewers to break free from the monopolistic grip of mainstream cable narratives and to explore a diverse array of content that is more harmonious with their preferences and values. This transition represents not merely a technological advancement but a societal progression towards a more balanced and unbiased media ecosystem. Final Thoughts As AI continues to redefine the television experience, it’s bringing to light the inherent shortcomings and biases of traditional media outlets, encouraging a move towards more impartial and viewer-centric platforms. The advent of AI is a step towards a future where media is not a tool for propagating singular viewpoints but a diverse and balanced space, echoing the varied voices and perspectives of the global audience.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Unrest Unleashed - Philadelphia Grapples with Mass Looting</title><link href="/news/2023/09/28/City-Unrest-Philadelphia/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Unrest Unleashed - Philadelphia Grapples with Mass Looting" /><published>2023-09-28T10:15:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-28T10:15:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/28/City-Unrest-Philadelphia</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/28/City-Unrest-Philadelphia/">&lt;p&gt;The city of Brotherly Love found itself amidst turmoil and chaos as groups, predominantly consisting of teenagers, orchestrated a series of lootings across various stores in Philadelphia, leaving a trail of destruction and stolen goods behind. This mass looting phenomenon targeted major retail outlets, including an Apple store, Foot Locker, and Lululemon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;sickening-display-of-opportunism&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sickening Display of Opportunism&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Philadelphia’s Mayor, Jim Kenney, and Interim Police Commissioner John Stanford, have vehemently condemned the acts of coordinated looting that ravaged the city. “This was a sickening display of opportunistic criminal activity, and we will not stand for it,” declared Mayor Kenney, asserting the city’s stance against such destructive behavior.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;swift-retaliation-by-law-enforcement&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Swift Retaliation by Law Enforcement&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With rapid response, the Philadelphia Police Department apprehended between 15 to 20 individuals involved in the flash-mob style ransacking of stores, displaying their commitment to maintaining public safety and order. Further investigations are underway, focusing on a possible connection between various vehicles moving from location to location during the looting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-city-in-anguish&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A City in Anguish&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This coordinated criminal activity sparked immense anger and frustration among city officials and citizens alike. Commissioner Stanford likened the incidents to the widespread protests and civil unrest that occurred in the aftermath of George Floyd’s death in 2020. “Everyone in this city should be angry,” emphasized Stanford, underscoring the impact such incidents have on the community and local businesses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;coordinated-criminal-activity&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Coordinated Criminal Activity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The incidents were a calculated effort by criminals seeking to exploit a situation, separate from a peaceful protest that took place after the dismissal of charges against a Philadelphia police officer. Videos surfacing on social media displayed masked individuals, armed with hoodies, swiftly entering stores, seizing merchandise, and fleeing the scene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;citys-resolve-to-restore-order&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;City’s Resolve to Restore Order&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite the unrest and disruption caused by the looting, the city’s resolve remains unbroken. Mayor Kenney extended his gratitude to the Philadelphia Police Department for its rapid and efficient response in dispersing crowds and making arrests related to the night’s incidents. He pledged that such criminal opportunism aimed at destroying the city would not be tolerated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;continued-vigilance&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Continued Vigilance&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Philadelphia Police Department remains vigilant and is actively investigating these incidents to prevent any future occurrences of such disruptive and criminal behavior. “The Philadelphia Police Department is committed to maintaining public safety and order,” the department stated, reflecting the city’s determination to protect its citizens and businesses from the plague of coordinated criminal activity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The aftermath of these looting incidents leaves a city grappling with restoring order and ensuring the safety of its residents, reflecting a broader national discourse on civil unrest and coordinated criminal activity. In these trying times, the commitment and resolve of Philadelphia’s officials and law enforcement are a beacon of hope for the beleaguered city.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">The city of Brotherly Love found itself amidst turmoil and chaos as groups, predominantly consisting of teenagers, orchestrated a series of lootings across various stores in Philadelphia, leaving a trail of destruction and stolen goods behind. This mass looting phenomenon targeted major retail outlets, including an Apple store, Foot Locker, and Lululemon. Sickening Display of Opportunism Philadelphia’s Mayor, Jim Kenney, and Interim Police Commissioner John Stanford, have vehemently condemned the acts of coordinated looting that ravaged the city. “This was a sickening display of opportunistic criminal activity, and we will not stand for it,” declared Mayor Kenney, asserting the city’s stance against such destructive behavior. Swift Retaliation by Law Enforcement With rapid response, the Philadelphia Police Department apprehended between 15 to 20 individuals involved in the flash-mob style ransacking of stores, displaying their commitment to maintaining public safety and order. Further investigations are underway, focusing on a possible connection between various vehicles moving from location to location during the looting. A City in Anguish This coordinated criminal activity sparked immense anger and frustration among city officials and citizens alike. Commissioner Stanford likened the incidents to the widespread protests and civil unrest that occurred in the aftermath of George Floyd’s death in 2020. “Everyone in this city should be angry,” emphasized Stanford, underscoring the impact such incidents have on the community and local businesses. Coordinated Criminal Activity The incidents were a calculated effort by criminals seeking to exploit a situation, separate from a peaceful protest that took place after the dismissal of charges against a Philadelphia police officer. Videos surfacing on social media displayed masked individuals, armed with hoodies, swiftly entering stores, seizing merchandise, and fleeing the scene. City’s Resolve to Restore Order Despite the unrest and disruption caused by the looting, the city’s resolve remains unbroken. Mayor Kenney extended his gratitude to the Philadelphia Police Department for its rapid and efficient response in dispersing crowds and making arrests related to the night’s incidents. He pledged that such criminal opportunism aimed at destroying the city would not be tolerated. Continued Vigilance The Philadelphia Police Department remains vigilant and is actively investigating these incidents to prevent any future occurrences of such disruptive and criminal behavior. “The Philadelphia Police Department is committed to maintaining public safety and order,” the department stated, reflecting the city’s determination to protect its citizens and businesses from the plague of coordinated criminal activity. The aftermath of these looting incidents leaves a city grappling with restoring order and ensuring the safety of its residents, reflecting a broader national discourse on civil unrest and coordinated criminal activity. In these trying times, the commitment and resolve of Philadelphia’s officials and law enforcement are a beacon of hope for the beleaguered city.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Celebrity Spotlight - Dax Shepard Slams Biden as “Insane Best Option”</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/28/Dax-Shepard-Criticism/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Celebrity Spotlight - Dax Shepard Slams Biden as “Insane Best Option”" /><published>2023-09-28T09:06:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-28T09:06:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/28/Dax-Shepard-Criticism</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/28/Dax-Shepard-Criticism/">&lt;p&gt;Renowned actor Dax Shepard boldly criticizes President Joe Biden, stating it’s “insane” he’s the country’s “best option” and declares, “It’s so embarrassing.” This explosive statement occurred during Monday’s episode of his podcast, the Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;shepards-strong-words&quot;&gt;Shepard’s Strong Words&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shepard, known for his roles in &lt;em&gt;Idiocracy&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Hit and Run&lt;/em&gt;, voiced his criticisms after witnessing a clip of Biden addressing the victims of the Maui fire. He expressed his embarrassment and refusal to be untruthful about his political stance, emphasizing his discontentment with the current administration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-fiery-debate-unveils&quot;&gt;A Fiery Debate Unveils&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jonathan Van Ness, the guest and &lt;em&gt;Queer Eye&lt;/em&gt; star, attempted to defend Biden but ended up sparking a heated debate with Shepard. Van Ness even remarked, “I will still vote Democratic, but…” indicating his internal conflict over supporting the current administration amidst the fiery discourse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;deep-emotional-moments&quot;&gt;Deep Emotional Moments&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The podcast saw intense emotional moments, particularly when the discussion shifted to transgender issues and legislation in conservative states. Van Ness, openly nonbinary and trans, expressed disappointment, frustration, and ended up in tears during the heated conversation, reflecting the deep emotional and personal impact these topics hold.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-debacle-over-sports&quot;&gt;The Debacle Over Sports&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Van Ness also highlighted the ongoing debate regarding the participation of trans individuals in sports. He passionately argued against those who find it dangerous or unfair when biological men compete against women, shifting the conversation to sports’ inherent dangers and unfairness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;shepards-relentless-criticism&quot;&gt;Shepard’s Relentless Criticism&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shepard continued to voice his concern and discontent with Biden’s comparison of a small kitchen fire he had to the devastation in Maui. He found the comparison out of context and reiterated his disappointment in Biden as the country’s leader, implying the need for more competent leadership.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-point-of-agreement&quot;&gt;A Point of Agreement&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite the emotional rollercoaster and heated disagreements, Shepard and Van Ness found a middle ground in their mutual support for some of the community concerns raised. They navigated through the debate maintaining a level of respect and understanding, although the conversation got tenser at times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This episode of the Armchair Expert shed light on the celebrities’ diverse opinions on the current administration and societal issues, reflecting the broader, multifaceted public opinion. It demonstrated the emotional and personal stakes involved in these discussions and showcased the importance of dialogue and understanding different perspectives in today’s polarized society.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Renowned actor Dax Shepard boldly criticizes President Joe Biden, stating it’s “insane” he’s the country’s “best option” and declares, “It’s so embarrassing.” This explosive statement occurred during Monday’s episode of his podcast, the Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard. Shepard’s Strong Words Shepard, known for his roles in Idiocracy and Hit and Run, voiced his criticisms after witnessing a clip of Biden addressing the victims of the Maui fire. He expressed his embarrassment and refusal to be untruthful about his political stance, emphasizing his discontentment with the current administration. A Fiery Debate Unveils Jonathan Van Ness, the guest and Queer Eye star, attempted to defend Biden but ended up sparking a heated debate with Shepard. Van Ness even remarked, “I will still vote Democratic, but…” indicating his internal conflict over supporting the current administration amidst the fiery discourse. Deep Emotional Moments The podcast saw intense emotional moments, particularly when the discussion shifted to transgender issues and legislation in conservative states. Van Ness, openly nonbinary and trans, expressed disappointment, frustration, and ended up in tears during the heated conversation, reflecting the deep emotional and personal impact these topics hold. The Debacle Over Sports Van Ness also highlighted the ongoing debate regarding the participation of trans individuals in sports. He passionately argued against those who find it dangerous or unfair when biological men compete against women, shifting the conversation to sports’ inherent dangers and unfairness. Shepard’s Relentless Criticism Shepard continued to voice his concern and discontent with Biden’s comparison of a small kitchen fire he had to the devastation in Maui. He found the comparison out of context and reiterated his disappointment in Biden as the country’s leader, implying the need for more competent leadership. A Point of Agreement Despite the emotional rollercoaster and heated disagreements, Shepard and Van Ness found a middle ground in their mutual support for some of the community concerns raised. They navigated through the debate maintaining a level of respect and understanding, although the conversation got tenser at times. Conclusion This episode of the Armchair Expert shed light on the celebrities’ diverse opinions on the current administration and societal issues, reflecting the broader, multifaceted public opinion. It demonstrated the emotional and personal stakes involved in these discussions and showcased the importance of dialogue and understanding different perspectives in today’s polarized society.</summary></entry></feed>