<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-10-18T15:12:56-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/18/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-18T15:12:56-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-18T15:12:56-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/18/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/18/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/18/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-18T15:12:56-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-18T15:12:56-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/18/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/18/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/">&lt;p&gt;Recent surprise attacks by Hamas on Israel has fueled ongoing tensions between staunchly conservative commentators and the progressive “Squad” Democrats known for criticizing Israel. The intensity of the backlash highlights the deep political divide over foreign policy in the Middle East.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Hamas’ shocking attack, several members of the “Squad,” including Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.), called for a “ceasefire and de-escalation,” condemning the violence. The absence of a statement from Rep. Rashida Tlaib (D-Mich.) was notably called out by conservative media outlets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;South Carolina GOP Rep. Nancy Mace quickly labeled Ocasio-Cortez a “Hamas apologist” in response to her call for peace and de-escalation. Rep. Ilhan Omar (D-Minn.), no stranger to controversy surrounding her views on Israel, echoed the call for de-escalation and ceasefire. Omar’s prior statements comparing the US and Israel to terrorist groups like Hamas and the Taliban resurfaced in the debate, fueling more criticisms. Omar’s 2019 tweet, where she opined that “Israel has hypnotized the world,” also continues to haunt her political career, often cited by critics to challenge her stance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conservative commentators have been especially vocal. “FOX &amp;amp; Friends Weekend” co-host Rachel Campos-Duffy took aim at Omar, saying she fails to recognize the peace in the Middle East under Trump’s administration. Conservative pundit John Hasson also called out Omar, claiming she insinuated that attacks on IDF forces were acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Massachusetts Democrat Rep. Ayanna Pressley’s concerns over the “devastating attacks on Israelis” were met with skepticism. A prominent conservative online personality, Comfortably Smug, accused the “Squad” of advising Israel to back down after the nation suffered massive attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Jamaal Bowman’s call for an end to the Gaza blockade, in addition to condemning the Hamas attacks, was met with criticism from conservative radio host Jason Rantz. He accused Bowman of pairing his condemnation of terrorism with unwarranted criticisms of Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Cori Bush emphasized the urgent need for a ceasefire, while pushing for an end to “U.S. support for Israeli military occupation and apartheid.” Defense attorney Marina Medvin criticized Bush, suggesting that she equates the death of Palestinian terrorists to the horrific acts committed against Jewish civilians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amidst the political turmoil and intense debate, the attacks have taken a heavy toll. Israeli media report over 300 dead due to the wide-ranging assault. Gaza health officials note that at least 200 Palestinians have perished in the retaliatory Israeli air strikes following the initial Hamas attack. As the situation remains volatile, both sides continue to count their casualties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This divisive issue showcases the challenge America faces in crafting a unified approach to foreign policy, with deeply entrenched political divides at play. As the situation develops, the debate is bound to intensify, shedding light on the complexities of U.S. politics in the global arena.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Alec Baldwin’s ‘Rust’ Saga: New Charges Loom as Case Reopens</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/18/Baldwin-Rust-Case-Revival/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Alec Baldwin’s ‘Rust’ Saga: New Charges Loom as Case Reopens" /><published>2023-10-18T12:58:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-18T12:58:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/18/Baldwin-Rust-Case-Revival</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/18/Baldwin-Rust-Case-Revival/">&lt;p&gt;In a turn of events that has gripped Hollywood, actor Alec Baldwin might be staring down new charges in relation to the tragic shooting that took place on the set of the movie “Rust” two years ago. New Mexico’s legal authorities have signalled their intention to present fresh evidence to a grand jury, breathing new life into a case that many believed had reached its conclusion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earlier in the year, prosecutors had shelved the involuntary manslaughter case against Baldwin. However, the tables seem to have turned again with the statement, “additional facts have come to light”, hinting at an extended investigation that unfolded over recent months.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What makes this case particularly harrowing for the film industry is the loss of cinematographer Halyna Hutchins, whose life was cut short when a gun discharged in Baldwin’s hand during a rehearsal. Joel Souza, the director of “Rust”, was also injured in this unfortunate incident.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The actual nature of these potential new charges remains shrouded in mystery. Nevertheless, reports from the New York Times indicate that the gun involved in the incident has undergone further analysis. Special prosecutors Kari Morrissey and Jason Lewis, shedding light on the matter, stated that the newfound evidence might suggest “Mr. Baldwin has criminal culpability in the death of Halyna Hutchins and the shooting of Joel Souza.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This announcement has sparked intense reactions from various quarters. Baldwin’s legal team, led by Luke Nikas and Alex Spiro, has been vocal about their disappointment, referring to the renewed interest in prosecution as a “misguided” move. Their statement read, “It is unfortunate that a terrible tragedy has been turned into this misguided prosecution. We will answer any charges in court.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the legal cloud hovering over it, “Rust” resumed its production in Montana earlier this year, and Baldwin rejoined the crew to complete the film. The release date for this indie western, however, remains undisclosed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The case has been a rollercoaster for Alec Baldwin, who has consistently asserted that the gun’s firing was unintentional. Aside from the looming criminal charges, Baldwin is also grappling with multiple civil lawsuits in connection to the on-set catastrophe.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">In a turn of events that has gripped Hollywood, actor Alec Baldwin might be staring down new charges in relation to the tragic shooting that took place on the set of the movie “Rust” two years ago. New Mexico’s legal authorities have signalled their intention to present fresh evidence to a grand jury, breathing new life into a case that many believed had reached its conclusion. Earlier in the year, prosecutors had shelved the involuntary manslaughter case against Baldwin. However, the tables seem to have turned again with the statement, “additional facts have come to light”, hinting at an extended investigation that unfolded over recent months. What makes this case particularly harrowing for the film industry is the loss of cinematographer Halyna Hutchins, whose life was cut short when a gun discharged in Baldwin’s hand during a rehearsal. Joel Souza, the director of “Rust”, was also injured in this unfortunate incident. The actual nature of these potential new charges remains shrouded in mystery. Nevertheless, reports from the New York Times indicate that the gun involved in the incident has undergone further analysis. Special prosecutors Kari Morrissey and Jason Lewis, shedding light on the matter, stated that the newfound evidence might suggest “Mr. Baldwin has criminal culpability in the death of Halyna Hutchins and the shooting of Joel Souza.” This announcement has sparked intense reactions from various quarters. Baldwin’s legal team, led by Luke Nikas and Alex Spiro, has been vocal about their disappointment, referring to the renewed interest in prosecution as a “misguided” move. Their statement read, “It is unfortunate that a terrible tragedy has been turned into this misguided prosecution. We will answer any charges in court.” Despite the legal cloud hovering over it, “Rust” resumed its production in Montana earlier this year, and Baldwin rejoined the crew to complete the film. The release date for this indie western, however, remains undisclosed. The case has been a rollercoaster for Alec Baldwin, who has consistently asserted that the gun’s firing was unintentional. Aside from the looming criminal charges, Baldwin is also grappling with multiple civil lawsuits in connection to the on-set catastrophe.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Biden’s Summit With Arab Leaders Sidetracked by Violence</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/18/Biden-Israel-Crisis/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Biden’s Summit With Arab Leaders Sidetracked by Violence" /><published>2023-10-18T11:45:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-18T11:45:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/18/Biden-Israel-Crisis</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/18/Biden-Israel-Crisis/">&lt;p&gt;In a surprising turn of events, President Joe Biden’s scheduled summit with Arab leaders was abruptly cancelled due to escalating conflict in the Israel-Hamas warfront. The move followed a tragic explosion at a Gaza hospital, claiming hundreds of lives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The White House announced that Biden would now only be visiting Israel, putting off his anticipated trip to Jordan. Palestinian leader, Mahmoud Abbas, had previously pulled out from the summit, condemning the attacks which the Hamas-run Health Ministry in Gaza attributed to an Israeli airstrike. However, the Israeli military denied any involvement, pointing to a misfired Palestinian rocket as the cause.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jordan’s response was unequivocal. Their foreign minister, Ayman Safadi, expressed deep concerns on a state-run network about the ongoing war and aggression, pushing the region towards a precipice. He emphasized that Jordan would consider hosting the summit only when all involved parties are on the same page, primarily focusing on halting the war, respecting Palestinian humanity, and delivering deserved aid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This situation underscores a mounting challenge for President Biden. As the leader of a superpower nation, the eyes of the world watch his every move. In a region fraught with tensions, Biden’s decision to personally visit showcases his commitment to a central role for the U.S. on the global stage, banking on personal diplomacy as a decisive instrument.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reflecting on Biden’s approach, Jon Alterman from the Center for Strategic and International Studies remarked, “This is how Joe Biden believes politics works and history is made.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, with the humanitarian crisis escalating, concerns are mounting over the potential expansion of the conflict beyond Gaza’s borders. Already there have been encounters on Israel’s northern frontier with Hezbollah, an Iran-backed faction stationed in Southern Lebanon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;President Biden’s journey to the region is fraught with potential pitfalls. Other U.S. officials’ visits have been disrupted due to rocket attacks into Israel. Further Israeli airstrikes in Gaza could intensify global condemnation just as Biden aims to fortify ties with a key ally.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The U.S. has subtly been amplifying its call for humanitarian assistance in Gaza amidst ongoing support for Israel. This dual stance arises from fears of worsening conditions in Gaza, leading to diminished Arab tolerance for Israel’s military actions. Such a scenario could significantly bolster Hamas and even inspire Iran to escalate its anti-Israel endeavors, potentially igniting a broader regional conflict.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a bid to bring relief, U.S. Secretary of State Antony Blinken has been working diligently with both Arab and Israeli leadership. His recent efforts resulted in an agreement outlining a strategy for humanitarian aid distribution in Gaza.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amidst these global dynamics, Biden remains steadfast in his commitment to allies. When asked about the simultaneous crises in Israel and Ukraine on CBS’ “60 Minutes”, he resolutely stated, “We’re the United States of America…We have the capacity to do this and we have an obligation to.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the upcoming days, Biden is set to meet Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu and other key officials. However, meetings with Jordan’s King Abdullah II, Egyptian President Abdel Fattah el-Sissi, and Palestinian leader Mahmoud Abbas have been shelved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the Israel-Palestinian conflict endures, the global community anxiously awaits the next steps from world leaders, with hopes for peace and stability in the region.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a surprising turn of events, President Joe Biden’s scheduled summit with Arab leaders was abruptly cancelled due to escalating conflict in the Israel-Hamas warfront. The move followed a tragic explosion at a Gaza hospital, claiming hundreds of lives. The White House announced that Biden would now only be visiting Israel, putting off his anticipated trip to Jordan. Palestinian leader, Mahmoud Abbas, had previously pulled out from the summit, condemning the attacks which the Hamas-run Health Ministry in Gaza attributed to an Israeli airstrike. However, the Israeli military denied any involvement, pointing to a misfired Palestinian rocket as the cause. Jordan’s response was unequivocal. Their foreign minister, Ayman Safadi, expressed deep concerns on a state-run network about the ongoing war and aggression, pushing the region towards a precipice. He emphasized that Jordan would consider hosting the summit only when all involved parties are on the same page, primarily focusing on halting the war, respecting Palestinian humanity, and delivering deserved aid. This situation underscores a mounting challenge for President Biden. As the leader of a superpower nation, the eyes of the world watch his every move. In a region fraught with tensions, Biden’s decision to personally visit showcases his commitment to a central role for the U.S. on the global stage, banking on personal diplomacy as a decisive instrument. Reflecting on Biden’s approach, Jon Alterman from the Center for Strategic and International Studies remarked, “This is how Joe Biden believes politics works and history is made.” However, with the humanitarian crisis escalating, concerns are mounting over the potential expansion of the conflict beyond Gaza’s borders. Already there have been encounters on Israel’s northern frontier with Hezbollah, an Iran-backed faction stationed in Southern Lebanon. President Biden’s journey to the region is fraught with potential pitfalls. Other U.S. officials’ visits have been disrupted due to rocket attacks into Israel. Further Israeli airstrikes in Gaza could intensify global condemnation just as Biden aims to fortify ties with a key ally. The U.S. has subtly been amplifying its call for humanitarian assistance in Gaza amidst ongoing support for Israel. This dual stance arises from fears of worsening conditions in Gaza, leading to diminished Arab tolerance for Israel’s military actions. Such a scenario could significantly bolster Hamas and even inspire Iran to escalate its anti-Israel endeavors, potentially igniting a broader regional conflict. In a bid to bring relief, U.S. Secretary of State Antony Blinken has been working diligently with both Arab and Israeli leadership. His recent efforts resulted in an agreement outlining a strategy for humanitarian aid distribution in Gaza. Amidst these global dynamics, Biden remains steadfast in his commitment to allies. When asked about the simultaneous crises in Israel and Ukraine on CBS’ “60 Minutes”, he resolutely stated, “We’re the United States of America…We have the capacity to do this and we have an obligation to.” In the upcoming days, Biden is set to meet Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu and other key officials. However, meetings with Jordan’s King Abdullah II, Egyptian President Abdel Fattah el-Sissi, and Palestinian leader Mahmoud Abbas have been shelved. As the Israel-Palestinian conflict endures, the global community anxiously awaits the next steps from world leaders, with hopes for peace and stability in the region.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Misuse of AI in the Courtroom? Fugees Rapper Cries Foul</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/18/AI-In-Courtroom/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Misuse of AI in the Courtroom? Fugees Rapper Cries Foul" /><published>2023-10-18T10:30:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-18T10:30:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/18/AI-In-Courtroom</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/18/AI-In-Courtroom/">&lt;p&gt;In an age where artificial intelligence is reshaping industries, the legal realm is not immune. However, the question arises - is the courtroom a suitable place for AI to play a role? The recent case of Pras Michel, a member of the iconic hip-hop group Fugees, brings this debate to the forefront.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Michel, who faced charges relating to an elaborate scheme to funnel millions in foreign funds for illicit lobbying and illegal campaign contributions allegedly at China’s behest, was convicted in April. But now, the rapper seeks a new trial. Why? He claims his then-defense attorney, David Kenner, leaned on “an experimental AI program” for his closing arguments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The alleged AI-powered argument, according to Michel, was riddled with baseless points, misconstrued the issues at hand, and glaringly overlooked critical weaknesses in the Government’s case against him. But it doesn’t stop there. Kenner allegedly took pride in the speed and efficiency of the AI tool, boasting that it condensed “hours or days of legal work into seconds.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s even more alarming is the potential conflict of interest. It’s reported that Kenner and his co-counsel had an undisclosed financial interest in the very AI program they used during Michel’s trial. Their intention? To plug the software in a press release following the trial’s conclusion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The situation raises eyebrows and ethical concerns. An attorney’s duty is to zealously represent their client and to ensure that their rights are preserved throughout the legal process. Relying on untested technology, especially with ulterior motives, might compromise this fundamental responsibility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The novelty of the AI’s application was seemingly not lost on Kenner. A press release by Eyelevel, an AI firm, in May stated that its technology “made history” by being the first instance of “generative AI in a federal trial.” Kenner himself hailed the AI’s capabilities as a “game changer for complex litigation.” Yet, for all its groundbreaking status, the very same press release glossed over the fact that Michel was found guilty on all counts after just three days of jury deliberation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This trial was not just another case. It spanned three weeks and included testimonies from A-list celebrities like Leonardo DiCaprio and former Attorney General Jeff Sessions. Given the case’s gravity, one would expect nothing less than a meticulous, human touch to every aspect of the defense, including the closing arguments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, where does this leave us? While technology, including AI, undoubtedly has immense potential benefits, its application must be judicious. The courtroom, where lives and liberties hang in the balance, is not a place for experimentation or showcasing tech prowess, especially not at the expense of a defendant’s right to a fair trial.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It remains to be seen how the court will react to Michel’s appeal. But this case serves as a cautionary tale about the perils of blind faith in technology in the legal domain.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">In an age where artificial intelligence is reshaping industries, the legal realm is not immune. However, the question arises - is the courtroom a suitable place for AI to play a role? The recent case of Pras Michel, a member of the iconic hip-hop group Fugees, brings this debate to the forefront. Michel, who faced charges relating to an elaborate scheme to funnel millions in foreign funds for illicit lobbying and illegal campaign contributions allegedly at China’s behest, was convicted in April. But now, the rapper seeks a new trial. Why? He claims his then-defense attorney, David Kenner, leaned on “an experimental AI program” for his closing arguments. The alleged AI-powered argument, according to Michel, was riddled with baseless points, misconstrued the issues at hand, and glaringly overlooked critical weaknesses in the Government’s case against him. But it doesn’t stop there. Kenner allegedly took pride in the speed and efficiency of the AI tool, boasting that it condensed “hours or days of legal work into seconds.” What’s even more alarming is the potential conflict of interest. It’s reported that Kenner and his co-counsel had an undisclosed financial interest in the very AI program they used during Michel’s trial. Their intention? To plug the software in a press release following the trial’s conclusion. The situation raises eyebrows and ethical concerns. An attorney’s duty is to zealously represent their client and to ensure that their rights are preserved throughout the legal process. Relying on untested technology, especially with ulterior motives, might compromise this fundamental responsibility. The novelty of the AI’s application was seemingly not lost on Kenner. A press release by Eyelevel, an AI firm, in May stated that its technology “made history” by being the first instance of “generative AI in a federal trial.” Kenner himself hailed the AI’s capabilities as a “game changer for complex litigation.” Yet, for all its groundbreaking status, the very same press release glossed over the fact that Michel was found guilty on all counts after just three days of jury deliberation. This trial was not just another case. It spanned three weeks and included testimonies from A-list celebrities like Leonardo DiCaprio and former Attorney General Jeff Sessions. Given the case’s gravity, one would expect nothing less than a meticulous, human touch to every aspect of the defense, including the closing arguments. So, where does this leave us? While technology, including AI, undoubtedly has immense potential benefits, its application must be judicious. The courtroom, where lives and liberties hang in the balance, is not a place for experimentation or showcasing tech prowess, especially not at the expense of a defendant’s right to a fair trial. It remains to be seen how the court will react to Michel’s appeal. But this case serves as a cautionary tale about the perils of blind faith in technology in the legal domain.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Rep. Waltz to Bill Gates: Ban Hamas from Four Seasons Qatar</title><link href="/news/2023/10/18/Ban-Hamas-Four-Seasons/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rep. Waltz to Bill Gates: Ban Hamas from Four Seasons Qatar" /><published>2023-10-18T09:17:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-18T09:17:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/18/Ban-Hamas-Four-Seasons</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/18/Ban-Hamas-Four-Seasons/">&lt;p&gt;In a recent development, Rep. Mike Waltz, R-Fla., a member of the prominent House Foreign Affairs Committee, has penned a letter addressed directly to Bill Gates. The letter urges the Microsoft co-founder to bar Hamas from all Four Seasons hotels. This comes in the wake of revelations that indicate Gates’ substantial control over the luxury hotel chain, achieved through a majority stake acquisition by his investment entity, Cascade Investment LLC, back in 2021.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Qatar Four Seasons, in particular, is under the microscope. The letter, which the New York Post had access to, cites instances of the hotel playing host to events spearheaded by Hamas’ political branch. These events were graced by the presence of influential figures, notably ex-Turkish Prime Minister Ahmet Davutoglu and top-tier Hamas leader Khaled Mashal. Furthermore, the letter underscores a stay by Ismail Haniyeh, who chairs the Hamas Politburo. Israel’s Foreign Ministry alleges that Haniyeh coordinated terrorist attacks on Israeli civilians from the comfort of the hotel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In response, the Four Seasons has refuted claims of Haniyeh’s current residence at the hotel but has remained tight-lipped about any prior stays.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The implications of this association are grave. The letter cautions Gates that failing to heed this call might render him vulnerable to “counterterrorism sanctions.” Rep. Waltz’s correspondence highlights the severity of offering “material support” to entities officially recognized as foreign terrorist organizations by the U.S., such as Hamas. The penalties for this can be severe, ranging from legal action, potential imprisonment for life, to the inclusion of Gates’ name in several government databases like the National Counterterrorism Center or even the Transportation Security Administration’s “Do Not Fly” list.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bill Gates isn’t the only one receiving this letter. Other recipients include Isadore Sharp, who founded and chairs the Four Seasons Hotels and Resorts, Secretary of State Antony Blinken, and Homeland Security Secretary Alejandro Mayorkas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the world watches, Gates’ next steps in addressing this matter will be under intense scrutiny. For now, the ball remains in his court, and the implications of his decisions will be felt far and wide.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a recent development, Rep. Mike Waltz, R-Fla., a member of the prominent House Foreign Affairs Committee, has penned a letter addressed directly to Bill Gates. The letter urges the Microsoft co-founder to bar Hamas from all Four Seasons hotels. This comes in the wake of revelations that indicate Gates’ substantial control over the luxury hotel chain, achieved through a majority stake acquisition by his investment entity, Cascade Investment LLC, back in 2021. The Qatar Four Seasons, in particular, is under the microscope. The letter, which the New York Post had access to, cites instances of the hotel playing host to events spearheaded by Hamas’ political branch. These events were graced by the presence of influential figures, notably ex-Turkish Prime Minister Ahmet Davutoglu and top-tier Hamas leader Khaled Mashal. Furthermore, the letter underscores a stay by Ismail Haniyeh, who chairs the Hamas Politburo. Israel’s Foreign Ministry alleges that Haniyeh coordinated terrorist attacks on Israeli civilians from the comfort of the hotel. In response, the Four Seasons has refuted claims of Haniyeh’s current residence at the hotel but has remained tight-lipped about any prior stays. The implications of this association are grave. The letter cautions Gates that failing to heed this call might render him vulnerable to “counterterrorism sanctions.” Rep. Waltz’s correspondence highlights the severity of offering “material support” to entities officially recognized as foreign terrorist organizations by the U.S., such as Hamas. The penalties for this can be severe, ranging from legal action, potential imprisonment for life, to the inclusion of Gates’ name in several government databases like the National Counterterrorism Center or even the Transportation Security Administration’s “Do Not Fly” list. Bill Gates isn’t the only one receiving this letter. Other recipients include Isadore Sharp, who founded and chairs the Four Seasons Hotels and Resorts, Secretary of State Antony Blinken, and Homeland Security Secretary Alejandro Mayorkas. As the world watches, Gates’ next steps in addressing this matter will be under intense scrutiny. For now, the ball remains in his court, and the implications of his decisions will be felt far and wide.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Squatting Surge Shakes Up Florida Neighborhood</title><link href="/news/2023/10/18/Squatting-Escalation-Florida/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Squatting Surge Shakes Up Florida Neighborhood" /><published>2023-10-18T08:10:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-18T08:10:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/18/Squatting-Escalation-Florida</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/18/Squatting-Escalation-Florida/">&lt;p&gt;Escambia County in Florida has been thrust into the limelight due to a troubling increase in squatting activity and homeless encampments on private lands. The community, which prides itself on its tranquility and harmony, finds itself grappling with an issue that has seen both homeowners and squatters at odds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gwen Gibson, a resident of Brent, Florida, voiced her frustrations over the constant trespassing on her property. “There are so many people going back and forth it’s ridiculous,” Gibson reported to the Pensacola News Journal, mentioning the rise in activities like drug trading and prostitution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adjacent to Gibson’s home is a plot owned by the Merrill family. Over the years, this land has become a hotspot for homeless camps. Only after several delays, following an order from the Escambia County magistrate, did local entrepreneur Collier Merrill initiate the cleanup of the site in August.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite posting “no trespassing” signs and installing security cameras, Merrill admits he has been lenient, hoping the squatters would voluntarily vacate the premises. Addressing the issue, he said, “We’ve been working on another project, hoping they would go ahead and move on their own, but actually they’re not going to do that.” He has now prioritized resolving this predicament in line with the county’s guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, Gibson’s observations suggest that the problem has amplified since the August cleanup. More individuals are reported to frequent the Merrill land daily, with many trespassing on her property to reach the site. The aftermath of squatting has also led to disturbing scenes: from squatters using trees as restrooms, visible from Gibson’s kitchen, to cleaning crews becoming physically ill from the distressing cleanup conditions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The broader sentiment in the community echoes Gibson’s concerns. The problems of squatting and homelessness aren’t isolated to her vicinity but have burgeoned across the county, with many attributing the pandemic as a significant exacerbating factor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tim Day, Escambia’s Senior Natural Resources Manager, pinpointed the change in behavior during the pandemic. Before the virus’s outbreak, campers typically hid deep within properties to remain inconspicuous. But with authorities refraining from removing them during the pandemic to prevent virus spread, many campers grew bolder, openly setting up camps without much concern for privacy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Local politicians like Escambia Commissioner Mike Kohler have also been inundated with grievances regarding the issue. “That is the biggest, No. 1 problem in the county,” said Kohler. The commissioner highlighted the urgency to address this escalating problem, an issue that’s fast becoming the main talking point amongst the local community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, for Gibson, the challenges extend beyond mere property invasion. She recounted menacing confrontations with campers, threats from men wielding machetes, and confrontations with church groups and advocacy bodies. She remains steadfast, though: “I’ve been dealing with this for years. I feel very unsafe,” said Gibson. “It’s been hard, and sometimes I think I can’t do this anymore, but I’m not giving up. I haven’t done anything wrong. Why should I have to leave?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the county searches for resolutions, the essence of the community is at stake, and residents like Gibson wait, hoping for a swift and fair solution.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Escambia County in Florida has been thrust into the limelight due to a troubling increase in squatting activity and homeless encampments on private lands. The community, which prides itself on its tranquility and harmony, finds itself grappling with an issue that has seen both homeowners and squatters at odds. Gwen Gibson, a resident of Brent, Florida, voiced her frustrations over the constant trespassing on her property. “There are so many people going back and forth it’s ridiculous,” Gibson reported to the Pensacola News Journal, mentioning the rise in activities like drug trading and prostitution. Adjacent to Gibson’s home is a plot owned by the Merrill family. Over the years, this land has become a hotspot for homeless camps. Only after several delays, following an order from the Escambia County magistrate, did local entrepreneur Collier Merrill initiate the cleanup of the site in August. Despite posting “no trespassing” signs and installing security cameras, Merrill admits he has been lenient, hoping the squatters would voluntarily vacate the premises. Addressing the issue, he said, “We’ve been working on another project, hoping they would go ahead and move on their own, but actually they’re not going to do that.” He has now prioritized resolving this predicament in line with the county’s guidelines. However, Gibson’s observations suggest that the problem has amplified since the August cleanup. More individuals are reported to frequent the Merrill land daily, with many trespassing on her property to reach the site. The aftermath of squatting has also led to disturbing scenes: from squatters using trees as restrooms, visible from Gibson’s kitchen, to cleaning crews becoming physically ill from the distressing cleanup conditions. The broader sentiment in the community echoes Gibson’s concerns. The problems of squatting and homelessness aren’t isolated to her vicinity but have burgeoned across the county, with many attributing the pandemic as a significant exacerbating factor. Tim Day, Escambia’s Senior Natural Resources Manager, pinpointed the change in behavior during the pandemic. Before the virus’s outbreak, campers typically hid deep within properties to remain inconspicuous. But with authorities refraining from removing them during the pandemic to prevent virus spread, many campers grew bolder, openly setting up camps without much concern for privacy. Local politicians like Escambia Commissioner Mike Kohler have also been inundated with grievances regarding the issue. “That is the biggest, No. 1 problem in the county,” said Kohler. The commissioner highlighted the urgency to address this escalating problem, an issue that’s fast becoming the main talking point amongst the local community. However, for Gibson, the challenges extend beyond mere property invasion. She recounted menacing confrontations with campers, threats from men wielding machetes, and confrontations with church groups and advocacy bodies. She remains steadfast, though: “I’ve been dealing with this for years. I feel very unsafe,” said Gibson. “It’s been hard, and sometimes I think I can’t do this anymore, but I’m not giving up. I haven’t done anything wrong. Why should I have to leave?” As the county searches for resolutions, the essence of the community is at stake, and residents like Gibson wait, hoping for a swift and fair solution.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Rep. Debbie Lesko Opts Out of 2024 Reelection Race</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/18/Debbie-Lesko-Reelection/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rep. Debbie Lesko Opts Out of 2024 Reelection Race" /><published>2023-10-18T07:04:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-18T07:04:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/18/Debbie-Lesko-Reelection</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/18/Debbie-Lesko-Reelection/">&lt;p&gt;In a surprising turn of events, Republican Congresswoman Debbie Lesko, representing Arizona’s eighth congressional district, has announced she will not be vying for reelection in 2024. Her district, encompassing Phoenix’s West Valley, has been a stronghold for the GOP, making her decision particularly noteworthy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a heartfelt statement, Lesko expressed her desire to cherish moments with her close family, mentioning her husband, her nonagenarian mother, her children, and grandchildren. “I want to spend more time with my husband, my 94-year-old mother, my three children, and my five grandchildren,” she remarked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond family reasons, Lesko didn’t shy away from calling out the prevailing challenges in the U.S. political landscape. With the House of Representatives witnessing unprecedented gridlock and being unable to finalize on a new speaker, Lesko voiced her concerns about the current inefficacies of Washington, D.C. “Right now, Washington, D.C., is broken; it is hard to get anything done,” Lesko stated, reaffirming her commitment to continue working towards betterment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to The Cook Political Report, the eighth congressional district of Arizona has a solid Republican foundation, with a partisan voting index that leans favorably towards Republicans by a significant ten percentage points. This metric underlines the dominance of the GOP in the area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With Lesko’s impending departure, the question on many minds is: Who will step up? Several prominent Republicans from Arizona have already been highlighted as potential successors. Names like Abraham Hamadeh, who previously ran for the attorney general, and Blake Masters, a former U.S. Senate candidate, are in the mix.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The state’s political atmosphere was further enlivened when Republican Senate candidate Kari Lake endorsed Hamadeh. In her endorsement, Lake touted him as “one of the toughest” combatants in Arizona’s political scene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Blake Masters took a moment to honor Lesko’s commitment and service to Arizonans. In a gracious statement, he said, “Congresswoman Lesko has been a great public servant for Arizonans. She loves our state, and we are better off for her service. Thank you Debbie.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the circulating speculations, neither Hamadeh nor Masters has made any official announcement regarding their intentions to contest for the soon-to-be-vacant seat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As Arizona’s political stage gets set for the 2024 elections, it will be intriguing to watch the developments unfold and witness who will emerge as the successor to Congresswoman Debbie Lesko’s legacy.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a surprising turn of events, Republican Congresswoman Debbie Lesko, representing Arizona’s eighth congressional district, has announced she will not be vying for reelection in 2024. Her district, encompassing Phoenix’s West Valley, has been a stronghold for the GOP, making her decision particularly noteworthy. In a heartfelt statement, Lesko expressed her desire to cherish moments with her close family, mentioning her husband, her nonagenarian mother, her children, and grandchildren. “I want to spend more time with my husband, my 94-year-old mother, my three children, and my five grandchildren,” she remarked. Beyond family reasons, Lesko didn’t shy away from calling out the prevailing challenges in the U.S. political landscape. With the House of Representatives witnessing unprecedented gridlock and being unable to finalize on a new speaker, Lesko voiced her concerns about the current inefficacies of Washington, D.C. “Right now, Washington, D.C., is broken; it is hard to get anything done,” Lesko stated, reaffirming her commitment to continue working towards betterment. According to The Cook Political Report, the eighth congressional district of Arizona has a solid Republican foundation, with a partisan voting index that leans favorably towards Republicans by a significant ten percentage points. This metric underlines the dominance of the GOP in the area. With Lesko’s impending departure, the question on many minds is: Who will step up? Several prominent Republicans from Arizona have already been highlighted as potential successors. Names like Abraham Hamadeh, who previously ran for the attorney general, and Blake Masters, a former U.S. Senate candidate, are in the mix. The state’s political atmosphere was further enlivened when Republican Senate candidate Kari Lake endorsed Hamadeh. In her endorsement, Lake touted him as “one of the toughest” combatants in Arizona’s political scene. Blake Masters took a moment to honor Lesko’s commitment and service to Arizonans. In a gracious statement, he said, “Congresswoman Lesko has been a great public servant for Arizonans. She loves our state, and we are better off for her service. Thank you Debbie.” Despite the circulating speculations, neither Hamadeh nor Masters has made any official announcement regarding their intentions to contest for the soon-to-be-vacant seat. As Arizona’s political stage gets set for the 2024 elections, it will be intriguing to watch the developments unfold and witness who will emerge as the successor to Congresswoman Debbie Lesko’s legacy.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">NFL Legend Terrell Owens Struck by Car Following Basketball Spat</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/18/Terrell-Owens-Car-Incident/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="NFL Legend Terrell Owens Struck by Car Following Basketball Spat" /><published>2023-10-18T06:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-18T06:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/18/Terrell-Owens-Car-Incident</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/18/Terrell-Owens-Car-Incident/">&lt;p&gt;In a shocking turn of events, former NFL star and Pro Football Hall of Famer, Terrell “T.O.” Owens, found himself in the headlines again, but this time for a disturbing reason. At 49, Owens, known for his unparalleled skills on the football field, was hit by a car on a Calabasas, California basketball court following a heated dispute. The event took place Monday evening, roughly around 9 p.m. local time, as reported by the Los Angeles County Sheriff’s Department.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Details surrounding the event remain murky. The authorities have not yet apprehended any suspects, nor have they released a complete description of the vehicle involved. However, celebrity news outlet TMZ disclosed that the same individual Owens clashed with on the basketball court was behind the wheel during the incident.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a stroke of luck, Owens reportedly suffered an impact to his knee but did not require any medical attention. The resilience showcased by the NFL veteran, who once played a Super Bowl with a broken leg, is commendable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Renowned for his spectacular tenure with the San Francisco 49ers, where he ranks second in the franchise’s history for receptions, yards, and touchdowns, Owens has been a prominent figure in the football realm. Beyond the 49ers, he showcased his talent with teams like the Dallas Cowboys, Buffalo Bills, Philadelphia Eagles, and Cincinnati Bengals, concluding his NFL journey in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Post-retirement, Owens’ life off the field has been peppered with a series of bizarre episodes. Notably, in 2022, Owens found himself in the middle of a legal wrangle with a female neighbor, leading to the woman facing criminal charges. The same year witnessed another scuffle involving Owens outside a CVS, where he confronted a heckler. In both instances, Owens steadfastly affirmed his innocence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the circumstances and motive behind this recent car incident remain uncertain, fans and well-wishers across the globe hope for Owens’ safety and well-being. As the investigation unfolds, many are eager to uncover the complete story behind this unexpected event in the life of an NFL legend.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">In a shocking turn of events, former NFL star and Pro Football Hall of Famer, Terrell “T.O.” Owens, found himself in the headlines again, but this time for a disturbing reason. At 49, Owens, known for his unparalleled skills on the football field, was hit by a car on a Calabasas, California basketball court following a heated dispute. The event took place Monday evening, roughly around 9 p.m. local time, as reported by the Los Angeles County Sheriff’s Department. Details surrounding the event remain murky. The authorities have not yet apprehended any suspects, nor have they released a complete description of the vehicle involved. However, celebrity news outlet TMZ disclosed that the same individual Owens clashed with on the basketball court was behind the wheel during the incident. In a stroke of luck, Owens reportedly suffered an impact to his knee but did not require any medical attention. The resilience showcased by the NFL veteran, who once played a Super Bowl with a broken leg, is commendable. Renowned for his spectacular tenure with the San Francisco 49ers, where he ranks second in the franchise’s history for receptions, yards, and touchdowns, Owens has been a prominent figure in the football realm. Beyond the 49ers, he showcased his talent with teams like the Dallas Cowboys, Buffalo Bills, Philadelphia Eagles, and Cincinnati Bengals, concluding his NFL journey in 2010. Post-retirement, Owens’ life off the field has been peppered with a series of bizarre episodes. Notably, in 2022, Owens found himself in the middle of a legal wrangle with a female neighbor, leading to the woman facing criminal charges. The same year witnessed another scuffle involving Owens outside a CVS, where he confronted a heckler. In both instances, Owens steadfastly affirmed his innocence. While the circumstances and motive behind this recent car incident remain uncertain, fans and well-wishers across the globe hope for Owens’ safety and well-being. As the investigation unfolds, many are eager to uncover the complete story behind this unexpected event in the life of an NFL legend.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump Vehemently Opposes California’s New Gender Law</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/17/Trump-California-Gender-Law/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump Vehemently Opposes California’s New Gender Law" /><published>2023-10-17T16:15:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-17T16:15:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/17/Trump-California-Gender-Law</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/17/Trump-California-Gender-Law/">&lt;p&gt;In a fervent address, former President Donald Trump expressed his strong disapproval of California’s recent “sanctuary law” for children undergoing transgender-related medical treatments without parental consent. Trump, eyeing a return to the Oval Office in 2024, pledged to use federal laws, including those against child abuse and kidnapping, to counteract this state legislation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;California’s controversial law allows children to travel to the state for transgender-related procedures even if their parents from other states oppose it. Describing the legislation as a “horrific scheme,” Trump asserted that it permits “barbaric and irreversible” treatments that infringe upon parental rights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It’s sick,” said the 45th president, emphasizing the disbelief many share about the existence of such a law. Trump described the act of overriding parents’ rights as a sterilization of children. “The state of California has no right to take your children away from parents and to sterilize them, which is exactly what they’re doing,” Trump stressed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further elaborating on his stance, Trump promised that if reelected, he would address the issue on his first day in office. “Upon my inauguration, we will aggressively challenge these perverted California laws that strip parents of their rights and that encourage minors to be transported across state lines for sexual mutilation purposes,” he voiced with a sense of urgency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Throughout his address, Trump reiterated his commitment to ensuring the safety and well-being of the nation’s youth. “I will protect your youth. I will protect your children. I will protect the right of parents to make decisions on behalf of their children,” he passionately declared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expressing a broader concern for the nation’s trajectory, Trump concluded by saying, “We’re in a failing nation. This nation is failing. We’re not going to let it fail any longer. We’re going to make America great again.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The evolving dialogue and growing acceptance of transgenderism and “non-binary” concepts have raised eyebrows, especially concerning the youth. Recent studies indicate that social contagion may play a role in younger generations identifying as transgender. Disturbing reports, such as the one indicating that over 600 underage girls underwent breast removal in Canada for transgender purposes, further fuel the debate around this sensitive issue.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a fervent address, former President Donald Trump expressed his strong disapproval of California’s recent “sanctuary law” for children undergoing transgender-related medical treatments without parental consent. Trump, eyeing a return to the Oval Office in 2024, pledged to use federal laws, including those against child abuse and kidnapping, to counteract this state legislation. California’s controversial law allows children to travel to the state for transgender-related procedures even if their parents from other states oppose it. Describing the legislation as a “horrific scheme,” Trump asserted that it permits “barbaric and irreversible” treatments that infringe upon parental rights. “It’s sick,” said the 45th president, emphasizing the disbelief many share about the existence of such a law. Trump described the act of overriding parents’ rights as a sterilization of children. “The state of California has no right to take your children away from parents and to sterilize them, which is exactly what they’re doing,” Trump stressed. Further elaborating on his stance, Trump promised that if reelected, he would address the issue on his first day in office. “Upon my inauguration, we will aggressively challenge these perverted California laws that strip parents of their rights and that encourage minors to be transported across state lines for sexual mutilation purposes,” he voiced with a sense of urgency. Throughout his address, Trump reiterated his commitment to ensuring the safety and well-being of the nation’s youth. “I will protect your youth. I will protect your children. I will protect the right of parents to make decisions on behalf of their children,” he passionately declared. Expressing a broader concern for the nation’s trajectory, Trump concluded by saying, “We’re in a failing nation. This nation is failing. We’re not going to let it fail any longer. We’re going to make America great again.” The evolving dialogue and growing acceptance of transgenderism and “non-binary” concepts have raised eyebrows, especially concerning the youth. Recent studies indicate that social contagion may play a role in younger generations identifying as transgender. Disturbing reports, such as the one indicating that over 600 underage girls underwent breast removal in Canada for transgender purposes, further fuel the debate around this sensitive issue.</summary></entry></feed>