<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-10-11T06:17:25-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/11/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-11T06:17:25-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-11T06:17:25-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/11/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/11/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/11/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-11T06:17:25-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-11T06:17:25-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/11/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/11/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/">&lt;p&gt;Recent surprise attacks by Hamas on Israel has fueled ongoing tensions between staunchly conservative commentators and the progressive “Squad” Democrats known for criticizing Israel. The intensity of the backlash highlights the deep political divide over foreign policy in the Middle East.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Hamas’ shocking attack, several members of the “Squad,” including Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.), called for a “ceasefire and de-escalation,” condemning the violence. The absence of a statement from Rep. Rashida Tlaib (D-Mich.) was notably called out by conservative media outlets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;South Carolina GOP Rep. Nancy Mace quickly labeled Ocasio-Cortez a “Hamas apologist” in response to her call for peace and de-escalation. Rep. Ilhan Omar (D-Minn.), no stranger to controversy surrounding her views on Israel, echoed the call for de-escalation and ceasefire. Omar’s prior statements comparing the US and Israel to terrorist groups like Hamas and the Taliban resurfaced in the debate, fueling more criticisms. Omar’s 2019 tweet, where she opined that “Israel has hypnotized the world,” also continues to haunt her political career, often cited by critics to challenge her stance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conservative commentators have been especially vocal. “FOX &amp;amp; Friends Weekend” co-host Rachel Campos-Duffy took aim at Omar, saying she fails to recognize the peace in the Middle East under Trump’s administration. Conservative pundit John Hasson also called out Omar, claiming she insinuated that attacks on IDF forces were acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Massachusetts Democrat Rep. Ayanna Pressley’s concerns over the “devastating attacks on Israelis” were met with skepticism. A prominent conservative online personality, Comfortably Smug, accused the “Squad” of advising Israel to back down after the nation suffered massive attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Jamaal Bowman’s call for an end to the Gaza blockade, in addition to condemning the Hamas attacks, was met with criticism from conservative radio host Jason Rantz. He accused Bowman of pairing his condemnation of terrorism with unwarranted criticisms of Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Cori Bush emphasized the urgent need for a ceasefire, while pushing for an end to “U.S. support for Israeli military occupation and apartheid.” Defense attorney Marina Medvin criticized Bush, suggesting that she equates the death of Palestinian terrorists to the horrific acts committed against Jewish civilians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amidst the political turmoil and intense debate, the attacks have taken a heavy toll. Israeli media report over 300 dead due to the wide-ranging assault. Gaza health officials note that at least 200 Palestinians have perished in the retaliatory Israeli air strikes following the initial Hamas attack. As the situation remains volatile, both sides continue to count their casualties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This divisive issue showcases the challenge America faces in crafting a unified approach to foreign policy, with deeply entrenched political divides at play. As the situation develops, the debate is bound to intensify, shedding light on the complexities of U.S. politics in the global arena.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">GOP Tensions Rise: Dueling Proposals Highlight Speaker Selection Struggle</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/11/House-Speaker-Debate/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="GOP Tensions Rise: Dueling Proposals Highlight Speaker Selection Struggle" /><published>2023-10-11T06:05:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-11T06:05:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/11/House-Speaker-Debate</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/11/House-Speaker-Debate/">&lt;p&gt;House Republicans are in a heated debate, introducing competing amendments to the House GOP rules, underlining the division within the party as they gear up to elect their new speaker.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the heart of the matter, Rep. Chip Roy proposed an amendment that raises the bar for nominating a speaker candidate, setting the requirement at 217 votes – equivalent to a House majority. This initiative comes in light of the memory of Former Speaker Kevin McCarthy’s lengthy 15-round election journey to acquire the gavel earlier in the year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Supporters of this amendment argue its merit, suggesting that it’s a pivotal step towards preventing future internal battles from taking the center stage, and ensuring greater unity within the House GOP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the rule hasn’t been met with unanimous approval. Rep. Tom McClintock, another significant Republican figure, labeled Roy’s proposal as “an absurdity on its face.” He emphasized the flaw in the existing process of ousting a speaker, which allows for the removal of the chosen speaker by merely a handful of disgruntled members. McClintock voiced his concern in strong terms, stating that such a system amounts to “childish despotism and utter nonsense.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In response, McClintock proposed an alternative: any member going against the collective decision of the conference on procedural matters, including speaker votes and rule changes, should face expulsion. To readmit such an expelled member, a two-thirds majority of the conference would have to vote in favor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, amidst these swirling controversies, there have been calls to bring back McCarthy as the speaker. However, the chances of that happening seem slim, given McCarthy’s own expressed disinclination to reclaim the position.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As of now, all eyes are on Majority Leader Steve Scalise and Judiciary Chair Jim Jordan, the two major contenders for the speaker’s position. House Republicans are geared up to hear their pitches and are expected to convene again to finalize their decision on the next speaker.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ongoing disagreements underscore the challenges that lie ahead for the GOP as they attempt to showcase unity and strength in these politically tumultuous times.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">House Republicans are in a heated debate, introducing competing amendments to the House GOP rules, underlining the division within the party as they gear up to elect their new speaker. At the heart of the matter, Rep. Chip Roy proposed an amendment that raises the bar for nominating a speaker candidate, setting the requirement at 217 votes – equivalent to a House majority. This initiative comes in light of the memory of Former Speaker Kevin McCarthy’s lengthy 15-round election journey to acquire the gavel earlier in the year. Supporters of this amendment argue its merit, suggesting that it’s a pivotal step towards preventing future internal battles from taking the center stage, and ensuring greater unity within the House GOP. However, the rule hasn’t been met with unanimous approval. Rep. Tom McClintock, another significant Republican figure, labeled Roy’s proposal as “an absurdity on its face.” He emphasized the flaw in the existing process of ousting a speaker, which allows for the removal of the chosen speaker by merely a handful of disgruntled members. McClintock voiced his concern in strong terms, stating that such a system amounts to “childish despotism and utter nonsense.” In response, McClintock proposed an alternative: any member going against the collective decision of the conference on procedural matters, including speaker votes and rule changes, should face expulsion. To readmit such an expelled member, a two-thirds majority of the conference would have to vote in favor. Interestingly, amidst these swirling controversies, there have been calls to bring back McCarthy as the speaker. However, the chances of that happening seem slim, given McCarthy’s own expressed disinclination to reclaim the position. As of now, all eyes are on Majority Leader Steve Scalise and Judiciary Chair Jim Jordan, the two major contenders for the speaker’s position. House Republicans are geared up to hear their pitches and are expected to convene again to finalize their decision on the next speaker. The ongoing disagreements underscore the challenges that lie ahead for the GOP as they attempt to showcase unity and strength in these politically tumultuous times.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Heart Alert: The New Syndrome Affecting 1 in 3 Americans</title><link href="/news/2023/10/10/Heart-Syndrome-Diagnosis/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Heart Alert: The New Syndrome Affecting 1 in 3 Americans" /><published>2023-10-10T15:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-10T15:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/10/Heart-Syndrome-Diagnosis</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/10/Heart-Syndrome-Diagnosis/">&lt;p&gt;A groundbreaking discovery by the American Heart Association has revealed a new medical syndrome, named Cardiovascular-Kidney-Metabolic Syndrome (CKM). This syndrome accentuates the strong link between obesity, heart disease, and kidney disorders. The main aim behind identifying CKM? To diagnose those most vulnerable to fatal cardiovascular diseases at the earliest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to Dr. Chiadi Ndumele, the advisory’s chief author and the director of obesity and cardiometabolic research at Johns Hopkins University, the core objective is “reducing the pipeline of individuals progressing toward heart disease.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Diving deep into the intricacies of CKM, research shows metabolic risk factors like abdominal fat, elevated blood pressure, heightened cholesterol, and increased blood sugar can adversely affect our vital organs. Dr. Pam Taub, a renowned cardiologist from the UC San Diego School of Medicine, considers CKM identification a pivotal moment for patients with high risks. The early detection and subsequent treatment of affected organs have resulted in a notable reduction in cardiovascular events.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CKM detection not only allows professionals to understand the interplay between organs but also paves the way for early diagnosis, preventing heart-wrenching cardiovascular outcomes. There’s a silver lining too: individuals diagnosed with this newly recognized condition can show improvement if it’s identified timely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For an efficient diagnosis process, Dr. Ndumele’s team has crafted a comprehensive four-stage system:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stage 0&lt;/strong&gt;: No discernible risk factors.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stage 1&lt;/strong&gt;: Targets those overweight or with signs of pre-diabetes. Recommendations include healthy lifestyle changes aiming for a minimum 5% weight reduction.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stage 2&lt;/strong&gt;: Focuses on individuals with Type 2 diabetes, kidney disease, high triglycerides, or increased blood pressure. Treatment may encompass medications controlling blood pressure, blood sugar, and cholesterol.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stage 3&lt;/strong&gt;: Individuals with metabolic risk factors but remain asymptomatic. Intervention might involve heart medicines and arterial examinations.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stage 4&lt;/strong&gt;: Persons diagnosed with heart disease or associated conditions. Treatment is devised based on the specific condition and associated symptoms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The numbers are staggering. Dr. Ndumele approximates a whopping 90% of U.S. adults lie somewhere on the CKM spectrum, attributable to the alarming rates of obesity and Type 2 diabetes observed in both adults and young ones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To put it in perspective, per the American Heart Association’s presidential advisory, every third adult in the U.S. showcases three or more risk elements, predisposing them to cardiovascular disease, metabolic disorders, or kidney ailments. CKM’s clasp is vast, impacting major organs including the heart, brain, kidney, and liver. Yet, its most profound influence is observed on the cardiovascular system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This breakthrough is bound to redefine medical paradigms. As Dr. Ndumele aptly put it, “Screening for kidney and metabolic disease will help us start protective therapies earlier, paving the way to more effectively prevent heart disease and manage existing ones.”&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">A groundbreaking discovery by the American Heart Association has revealed a new medical syndrome, named Cardiovascular-Kidney-Metabolic Syndrome (CKM). This syndrome accentuates the strong link between obesity, heart disease, and kidney disorders. The main aim behind identifying CKM? To diagnose those most vulnerable to fatal cardiovascular diseases at the earliest. According to Dr. Chiadi Ndumele, the advisory’s chief author and the director of obesity and cardiometabolic research at Johns Hopkins University, the core objective is “reducing the pipeline of individuals progressing toward heart disease.” Diving deep into the intricacies of CKM, research shows metabolic risk factors like abdominal fat, elevated blood pressure, heightened cholesterol, and increased blood sugar can adversely affect our vital organs. Dr. Pam Taub, a renowned cardiologist from the UC San Diego School of Medicine, considers CKM identification a pivotal moment for patients with high risks. The early detection and subsequent treatment of affected organs have resulted in a notable reduction in cardiovascular events. CKM detection not only allows professionals to understand the interplay between organs but also paves the way for early diagnosis, preventing heart-wrenching cardiovascular outcomes. There’s a silver lining too: individuals diagnosed with this newly recognized condition can show improvement if it’s identified timely. For an efficient diagnosis process, Dr. Ndumele’s team has crafted a comprehensive four-stage system: Stage 0: No discernible risk factors. Stage 1: Targets those overweight or with signs of pre-diabetes. Recommendations include healthy lifestyle changes aiming for a minimum 5% weight reduction. Stage 2: Focuses on individuals with Type 2 diabetes, kidney disease, high triglycerides, or increased blood pressure. Treatment may encompass medications controlling blood pressure, blood sugar, and cholesterol. Stage 3: Individuals with metabolic risk factors but remain asymptomatic. Intervention might involve heart medicines and arterial examinations. Stage 4: Persons diagnosed with heart disease or associated conditions. Treatment is devised based on the specific condition and associated symptoms. The numbers are staggering. Dr. Ndumele approximates a whopping 90% of U.S. adults lie somewhere on the CKM spectrum, attributable to the alarming rates of obesity and Type 2 diabetes observed in both adults and young ones. To put it in perspective, per the American Heart Association’s presidential advisory, every third adult in the U.S. showcases three or more risk elements, predisposing them to cardiovascular disease, metabolic disorders, or kidney ailments. CKM’s clasp is vast, impacting major organs including the heart, brain, kidney, and liver. Yet, its most profound influence is observed on the cardiovascular system. This breakthrough is bound to redefine medical paradigms. As Dr. Ndumele aptly put it, “Screening for kidney and metabolic disease will help us start protective therapies earlier, paving the way to more effectively prevent heart disease and manage existing ones.”</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Amazon’s Alexa Makes Stolen Election Claims</title><link href="/news/2023/10/10/Amazon-Alexa-Claims/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Amazon’s Alexa Makes Stolen Election Claims" /><published>2023-10-10T14:01:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-10T14:01:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/10/Amazon-Alexa-Claims</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/10/Amazon-Alexa-Claims/">&lt;p&gt;In a startling revelation, Amazon’s widely-used voice assistant, Alexa, reportedly claimed that the 2020 U.S. presidential election was “stolen by a massive amount of election fraud.” The election saw a contest between former President Donald Trump and President Joe Biden.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Washington Post, a leading newspaper, reported that Alexa provided users with information suggesting that the 2020 presidential election had been “stolen.” While details about the specific Alexa version tested weren’t mentioned, the assistant’s source for the claim was cited as Rumble. For those unaware, Rumble serves as an alternative video streaming platform to Google’s YouTube.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, Alexa was reported to inform users that the 2020 election was characterized by “many incidents of irregularities and indications pointing to electoral fraud occurring in major metro centers.” Interestingly, the voice assistant also referenced the newsletter service, Substack, as its source.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Such assertions from a leading tech giant’s voice assistant understandably raise eyebrows, given the broader conversations around misinformation and the role of technology platforms in curating content. Addressing the issue, Amazon promptly responded to the Washington Post, clarifying that the claims were an error. An Amazon spokesperson stated, “These responses were errors that were delivered a small number of times, and quickly fixed when brought to our attention.” Amazon emphasizes its commitment to accuracy by continually auditing and refining systems in place to detect and prevent inaccurate content dissemination.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, following the issue being flagged and Amazon’s statement, Alexa, when posed with questions regarding the legitimacy of the 2020 U.S. presidential election, began abstaining from answering, as noted by the Washington Post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As voice assistants become an integral part of daily life, influencing decisions from shopping to news consumption, the accuracy of the information they provide becomes paramount. With Alexa’s reach in numerous households, claims like these highlight the significance of ensuring accurate and unbiased content delivery. As the world navigates the challenges of misinformation in the digital age, the role of tech giants like Amazon becomes ever crucial in shaping informed societies.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a startling revelation, Amazon’s widely-used voice assistant, Alexa, reportedly claimed that the 2020 U.S. presidential election was “stolen by a massive amount of election fraud.” The election saw a contest between former President Donald Trump and President Joe Biden. The Washington Post, a leading newspaper, reported that Alexa provided users with information suggesting that the 2020 presidential election had been “stolen.” While details about the specific Alexa version tested weren’t mentioned, the assistant’s source for the claim was cited as Rumble. For those unaware, Rumble serves as an alternative video streaming platform to Google’s YouTube. Furthermore, Alexa was reported to inform users that the 2020 election was characterized by “many incidents of irregularities and indications pointing to electoral fraud occurring in major metro centers.” Interestingly, the voice assistant also referenced the newsletter service, Substack, as its source. Such assertions from a leading tech giant’s voice assistant understandably raise eyebrows, given the broader conversations around misinformation and the role of technology platforms in curating content. Addressing the issue, Amazon promptly responded to the Washington Post, clarifying that the claims were an error. An Amazon spokesperson stated, “These responses were errors that were delivered a small number of times, and quickly fixed when brought to our attention.” Amazon emphasizes its commitment to accuracy by continually auditing and refining systems in place to detect and prevent inaccurate content dissemination. Interestingly, following the issue being flagged and Amazon’s statement, Alexa, when posed with questions regarding the legitimacy of the 2020 U.S. presidential election, began abstaining from answering, as noted by the Washington Post. As voice assistants become an integral part of daily life, influencing decisions from shopping to news consumption, the accuracy of the information they provide becomes paramount. With Alexa’s reach in numerous households, claims like these highlight the significance of ensuring accurate and unbiased content delivery. As the world navigates the challenges of misinformation in the digital age, the role of tech giants like Amazon becomes ever crucial in shaping informed societies.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Massive Walgreens Walkout: Pharmacy Workers Demand Better Working Conditions</title><link href="/news/2023/10/10/Walgreens-Walkout/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Massive Walgreens Walkout: Pharmacy Workers Demand Better Working Conditions" /><published>2023-10-10T13:07:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-10T13:07:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/10/Walgreens-Walkout</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/10/Walgreens-Walkout/">&lt;p&gt;Walgreens, a major pharmacy chain in the U.S., is facing a significant disruption in its operations as hundreds of employees across numerous stores stage walkouts. The primary reason behind this wave of protests? Alarming working conditions that employees claim jeopardize both their well-being and the safety of customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to inside sources who spoke with CNN, over 500 of Walgreens’ approximately 9,000 locations — a staggering 5.5 percent — have shown interest in participating in the strike, scheduled from Monday to Wednesday. As a result, many pharmacies in states like Arizona, Washington, Massachusetts, and Oregon have temporarily ceased operations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stores that remain operational are grappling with acute staff shortages as a large fraction of workers abstain from showing up. Some Walgreens outlets are striving to keep their drive-through services running, while others contemplate shutting their doors temporarily.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, what’s driving these pharmacy workers to take such drastic measures? The grievances listed are manifold: an uptick in responsibilities like vaccinations, coupled with confronting hostile customers and dealing with various forms of harassment. Amanda Applegate, interim executive director of the Kansas Pharmacists Association, described the plight of the pharmacists, likening them to ATMs, where the emphasis on volume trumps quality of service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The grassroots nature of this protest is evident. Without a central union leader orchestrating the demonstrations, the movement gains traction through word-of-mouth, social media, and even fliers. Under the hashtag “#OperationSpotlight,” pharmacy employees voice their concerns and frustrations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One striking visual that resonates with the sentiment of these workers is a placard outside a Walgreens store that reads: “Dear Public, There is NOT a Shortage of Pharmacists, Technicians. There is a shortage of pharmacy employees willing to work in conditions which put their lives and your life in danger!!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the outcry and visible impact on store operations, Walgreens’ corporate response seems underplayed. Although they acknowledge “some activity,” the company’s statement to CNN emphasizes that the “vast majority of pharmacies are operating across the country.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This wave of protests and the spotlight on working conditions come amidst another challenge retail stores face: increasing thefts. CVS, another pharmaceutical retail giant, announced plans to close around 900 of its stores by 2024 due to a spike in shoplifting incidents. Similarly, multiple CVS stores in Kansas City, Missouri, have had to close their doors for weeks owing to employee walkouts, echoing concerns about a “dangerous environment.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a country that heavily relies on retail pharmacies like Walgreens and CVS for their healthcare and medicinal needs, these walkouts are a wakeup call. The message from employees is clear: prioritize their safety and well-being for better services and a safer community.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Walgreens, a major pharmacy chain in the U.S., is facing a significant disruption in its operations as hundreds of employees across numerous stores stage walkouts. The primary reason behind this wave of protests? Alarming working conditions that employees claim jeopardize both their well-being and the safety of customers. According to inside sources who spoke with CNN, over 500 of Walgreens’ approximately 9,000 locations — a staggering 5.5 percent — have shown interest in participating in the strike, scheduled from Monday to Wednesday. As a result, many pharmacies in states like Arizona, Washington, Massachusetts, and Oregon have temporarily ceased operations. Stores that remain operational are grappling with acute staff shortages as a large fraction of workers abstain from showing up. Some Walgreens outlets are striving to keep their drive-through services running, while others contemplate shutting their doors temporarily. So, what’s driving these pharmacy workers to take such drastic measures? The grievances listed are manifold: an uptick in responsibilities like vaccinations, coupled with confronting hostile customers and dealing with various forms of harassment. Amanda Applegate, interim executive director of the Kansas Pharmacists Association, described the plight of the pharmacists, likening them to ATMs, where the emphasis on volume trumps quality of service. The grassroots nature of this protest is evident. Without a central union leader orchestrating the demonstrations, the movement gains traction through word-of-mouth, social media, and even fliers. Under the hashtag “#OperationSpotlight,” pharmacy employees voice their concerns and frustrations. One striking visual that resonates with the sentiment of these workers is a placard outside a Walgreens store that reads: “Dear Public, There is NOT a Shortage of Pharmacists, Technicians. There is a shortage of pharmacy employees willing to work in conditions which put their lives and your life in danger!!” Despite the outcry and visible impact on store operations, Walgreens’ corporate response seems underplayed. Although they acknowledge “some activity,” the company’s statement to CNN emphasizes that the “vast majority of pharmacies are operating across the country.” This wave of protests and the spotlight on working conditions come amidst another challenge retail stores face: increasing thefts. CVS, another pharmaceutical retail giant, announced plans to close around 900 of its stores by 2024 due to a spike in shoplifting incidents. Similarly, multiple CVS stores in Kansas City, Missouri, have had to close their doors for weeks owing to employee walkouts, echoing concerns about a “dangerous environment.” In a country that heavily relies on retail pharmacies like Walgreens and CVS for their healthcare and medicinal needs, these walkouts are a wakeup call. The message from employees is clear: prioritize their safety and well-being for better services and a safer community.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Virginia Man Faces Dual Life Sentences Over Fatal Assault on Toddler</title><link href="/news/2023/10/10/Child-Tragedy-Virginia/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Virginia Man Faces Dual Life Sentences Over Fatal Assault on Toddler" /><published>2023-10-10T11:45:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-10T11:45:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/10/Child-Tragedy-Virginia</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/10/Child-Tragedy-Virginia/">&lt;p&gt;In a tragic event that has shaken the state of Virginia, a man has been sentenced to two life terms after being found guilty of fatally attacking a 2-year-old toddler and later neglecting to provide her with the needed medical care, which led to her unfortunate demise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The assailant, 37-year-old Andrew Byrd, was convicted in March on multiple counts, including aggravated murder and aggravated malicious wounding, for the 2020 assault on Harper Mitchell, his girlfriend’s young daughter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chris Rehak, the Commonwealth’s Attorney, shared his sentiments on the case, noting that it was one of the gravest crimes on record. The horrific details paint a clear picture of a brutal attack on an innocent child, with Rehak stating, “&lt;em&gt;This defendant tortured that poor little girl.&lt;/em&gt;”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The incident occurred on April 16 in Byrd’s Roanoke residence. The child’s mother, Amanda Mitchell, was away at work, leaving Harper and her siblings under Byrd’s supervision. Upon her return, Amanda found Harper in a distressing state — bruised, cold, and unresponsive. However, Byrd’s violent tendencies did not end there. As Mitchell tried to seek medical help, Byrd stopped her, going as far as threatening the life of her other children, the local media sources reported.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Roanoke Times described how Byrd prioritized his drug habits over the life of the young child, with Rehak mentioning that Byrd’s primary concern that fateful night was “&lt;em&gt;getting high&lt;/em&gt;”. It was only the following morning that Mitchell could reach out to Byrd’s mother, leading to a 911 call. Although Harper was immediately rushed to a hospital, she could not be saved. The extent of her injuries, as described by medical examiner Dr. Amy Tharp, resembled those sustained in a severe car accident. The cause of death: blunt-force trauma to the head.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the defense tried to protect Byrd by pointing out the lack of eyewitnesses and highlighting his history with substance abuse, their arguments did not hold up against the overwhelming evidence. Byrd had previously attempted to justify Harper’s injuries by suggesting she might have fallen down stairs or off a four-wheeler. Commonwealth’s Attorney Rehak didn’t mince words in court, describing Byrd as a “&lt;em&gt;dangerous, violent liar&lt;/em&gt;”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a moving statement during the sentencing, the child’s father, TJ Mitchell, expressed the deep void left behind by Harper’s tragic passing. Circuit Judge Joey Showalter emphasized that no individual, especially an innocent child, should ever face such brutality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the case unfolds further, Amanda Mitchell faces her own legal battles with charges of child abuse, cruelty, and drug possession. Byrd also has additional charges to answer for, related to the alleged abuse of Mitchell’s sons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a world where child abuse continues to be a haunting reality, Harper Mitchell’s story serves as a heartbreaking reminder of the need for continued vigilance, protection, and justice for the most vulnerable.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a tragic event that has shaken the state of Virginia, a man has been sentenced to two life terms after being found guilty of fatally attacking a 2-year-old toddler and later neglecting to provide her with the needed medical care, which led to her unfortunate demise. The assailant, 37-year-old Andrew Byrd, was convicted in March on multiple counts, including aggravated murder and aggravated malicious wounding, for the 2020 assault on Harper Mitchell, his girlfriend’s young daughter. Chris Rehak, the Commonwealth’s Attorney, shared his sentiments on the case, noting that it was one of the gravest crimes on record. The horrific details paint a clear picture of a brutal attack on an innocent child, with Rehak stating, “This defendant tortured that poor little girl.” The incident occurred on April 16 in Byrd’s Roanoke residence. The child’s mother, Amanda Mitchell, was away at work, leaving Harper and her siblings under Byrd’s supervision. Upon her return, Amanda found Harper in a distressing state — bruised, cold, and unresponsive. However, Byrd’s violent tendencies did not end there. As Mitchell tried to seek medical help, Byrd stopped her, going as far as threatening the life of her other children, the local media sources reported. The Roanoke Times described how Byrd prioritized his drug habits over the life of the young child, with Rehak mentioning that Byrd’s primary concern that fateful night was “getting high”. It was only the following morning that Mitchell could reach out to Byrd’s mother, leading to a 911 call. Although Harper was immediately rushed to a hospital, she could not be saved. The extent of her injuries, as described by medical examiner Dr. Amy Tharp, resembled those sustained in a severe car accident. The cause of death: blunt-force trauma to the head. While the defense tried to protect Byrd by pointing out the lack of eyewitnesses and highlighting his history with substance abuse, their arguments did not hold up against the overwhelming evidence. Byrd had previously attempted to justify Harper’s injuries by suggesting she might have fallen down stairs or off a four-wheeler. Commonwealth’s Attorney Rehak didn’t mince words in court, describing Byrd as a “dangerous, violent liar”. In a moving statement during the sentencing, the child’s father, TJ Mitchell, expressed the deep void left behind by Harper’s tragic passing. Circuit Judge Joey Showalter emphasized that no individual, especially an innocent child, should ever face such brutality. As the case unfolds further, Amanda Mitchell faces her own legal battles with charges of child abuse, cruelty, and drug possession. Byrd also has additional charges to answer for, related to the alleged abuse of Mitchell’s sons. In a world where child abuse continues to be a haunting reality, Harper Mitchell’s story serves as a heartbreaking reminder of the need for continued vigilance, protection, and justice for the most vulnerable.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Republicans Call on Biden to Halt $6 Billion Deal with Iran Amid Israel Attacks</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/10/Biden-Iran-Funds/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Republicans Call on Biden to Halt $6 Billion Deal with Iran Amid Israel Attacks" /><published>2023-10-10T10:21:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-10T10:21:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/10/Biden-Iran-Funds</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/10/Biden-Iran-Funds/">&lt;p&gt;Amidst the turmoil in Israel, Republicans are raising alarm bells over a $6 billion agreement between the Biden administration and Iran. Senator Marsha Blackburn (R-TN) and several other GOP members are urging President Biden to reconsider this arrangement, particularly in light of Iran’s alleged involvement in recent attacks on Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Blackburn highlighted her concerns on X, formerly known as Twitter, stating, “&lt;em&gt;The Biden administration is refusing to acknowledge Iran’s role in the unprovoked terrorist attacks on Israel.&lt;/em&gt;” Drawing on a Wall Street Journal report, she emphasized Iran’s potential contribution to plotting the assaults on Israel. Her message was clear: “&lt;em&gt;The United States should not be sending a single penny to Iran — let alone $6 billion. I am immediately calling on Biden to reverse course and cancel the ransom agreement.&lt;/em&gt;”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Supporting Blackburn’s stance, Pennsylvania Senate Republican candidate Dave McCormick called upon the Biden administration to block the transfer of promised funds to Iran, especially in light of the Hamas-led strike on Israel. He pledged that as a Senator, he would spearhead legislation to prevent the allocation of these funds, emphasizing, “&lt;em&gt;Don’t give Iran a penny.&lt;/em&gt;”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The concerns aren’t only about recent events. Former President Donald Trump chimed in on the issue, suggesting that the Biden administration’s decision to move the $6 billion in previously frozen Iranian assets indirectly enabled the recent terrorist activity in Israel. He was quoted saying, “&lt;em&gt;This war happened for three reasons: … the United States giving Iran $6 billion dollars ransom; and our country’s perceived weakness with an incompetent and corrupt leader, Joe Biden, who’s laughed at all over the world&lt;/em&gt;.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adding to the chorus, Sen. Tim Scott (R-SC) expressed his reservations about the Biden administration’s foreign policy decisions, emphasizing that perceived weakness could incite global aggression.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As tensions continue to rise in the Middle East and concerns about the U.S.’s role and responsibility in global politics remain at the forefront, it remains to be seen how the Biden administration will navigate this complex and sensitive issue.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Amidst the turmoil in Israel, Republicans are raising alarm bells over a $6 billion agreement between the Biden administration and Iran. Senator Marsha Blackburn (R-TN) and several other GOP members are urging President Biden to reconsider this arrangement, particularly in light of Iran’s alleged involvement in recent attacks on Israel. Blackburn highlighted her concerns on X, formerly known as Twitter, stating, “The Biden administration is refusing to acknowledge Iran’s role in the unprovoked terrorist attacks on Israel.” Drawing on a Wall Street Journal report, she emphasized Iran’s potential contribution to plotting the assaults on Israel. Her message was clear: “The United States should not be sending a single penny to Iran — let alone $6 billion. I am immediately calling on Biden to reverse course and cancel the ransom agreement.” Supporting Blackburn’s stance, Pennsylvania Senate Republican candidate Dave McCormick called upon the Biden administration to block the transfer of promised funds to Iran, especially in light of the Hamas-led strike on Israel. He pledged that as a Senator, he would spearhead legislation to prevent the allocation of these funds, emphasizing, “Don’t give Iran a penny.” The concerns aren’t only about recent events. Former President Donald Trump chimed in on the issue, suggesting that the Biden administration’s decision to move the $6 billion in previously frozen Iranian assets indirectly enabled the recent terrorist activity in Israel. He was quoted saying, “This war happened for three reasons: … the United States giving Iran $6 billion dollars ransom; and our country’s perceived weakness with an incompetent and corrupt leader, Joe Biden, who’s laughed at all over the world.” Adding to the chorus, Sen. Tim Scott (R-SC) expressed his reservations about the Biden administration’s foreign policy decisions, emphasizing that perceived weakness could incite global aggression. As tensions continue to rise in the Middle East and concerns about the U.S.’s role and responsibility in global politics remain at the forefront, it remains to be seen how the Biden administration will navigate this complex and sensitive issue.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump Holds Biden Responsible for Israel Crisis</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/10/Trump-Israel-Conflict/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump Holds Biden Responsible for Israel Crisis" /><published>2023-10-10T09:15:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-10T09:15:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/10/Trump-Israel-Conflict</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/10/Trump-Israel-Conflict/">&lt;p&gt;WOLFEBORO, N.H. – At a crucial campaign stop in New Hampshire, former President Donald Trump levied strong criticisms against President Joe Biden regarding the recent deadly attacks on Israel by Hamas. Trump is of the firm belief that such atrocities in Israel would never have occurred had he still been in office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump, who is seeking the presidency for the third consecutive time, emphasized that under his leadership, peace in the Middle East was maintained, specifically citing the Abraham Accords. Drawing a clear line between the peace of his term and the current unrest, Trump stated, “Today we have an all-out war in Israel, and it’s going to spread very quickly. What a difference a president makes.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A significant point of contention in Trump’s speech was a recent move by the Biden administration involving a $6 billion transfer to Iran. This move, aimed at releasing five detained U.S. citizens, involved the transfer of frozen Iranian assets from South Korea to an account in Doha, Qatar. Republicans, including Trump, argue that this deal inadvertently provided resources that aided Hamas’ assault on Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Biden administration has emphasized its unwavering support for Israel in these trying times. President Biden remarked that the U.S. stands firmly with the people of Israel and will ensure the nation has the resources to defend itself. Despite these assurances, the central criticism from the Republican side remains fixated on the financial transfer to Iran, seeing it as a misstep that indirectly fueled the conflict.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump further elaborated on his administration’s tough stance on Iran, highlighting how he reduced the Iranian economy, withdrew from the Iran nuclear deal, and imposed sanctions. In a bid to keep America safe, he also initiated strict travel bans targeting radical Islamic terrorists.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His commitment to Israel was clear as he vowed, “As president, I will once again stand strongly with the state of Israel, and we will cut off the money to the terrorists on day one.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the criticism from Trump and other Republicans, the Biden administration continues to assert its firm support for Israel’s right to defend itself, with many in the administration condemning the actions of Hamas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The political landscape is certainly heating up as the 2024 presidential race approaches, and Trump’s campaign stops are likely to be a focal point of interest in the lead-up to the election.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">WOLFEBORO, N.H. – At a crucial campaign stop in New Hampshire, former President Donald Trump levied strong criticisms against President Joe Biden regarding the recent deadly attacks on Israel by Hamas. Trump is of the firm belief that such atrocities in Israel would never have occurred had he still been in office. Trump, who is seeking the presidency for the third consecutive time, emphasized that under his leadership, peace in the Middle East was maintained, specifically citing the Abraham Accords. Drawing a clear line between the peace of his term and the current unrest, Trump stated, “Today we have an all-out war in Israel, and it’s going to spread very quickly. What a difference a president makes.” A significant point of contention in Trump’s speech was a recent move by the Biden administration involving a $6 billion transfer to Iran. This move, aimed at releasing five detained U.S. citizens, involved the transfer of frozen Iranian assets from South Korea to an account in Doha, Qatar. Republicans, including Trump, argue that this deal inadvertently provided resources that aided Hamas’ assault on Israel. The Biden administration has emphasized its unwavering support for Israel in these trying times. President Biden remarked that the U.S. stands firmly with the people of Israel and will ensure the nation has the resources to defend itself. Despite these assurances, the central criticism from the Republican side remains fixated on the financial transfer to Iran, seeing it as a misstep that indirectly fueled the conflict. Trump further elaborated on his administration’s tough stance on Iran, highlighting how he reduced the Iranian economy, withdrew from the Iran nuclear deal, and imposed sanctions. In a bid to keep America safe, he also initiated strict travel bans targeting radical Islamic terrorists. His commitment to Israel was clear as he vowed, “As president, I will once again stand strongly with the state of Israel, and we will cut off the money to the terrorists on day one.” Despite the criticism from Trump and other Republicans, the Biden administration continues to assert its firm support for Israel’s right to defend itself, with many in the administration condemning the actions of Hamas. The political landscape is certainly heating up as the 2024 presidential race approaches, and Trump’s campaign stops are likely to be a focal point of interest in the lead-up to the election.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Mia Khalifa Stirs Controversy with Support for Palestinian Fighters</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/10/Mia-Khalifa-Palestine-Support/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Mia Khalifa Stirs Controversy with Support for Palestinian Fighters" /><published>2023-10-10T08:08:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-10T08:08:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/10/Mia-Khalifa-Palestine-Support</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/10/Mia-Khalifa-Palestine-Support/">&lt;p&gt;Amidst rising tensions in the Middle East, Mia Khalifa, the once adult film actress turned social media sensation, has made waves with her support for Palestinian fighters during the recent Hamas attacks on Israel. Her opinions, shared with her millions of followers, have sparked significant debate online.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Khalifa, boasting a massive following of 5 million on Twitter and 27.5 million on Instagram, shared a plethora of posts on Saturday expressing her firm stance on the Israeli-Palestinian conflict. Referring to one image of the aggressors, she commented that it looked like a “Renaissance painting.” Mia Khalifa’s significant reach ensures that her perspectives make a notable impact.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the subject of the long-standing conflict, Khalifa remarked, “If you can look at the situation in Palestine and not be on the side of Palestinians, then you are on the wrong side of apartheid and history will show that in time.” She further expressed disbelief at the idea of the “Zionist apartheid regime” facing challenges from guerrilla fighters, some of whom she humorously noted were donned in “fake Gucci shirts”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Khalifa was not alone in her sentiments. She reposted statements from fellow influencers, such as Kelbin with 130,000 followers, who expressed that the attacks showcased the oppressed fighting their oppressor. Another influencer, Sana Saeed with 110,000 followers, shared her personal experience of receiving applause and support when identifying as Palestinian in Istanbul markets. A sentiment of supporting Palestinians was prevalent among various posts shared by Khalifa.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it’s essential to note that Mia Khalifa’s outspokenness is not solely restricted to political matters. Known for her brief yet impactful stint in the adult film industry, she has been vocal about her regrets concerning her past decisions. In 2020, she joined OnlyFans, where she shares content described as “safe for work, but spicy.” By August 2023, Mia made headlines with a clip promoting “marriage advice,” wherein she advocated for women to leave unsatisfactory relationships, emphasizing the non-sanctimonious nature of marriage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the vast realm of social media, where opinions are shared and spread at lightning speed, voices like Mia Khalifa’s play a pivotal role. Whether one agrees or disagrees with her positions, the influence she wields cannot be denied. As the Israeli-Palestinian conflict continues to evolve, it’s clear that celebrities and influencers will remain vocal in shaping public opinion.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Amidst rising tensions in the Middle East, Mia Khalifa, the once adult film actress turned social media sensation, has made waves with her support for Palestinian fighters during the recent Hamas attacks on Israel. Her opinions, shared with her millions of followers, have sparked significant debate online. Khalifa, boasting a massive following of 5 million on Twitter and 27.5 million on Instagram, shared a plethora of posts on Saturday expressing her firm stance on the Israeli-Palestinian conflict. Referring to one image of the aggressors, she commented that it looked like a “Renaissance painting.” Mia Khalifa’s significant reach ensures that her perspectives make a notable impact. On the subject of the long-standing conflict, Khalifa remarked, “If you can look at the situation in Palestine and not be on the side of Palestinians, then you are on the wrong side of apartheid and history will show that in time.” She further expressed disbelief at the idea of the “Zionist apartheid regime” facing challenges from guerrilla fighters, some of whom she humorously noted were donned in “fake Gucci shirts”. Khalifa was not alone in her sentiments. She reposted statements from fellow influencers, such as Kelbin with 130,000 followers, who expressed that the attacks showcased the oppressed fighting their oppressor. Another influencer, Sana Saeed with 110,000 followers, shared her personal experience of receiving applause and support when identifying as Palestinian in Istanbul markets. A sentiment of supporting Palestinians was prevalent among various posts shared by Khalifa. However, it’s essential to note that Mia Khalifa’s outspokenness is not solely restricted to political matters. Known for her brief yet impactful stint in the adult film industry, she has been vocal about her regrets concerning her past decisions. In 2020, she joined OnlyFans, where she shares content described as “safe for work, but spicy.” By August 2023, Mia made headlines with a clip promoting “marriage advice,” wherein she advocated for women to leave unsatisfactory relationships, emphasizing the non-sanctimonious nature of marriage. In the vast realm of social media, where opinions are shared and spread at lightning speed, voices like Mia Khalifa’s play a pivotal role. Whether one agrees or disagrees with her positions, the influence she wields cannot be denied. As the Israeli-Palestinian conflict continues to evolve, it’s clear that celebrities and influencers will remain vocal in shaping public opinion.</summary></entry></feed>