<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-10-07T10:12:38-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/07/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-07T10:12:38-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-07T10:12:38-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/07/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/07/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump’s Legal Team Pushes to Pause High-Profile Fraud Trial</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/07/Trump-Trial-Halted/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump’s Legal Team Pushes to Pause High-Profile Fraud Trial" /><published>2023-10-07T08:15:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-07T08:15:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/07/Trump-Trial-Halted</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/07/Trump-Trial-Halted/">&lt;p&gt;Former President Donald Trump finds himself at the center of a legal maelstrom, as his attorneys fervently appeal to halt a Manhattan civil fraud trial. The crux? Trump’s most prized assets, including the iconic Trump Tower.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a bid to delay the trial, Trump’s legal team is challenging a court ruling by Judge Arthur Engoron, which could spell the dissolution of companies controlling some of Trump’s major assets. The gravity of this ruling suggests a court-appointed receiver might oversee Trump’s businesses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Drawing attention, Trump lawyers Clifford Robert, Michael Farina, and Michael Madaio penned a 41-page appellate brief, describing the potential havoc Engoron’s verdict could bring. They emphasized the “severe and irreparable harm” not just to Trump and the defendants but also to countless employees relying on those businesses for their livelihood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The backdrop is set with the appellate court already dismissing a previous attempt to delay the trial, mere days before its commencement. Adding to the evolving scenario, Trump’s legal representatives withdrew a lawsuit against Judge Engoron last Thursday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet, the Attorney General of New York, Letitia James, remains steadfast. James’ office conveyed their openness to discuss enforcing Engoron’s verdict post-trial. However, they desire the trial to persist without interruptions. Senior Assistant Solicitor General Dennis Fan argued against abruptly halting the trial, citing the logistical intricacies, security arrangements, and potential inconvenience to scheduled witnesses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Revealing an intriguing turn of events, Engoron concluded last week that Trump engaged in fraudulent activities while establishing his real estate empire. This verdict stems from James’ lawsuit that accused Trump of deceiving various stakeholders by inflating the value of his assets in annual financial reports.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump, however, rebuts these allegations, contending that many of his assets are undervalued in those statements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ensuring clarity, Engoron delineated the procedures for enforcing his ruling last Thursday. He allocated deadlines for both parties to suggest potential receivers and directed Trump and the defendants to inform a court-appointed monitor about the entities affected by his verdict.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A significant directive also mandated the defendants to notify the monitor before applying for new business licenses or trying to form new entities that might inherit the assets of a dissolving company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump’s attorneys, though, counter-argue that Engoron’s decision lacks a coherent legal basis, dubbing it as “the corporate death penalty.” They further criticize the judge for ambiguity in elucidating the real-world implications of his verdict.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In an earlier pretrial hearing, another Trump lawyer, Christopher Kise, sought clarity from Engoron on the extent of the ruling’s impact on Trump’s assets. Engoron, however, deferred his response.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Summarizing their appeal, Trump’s legal team underscores their concerns about the far-reaching consequences of Engoron’s “overbroad directive,” emphasizing its potential to usher in “confusion and chaos.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the political world watches with bated breath, only time will unveil the outcome of this legal tussle between Trump and the New York Attorney General’s office.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Former President Donald Trump finds himself at the center of a legal maelstrom, as his attorneys fervently appeal to halt a Manhattan civil fraud trial. The crux? Trump’s most prized assets, including the iconic Trump Tower. In a bid to delay the trial, Trump’s legal team is challenging a court ruling by Judge Arthur Engoron, which could spell the dissolution of companies controlling some of Trump’s major assets. The gravity of this ruling suggests a court-appointed receiver might oversee Trump’s businesses. Drawing attention, Trump lawyers Clifford Robert, Michael Farina, and Michael Madaio penned a 41-page appellate brief, describing the potential havoc Engoron’s verdict could bring. They emphasized the “severe and irreparable harm” not just to Trump and the defendants but also to countless employees relying on those businesses for their livelihood. The backdrop is set with the appellate court already dismissing a previous attempt to delay the trial, mere days before its commencement. Adding to the evolving scenario, Trump’s legal representatives withdrew a lawsuit against Judge Engoron last Thursday. Yet, the Attorney General of New York, Letitia James, remains steadfast. James’ office conveyed their openness to discuss enforcing Engoron’s verdict post-trial. However, they desire the trial to persist without interruptions. Senior Assistant Solicitor General Dennis Fan argued against abruptly halting the trial, citing the logistical intricacies, security arrangements, and potential inconvenience to scheduled witnesses. Revealing an intriguing turn of events, Engoron concluded last week that Trump engaged in fraudulent activities while establishing his real estate empire. This verdict stems from James’ lawsuit that accused Trump of deceiving various stakeholders by inflating the value of his assets in annual financial reports. Trump, however, rebuts these allegations, contending that many of his assets are undervalued in those statements. Ensuring clarity, Engoron delineated the procedures for enforcing his ruling last Thursday. He allocated deadlines for both parties to suggest potential receivers and directed Trump and the defendants to inform a court-appointed monitor about the entities affected by his verdict. A significant directive also mandated the defendants to notify the monitor before applying for new business licenses or trying to form new entities that might inherit the assets of a dissolving company. Trump’s attorneys, though, counter-argue that Engoron’s decision lacks a coherent legal basis, dubbing it as “the corporate death penalty.” They further criticize the judge for ambiguity in elucidating the real-world implications of his verdict. In an earlier pretrial hearing, another Trump lawyer, Christopher Kise, sought clarity from Engoron on the extent of the ruling’s impact on Trump’s assets. Engoron, however, deferred his response. Summarizing their appeal, Trump’s legal team underscores their concerns about the far-reaching consequences of Engoron’s “overbroad directive,” emphasizing its potential to usher in “confusion and chaos.” While the political world watches with bated breath, only time will unveil the outcome of this legal tussle between Trump and the New York Attorney General’s office.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Downfall of Senator Bob Menendez: A Glimpse into Years of Alleged Corruption</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/07/Senator-Menendez-Indictment/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Downfall of Senator Bob Menendez: A Glimpse into Years of Alleged Corruption" /><published>2023-10-07T06:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-07T06:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/07/Senator-Menendez-Indictment</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/07/Senator-Menendez-Indictment/">&lt;p&gt;New revelations about New Jersey Democrat Senator Bob Menendez and his wife, Nadine Arslanian Menendez, are shaking the political landscape. The power couple now faces a federal indictment linked to a bribery scheme spanning multiple years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The hefty allegations trace back to a seemingly opulent lifestyle: a $60,000 Mercedes-Benz convertible, bars of gold, and an influx of hard cash. With these revelations, it’s no wonder that Sen. Menendez recently resigned from his esteemed position as chair of the Senate Foreign Relations Committee. This isn’t his first rendezvous with the law either. Back in 2016, he was indicted on similar bribery charges, a case that eventually resulted in his acquittal in 2018.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The story unfolds as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In February 2018, Arslanian starts her romantic journey with Menendez. It’s during this time that Menendez becomes acquainted with businessman Wael Hana. Hana’s close ties with Egyptian officials, coupled with connections to New Jersey real estate developer Fred Daibes and insurance expert Jose Uribe, become central to the story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From 2018 to 2022, Menendez and Arslanian allegedly receive a myriad of bribes from their new circle: gold bars, substantial cash amounts, a luxury Mercedes-Benz, mortgage payments, and home furnishings. The indictment even claims Menendez leaked sensitive U.S. government intel to Egyptian officials.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In October 2018, Daibes faces federal charges. However, two months later, Arslanian finds herself in the limelight after fatally hitting a pedestrian. Curiously, she was quickly released without a DUI test.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By 2019, Uribe extends an offer to purchase a new Mercedes-Benz for the couple following Arslanian’s tragic accident. Menendez, in return, allegedly seeks to influence an investigation involving Uribe. Hana’s business then steps in, settling Arslanian’s house mortgage. Menendez is also said to have leveraged his influence to protect Hana’s business interests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From 2020 to 2022, Menendez allegedly agrees to manipulate the prosecution of Daibes in a quid pro quo involving cash, gold, and furniture. By June 2022, an FBI raid at the Menendez residence unveils over half a million dollars in cash and multiple gold bars.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In September 2023, charges are officially brought against both Arslanian and Menendez. Despite the growing clamor for his resignation, Menendez remains steadfast, pleading not guilty to all accusations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Senator Menendez’s career now hangs in the balance, with the weight of years-long alleged corruption casting a long shadow. Only time will reveal the ultimate fate of one of New Jersey’s most prominent political figures.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">New revelations about New Jersey Democrat Senator Bob Menendez and his wife, Nadine Arslanian Menendez, are shaking the political landscape. The power couple now faces a federal indictment linked to a bribery scheme spanning multiple years. The hefty allegations trace back to a seemingly opulent lifestyle: a $60,000 Mercedes-Benz convertible, bars of gold, and an influx of hard cash. With these revelations, it’s no wonder that Sen. Menendez recently resigned from his esteemed position as chair of the Senate Foreign Relations Committee. This isn’t his first rendezvous with the law either. Back in 2016, he was indicted on similar bribery charges, a case that eventually resulted in his acquittal in 2018. The story unfolds as follows: In February 2018, Arslanian starts her romantic journey with Menendez. It’s during this time that Menendez becomes acquainted with businessman Wael Hana. Hana’s close ties with Egyptian officials, coupled with connections to New Jersey real estate developer Fred Daibes and insurance expert Jose Uribe, become central to the story. From 2018 to 2022, Menendez and Arslanian allegedly receive a myriad of bribes from their new circle: gold bars, substantial cash amounts, a luxury Mercedes-Benz, mortgage payments, and home furnishings. The indictment even claims Menendez leaked sensitive U.S. government intel to Egyptian officials. In October 2018, Daibes faces federal charges. However, two months later, Arslanian finds herself in the limelight after fatally hitting a pedestrian. Curiously, she was quickly released without a DUI test. By 2019, Uribe extends an offer to purchase a new Mercedes-Benz for the couple following Arslanian’s tragic accident. Menendez, in return, allegedly seeks to influence an investigation involving Uribe. Hana’s business then steps in, settling Arslanian’s house mortgage. Menendez is also said to have leveraged his influence to protect Hana’s business interests. From 2020 to 2022, Menendez allegedly agrees to manipulate the prosecution of Daibes in a quid pro quo involving cash, gold, and furniture. By June 2022, an FBI raid at the Menendez residence unveils over half a million dollars in cash and multiple gold bars. In September 2023, charges are officially brought against both Arslanian and Menendez. Despite the growing clamor for his resignation, Menendez remains steadfast, pleading not guilty to all accusations. Senator Menendez’s career now hangs in the balance, with the weight of years-long alleged corruption casting a long shadow. Only time will reveal the ultimate fate of one of New Jersey’s most prominent political figures.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">US Forces Neutralize Turkish Drone: Rising Tensions in Syria</title><link href="/news/2023/10/06/Turkish-Drone-Downed/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="US Forces Neutralize Turkish Drone: Rising Tensions in Syria" /><published>2023-10-06T17:51:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-06T17:51:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/06/Turkish-Drone-Downed</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/06/Turkish-Drone-Downed/">&lt;p&gt;In a developing situation that highlights the complexities of the Syrian arena, US Armed Forces shot down a Turkish drone close to an American base in northeast Syria. The incident, confirmed by the Pentagon, occurred near Hasakah and was a direct response to the drone being perceived as a “potential threat.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Defense Secretary Lloyd Austin communicated with his Turkish counterpart, Minister of National Defense Yasar Guler, emphasizing both nations’ joint commitment to defeating ISIS and ensuring regional stability. Despite the collapse of the ISIS “caliphate” in Raqqa in 2017, the US continues its military presence in Syria.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In recent actions, Turkey commenced aerial bombings in both Syria and Iraq on October 1. This move came in retaliation to an attempted suicide bombing in Ankara, claimed by the Kurdistan Workers’ Party (PKK), a US-designated terrorist group. The Turkish administration, led by President Recep Tayyip Erdogan, has asserted that these airstrikes aimed to dismantle PKK bases and resources. However, Turkey broadly categorizes several Kurdish factions in Syria and Iraq, some of which are US allies, under the same PKK label.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This backdrop brings into context the Turkish drone’s proximity to the American outpost. Pentagon Press Secretary Air Force Brig. Gen. Pat Ryder highlighted the immediate threat the drone posed, leading to the necessary defense action by US F-16 fighters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the US views this as a regrettable but necessary measure, Turkey’s state-run Anadolu news agency did not discuss the drone’s downing. However, the Turkish media did acknowledge their defense operations’ success in Syria, emphasizing the destruction of multiple PKK targets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s growing concern on the ground. Reports from Kurdish news sources indicate that recent Turkish bombings in Syrian Kurdistan led to civilian casualties. Farhad Shami, head of the SDF media center, condemned Turkey’s targeting of infrastructure and public service facilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The incident underscores the volatile dynamics in Syria, involving a matrix of actors with overlapping alliances and conflicting objectives. With US forces primarily in Syria to combat the ISIS threat, situations like these drone incidents emphasize the necessity for clear communication and cooperation between regional players to avoid unnecessary escalations.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a developing situation that highlights the complexities of the Syrian arena, US Armed Forces shot down a Turkish drone close to an American base in northeast Syria. The incident, confirmed by the Pentagon, occurred near Hasakah and was a direct response to the drone being perceived as a “potential threat.” Defense Secretary Lloyd Austin communicated with his Turkish counterpart, Minister of National Defense Yasar Guler, emphasizing both nations’ joint commitment to defeating ISIS and ensuring regional stability. Despite the collapse of the ISIS “caliphate” in Raqqa in 2017, the US continues its military presence in Syria. In recent actions, Turkey commenced aerial bombings in both Syria and Iraq on October 1. This move came in retaliation to an attempted suicide bombing in Ankara, claimed by the Kurdistan Workers’ Party (PKK), a US-designated terrorist group. The Turkish administration, led by President Recep Tayyip Erdogan, has asserted that these airstrikes aimed to dismantle PKK bases and resources. However, Turkey broadly categorizes several Kurdish factions in Syria and Iraq, some of which are US allies, under the same PKK label. This backdrop brings into context the Turkish drone’s proximity to the American outpost. Pentagon Press Secretary Air Force Brig. Gen. Pat Ryder highlighted the immediate threat the drone posed, leading to the necessary defense action by US F-16 fighters. While the US views this as a regrettable but necessary measure, Turkey’s state-run Anadolu news agency did not discuss the drone’s downing. However, the Turkish media did acknowledge their defense operations’ success in Syria, emphasizing the destruction of multiple PKK targets. There’s growing concern on the ground. Reports from Kurdish news sources indicate that recent Turkish bombings in Syrian Kurdistan led to civilian casualties. Farhad Shami, head of the SDF media center, condemned Turkey’s targeting of infrastructure and public service facilities. The incident underscores the volatile dynamics in Syria, involving a matrix of actors with overlapping alliances and conflicting objectives. With US forces primarily in Syria to combat the ISIS threat, situations like these drone incidents emphasize the necessity for clear communication and cooperation between regional players to avoid unnecessary escalations.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Explosive Testimony in FTX Fraud Case: Co-Founder Admits Guilt</title><link href="/news/2023/10/06/FTX-Fraud-Revelation/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Explosive Testimony in FTX Fraud Case: Co-Founder Admits Guilt" /><published>2023-10-06T15:45:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-06T15:45:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/06/FTX-Fraud-Revelation</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/06/FTX-Fraud-Revelation/">&lt;p&gt;In a gripping courtroom drama, Gary Wang, co-founder of the controversial cryptocurrency exchange FTX, dropped bombshell testimonies on Thursday. Wang, once the chief technical officer of FTX, openly admitted to collaborating with ex-FTX CEO, Sam Bankman-Fried, in committing multiple counts of fraud.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Detailing the extent of the malfeasance, Wang revealed, “Wire fraud, commodities fraud, securities fraud.” This admission, coming from a core member of the FTX leadership, has sent shockwaves across the crypto community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://media.breitbart.com/media/2022/12/sam-bankman-fried-ftx-arrest-getty.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Sam Bankman-Fried escorted by police&quot; /&gt;(MARIO DUNCANSON/AFP via Getty Images)
&lt;em&gt;FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried being escorted by the Royal Bahamas Police Force in Nassau.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Elevating the intrigue surrounding the case, Wang is highlighted as one of the prosecution’s ace witnesses. He shed light on the involvement of other key FTX leaders, including Caroline Ellison and Nishad Singh. Ellison, known to have a close personal relationship with Bankman-Fried, helmed Alameda Research, a hedge fund closely affiliated with FTX. Singh, a prominent FTX engineer, and Ellison have both accepted their involvement in the alleged illicit activities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wang’s testimonies further unveiled the intricate ties between FTX and Alameda Research. He stated, “We extended exclusive benefits to Alameda Research, enabling them to extract unrestricted funds from FTX. Unfortunately, these actions were misrepresented to our user base.” Alarmingly, Wang confessed that Alameda had borrowed a staggering $8 billion from FTX—funds that originally belonged to FTX’s customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the case unfolds, Sam Bankman-Fried, the former FTX CEO and a notable Democrat donor, faces seven severe charges, including fraud, conspiracy, and money laundering. These allegations revolve around Bankman-Fried’s purported misuse of FTX customer assets to compensate for Alameda Research’s financial deficits. Additionally, he is accused of channeling these funds for personal real estate acquisitions and other individual expenditures. Despite the weight of these allegations, Bankman-Fried maintains his innocence, pleading not guilty to all charges. If convicted, he stares down the possibility of an astounding 110-year prison sentence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a recent development, Bankman-Fried’s defense counsel presented their perspective, portraying the former CEO as a dedicated “math nerd” who led an austere life. They stated, “Sam was not involved in any theft. Instead, he genuinely believed that the loans FTX provided to Alameda were fully legitimate, backed by substantial security and collateral.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As this high-stakes trial progresses, it promises more twists and turns, holding the cryptocurrency world in rapt attention. The outcomes could set significant precedents for future crypto-related legal cases.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a gripping courtroom drama, Gary Wang, co-founder of the controversial cryptocurrency exchange FTX, dropped bombshell testimonies on Thursday. Wang, once the chief technical officer of FTX, openly admitted to collaborating with ex-FTX CEO, Sam Bankman-Fried, in committing multiple counts of fraud. Detailing the extent of the malfeasance, Wang revealed, “Wire fraud, commodities fraud, securities fraud.” This admission, coming from a core member of the FTX leadership, has sent shockwaves across the crypto community. (MARIO DUNCANSON/AFP via Getty Images) FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried being escorted by the Royal Bahamas Police Force in Nassau. Elevating the intrigue surrounding the case, Wang is highlighted as one of the prosecution’s ace witnesses. He shed light on the involvement of other key FTX leaders, including Caroline Ellison and Nishad Singh. Ellison, known to have a close personal relationship with Bankman-Fried, helmed Alameda Research, a hedge fund closely affiliated with FTX. Singh, a prominent FTX engineer, and Ellison have both accepted their involvement in the alleged illicit activities. Wang’s testimonies further unveiled the intricate ties between FTX and Alameda Research. He stated, “We extended exclusive benefits to Alameda Research, enabling them to extract unrestricted funds from FTX. Unfortunately, these actions were misrepresented to our user base.” Alarmingly, Wang confessed that Alameda had borrowed a staggering $8 billion from FTX—funds that originally belonged to FTX’s customers. As the case unfolds, Sam Bankman-Fried, the former FTX CEO and a notable Democrat donor, faces seven severe charges, including fraud, conspiracy, and money laundering. These allegations revolve around Bankman-Fried’s purported misuse of FTX customer assets to compensate for Alameda Research’s financial deficits. Additionally, he is accused of channeling these funds for personal real estate acquisitions and other individual expenditures. Despite the weight of these allegations, Bankman-Fried maintains his innocence, pleading not guilty to all charges. If convicted, he stares down the possibility of an astounding 110-year prison sentence. In a recent development, Bankman-Fried’s defense counsel presented their perspective, portraying the former CEO as a dedicated “math nerd” who led an austere life. They stated, “Sam was not involved in any theft. Instead, he genuinely believed that the loans FTX provided to Alameda were fully legitimate, backed by substantial security and collateral.” As this high-stakes trial progresses, it promises more twists and turns, holding the cryptocurrency world in rapt attention. The outcomes could set significant precedents for future crypto-related legal cases.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump Triumphs in Court: Delay Granted in Classified Documents Trial</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/06/Trump-Classified-Docs-Delay/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump Triumphs in Court: Delay Granted in Classified Documents Trial" /><published>2023-10-06T14:33:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-06T14:33:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/06/Trump-Classified-Docs-Delay</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/06/Trump-Classified-Docs-Delay/">&lt;p&gt;Former President Donald Trump experienced a legal victory on Friday, obtaining a delay in the upcoming classified documents trial. Judge Aileen Cannon granted a delay in a pre-trial filing deadline, providing Trump’s legal team with additional time in the case related to the Classified Information Procedures Act (CIPA).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This significant decision arrived shortly after Trump’s team requested the judge to defer his classified documents trial to a date post the 2024 presidential election. The current date set for this trial is May 20 in Florida, while the general election is scheduled for November 5, 2024.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the heart of this high-profile case is the accusation that Trump illicitly stockpiled classified documents during his presidency. However, Trump, standing firm, has refuted all allegations of misconduct.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Highlighting potential scheduling conflicts as a primary reason for the requested delay, Trump’s attorneys mentioned another criminal trial scheduled for March 4, 2023. They emphasized the challenge of managing overlapping trial schedules, particularly when Trump and his lawyers would be required to be present in different locations simultaneously. This brings to light the demanding logistics of managing multiple legal fronts for the former president.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An additional point of contention raised by Trump’s legal representatives revolves around delays in acquiring classified evidence. This evidence, under the jurisdiction of special counsel Jack Smith’s office, has been acknowledged but not entirely handed over to Trump’s team. The lawyers stress the importance of thoroughly reviewing all discovery items before proceeding with the CIPA litigation process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Neama Rahmani, a former federal prosecutor, weighed in on the situation, explaining to Salon that Trump’s attorneys are strategically employing CIPA to buy time. The goal? To ensure they have all the evidence at hand and subsequently lay the groundwork for a strong defense.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As political observers keep a close eye on this case, it’s evident that the stakes are high. With the 2024 elections around the corner, the outcome of this trial could have profound implications for Trump’s political future. Moreover, this case has further intensified the national conversation around the handling and protection of classified information by officials at the highest level of governance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the coming months, as both sides prepare for the eventual courtroom battle, the nation will be watching intently, anticipating how this legal saga might impact the broader political landscape of the United States.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Former President Donald Trump experienced a legal victory on Friday, obtaining a delay in the upcoming classified documents trial. Judge Aileen Cannon granted a delay in a pre-trial filing deadline, providing Trump’s legal team with additional time in the case related to the Classified Information Procedures Act (CIPA). This significant decision arrived shortly after Trump’s team requested the judge to defer his classified documents trial to a date post the 2024 presidential election. The current date set for this trial is May 20 in Florida, while the general election is scheduled for November 5, 2024. At the heart of this high-profile case is the accusation that Trump illicitly stockpiled classified documents during his presidency. However, Trump, standing firm, has refuted all allegations of misconduct. Highlighting potential scheduling conflicts as a primary reason for the requested delay, Trump’s attorneys mentioned another criminal trial scheduled for March 4, 2023. They emphasized the challenge of managing overlapping trial schedules, particularly when Trump and his lawyers would be required to be present in different locations simultaneously. This brings to light the demanding logistics of managing multiple legal fronts for the former president. An additional point of contention raised by Trump’s legal representatives revolves around delays in acquiring classified evidence. This evidence, under the jurisdiction of special counsel Jack Smith’s office, has been acknowledged but not entirely handed over to Trump’s team. The lawyers stress the importance of thoroughly reviewing all discovery items before proceeding with the CIPA litigation process. Neama Rahmani, a former federal prosecutor, weighed in on the situation, explaining to Salon that Trump’s attorneys are strategically employing CIPA to buy time. The goal? To ensure they have all the evidence at hand and subsequently lay the groundwork for a strong defense. As political observers keep a close eye on this case, it’s evident that the stakes are high. With the 2024 elections around the corner, the outcome of this trial could have profound implications for Trump’s political future. Moreover, this case has further intensified the national conversation around the handling and protection of classified information by officials at the highest level of governance. In the coming months, as both sides prepare for the eventual courtroom battle, the nation will be watching intently, anticipating how this legal saga might impact the broader political landscape of the United States.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hillary Clinton Sparks Controversy: Trump Supporters Require ‘Deprogramming’</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/06/Trump-Backers-Deprogramming/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hillary Clinton Sparks Controversy: Trump Supporters Require ‘Deprogramming’" /><published>2023-10-06T13:38:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-06T13:38:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/06/Trump-Backers-Deprogramming</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/06/Trump-Backers-Deprogramming/">&lt;p&gt;Tensions flared as Hillary Clinton, the 2016 presidential campaign rival to former President Donald Trump, made controversial remarks suggesting a “formal deprogramming” for Trump’s supporters, whom she labeled as “cult members.” The comments have ignited swift reactions from MAGA Inc., the super PAC supporting Trump.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a recent interview set to air on CNN with Christiane Amanpour, Clinton speculated on the possible nomination of Trump by the GOP in the upcoming 2024 elections. She firmly believed that the current president, Joe Biden, holds the capability to best Trump in a head-to-head battle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clinton did not mince words when discussing the dynamics within the Republican Party. Highlighting past disagreements on topics like gun control, climate change, taxes, and the economy, she expressed concern over the current trajectory of the party. According to Clinton, an “extremist” faction within the GOP, heavily influenced by Trump, is shifting the party’s focus and direction. She lamented, “There wasn’t this little tail of extremism wagging the dog of the Republican Party as it is today.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As tensions continue to simmer, Clinton did not shy away from direct criticism of Trump. She emphasized his diminishing credibility and highlighted his entanglements in various legal actions, both civil and criminal. Furthermore, she posed a thought-provoking question, wondering when party members might begin distancing themselves from the former president.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In her detailed critique, Clinton posed a comparative analysis of Biden and Trump, insinuating a stark contrast between their approaches and impacts. While she lauded Biden for his accomplishments and effectiveness in office, she presented Trump as a direct threat to the foundation of American democracy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ousting of former House Speaker Kevin McCarthy also emerged as a topic of discussion. Clinton denounced the conservatives responsible for the vote leading to his removal. She attributed McCarthy’s removal to his collaboration with Democrats on a 45-day continuing resolution designed to maintain governmental operations. Highlighting Rep. Jim Jordan of Ohio, who has gained Trump’s endorsement for the Speaker position, Clinton described him as one of the main orchestrators of the GOP’s ongoing political “circus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In her concluding remarks, Clinton expressed hope that the influence of a “small group of extremists” within the GOP would face challenges and resistance. As for who might rise to that challenge, she remained optimistic about the emergence of a unifying figure within the Republican Party.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Responding to Clinton’s comments, MAGA Inc. spokeswoman Karoline Leavitt issued a statement emphasizing Trump’s perspective. She reiterated the belief that critics like Clinton target Trump mainly to undermine his vast supporter base. Leavitt further projected confidence in the potential re-election of Trump in 2024, proclaiming him the “47th President of the United States.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With these escalating exchanges, the political landscape appears more polarized than ever, setting the stage for a fiercely contested 2024 election.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Tensions flared as Hillary Clinton, the 2016 presidential campaign rival to former President Donald Trump, made controversial remarks suggesting a “formal deprogramming” for Trump’s supporters, whom she labeled as “cult members.” The comments have ignited swift reactions from MAGA Inc., the super PAC supporting Trump. In a recent interview set to air on CNN with Christiane Amanpour, Clinton speculated on the possible nomination of Trump by the GOP in the upcoming 2024 elections. She firmly believed that the current president, Joe Biden, holds the capability to best Trump in a head-to-head battle. Clinton did not mince words when discussing the dynamics within the Republican Party. Highlighting past disagreements on topics like gun control, climate change, taxes, and the economy, she expressed concern over the current trajectory of the party. According to Clinton, an “extremist” faction within the GOP, heavily influenced by Trump, is shifting the party’s focus and direction. She lamented, “There wasn’t this little tail of extremism wagging the dog of the Republican Party as it is today.” As tensions continue to simmer, Clinton did not shy away from direct criticism of Trump. She emphasized his diminishing credibility and highlighted his entanglements in various legal actions, both civil and criminal. Furthermore, she posed a thought-provoking question, wondering when party members might begin distancing themselves from the former president. In her detailed critique, Clinton posed a comparative analysis of Biden and Trump, insinuating a stark contrast between their approaches and impacts. While she lauded Biden for his accomplishments and effectiveness in office, she presented Trump as a direct threat to the foundation of American democracy. The ousting of former House Speaker Kevin McCarthy also emerged as a topic of discussion. Clinton denounced the conservatives responsible for the vote leading to his removal. She attributed McCarthy’s removal to his collaboration with Democrats on a 45-day continuing resolution designed to maintain governmental operations. Highlighting Rep. Jim Jordan of Ohio, who has gained Trump’s endorsement for the Speaker position, Clinton described him as one of the main orchestrators of the GOP’s ongoing political “circus.” In her concluding remarks, Clinton expressed hope that the influence of a “small group of extremists” within the GOP would face challenges and resistance. As for who might rise to that challenge, she remained optimistic about the emergence of a unifying figure within the Republican Party. Responding to Clinton’s comments, MAGA Inc. spokeswoman Karoline Leavitt issued a statement emphasizing Trump’s perspective. She reiterated the belief that critics like Clinton target Trump mainly to undermine his vast supporter base. Leavitt further projected confidence in the potential re-election of Trump in 2024, proclaiming him the “47th President of the United States.” With these escalating exchanges, the political landscape appears more polarized than ever, setting the stage for a fiercely contested 2024 election.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Gavin’s Choices - The Reimagination of California’s Political Landscape</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/06/Newsom-California-Appointments/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Gavin’s Choices - The Reimagination of California’s Political Landscape" /><published>2023-10-06T13:02:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-06T13:02:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/06/Newsom-California-Appointments</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/06/Newsom-California-Appointments/">&lt;p&gt;With the passing of Senator Dianne Feinstein at the age of 90, California’s Governor Gavin Newsom finds himself in the singular position of appointing individuals to the state’s most influential political roles, shaping the Golden State’s future political panorama.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-governors-palette&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Governor’s Palette&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The vacancy left by Feinstein gives Newsom the unprecedented opportunity to handpick appointees to all of California’s pivotal positions. He had previously appointed Alex Padilla to fill the seat vacated by now Vice President Kamala Harris in 2021. With his authority extending over the appointments of two senators, the secretary of state, and the state’s attorney general, Newsom is perceived as wielding the brush that colors California’s political canvas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;shaping-californias-political-spectrum&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shaping California’s Political Spectrum&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Newsom’s appointments have the power to define the political and legislative trajectory of the state. These roles are instrumental in steering policies, legislative decisions, and statewide initiatives. The appointments will impact various aspects of California’s political, economic, and social spheres, highlighting Newsom’s vision for the state’s future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;commitment-and-controversy&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Commitment and Controversy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Earlier, Governor Newsom had vowed to appoint a Black woman to the U.S. Senate should a vacancy arise. However, he has recently opted for a more interim approach, stating his preference to avoid involvement in the primary. Newsom’s careful maneuvering in these appointments has sparked debates on his commitments and the implications of his selections on the state’s Democratic primaries and overall political equilibrium.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;balancing-act&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Balancing Act&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The decision of who will fill these vital roles brings forth the complex task of balancing promise, performance, preference, and politics. There’s an expectation for Newsom to consider candidates who will address critical issues such as inflation, homelessness, and crime, and not merely pursue national recognition or indulge in polarizing political discourse. California Assembly Republican Leader James Gallagher emphasized the hope that Newsom’s selections would be driven by performance over politics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;california-at-a-crossroad&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;California at a Crossroad&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The unfolding scenario places California at a strategic crossroad, where the governor’s appointments will play a decisive role in shaping the state’s ideological and legislative outlook. It draws attention to Newsom’s commitments, decision-making, and the resulting political landscape of California. The Governor’s choices, invariably, will sculpt the political narrative and policy directions of the state in the foreseeable future, marking a pivotal moment in California’s political evolution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, Governor Newsom’s successive appointments underscore a transformative phase for California, where the implications of each selection will reverberate through the state’s political corridors, potentially redefining California’s identity on the national stage. The impact of Newsom’s choices will not only shape the immediate political climate but will also etch the pathways for the state’s long-term political, social, and economic journey.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">With the passing of Senator Dianne Feinstein at the age of 90, California’s Governor Gavin Newsom finds himself in the singular position of appointing individuals to the state’s most influential political roles, shaping the Golden State’s future political panorama. The Governor’s Palette The vacancy left by Feinstein gives Newsom the unprecedented opportunity to handpick appointees to all of California’s pivotal positions. He had previously appointed Alex Padilla to fill the seat vacated by now Vice President Kamala Harris in 2021. With his authority extending over the appointments of two senators, the secretary of state, and the state’s attorney general, Newsom is perceived as wielding the brush that colors California’s political canvas. Shaping California’s Political Spectrum Newsom’s appointments have the power to define the political and legislative trajectory of the state. These roles are instrumental in steering policies, legislative decisions, and statewide initiatives. The appointments will impact various aspects of California’s political, economic, and social spheres, highlighting Newsom’s vision for the state’s future. Commitment and Controversy Earlier, Governor Newsom had vowed to appoint a Black woman to the U.S. Senate should a vacancy arise. However, he has recently opted for a more interim approach, stating his preference to avoid involvement in the primary. Newsom’s careful maneuvering in these appointments has sparked debates on his commitments and the implications of his selections on the state’s Democratic primaries and overall political equilibrium. Balancing Act The decision of who will fill these vital roles brings forth the complex task of balancing promise, performance, preference, and politics. There’s an expectation for Newsom to consider candidates who will address critical issues such as inflation, homelessness, and crime, and not merely pursue national recognition or indulge in polarizing political discourse. California Assembly Republican Leader James Gallagher emphasized the hope that Newsom’s selections would be driven by performance over politics. California at a Crossroad The unfolding scenario places California at a strategic crossroad, where the governor’s appointments will play a decisive role in shaping the state’s ideological and legislative outlook. It draws attention to Newsom’s commitments, decision-making, and the resulting political landscape of California. The Governor’s choices, invariably, will sculpt the political narrative and policy directions of the state in the foreseeable future, marking a pivotal moment in California’s political evolution. In conclusion, Governor Newsom’s successive appointments underscore a transformative phase for California, where the implications of each selection will reverberate through the state’s political corridors, potentially redefining California’s identity on the national stage. The impact of Newsom’s choices will not only shape the immediate political climate but will also etch the pathways for the state’s long-term political, social, and economic journey.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Fresh From Jail, Florida Man Accused in Shocking Daylight Carjacking</title><link href="/news/2023/10/06/Florida-Carjacking/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Fresh From Jail, Florida Man Accused in Shocking Daylight Carjacking" /><published>2023-10-06T12:35:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-06T12:35:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/06/Florida-Carjacking</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/06/Florida-Carjacking/">&lt;p&gt;In a startling turn of events, Andrew McClellan, a 31-year-old Florida man, was taken into custody for allegedly carjacking a woman at a Mobil gas station in Apopka. What makes this case even more shocking? McClellan had been released from jail merely a week prior.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The incident, captured in vivid detail by surveillance cameras, unfolded when McClellan, driving a previously stolen Toyota, parked beside a woman who was in the process of refueling her SUV. Within moments, he allegedly dashed from his car to hers, clambering into the driver’s seat to make his escape. Despite the woman’s brave attempts to thwart him, a brief tussle ensued, culminating with McClellan driving away, dragging the woman several feet in the process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Morning Leveille, an eyewitness to the event, recounted to FOX 35 Orlando how she watched in disbelief from a nearby traffic light. She recalled the victim’s desperate pleas: “She was like, ‘Get out of my car!’ And he said, ‘No.’” Leveille, along with a store clerk, later provided assistance to the injured woman as they awaited the arrival of the police.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But the drama didn’t end with the carjacking. McClellan’s subsequent arrest in Daytona Beach by local police came with its own set of challenges. Officers had to physically subdue him after he reportedly tried to attack them following an initial attempt to escape his handcuffs. His behavior escalated further when he tried to tighten a restraining device around his neck in the back of a police vehicle, necessitating hospital transport.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The backdrop to this entire episode is rife with controversy. McClellan, the alleged carjacker, had tasted freedom for only a handful of days. He was released from jail on September 29, after charges from a prior case were dropped due to its unsuitability for prosecution. A document from the Orange-Osceola State Attorney’s office provided insight into this, revealing that the charges — which included burglary of a structure, petit theft, and criminal mischief — were deemed unsuitable for prosecution. Further adding to the controversy, McClellan was released from jail without formal charges filed in another case, in accordance with Florida laws.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the residents of Florida, this chain of events has sparked concern and debate, prompting many to question the state’s judicial system and processes. As the story unfolds, communities await further developments, hoping for justice and a resolution that ensures safety for all.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a startling turn of events, Andrew McClellan, a 31-year-old Florida man, was taken into custody for allegedly carjacking a woman at a Mobil gas station in Apopka. What makes this case even more shocking? McClellan had been released from jail merely a week prior. The incident, captured in vivid detail by surveillance cameras, unfolded when McClellan, driving a previously stolen Toyota, parked beside a woman who was in the process of refueling her SUV. Within moments, he allegedly dashed from his car to hers, clambering into the driver’s seat to make his escape. Despite the woman’s brave attempts to thwart him, a brief tussle ensued, culminating with McClellan driving away, dragging the woman several feet in the process. Morning Leveille, an eyewitness to the event, recounted to FOX 35 Orlando how she watched in disbelief from a nearby traffic light. She recalled the victim’s desperate pleas: “She was like, ‘Get out of my car!’ And he said, ‘No.’” Leveille, along with a store clerk, later provided assistance to the injured woman as they awaited the arrival of the police. But the drama didn’t end with the carjacking. McClellan’s subsequent arrest in Daytona Beach by local police came with its own set of challenges. Officers had to physically subdue him after he reportedly tried to attack them following an initial attempt to escape his handcuffs. His behavior escalated further when he tried to tighten a restraining device around his neck in the back of a police vehicle, necessitating hospital transport. The backdrop to this entire episode is rife with controversy. McClellan, the alleged carjacker, had tasted freedom for only a handful of days. He was released from jail on September 29, after charges from a prior case were dropped due to its unsuitability for prosecution. A document from the Orange-Osceola State Attorney’s office provided insight into this, revealing that the charges — which included burglary of a structure, petit theft, and criminal mischief — were deemed unsuitable for prosecution. Further adding to the controversy, McClellan was released from jail without formal charges filed in another case, in accordance with Florida laws. For the residents of Florida, this chain of events has sparked concern and debate, prompting many to question the state’s judicial system and processes. As the story unfolds, communities await further developments, hoping for justice and a resolution that ensures safety for all.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump Throws Weight Behind Jim Jordan for House Speaker Role</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/06/Trump-Endorses-Jordan/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump Throws Weight Behind Jim Jordan for House Speaker Role" /><published>2023-10-06T11:21:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-06T11:21:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/06/Trump-Endorses-Jordan</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/06/Trump-Endorses-Jordan/">&lt;p&gt;Former President Donald Trump has endorsed Rep. Jim Jordan in the highly-anticipated race for the Speaker of the House. Making the announcement on his TRUTH Social platform, Trump lauded Jordan’s impressive track record, both in the wrestling ring and within the political arena.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump’s endorsement shined a spotlight on Jordan’s illustrious past. The Congressman from Ohio’s 4th Congressional District boasted a formidable wrestling record during his high school and university years. A State Championship winner for four straight years in high school with an astonishing 156-1 record, Jordan continued his winning streak at the University of Wisconsin-Madison, earning two NCAA Division I Wrestling Championships.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond his sports accomplishments, Jordan also holds a master’s degree in Education from Ohio State University and a Law Degree from Capital University. Trump emphasized Jordan’s unwavering stances on crime, military and veterans’ affairs, border security, and the 2nd Amendment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The current race for the House Speaker position has seen several significant shifts. Following the historical removal of Rep. Kevin McCarthy, both Rep. Jim Jordan and House Majority Leader Steve Scalise announced their candidacy. With Trump’s recent endorsement, Jordan’s bid for the position seems to have gained considerable momentum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, an unexpected twist has added drama to the unfolding political saga. Trump revealed to Fox News Digital that if the Republican party struggles to unite behind either Jordan or Scalise, he would be open to accepting a temporary speakership role. Emphasizing that his primary focus remains his presidential campaign, Trump expressed his willingness to step in for a “short period” – potentially 30 to 90 days – if it serves the best interest of the party.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The race for the Speaker’s chair isn’t just about political positions; it’s about unifying the party. Jordan, with his history of rallying both moderates and conservatives, seems poised to garner the required 218 votes, as highlighted by a congressional source speaking to Fox News Digital. Given the current dynamics, Trump’s endorsement has provided a significant boost to Jordan’s campaign, further underscoring his potential as a unifying figure within the GOP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As political analysts and enthusiasts watch closely, the developments around the House Speaker race promise a gripping narrative for U.S. politics, with consequences that will shape the direction of the Republican party and, potentially, the nation itself.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Former President Donald Trump has endorsed Rep. Jim Jordan in the highly-anticipated race for the Speaker of the House. Making the announcement on his TRUTH Social platform, Trump lauded Jordan’s impressive track record, both in the wrestling ring and within the political arena. Trump’s endorsement shined a spotlight on Jordan’s illustrious past. The Congressman from Ohio’s 4th Congressional District boasted a formidable wrestling record during his high school and university years. A State Championship winner for four straight years in high school with an astonishing 156-1 record, Jordan continued his winning streak at the University of Wisconsin-Madison, earning two NCAA Division I Wrestling Championships. Beyond his sports accomplishments, Jordan also holds a master’s degree in Education from Ohio State University and a Law Degree from Capital University. Trump emphasized Jordan’s unwavering stances on crime, military and veterans’ affairs, border security, and the 2nd Amendment. The current race for the House Speaker position has seen several significant shifts. Following the historical removal of Rep. Kevin McCarthy, both Rep. Jim Jordan and House Majority Leader Steve Scalise announced their candidacy. With Trump’s recent endorsement, Jordan’s bid for the position seems to have gained considerable momentum. However, an unexpected twist has added drama to the unfolding political saga. Trump revealed to Fox News Digital that if the Republican party struggles to unite behind either Jordan or Scalise, he would be open to accepting a temporary speakership role. Emphasizing that his primary focus remains his presidential campaign, Trump expressed his willingness to step in for a “short period” – potentially 30 to 90 days – if it serves the best interest of the party. The race for the Speaker’s chair isn’t just about political positions; it’s about unifying the party. Jordan, with his history of rallying both moderates and conservatives, seems poised to garner the required 218 votes, as highlighted by a congressional source speaking to Fox News Digital. Given the current dynamics, Trump’s endorsement has provided a significant boost to Jordan’s campaign, further underscoring his potential as a unifying figure within the GOP. As political analysts and enthusiasts watch closely, the developments around the House Speaker race promise a gripping narrative for U.S. politics, with consequences that will shape the direction of the Republican party and, potentially, the nation itself.</summary></entry></feed>