<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-10-08T08:28:08-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/08/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-08T08:28:08-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-08T08:28:08-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/08/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/08/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Republicans Decry Biden’s $6 Billion Release to Iran Preceding Hamas Assault on Israel</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/08/Republican-Critique-on-Biden-Iran-Funding/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Republicans Decry Biden’s $6 Billion Release to Iran Preceding Hamas Assault on Israel" /><published>2023-10-08T07:45:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-08T07:45:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/08/Republican-Critique-on-Biden-Iran-Funding</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/08/Republican-Critique-on-Biden-Iran-Funding/">&lt;p&gt;In the aftermath of a fierce attack on Israel, leading Republican figures voice harsh criticism against the Biden administration for releasing $6 billion of frozen Iranian assets, arguing a potential link to the escalated Hamas aggression.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Republicans from both the House and Senate have pointed fingers at the timing of the asset release, which occurred a few months prior to the sudden surge in Hamas terrorism in Israel. The assault witnessed a barrage of rockets launched into Israeli territories, accompanied by a ground invasion that resulted in significant casualties. Reportedly, over 100 Israelis perished in these unexpected attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tennessee Senator Marsha Blackburn expressed her dismay, connecting the release of funds to Iran with the bloodshed in Israel, asserting, “Just weeks ago, the Biden administration handed over $6 billion to Iran, and today, innocent Israelis were murdered by Iran-backed terrorists.” Such sentiments resonate strongly with various Republican voices that see the unfreezing of assets as an indirect support to Iran’s historical backing of Hamas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In defense, the Biden administration clarifies that the $6 billion, transferred from South Korea to accounts in Qatar, is explicitly earmarked for humanitarian efforts, with stringent U.S. oversight ensuring its appropriate use. However, critiques question the genuine nature of such restrictions, highlighting the inherent malleability of finances that could potentially support Iran-sponsored terrorism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Highlighting Iran’s perennial backing of Hamas, the State Department acknowledges the allocation of roughly $100 million annually by Iran to Palestinian militant groups. This revelation strengthens the skepticism surrounding the released funds, with critics insisting on a direct correlation between the assets’ unfreezing and the subsequent Hamas-initiated violence in Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a digital outburst, Florida Senator Rick Scott encapsulated the Republican dismay: “This is exactly why so many Americans &amp;amp; Israelis were DISGUSTED to see [President Biden] give the Iranian regime $6 billion last month.” Similar sentiments, iterating the perceived funding-terrorism connection, echoed across various digital platforms and statements by Republican leaders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the debate intensifies, the crux remains the safety and security of Israel and its citizens. With increased global scrutiny, the Biden administration’s approach towards foreign relations, especially with stakeholders in the Middle East, will be a pivotal facet in shaping future geopolitical dynamics.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In the aftermath of a fierce attack on Israel, leading Republican figures voice harsh criticism against the Biden administration for releasing $6 billion of frozen Iranian assets, arguing a potential link to the escalated Hamas aggression. Republicans from both the House and Senate have pointed fingers at the timing of the asset release, which occurred a few months prior to the sudden surge in Hamas terrorism in Israel. The assault witnessed a barrage of rockets launched into Israeli territories, accompanied by a ground invasion that resulted in significant casualties. Reportedly, over 100 Israelis perished in these unexpected attacks. Tennessee Senator Marsha Blackburn expressed her dismay, connecting the release of funds to Iran with the bloodshed in Israel, asserting, “Just weeks ago, the Biden administration handed over $6 billion to Iran, and today, innocent Israelis were murdered by Iran-backed terrorists.” Such sentiments resonate strongly with various Republican voices that see the unfreezing of assets as an indirect support to Iran’s historical backing of Hamas. In defense, the Biden administration clarifies that the $6 billion, transferred from South Korea to accounts in Qatar, is explicitly earmarked for humanitarian efforts, with stringent U.S. oversight ensuring its appropriate use. However, critiques question the genuine nature of such restrictions, highlighting the inherent malleability of finances that could potentially support Iran-sponsored terrorism. Highlighting Iran’s perennial backing of Hamas, the State Department acknowledges the allocation of roughly $100 million annually by Iran to Palestinian militant groups. This revelation strengthens the skepticism surrounding the released funds, with critics insisting on a direct correlation between the assets’ unfreezing and the subsequent Hamas-initiated violence in Israel. In a digital outburst, Florida Senator Rick Scott encapsulated the Republican dismay: “This is exactly why so many Americans &amp;amp; Israelis were DISGUSTED to see [President Biden] give the Iranian regime $6 billion last month.” Similar sentiments, iterating the perceived funding-terrorism connection, echoed across various digital platforms and statements by Republican leaders. While the debate intensifies, the crux remains the safety and security of Israel and its citizens. With increased global scrutiny, the Biden administration’s approach towards foreign relations, especially with stakeholders in the Middle East, will be a pivotal facet in shaping future geopolitical dynamics.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Washington D.C. Sees Staggering Surge in Carjackings: An Alarming 111% Rise!</title><link href="/news/2023/10/08/DC-Carjackings-Surge/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Washington D.C. Sees Staggering Surge in Carjackings: An Alarming 111% Rise!" /><published>2023-10-08T06:34:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-08T06:34:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/08/DC-Carjackings-Surge</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/08/DC-Carjackings-Surge/">&lt;p&gt;In a startling revelation, carjackings in Washington D.C. skyrocketed by an astounding 111% in the first ten months of 2023, compared to the same period in 2022. Police, while still piecing together the ‘why,’ highlight a noteworthy detail: the majority of the arrested individuals are below 18 years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2023, the U.S. capital reported a whopping 760 carjackings. In contrast, there were only 360 in the same time frame last year. To put things into perspective, the carjackings this year alone surpassed the total of 2018, 2019, and 2020 combined. These alarming figures suggest a deep-rooted issue that law enforcement and the justice system must address.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most carjackings reportedly occur around the &lt;strong&gt;H Street Corridor&lt;/strong&gt; and the regions adjacent to the &lt;strong&gt;Anacostia River bordering Maryland&lt;/strong&gt;. Police data emphasizes that a staggering &lt;strong&gt;65% of those involved in these thefts are juveniles&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s not just the age of the culprits that’s concerning. U.S. Attorney for D.C., Matthew Graves, admitted that the majority of individuals arrested for such crimes are young. However, his office often does not prosecute them, especially if they are under 16. In 2022, Graves &lt;strong&gt;refused to prosecute 67%&lt;/strong&gt; of those who could have been tried in the D.C. Superior Court. This number is notably high when considering juvenile crimes, where he did not press charges for 26%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One might wonder if this trend of non-prosecution is contributing to the surge. D.C.’s juvenile court has jurisdiction over various offenses, from drug-related crimes to property offenses. Yet, to try a juvenile as an adult, prosecutors need to initiate a transfer. The U.S. Attorney’s Office only prosecutes the serious crimes listed in the statute.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Graves’ office can potentially prosecute 16 and 17-year-olds as adults, they seem to prioritize certain cases. The police affirm that the U.S. Attorney’s Office holds the initial right to decide on the prosecution. If they refuse, the case gets presented to the office of the Attorney General.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Police officials, like Assistant Chief of the Investigative Services Bureau Carlos Heraud, are still trying to pinpoint the exact reasons for this surge. Is it due to influence from social media, a lack of perceived consequences, or peer discussions at schools? The exact cause remains elusive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This surge in crime isn’t isolated to carjackings. The entire District witnessed a significant escalation in violent crimes this year. The rates have soared up by nearly &lt;strong&gt;40%&lt;/strong&gt; year over year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The city’s deteriorating safety was further underscored when Rep. Henry Cuellar (D-TX) faced a carjacking near the Capitol Building. He described the horrifying ordeal, stating that while he has a black belt, facing multiple guns left him with no choice but to hand over his vehicle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As D.C. grapples with this unsettling rise in crime, the immediate focus should be on understanding the underlying causes and implementing robust preventive measures. Only then can residents hope for safer streets.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a startling revelation, carjackings in Washington D.C. skyrocketed by an astounding 111% in the first ten months of 2023, compared to the same period in 2022. Police, while still piecing together the ‘why,’ highlight a noteworthy detail: the majority of the arrested individuals are below 18 years. In 2023, the U.S. capital reported a whopping 760 carjackings. In contrast, there were only 360 in the same time frame last year. To put things into perspective, the carjackings this year alone surpassed the total of 2018, 2019, and 2020 combined. These alarming figures suggest a deep-rooted issue that law enforcement and the justice system must address. Most carjackings reportedly occur around the H Street Corridor and the regions adjacent to the Anacostia River bordering Maryland. Police data emphasizes that a staggering 65% of those involved in these thefts are juveniles. It’s not just the age of the culprits that’s concerning. U.S. Attorney for D.C., Matthew Graves, admitted that the majority of individuals arrested for such crimes are young. However, his office often does not prosecute them, especially if they are under 16. In 2022, Graves refused to prosecute 67% of those who could have been tried in the D.C. Superior Court. This number is notably high when considering juvenile crimes, where he did not press charges for 26%. One might wonder if this trend of non-prosecution is contributing to the surge. D.C.’s juvenile court has jurisdiction over various offenses, from drug-related crimes to property offenses. Yet, to try a juvenile as an adult, prosecutors need to initiate a transfer. The U.S. Attorney’s Office only prosecutes the serious crimes listed in the statute. While Graves’ office can potentially prosecute 16 and 17-year-olds as adults, they seem to prioritize certain cases. The police affirm that the U.S. Attorney’s Office holds the initial right to decide on the prosecution. If they refuse, the case gets presented to the office of the Attorney General. Police officials, like Assistant Chief of the Investigative Services Bureau Carlos Heraud, are still trying to pinpoint the exact reasons for this surge. Is it due to influence from social media, a lack of perceived consequences, or peer discussions at schools? The exact cause remains elusive. This surge in crime isn’t isolated to carjackings. The entire District witnessed a significant escalation in violent crimes this year. The rates have soared up by nearly 40% year over year. The city’s deteriorating safety was further underscored when Rep. Henry Cuellar (D-TX) faced a carjacking near the Capitol Building. He described the horrifying ordeal, stating that while he has a black belt, facing multiple guns left him with no choice but to hand over his vehicle. As D.C. grapples with this unsettling rise in crime, the immediate focus should be on understanding the underlying causes and implementing robust preventive measures. Only then can residents hope for safer streets.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Faith at the Forefront: Det. Fil Waters’ Journey to Truth</title><link href="/news/2023/10/07/Faith-and-Justice/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Faith at the Forefront: Det. Fil Waters’ Journey to Truth" /><published>2023-10-07T17:07:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-07T17:07:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/07/Faith-and-Justice</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/07/Faith-and-Justice/">&lt;p&gt;Detective Fil Waters, once a significant figure in the Houston Police Department’s (HPD) homicide unit, is not just another detective; he is a man of deep faith and conviction. With a remarkable 96% clearance rate and a 90% confession rate, he humbly credits a higher power - God.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After giving up a lucrative career in construction management, Waters felt a powerful “calling” to law enforcement. Over his 24-year tenure at HPD, he worked diligently on 400 homicide cases, clearing an overwhelming majority.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“My faith grew stronger… and I was getting more in tune with God’s plan for me,” Waters shared in a recent interview. Throughout his service, Waters felt that his connection with the divine played a pivotal role. From undercover narcotics operations, where he had to assume different identities, to the nuanced interview processes of his homicide days, he believed God was guiding him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For Waters, his communication skills were integral. Not just the verbal exchange, but the capacity to empathize, listen, and build trust. He emphasized the necessity of patience and open-mindedness in interviews, especially when confronted with suspects accused of heinous crimes. To him, it was always about uncovering the truth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“You have to be patient. And empathetic,” Waters stressed. “It’s always a journey for the truth.” He often entered interrogation rooms, conscious of a divine presence, praying for transparency and the ability to reflect Christ’s love.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One such challenging case was a 2015 triple homicide at a Houston car dealership. The investigation, later featured in Investigation Discovery’s “The Interrogator,” revolved around James Tinsley. Tinsley was convicted in 2017 for the brutal killing of three family members over car payments. Waters recounts this particular interrogation with Tinsley as intense, but he managed to extract valuable information even without a formal confession.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a seasoned detective, Waters emphasizes the importance of listening more and speaking less. He encourages budding law enforcement officers to be open-minded and attentive, treating everyone with dignity and respect, regardless of their background or beliefs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Waters’ legacy in HPD and his unwavering faith serve as a testament that in the search for truth, sometimes, the guiding light comes from above.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Detective Fil Waters, once a significant figure in the Houston Police Department’s (HPD) homicide unit, is not just another detective; he is a man of deep faith and conviction. With a remarkable 96% clearance rate and a 90% confession rate, he humbly credits a higher power - God. After giving up a lucrative career in construction management, Waters felt a powerful “calling” to law enforcement. Over his 24-year tenure at HPD, he worked diligently on 400 homicide cases, clearing an overwhelming majority. “My faith grew stronger… and I was getting more in tune with God’s plan for me,” Waters shared in a recent interview. Throughout his service, Waters felt that his connection with the divine played a pivotal role. From undercover narcotics operations, where he had to assume different identities, to the nuanced interview processes of his homicide days, he believed God was guiding him. For Waters, his communication skills were integral. Not just the verbal exchange, but the capacity to empathize, listen, and build trust. He emphasized the necessity of patience and open-mindedness in interviews, especially when confronted with suspects accused of heinous crimes. To him, it was always about uncovering the truth. “You have to be patient. And empathetic,” Waters stressed. “It’s always a journey for the truth.” He often entered interrogation rooms, conscious of a divine presence, praying for transparency and the ability to reflect Christ’s love. One such challenging case was a 2015 triple homicide at a Houston car dealership. The investigation, later featured in Investigation Discovery’s “The Interrogator,” revolved around James Tinsley. Tinsley was convicted in 2017 for the brutal killing of three family members over car payments. Waters recounts this particular interrogation with Tinsley as intense, but he managed to extract valuable information even without a formal confession. As a seasoned detective, Waters emphasizes the importance of listening more and speaking less. He encourages budding law enforcement officers to be open-minded and attentive, treating everyone with dignity and respect, regardless of their background or beliefs. Waters’ legacy in HPD and his unwavering faith serve as a testament that in the search for truth, sometimes, the guiding light comes from above.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">‘The Essential Church’ Documentary Climbs the Charts: A Tale of Defiance</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/07/Essential-Church-Documentary/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="‘The Essential Church’ Documentary Climbs the Charts: A Tale of Defiance" /><published>2023-10-07T15:52:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-07T15:52:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/07/Essential-Church-Documentary</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/07/Essential-Church-Documentary/">&lt;p&gt;Amidst a flurry of films and documentaries capturing different facets of the global COVID-19 experience, one documentary stands out, seizing the #1 spot in the iTunes documentaries category: “The Essential Church”. Produced by Grace Productions, this film delves deep into the compelling journey of three churches that resisted government lockdowns during the pandemic’s peak.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chronicling the endeavors of Grace Community Church in Los Angeles, Fairview Baptist Church in Calgary, Canada, and GraceLife Church, also in Canada, the film captures the raw emotions, decisions, and spiritual dilemmas faced by the Christian community. These churches, led by their dedicated pastors, believed in their divine duty to remain open, even as governments issued directives to shut down public gatherings, including religious assemblies, to curb the spread of the virus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond merely capturing events, “The Essential Church” raises potent questions: How real was the threat of the COVID-19 virus? What right does the government have to close places of worship? Should Christians prioritize obeying civil authorities or their spiritual convictions?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The onset of the COVID-19 pandemic saw sweeping predictions about its transmission rate and lethal potential. Many health experts declared it a significant health crisis. Guided by such alarming forecasts, governments worldwide took drastic steps, including shutting down religious gatherings. These actions sparked debates about the violation of freedom of religion, especially when predictions about the virus turned out to be inflated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But as the documentary explores, was it right for these churches to oppose these shutdowns when the world was still grappling with understanding the virus? Was the government’s approach—employing police force to ensure compliance—an overreach, impinging upon religious freedoms?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As “The Essential Church” ascends to the top of Apple’s iTunes Store charts, its success signals the resonance of its themes with audiences. The film offers not just an insightful look into the churches’ battles but also acts as a mirror, prompting viewers to reflect on the balance between civil duties and spiritual obligations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those not on the iTunes platform, the film’s gripping narrative is accessible directly through its official website, ensuring that this essential story reaches as many eyes and hearts as possible.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Amidst a flurry of films and documentaries capturing different facets of the global COVID-19 experience, one documentary stands out, seizing the #1 spot in the iTunes documentaries category: “The Essential Church”. Produced by Grace Productions, this film delves deep into the compelling journey of three churches that resisted government lockdowns during the pandemic’s peak. Chronicling the endeavors of Grace Community Church in Los Angeles, Fairview Baptist Church in Calgary, Canada, and GraceLife Church, also in Canada, the film captures the raw emotions, decisions, and spiritual dilemmas faced by the Christian community. These churches, led by their dedicated pastors, believed in their divine duty to remain open, even as governments issued directives to shut down public gatherings, including religious assemblies, to curb the spread of the virus. Beyond merely capturing events, “The Essential Church” raises potent questions: How real was the threat of the COVID-19 virus? What right does the government have to close places of worship? Should Christians prioritize obeying civil authorities or their spiritual convictions? The onset of the COVID-19 pandemic saw sweeping predictions about its transmission rate and lethal potential. Many health experts declared it a significant health crisis. Guided by such alarming forecasts, governments worldwide took drastic steps, including shutting down religious gatherings. These actions sparked debates about the violation of freedom of religion, especially when predictions about the virus turned out to be inflated. But as the documentary explores, was it right for these churches to oppose these shutdowns when the world was still grappling with understanding the virus? Was the government’s approach—employing police force to ensure compliance—an overreach, impinging upon religious freedoms? As “The Essential Church” ascends to the top of Apple’s iTunes Store charts, its success signals the resonance of its themes with audiences. The film offers not just an insightful look into the churches’ battles but also acts as a mirror, prompting viewers to reflect on the balance between civil duties and spiritual obligations. For those not on the iTunes platform, the film’s gripping narrative is accessible directly through its official website, ensuring that this essential story reaches as many eyes and hearts as possible.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hunter Biden’s Financial Desperation: Daughter’s College Fund Misused?</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/07/Hunter-Biden-College-Fund/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hunter Biden’s Financial Desperation: Daughter’s College Fund Misused?" /><published>2023-10-07T14:37:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-07T14:37:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/07/Hunter-Biden-College-Fund</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/07/Hunter-Biden-College-Fund/">&lt;p&gt;Recent revelations claim that Hunter Biden, President Joe Biden’s son, diverted funds from his daughter Maisy’s college savings during a period of financial turmoil. The controversy highlights the complex web of personal challenges and public scrutiny surrounding the president’s son.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to a report by the Daily Mail, Hunter, facing a nearly depleted bank account, withdrew a substantial sum of $20,000 from Maisy’s college fund. This decision followed an email alert from Wells Fargo on December 17, 2018, revealing a mere 44 cents balance in his account. A hasty instruction to the bank ensued, directing them to transfer the said amount from his daughter’s savings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hunter’s expenditures during this period raise eyebrows. With admissions of a “full-blown addiction” to crack cocaine and spending on prostitutes, emails suggest the diverted money funded not just these vices but also high-end commodities like sports cars and online adult subscriptions. Such revelations, sourced from Hunter’s much-discussed laptop, continue to taint his image and, by extension, cast shadows on the Biden family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, emails from Hunter’s assistant, Katie Dodge, underscored his financial distress. Amid reminders of pending bills and expenditures, Hunter’s response painted a bleak picture: reduced payments to staff, deferred expenses, and references to his business partner’s incarceration in China – a nod to businessman Ye Jianming’s mysterious public disappearance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hunter’s financial challenges don’t stand alone. He appeared in federal court, accused of making false statements related to firearm purchases and possessing a firearm as an unlawful drug user or addict. Pleading not guilty to these allegations, Hunter faces potential penalties ranging up to 25 years in prison, with each count also carrying a potential fine of $250,000.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The combination of financial distress, alleged misuse of family funds, and legal challenges adds another chapter to Hunter Biden’s tumultuous public narrative. As he navigates these controversies, the Biden family also faces the challenge of maintaining their public standing amid these personal and potentially damaging revelations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the president’s son remains a topic of both media and public interest, it’s essential to discern factual reports from politically motivated narratives. As details emerge and legal proceedings progress, the true depth of these allegations and their potential implications for the Biden administration will become clearer.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Recent revelations claim that Hunter Biden, President Joe Biden’s son, diverted funds from his daughter Maisy’s college savings during a period of financial turmoil. The controversy highlights the complex web of personal challenges and public scrutiny surrounding the president’s son. According to a report by the Daily Mail, Hunter, facing a nearly depleted bank account, withdrew a substantial sum of $20,000 from Maisy’s college fund. This decision followed an email alert from Wells Fargo on December 17, 2018, revealing a mere 44 cents balance in his account. A hasty instruction to the bank ensued, directing them to transfer the said amount from his daughter’s savings. Hunter’s expenditures during this period raise eyebrows. With admissions of a “full-blown addiction” to crack cocaine and spending on prostitutes, emails suggest the diverted money funded not just these vices but also high-end commodities like sports cars and online adult subscriptions. Such revelations, sourced from Hunter’s much-discussed laptop, continue to taint his image and, by extension, cast shadows on the Biden family. Furthermore, emails from Hunter’s assistant, Katie Dodge, underscored his financial distress. Amid reminders of pending bills and expenditures, Hunter’s response painted a bleak picture: reduced payments to staff, deferred expenses, and references to his business partner’s incarceration in China – a nod to businessman Ye Jianming’s mysterious public disappearance. Hunter’s financial challenges don’t stand alone. He appeared in federal court, accused of making false statements related to firearm purchases and possessing a firearm as an unlawful drug user or addict. Pleading not guilty to these allegations, Hunter faces potential penalties ranging up to 25 years in prison, with each count also carrying a potential fine of $250,000. The combination of financial distress, alleged misuse of family funds, and legal challenges adds another chapter to Hunter Biden’s tumultuous public narrative. As he navigates these controversies, the Biden family also faces the challenge of maintaining their public standing amid these personal and potentially damaging revelations. While the president’s son remains a topic of both media and public interest, it’s essential to discern factual reports from politically motivated narratives. As details emerge and legal proceedings progress, the true depth of these allegations and their potential implications for the Biden administration will become clearer.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Bill Maher on Biden’s Dipping Approval: ‘Tents Everywhere &amp;amp; Locked Hair Scrunchies’</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/07/Maher-Biden-Approval-Ratings/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bill Maher on Biden’s Dipping Approval: ‘Tents Everywhere &amp;amp; Locked Hair Scrunchies’" /><published>2023-10-07T12:48:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-07T12:48:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/07/Maher-Biden-Approval-Ratings</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/07/Maher-Biden-Approval-Ratings/">&lt;p&gt;Television host Bill Maher of HBO’s “Real Time” recently weighed in on President Joe Biden’s waning approval ratings. Maher attributed this decline to the stark visual of homelessness and the rise in theft cases, such as the need for store items like hair scrunchies to be locked up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It just doesn’t feel good when you see tents everywhere on the street,” remarked Maher, highlighting the increasing visibility of homelessness as a factor in the public’s perception of the nation’s wellbeing. The sentiment was strong: witnessing homelessness at such a scale gives a sense that “the country’s [not] right.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthering his argument on the atmosphere of insecurity, Maher commented on the stringent security measures some stores have been forced to adopt due to theft. He voiced his own displeasure, “It just doesn’t feel good when I’ve got to get a sales associate to unlock the hair scrunchies.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The talk show host’s comments reflect a broader debate surrounding law enforcement, crime rates, and societal compassion. Maher raised the question of balance, pondering the difficulty in finding a “middle ground” between liberal cities downplaying certain crimes and the aggressive approach of figures like former President Donald Trump, who once mentioned “shooting shoplifters.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sarah Isgur, ABC News Contributor and The Dispatch Editor, joined the discussion, criticizing what she termed as “luxury beliefs” held by those untouched by the direct consequences of crime. According to Isgur, such views masquerade as compassion but may indirectly promote harmful practices, such as drug cartels profiting from human smuggling or being nonchalant about rampant drug use on streets. “It’s not compassionate to tell someone that they should die on the sidewalk,” she pointed out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maher concurred, drawing attention to the psychological toll such issues can have on individuals. He reiterated that these real-world situations and their direct impact on the lives of Americans might be the underlying reason for the disapproval sentiments against Biden. In his words, “Biden’s always saying, why don’t people like me more? And then they cite numbers.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This candid exchange on Maher’s show brings to the forefront issues that many Americans face daily. The conversation underscores the importance of addressing pressing societal challenges, like homelessness and theft, that may significantly influence political approval ratings and public sentiment.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Television host Bill Maher of HBO’s “Real Time” recently weighed in on President Joe Biden’s waning approval ratings. Maher attributed this decline to the stark visual of homelessness and the rise in theft cases, such as the need for store items like hair scrunchies to be locked up. “It just doesn’t feel good when you see tents everywhere on the street,” remarked Maher, highlighting the increasing visibility of homelessness as a factor in the public’s perception of the nation’s wellbeing. The sentiment was strong: witnessing homelessness at such a scale gives a sense that “the country’s [not] right.” Furthering his argument on the atmosphere of insecurity, Maher commented on the stringent security measures some stores have been forced to adopt due to theft. He voiced his own displeasure, “It just doesn’t feel good when I’ve got to get a sales associate to unlock the hair scrunchies.” The talk show host’s comments reflect a broader debate surrounding law enforcement, crime rates, and societal compassion. Maher raised the question of balance, pondering the difficulty in finding a “middle ground” between liberal cities downplaying certain crimes and the aggressive approach of figures like former President Donald Trump, who once mentioned “shooting shoplifters.” Sarah Isgur, ABC News Contributor and The Dispatch Editor, joined the discussion, criticizing what she termed as “luxury beliefs” held by those untouched by the direct consequences of crime. According to Isgur, such views masquerade as compassion but may indirectly promote harmful practices, such as drug cartels profiting from human smuggling or being nonchalant about rampant drug use on streets. “It’s not compassionate to tell someone that they should die on the sidewalk,” she pointed out. Maher concurred, drawing attention to the psychological toll such issues can have on individuals. He reiterated that these real-world situations and their direct impact on the lives of Americans might be the underlying reason for the disapproval sentiments against Biden. In his words, “Biden’s always saying, why don’t people like me more? And then they cite numbers.” This candid exchange on Maher’s show brings to the forefront issues that many Americans face daily. The conversation underscores the importance of addressing pressing societal challenges, like homelessness and theft, that may significantly influence political approval ratings and public sentiment.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump Surges in Polls, Leaving DeSantis Behind by 20%</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/07/Trump-DeSantis-Poll-Shift/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump Surges in Polls, Leaving DeSantis Behind by 20%" /><published>2023-10-07T11:59:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-07T11:59:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/07/Trump-DeSantis-Poll-Shift</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/07/Trump-DeSantis-Poll-Shift/">&lt;p&gt;In the ever-evolving political landscape, former President Donald Trump’s popularity seems to remain resilient. Recent polling data reveals Trump’s lead over Florida Governor Ron DeSantis has surged by a staggering 20 points nationally in just over two months.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This dramatic shift was highlighted by a recent poll published on Wednesday, showcasing Trump’s support among registered Republicans and independents who lean Republican at 56%. This marks a 10-point increase from July’s Marquette poll, which pegged him at 46%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the flip side, DeSantis experienced a drop in support, losing ten points since July. The Florida Governor now garners only 12% of the support, indicating a significant shift in the political landscape within the Republican camp.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The New York Times further highlighted DeSantis’s challenges, noting the campaign’s decision to relocate a third of its staff to Iowa and its current financial status. DeSantis’s campaign war chest for GOP primary purposes stands at a concerning $5 million.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Republican field remains diverse, with Nikki Haley, the former Governor of South Carolina, not far behind DeSantis at six percent. Vivek Ramaswamy, an entrepreneur, and former Vice President Mike Pence share fourth place, each holding four percent of the support. Interestingly, Ramaswamy witnessed a three-point increase from July, while Pence saw a three percent decrease.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this political poll mix, Sen. Tim Scott (R-SC) and former Gov. Chris Christie (R-NJ) also made appearances, holding two percent and one percent support, respectively.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Marquette University provided further food for thought by examining a hypothetical election match-up between Trump and current President Joe Biden. Results fluctuated based on the voter sample. Among registered voters, Trump led by a slight margin, while Biden had a minuscule advantage among likely voters. Both scenarios present statistical ties, keeping the political waters murky.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With these developments, it’s evident that the political tides are shifting, re-establishing Trump’s dominance within the Republican sphere and placing DeSantis on unsure footing. As the Republican race heats up, the nation watches closely, anticipating the next move in this intricate political chess game.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In the ever-evolving political landscape, former President Donald Trump’s popularity seems to remain resilient. Recent polling data reveals Trump’s lead over Florida Governor Ron DeSantis has surged by a staggering 20 points nationally in just over two months. This dramatic shift was highlighted by a recent poll published on Wednesday, showcasing Trump’s support among registered Republicans and independents who lean Republican at 56%. This marks a 10-point increase from July’s Marquette poll, which pegged him at 46%. On the flip side, DeSantis experienced a drop in support, losing ten points since July. The Florida Governor now garners only 12% of the support, indicating a significant shift in the political landscape within the Republican camp. The New York Times further highlighted DeSantis’s challenges, noting the campaign’s decision to relocate a third of its staff to Iowa and its current financial status. DeSantis’s campaign war chest for GOP primary purposes stands at a concerning $5 million. The Republican field remains diverse, with Nikki Haley, the former Governor of South Carolina, not far behind DeSantis at six percent. Vivek Ramaswamy, an entrepreneur, and former Vice President Mike Pence share fourth place, each holding four percent of the support. Interestingly, Ramaswamy witnessed a three-point increase from July, while Pence saw a three percent decrease. In this political poll mix, Sen. Tim Scott (R-SC) and former Gov. Chris Christie (R-NJ) also made appearances, holding two percent and one percent support, respectively. Marquette University provided further food for thought by examining a hypothetical election match-up between Trump and current President Joe Biden. Results fluctuated based on the voter sample. Among registered voters, Trump led by a slight margin, while Biden had a minuscule advantage among likely voters. Both scenarios present statistical ties, keeping the political waters murky. With these developments, it’s evident that the political tides are shifting, re-establishing Trump’s dominance within the Republican sphere and placing DeSantis on unsure footing. As the Republican race heats up, the nation watches closely, anticipating the next move in this intricate political chess game.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hamas Launches Historic Assault on Israel: 100+ Fatalities</title><link href="/news/2023/10/07/Hamas-Attack-On-Israel/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hamas Launches Historic Assault on Israel: 100+ Fatalities" /><published>2023-10-07T10:45:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-07T10:45:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/07/Hamas-Attack-On-Israel</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/07/Hamas-Attack-On-Israel/">&lt;p&gt;In a striking display of aggression not witnessed before, Hamas, the militant Islamist group, has claimed responsibility for a brutal attack on Israel that has resulted in over 100 Israeli casualties. The incursion marked a significant escalation in the conflict between the two territories.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Saturday, rockets flew from the Gaza Strip, hitting regions of southern Israel. The assault, which Hamas has proudly taken responsibility for, has led to over 100 Israelis losing their lives. The conflict’s gravity deepened as Mohammad Deif, a senior Hamas military commander, dubbed the attack “the day of the greatest battle to end the last occupation on earth.” He called on Palestinians everywhere to confront Israelis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In retaliation, Israeli air strikes took the lives of 198 Palestinians, Gaza health officials confirmed. The wave of attacks has overwhelmed hospitals, which are currently treating nearly 985 injured individuals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Israel’s Prime Minister, Benjamin Netanyahu, in a video message, explicitly stated, “Citizens of Israel, we are at war.” Ambulance crews raced to regions around the Gaza Strip, while sirens warned residents across Israel. Hospital reports indicate hundreds of wounded, including civilians, signaling the broad reach of the conflict.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gunmen have targeted civilians in Israeli towns, with video footage capturing confrontations in city streets. The Israeli military commented, “A number of terrorists have infiltrated into Israeli territory from the Gaza Strip,” urging residents near the Gaza border to stay indoors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;U.S. National Security Council Spokesperson Adrienne Watson firmly condemned the unprovoked attacks. She stressed, “There is never any justification for terrorism,” reaffirming America’s allegiance to Israel. European leaders, too, stood in solidarity with Israel, denouncing Hamas’s actions. Ursula von der Leyen, the head of the European Union’s executive commission, labeled the attack as “terrorism in its most despicable form,” asserting Israel’s right to self-defense. Prominent European heads of state echoed this sentiment, highlighting their strong support for Israel during these trying times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While confrontations between Israel and Gaza are not unprecedented, the recent surge in aggression is unparalleled. With the Israeli defense establishment making strategic evaluations and preparations, the conflict, which started with Hamas’s surprise attacks on Saturday, is anticipated to extend for several days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world watches closely, hoping for a swift resolution to prevent further loss of life and restore peace in the region.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a striking display of aggression not witnessed before, Hamas, the militant Islamist group, has claimed responsibility for a brutal attack on Israel that has resulted in over 100 Israeli casualties. The incursion marked a significant escalation in the conflict between the two territories. On Saturday, rockets flew from the Gaza Strip, hitting regions of southern Israel. The assault, which Hamas has proudly taken responsibility for, has led to over 100 Israelis losing their lives. The conflict’s gravity deepened as Mohammad Deif, a senior Hamas military commander, dubbed the attack “the day of the greatest battle to end the last occupation on earth.” He called on Palestinians everywhere to confront Israelis. In retaliation, Israeli air strikes took the lives of 198 Palestinians, Gaza health officials confirmed. The wave of attacks has overwhelmed hospitals, which are currently treating nearly 985 injured individuals. Israel’s Prime Minister, Benjamin Netanyahu, in a video message, explicitly stated, “Citizens of Israel, we are at war.” Ambulance crews raced to regions around the Gaza Strip, while sirens warned residents across Israel. Hospital reports indicate hundreds of wounded, including civilians, signaling the broad reach of the conflict. Gunmen have targeted civilians in Israeli towns, with video footage capturing confrontations in city streets. The Israeli military commented, “A number of terrorists have infiltrated into Israeli territory from the Gaza Strip,” urging residents near the Gaza border to stay indoors. U.S. National Security Council Spokesperson Adrienne Watson firmly condemned the unprovoked attacks. She stressed, “There is never any justification for terrorism,” reaffirming America’s allegiance to Israel. European leaders, too, stood in solidarity with Israel, denouncing Hamas’s actions. Ursula von der Leyen, the head of the European Union’s executive commission, labeled the attack as “terrorism in its most despicable form,” asserting Israel’s right to self-defense. Prominent European heads of state echoed this sentiment, highlighting their strong support for Israel during these trying times. While confrontations between Israel and Gaza are not unprecedented, the recent surge in aggression is unparalleled. With the Israeli defense establishment making strategic evaluations and preparations, the conflict, which started with Hamas’s surprise attacks on Saturday, is anticipated to extend for several days. The world watches closely, hoping for a swift resolution to prevent further loss of life and restore peace in the region.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump’s Legal Team Pushes to Pause High-Profile Fraud Trial</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/07/Trump-Trial-Halted/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump’s Legal Team Pushes to Pause High-Profile Fraud Trial" /><published>2023-10-07T08:15:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-07T08:15:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/07/Trump-Trial-Halted</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/07/Trump-Trial-Halted/">&lt;p&gt;Former President Donald Trump finds himself at the center of a legal maelstrom, as his attorneys fervently appeal to halt a Manhattan civil fraud trial. The crux? Trump’s most prized assets, including the iconic Trump Tower.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a bid to delay the trial, Trump’s legal team is challenging a court ruling by Judge Arthur Engoron, which could spell the dissolution of companies controlling some of Trump’s major assets. The gravity of this ruling suggests a court-appointed receiver might oversee Trump’s businesses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Drawing attention, Trump lawyers Clifford Robert, Michael Farina, and Michael Madaio penned a 41-page appellate brief, describing the potential havoc Engoron’s verdict could bring. They emphasized the “severe and irreparable harm” not just to Trump and the defendants but also to countless employees relying on those businesses for their livelihood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The backdrop is set with the appellate court already dismissing a previous attempt to delay the trial, mere days before its commencement. Adding to the evolving scenario, Trump’s legal representatives withdrew a lawsuit against Judge Engoron last Thursday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet, the Attorney General of New York, Letitia James, remains steadfast. James’ office conveyed their openness to discuss enforcing Engoron’s verdict post-trial. However, they desire the trial to persist without interruptions. Senior Assistant Solicitor General Dennis Fan argued against abruptly halting the trial, citing the logistical intricacies, security arrangements, and potential inconvenience to scheduled witnesses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Revealing an intriguing turn of events, Engoron concluded last week that Trump engaged in fraudulent activities while establishing his real estate empire. This verdict stems from James’ lawsuit that accused Trump of deceiving various stakeholders by inflating the value of his assets in annual financial reports.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump, however, rebuts these allegations, contending that many of his assets are undervalued in those statements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ensuring clarity, Engoron delineated the procedures for enforcing his ruling last Thursday. He allocated deadlines for both parties to suggest potential receivers and directed Trump and the defendants to inform a court-appointed monitor about the entities affected by his verdict.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A significant directive also mandated the defendants to notify the monitor before applying for new business licenses or trying to form new entities that might inherit the assets of a dissolving company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump’s attorneys, though, counter-argue that Engoron’s decision lacks a coherent legal basis, dubbing it as “the corporate death penalty.” They further criticize the judge for ambiguity in elucidating the real-world implications of his verdict.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In an earlier pretrial hearing, another Trump lawyer, Christopher Kise, sought clarity from Engoron on the extent of the ruling’s impact on Trump’s assets. Engoron, however, deferred his response.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Summarizing their appeal, Trump’s legal team underscores their concerns about the far-reaching consequences of Engoron’s “overbroad directive,” emphasizing its potential to usher in “confusion and chaos.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the political world watches with bated breath, only time will unveil the outcome of this legal tussle between Trump and the New York Attorney General’s office.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Former President Donald Trump finds himself at the center of a legal maelstrom, as his attorneys fervently appeal to halt a Manhattan civil fraud trial. The crux? Trump’s most prized assets, including the iconic Trump Tower. In a bid to delay the trial, Trump’s legal team is challenging a court ruling by Judge Arthur Engoron, which could spell the dissolution of companies controlling some of Trump’s major assets. The gravity of this ruling suggests a court-appointed receiver might oversee Trump’s businesses. Drawing attention, Trump lawyers Clifford Robert, Michael Farina, and Michael Madaio penned a 41-page appellate brief, describing the potential havoc Engoron’s verdict could bring. They emphasized the “severe and irreparable harm” not just to Trump and the defendants but also to countless employees relying on those businesses for their livelihood. The backdrop is set with the appellate court already dismissing a previous attempt to delay the trial, mere days before its commencement. Adding to the evolving scenario, Trump’s legal representatives withdrew a lawsuit against Judge Engoron last Thursday. Yet, the Attorney General of New York, Letitia James, remains steadfast. James’ office conveyed their openness to discuss enforcing Engoron’s verdict post-trial. However, they desire the trial to persist without interruptions. Senior Assistant Solicitor General Dennis Fan argued against abruptly halting the trial, citing the logistical intricacies, security arrangements, and potential inconvenience to scheduled witnesses. Revealing an intriguing turn of events, Engoron concluded last week that Trump engaged in fraudulent activities while establishing his real estate empire. This verdict stems from James’ lawsuit that accused Trump of deceiving various stakeholders by inflating the value of his assets in annual financial reports. Trump, however, rebuts these allegations, contending that many of his assets are undervalued in those statements. Ensuring clarity, Engoron delineated the procedures for enforcing his ruling last Thursday. He allocated deadlines for both parties to suggest potential receivers and directed Trump and the defendants to inform a court-appointed monitor about the entities affected by his verdict. A significant directive also mandated the defendants to notify the monitor before applying for new business licenses or trying to form new entities that might inherit the assets of a dissolving company. Trump’s attorneys, though, counter-argue that Engoron’s decision lacks a coherent legal basis, dubbing it as “the corporate death penalty.” They further criticize the judge for ambiguity in elucidating the real-world implications of his verdict. In an earlier pretrial hearing, another Trump lawyer, Christopher Kise, sought clarity from Engoron on the extent of the ruling’s impact on Trump’s assets. Engoron, however, deferred his response. Summarizing their appeal, Trump’s legal team underscores their concerns about the far-reaching consequences of Engoron’s “overbroad directive,” emphasizing its potential to usher in “confusion and chaos.” While the political world watches with bated breath, only time will unveil the outcome of this legal tussle between Trump and the New York Attorney General’s office.</summary></entry></feed>