<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-11-03T09:19:41-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/11/03/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-11-03T09:19:41-04:00</published><updated>2023-11-03T09:19:41-04:00</updated><id>/2023/11/03/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/11/03/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/11/03/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-11-03T09:19:41-04:00</published><updated>2023-11-03T09:19:41-04:00</updated><id>/2023/11/03/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/11/03/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/">&lt;p&gt;Recent surprise attacks by Hamas on Israel has fueled ongoing tensions between staunchly conservative commentators and the progressive “Squad” Democrats known for criticizing Israel. The intensity of the backlash highlights the deep political divide over foreign policy in the Middle East.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Hamas’ shocking attack, several members of the “Squad,” including Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.), called for a “ceasefire and de-escalation,” condemning the violence. The absence of a statement from Rep. Rashida Tlaib (D-Mich.) was notably called out by conservative media outlets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;South Carolina GOP Rep. Nancy Mace quickly labeled Ocasio-Cortez a “Hamas apologist” in response to her call for peace and de-escalation. Rep. Ilhan Omar (D-Minn.), no stranger to controversy surrounding her views on Israel, echoed the call for de-escalation and ceasefire. Omar’s prior statements comparing the US and Israel to terrorist groups like Hamas and the Taliban resurfaced in the debate, fueling more criticisms. Omar’s 2019 tweet, where she opined that “Israel has hypnotized the world,” also continues to haunt her political career, often cited by critics to challenge her stance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conservative commentators have been especially vocal. “FOX &amp;amp; Friends Weekend” co-host Rachel Campos-Duffy took aim at Omar, saying she fails to recognize the peace in the Middle East under Trump’s administration. Conservative pundit John Hasson also called out Omar, claiming she insinuated that attacks on IDF forces were acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Massachusetts Democrat Rep. Ayanna Pressley’s concerns over the “devastating attacks on Israelis” were met with skepticism. A prominent conservative online personality, Comfortably Smug, accused the “Squad” of advising Israel to back down after the nation suffered massive attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Jamaal Bowman’s call for an end to the Gaza blockade, in addition to condemning the Hamas attacks, was met with criticism from conservative radio host Jason Rantz. He accused Bowman of pairing his condemnation of terrorism with unwarranted criticisms of Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Cori Bush emphasized the urgent need for a ceasefire, while pushing for an end to “U.S. support for Israeli military occupation and apartheid.” Defense attorney Marina Medvin criticized Bush, suggesting that she equates the death of Palestinian terrorists to the horrific acts committed against Jewish civilians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amidst the political turmoil and intense debate, the attacks have taken a heavy toll. Israeli media report over 300 dead due to the wide-ranging assault. Gaza health officials note that at least 200 Palestinians have perished in the retaliatory Israeli air strikes following the initial Hamas attack. As the situation remains volatile, both sides continue to count their casualties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This divisive issue showcases the challenge America faces in crafting a unified approach to foreign policy, with deeply entrenched political divides at play. As the situation develops, the debate is bound to intensify, shedding light on the complexities of U.S. politics in the global arena.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump Trial Turmoil: Clerk’s Political Donations Raise Questions of Impartiality</title><link href="/politics/2023/11/03/Trump-Trial-Clerk-Ethics/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump Trial Turmoil: Clerk’s Political Donations Raise Questions of Impartiality" /><published>2023-11-03T08:21:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-11-03T08:21:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/11/03/Trump-Trial-Clerk-Ethics</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/11/03/Trump-Trial-Clerk-Ethics/">&lt;p&gt;In the heart of New York’s bustling legal district, a story is unfolding that could well read like the plot of a political thriller. At the center is the principal law clerk for Justice Arthur Engoron, who appears to have entangled herself in a web of political donations that breach the ethical boundaries set for court officials.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is not just another yarn in the complex tapestry of American politics; it is a matter that strikes at the very foundation of judicial impartiality. Allison Greenfield, the clerk in question, has been exposed for making political contributions that vastly exceed the stipulated limits for court officers. The 72-page complaint, a public document thanks to the efforts of a vigilant citizen, lays bare the extent of Greenfield’s political involvement and donations. It paints a picture that is at best, one of negligence, and at worst, one of blatant disregard for the ethical standards expected of someone in her position.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What makes this issue more piquant is its timing. As former President Donald Trump faces a non-jury trial over claims laid out by New York Attorney General Letitia James, the spotlight turns not only to the merits of the case but also to those who orbit it. The gag order imposed on President Trump, and the subsequent fines for his commentary, have further stirred the cauldron of public discourse. Many see this as an infringement on Trump’s First Amendment rights, an issue that reverberates deeply within conservative circles and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Greenfield’s contributions tell a tale of partisanship that will unsettle those who cling to the ideal of an unbiased judiciary. With thousands of dollars funnelled to Democrat causes and campaigns, the discrepancy between her actions and the allowed $500 limit is not just a minor oversight; it is a chasm that calls into question her suitability to serve in a judicial capacity on such a high-profile case.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ethical guidelines are clear and unambiguous, designed to prevent the very scenario that seems to be unfolding. Court officials must remain above the political fray, ensuring that their personal beliefs do not cast a shadow over their professional duties. Yet, when Greenfield’s donations are tallied, the sum vastly outstrips the benchmark of neutrality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The conservative audience will find this particularly troubling, seeing it as part of a larger pattern of bias against Trump and his allies. The allegations against Greenfield, the involvement of high-profile Democrats, and the judge’s seeming reluctance to address these concerns are adding fuel to a fire that threatens to engulf the credibility of the legal process itself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the trial progresses, and the drama continues to unfold, one cannot help but question the implications of such actions. If the allegations hold true, they undermine not only the fairness of Trump’s trial but also erode the public trust in a system that must remain impartial to maintain its integrity. The calls for accountability will only grow louder, and the need for transparency never more clear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As we stand at this crossroads, the conservative community watches with bated breath, waiting to see if justice will truly be blind, or if it will peek from behind its blindfold, swayed by the winds of political bias.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In the heart of New York’s bustling legal district, a story is unfolding that could well read like the plot of a political thriller. At the center is the principal law clerk for Justice Arthur Engoron, who appears to have entangled herself in a web of political donations that breach the ethical boundaries set for court officials. This is not just another yarn in the complex tapestry of American politics; it is a matter that strikes at the very foundation of judicial impartiality. Allison Greenfield, the clerk in question, has been exposed for making political contributions that vastly exceed the stipulated limits for court officers. The 72-page complaint, a public document thanks to the efforts of a vigilant citizen, lays bare the extent of Greenfield’s political involvement and donations. It paints a picture that is at best, one of negligence, and at worst, one of blatant disregard for the ethical standards expected of someone in her position. What makes this issue more piquant is its timing. As former President Donald Trump faces a non-jury trial over claims laid out by New York Attorney General Letitia James, the spotlight turns not only to the merits of the case but also to those who orbit it. The gag order imposed on President Trump, and the subsequent fines for his commentary, have further stirred the cauldron of public discourse. Many see this as an infringement on Trump’s First Amendment rights, an issue that reverberates deeply within conservative circles and beyond. Greenfield’s contributions tell a tale of partisanship that will unsettle those who cling to the ideal of an unbiased judiciary. With thousands of dollars funnelled to Democrat causes and campaigns, the discrepancy between her actions and the allowed $500 limit is not just a minor oversight; it is a chasm that calls into question her suitability to serve in a judicial capacity on such a high-profile case. The ethical guidelines are clear and unambiguous, designed to prevent the very scenario that seems to be unfolding. Court officials must remain above the political fray, ensuring that their personal beliefs do not cast a shadow over their professional duties. Yet, when Greenfield’s donations are tallied, the sum vastly outstrips the benchmark of neutrality. The conservative audience will find this particularly troubling, seeing it as part of a larger pattern of bias against Trump and his allies. The allegations against Greenfield, the involvement of high-profile Democrats, and the judge’s seeming reluctance to address these concerns are adding fuel to a fire that threatens to engulf the credibility of the legal process itself. As the trial progresses, and the drama continues to unfold, one cannot help but question the implications of such actions. If the allegations hold true, they undermine not only the fairness of Trump’s trial but also erode the public trust in a system that must remain impartial to maintain its integrity. The calls for accountability will only grow louder, and the need for transparency never more clear. As we stand at this crossroads, the conservative community watches with bated breath, waiting to see if justice will truly be blind, or if it will peek from behind its blindfold, swayed by the winds of political bias.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">House Speaker’s ‘Paycheck to Paycheck’ Reality Resonates with Many Americans</title><link href="/news/2023/11/03/House-Speaker-Relatability/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="House Speaker’s ‘Paycheck to Paycheck’ Reality Resonates with Many Americans" /><published>2023-11-03T07:17:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-11-03T07:17:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/11/03/House-Speaker-Relatability</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/11/03/House-Speaker-Relatability/">&lt;p&gt;In a landscape where the cost of living is ever-rising and the economic challenges are real for the average American, the spotlight on House Speaker Mike Johnson’s personal finances has struck a different chord than intended. A report intended to scrutinize has instead highlighted a relatable scenario for many: living paycheck to paycheck.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A recent article by The Daily Beast surfaced details suggesting Speaker Johnson does not boast of extensive assets or a bloated bank account. But rather than resonating as a potential scandal, it reflects a reality many Americans face amidst the nation’s inflationary pressures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This revelation comes at a time when economic anxiety runs high. Reports indicate a significant portion of the country could not afford an unexpected $400 expense, mirroring the financial vulnerability suggested in Johnson’s disclosed financial situation. This condition resonates more than ever with constituents who navigate the same tightrope of financial precarity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s not uncommon for politicians to be chastised for their wealth, with critics accusing them of being out of touch with the common person. However, when a leader appears to share in the financial struggles of their electorate, the typical narrative flips. The backlash against the report was swift, with supporters defending Johnson as a politician who, unlike many, hasn’t profited from his position.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Commentary across social media has taken a defensive stance, asserting that if the disclosures are accurate, Johnson’s financial situation makes him more akin to his constituents, not less suited to represent them. Such a financial standing is no mark of shame but a sign of shared experience with the electorate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The public reaction to the news suggests that the state of a lawmaker’s finances can cut both ways in the court of public opinion. On one side, affluence can suggest disconnection from the electorate. On the other, the absence of wealth, especially in a climate where many feel economically squeezed, can suggest solidarity and perhaps, integrity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moreover, the report inadvertently touches on a broader, perhaps more concerning issue — the expectation of wealth accumulation through political office. As the public grows increasingly aware and weary of politicians amassing significant wealth during their tenure, a profile like Johnson’s stands out for its lack of financial controversy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the era where financial stability is an aspiration rather than a given, Speaker Johnson’s reported financial profile, rather than alienating, may indeed endear him to the voting public. It portrays a level of commonality in the struggle to maintain economic stability, something that resonates with many Americans amid these challenging economic times.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a landscape where the cost of living is ever-rising and the economic challenges are real for the average American, the spotlight on House Speaker Mike Johnson’s personal finances has struck a different chord than intended. A report intended to scrutinize has instead highlighted a relatable scenario for many: living paycheck to paycheck. A recent article by The Daily Beast surfaced details suggesting Speaker Johnson does not boast of extensive assets or a bloated bank account. But rather than resonating as a potential scandal, it reflects a reality many Americans face amidst the nation’s inflationary pressures. This revelation comes at a time when economic anxiety runs high. Reports indicate a significant portion of the country could not afford an unexpected $400 expense, mirroring the financial vulnerability suggested in Johnson’s disclosed financial situation. This condition resonates more than ever with constituents who navigate the same tightrope of financial precarity. It’s not uncommon for politicians to be chastised for their wealth, with critics accusing them of being out of touch with the common person. However, when a leader appears to share in the financial struggles of their electorate, the typical narrative flips. The backlash against the report was swift, with supporters defending Johnson as a politician who, unlike many, hasn’t profited from his position. Commentary across social media has taken a defensive stance, asserting that if the disclosures are accurate, Johnson’s financial situation makes him more akin to his constituents, not less suited to represent them. Such a financial standing is no mark of shame but a sign of shared experience with the electorate. The public reaction to the news suggests that the state of a lawmaker’s finances can cut both ways in the court of public opinion. On one side, affluence can suggest disconnection from the electorate. On the other, the absence of wealth, especially in a climate where many feel economically squeezed, can suggest solidarity and perhaps, integrity. Moreover, the report inadvertently touches on a broader, perhaps more concerning issue — the expectation of wealth accumulation through political office. As the public grows increasingly aware and weary of politicians amassing significant wealth during their tenure, a profile like Johnson’s stands out for its lack of financial controversy. In the era where financial stability is an aspiration rather than a given, Speaker Johnson’s reported financial profile, rather than alienating, may indeed endear him to the voting public. It portrays a level of commonality in the struggle to maintain economic stability, something that resonates with many Americans amid these challenging economic times.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Sam Bankman-Fried Convicted: A Cautionary Tale in the Crypto World</title><link href="/news/2023/11/03/Bankman-Fried-Guilty-Fraud/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sam Bankman-Fried Convicted: A Cautionary Tale in the Crypto World" /><published>2023-11-03T06:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-11-03T06:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/11/03/Bankman-Fried-Guilty-Fraud</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/11/03/Bankman-Fried-Guilty-Fraud/">&lt;p&gt;FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried has been found guilty on all charges related to the collapse of the crypto exchange that he once helmed. The verdict arrived at a New York federal court, where a jury sided with prosecutors in the first of two criminal trials for Bankman-Fried.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The downfall of FTX has been nothing short of dramatic, unfolding like a modern-day financial tragedy. Accusations against Bankman-Fried painted a dark picture of deceit, with the FTX CEO misappropriating billions of dollars and engaging in fraudulent acts that have rocked investor confidence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the news broke, it reverberated through the corridors of finance and technology alike. Once a golden boy of the crypto boom, Bankman-Fried’s net worth skyrocketed along with the rise of Bitcoin and other digital currencies, positioning him as a key political and philanthropic figure. But his empire built on digital assets came crashing down when FTX declared bankruptcy in late 2022, leading to a spiral of legal challenges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The charges, which included wire fraud and conspiracy, could consign Bankman-Fried to over a century in prison, a staggering fall from grace for the former billionaire. The maximum sentence of 110 years sends a strong message about the severity of the crimes and the legal repercussions of financial mismanagement and corruption.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the verdict, defense statements pointed to an appeal, a clear sign that Bankman-Fried and his legal team are not ready to accept the jury’s decision. Throughout the trial, he maintained his innocence, claiming mistakes were made but outright fraud or theft was never his intent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The prosecution brought forth a compelling case with testimonies from several members of Bankman-Fried’s inner circle, all who had previously pleaded guilty and cooperated with the government. This included his ex-girlfriend and Alameda Research CEO Caroline Ellison, alongside FTX co-founder Gary Wang and engineering chief Nishad Singh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The guilty verdict has cast a shadow over the crypto industry, with Bankman-Fried’s case highlighting vulnerabilities and the urgent need for regulation. While the industry is innovative and the players are relatively new, the message from U.S. Attorney Damian Williams rings clear: traditional corruption in high finance will be pursued and punished, no matter the modern digital disguise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As we await the second criminal trial set for March 2024, the story of Sam Bankman-Fried serves as a stern warning of hubris and the potential perils of the unregulated crypto market. It also underscores the importance of due diligence and ethical conduct in financial leadership.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The crypto community and investors are now left to ponder the ramifications of this conviction, as the shockwaves of this high-profile case continue to be felt across the global financial landscape.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried has been found guilty on all charges related to the collapse of the crypto exchange that he once helmed. The verdict arrived at a New York federal court, where a jury sided with prosecutors in the first of two criminal trials for Bankman-Fried. The downfall of FTX has been nothing short of dramatic, unfolding like a modern-day financial tragedy. Accusations against Bankman-Fried painted a dark picture of deceit, with the FTX CEO misappropriating billions of dollars and engaging in fraudulent acts that have rocked investor confidence. As the news broke, it reverberated through the corridors of finance and technology alike. Once a golden boy of the crypto boom, Bankman-Fried’s net worth skyrocketed along with the rise of Bitcoin and other digital currencies, positioning him as a key political and philanthropic figure. But his empire built on digital assets came crashing down when FTX declared bankruptcy in late 2022, leading to a spiral of legal challenges. The charges, which included wire fraud and conspiracy, could consign Bankman-Fried to over a century in prison, a staggering fall from grace for the former billionaire. The maximum sentence of 110 years sends a strong message about the severity of the crimes and the legal repercussions of financial mismanagement and corruption. After the verdict, defense statements pointed to an appeal, a clear sign that Bankman-Fried and his legal team are not ready to accept the jury’s decision. Throughout the trial, he maintained his innocence, claiming mistakes were made but outright fraud or theft was never his intent. The prosecution brought forth a compelling case with testimonies from several members of Bankman-Fried’s inner circle, all who had previously pleaded guilty and cooperated with the government. This included his ex-girlfriend and Alameda Research CEO Caroline Ellison, alongside FTX co-founder Gary Wang and engineering chief Nishad Singh. The guilty verdict has cast a shadow over the crypto industry, with Bankman-Fried’s case highlighting vulnerabilities and the urgent need for regulation. While the industry is innovative and the players are relatively new, the message from U.S. Attorney Damian Williams rings clear: traditional corruption in high finance will be pursued and punished, no matter the modern digital disguise. As we await the second criminal trial set for March 2024, the story of Sam Bankman-Fried serves as a stern warning of hubris and the potential perils of the unregulated crypto market. It also underscores the importance of due diligence and ethical conduct in financial leadership. The crypto community and investors are now left to ponder the ramifications of this conviction, as the shockwaves of this high-profile case continue to be felt across the global financial landscape.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Over 500 Americans Trapped: A Crisis Unfolding in Gaza</title><link href="/news/2023/11/02/Held-Hostage-Gaza/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Over 500 Americans Trapped: A Crisis Unfolding in Gaza" /><published>2023-11-02T15:07:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-11-02T15:07:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/11/02/Held-Hostage-Gaza</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/11/02/Held-Hostage-Gaza/">&lt;p&gt;The crisis in Gaza escalates as over 500 Americans and their family members find themselves trapped, their exit denied by Hamas authorities. Reports vary, with Israel Defense Forces claiming 230 Americans are being held, while other sources report numbers as high as 500. Secretary of State Antony Blinken confirmed the gravity of the situation in a recent Senate Committee on Appropriations, stating that around 1,000 individuals, comprising 400 American citizens and their family members, are stuck in Gaza, desperately wanting to leave.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The situation has garnered international attention, with major news outlets reporting on the unfolding crisis. The Washington Post highlighted the plight of at least 400 American hostages unable to leave due to the ongoing tensions and restrictions in the area. CBS News further reported that between 500 and 600 Americans are among the 2.3 million people trapped in the Gaza Strip since the Palestinian territory’s Hamas rulers initiated their terror attack on October 7.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Americans in Gaza find themselves in a precarious situation. While not directly held by armed Hamas terrorists, they are nonetheless trapped against their will, their freedom of movement severely restricted. Senator Marsha Blackburn brought attention to this issue, questioning whether dual passport holders and Palestinians are also being counted among the hostages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The White House has pointed out that Hamas is actively preventing people from leaving Gaza via the Rafah crossing into Egypt, adding another layer of complexity to the crisis. However, there seems to be a glimmer of hope as reports emerged of dozens of people being allowed to enter the Rafah crossing — marking the first time foreign passport holders have been permitted to leave since the Israel-Hamas war began.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The stakes are high, and the world watches as the crisis in Gaza unfolds. The safety and well-being of over 500 Americans are on the line, and the urgency for a resolution has never been greater. The American government, international bodies, and concerned citizens alike are calling for immediate action, hoping to bring an end to this crisis and safely bring home those trapped in Gaza.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">The crisis in Gaza escalates as over 500 Americans and their family members find themselves trapped, their exit denied by Hamas authorities. Reports vary, with Israel Defense Forces claiming 230 Americans are being held, while other sources report numbers as high as 500. Secretary of State Antony Blinken confirmed the gravity of the situation in a recent Senate Committee on Appropriations, stating that around 1,000 individuals, comprising 400 American citizens and their family members, are stuck in Gaza, desperately wanting to leave. The situation has garnered international attention, with major news outlets reporting on the unfolding crisis. The Washington Post highlighted the plight of at least 400 American hostages unable to leave due to the ongoing tensions and restrictions in the area. CBS News further reported that between 500 and 600 Americans are among the 2.3 million people trapped in the Gaza Strip since the Palestinian territory’s Hamas rulers initiated their terror attack on October 7. The Americans in Gaza find themselves in a precarious situation. While not directly held by armed Hamas terrorists, they are nonetheless trapped against their will, their freedom of movement severely restricted. Senator Marsha Blackburn brought attention to this issue, questioning whether dual passport holders and Palestinians are also being counted among the hostages. The White House has pointed out that Hamas is actively preventing people from leaving Gaza via the Rafah crossing into Egypt, adding another layer of complexity to the crisis. However, there seems to be a glimmer of hope as reports emerged of dozens of people being allowed to enter the Rafah crossing — marking the first time foreign passport holders have been permitted to leave since the Israel-Hamas war began. The stakes are high, and the world watches as the crisis in Gaza unfolds. The safety and well-being of over 500 Americans are on the line, and the urgency for a resolution has never been greater. The American government, international bodies, and concerned citizens alike are calling for immediate action, hoping to bring an end to this crisis and safely bring home those trapped in Gaza.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Unmasking Biden’s Financial Web: The 10% Connection Unveiled</title><link href="/politics/2023/11/02/Biden-Bank-Records/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Unmasking Biden’s Financial Web: The 10% Connection Unveiled" /><published>2023-11-02T13:58:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-11-02T13:58:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/11/02/Biden-Bank-Records</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/11/02/Biden-Bank-Records/">&lt;p&gt;In an eye-opening episode of ‘Jesse Watters Primetime’, the popular FOX News host meticulously unraveled the intricate financial web surrounding President Biden, raising severe concerns about the alleged money laundering schemes that seem to trace back directly to China. Jesse Watters, known for his sharp analysis and no-holds-barred commentary, left no stone unturned as he dissected the money trail, bringing to light the unsettling connections that many have long suspected but were never able to conclusively prove.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For years, whispers and speculations have circulated around President Biden’s financial dealings, particularly regarding his ties to China. However, it seemed as if Biden believed he could simply run out the clock, evading the need to disclose his bank records, and with them, the truth. But as Watters pointed out, in today’s digital age, accessing bank records is a far cry from the tedious process of rummaging through physical files. With a simple account number, the truth can be printed out in black and white, laid bare for all to see.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Representative James Comer has been at the forefront of this investigation, diligently working to uncover the facts and follow the money straight to the source. And it seems his efforts are finally bearing fruit. Despite the left’s persistent claims of innocence and lack of evidence, the Biden family bank records are beginning to tell a different story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the heart of this controversy is a $40,000 check made out directly to Joe Biden. While the left continues to insist that there is no incriminating evidence against the President, this check raises a multitude of questions. The funds can be traced back to China, as uncovered by Rep. Comer. The money trail is convoluted, yet undeniable: China wired $5 million to Hunter Biden’s company, which then sent $400,000 to Hunter, and subsequently, money was sent to Biden’s brother, finally culminating in a $40,000 check to Biden himself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Breaking down the numbers, a startling realization comes to light: $40,000 is precisely 10% of $400,000. Watters aptly coined this the ‘10% for “The Big Guy”’ scenario, drawing a direct line between the money from China and Biden’s bank account. This revelation raises the stakes significantly, challenging the Democrats’ narrative and forcing the question: What does a smoking gun look like in the face of such compelling evidence?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the country watches closely, the Biden money saga continues to unfold. Watters’ exposé has brought to light the uncomfortable truths and unanswered questions that linger around President Biden’s financial dealings, making it clear that this story is far from over. The call for transparency and accountability has never been louder, as Americans from coast to coast demand answers. It’s time to follow the money, and the trail does not lie.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In an eye-opening episode of ‘Jesse Watters Primetime’, the popular FOX News host meticulously unraveled the intricate financial web surrounding President Biden, raising severe concerns about the alleged money laundering schemes that seem to trace back directly to China. Jesse Watters, known for his sharp analysis and no-holds-barred commentary, left no stone unturned as he dissected the money trail, bringing to light the unsettling connections that many have long suspected but were never able to conclusively prove. For years, whispers and speculations have circulated around President Biden’s financial dealings, particularly regarding his ties to China. However, it seemed as if Biden believed he could simply run out the clock, evading the need to disclose his bank records, and with them, the truth. But as Watters pointed out, in today’s digital age, accessing bank records is a far cry from the tedious process of rummaging through physical files. With a simple account number, the truth can be printed out in black and white, laid bare for all to see. Representative James Comer has been at the forefront of this investigation, diligently working to uncover the facts and follow the money straight to the source. And it seems his efforts are finally bearing fruit. Despite the left’s persistent claims of innocence and lack of evidence, the Biden family bank records are beginning to tell a different story. At the heart of this controversy is a $40,000 check made out directly to Joe Biden. While the left continues to insist that there is no incriminating evidence against the President, this check raises a multitude of questions. The funds can be traced back to China, as uncovered by Rep. Comer. The money trail is convoluted, yet undeniable: China wired $5 million to Hunter Biden’s company, which then sent $400,000 to Hunter, and subsequently, money was sent to Biden’s brother, finally culminating in a $40,000 check to Biden himself. Breaking down the numbers, a startling realization comes to light: $40,000 is precisely 10% of $400,000. Watters aptly coined this the ‘10% for “The Big Guy”’ scenario, drawing a direct line between the money from China and Biden’s bank account. This revelation raises the stakes significantly, challenging the Democrats’ narrative and forcing the question: What does a smoking gun look like in the face of such compelling evidence? As the country watches closely, the Biden money saga continues to unfold. Watters’ exposé has brought to light the uncomfortable truths and unanswered questions that linger around President Biden’s financial dealings, making it clear that this story is far from over. The call for transparency and accountability has never been louder, as Americans from coast to coast demand answers. It’s time to follow the money, and the trail does not lie.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A Farewell to ‘The General’: Bob Knight’s Indelible Legacy in College Basketball</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/11/02/Basketball-Legend-Bob-Knight-Passes-Away/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Farewell to ‘The General’: Bob Knight’s Indelible Legacy in College Basketball" /><published>2023-11-02T12:48:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-11-02T12:48:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/11/02/Basketball-Legend-Bob-Knight-Passes-Away</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/11/02/Basketball-Legend-Bob-Knight-Passes-Away/">&lt;p&gt;Bob Knight, the iconic figure of college basketball, has left an indelible mark on the sport and on the lives of many. With his passing at the age of 83, the basketball world has lost a true giant. His family announced his passing, expressing their gratitude for the outpouring of support and requesting privacy during this difficult time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Coach Knight, also known as “The General,” was known for his fiery demeanor, intense coaching style, and unparalleled dedication to the game. His career spanned over four decades, amassing 902 victories and leading his teams to three NCAA championships. His contributions to basketball were recognized with his induction into the Hall of Fame, and he also led the U.S. Olympic team to a gold medal in 1984.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Knight’s coaching style was not without controversy, but his supporters were steadfast. His insistence on players maintaining high academic standards, coupled with his unwavering adherence to NCAA rules, showcased his dedication to integrity in sports. He was a staunch advocate for doing things his way, a principle that resonated with many of his players and fans.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The impact of Bob Knight on college basketball is immeasurable. He was a mentor to some of America’s most successful coaches, and his influence extended far beyond the basketball court. His players were expected to excel in both their academic and athletic pursuits, a testament to his belief in the holistic development of young men.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Steve Alford, a key player in Knight’s last national championship team, praised him for changing the way basketball is played, not just in Indiana but across the nation. Knight’s innovative strategies, particularly the motion offense, became a staple in college basketball, adopted by coaches nationwide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bob Knight was a figure larger than life, a coach whose legacy will live on in the annals of college basketball history. His fierce competitiveness, commitment to excellence, and unwavering principles have left an indelible mark on the sport. Today, we remember a coach who changed the game, a mentor who shaped lives, and a legend who will never be forgotten.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His story serves as a reminder that passion, dedication, and adherence to one’s principles can leave a lasting legacy. Bob Knight was not just a coach; he was a force of nature, a titan of college basketball whose impact will be felt for generations to come.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Bob Knight, the iconic figure of college basketball, has left an indelible mark on the sport and on the lives of many. With his passing at the age of 83, the basketball world has lost a true giant. His family announced his passing, expressing their gratitude for the outpouring of support and requesting privacy during this difficult time. Coach Knight, also known as “The General,” was known for his fiery demeanor, intense coaching style, and unparalleled dedication to the game. His career spanned over four decades, amassing 902 victories and leading his teams to three NCAA championships. His contributions to basketball were recognized with his induction into the Hall of Fame, and he also led the U.S. Olympic team to a gold medal in 1984. Knight’s coaching style was not without controversy, but his supporters were steadfast. His insistence on players maintaining high academic standards, coupled with his unwavering adherence to NCAA rules, showcased his dedication to integrity in sports. He was a staunch advocate for doing things his way, a principle that resonated with many of his players and fans. The impact of Bob Knight on college basketball is immeasurable. He was a mentor to some of America’s most successful coaches, and his influence extended far beyond the basketball court. His players were expected to excel in both their academic and athletic pursuits, a testament to his belief in the holistic development of young men. Steve Alford, a key player in Knight’s last national championship team, praised him for changing the way basketball is played, not just in Indiana but across the nation. Knight’s innovative strategies, particularly the motion offense, became a staple in college basketball, adopted by coaches nationwide. Bob Knight was a figure larger than life, a coach whose legacy will live on in the annals of college basketball history. His fierce competitiveness, commitment to excellence, and unwavering principles have left an indelible mark on the sport. Today, we remember a coach who changed the game, a mentor who shaped lives, and a legend who will never be forgotten. His story serves as a reminder that passion, dedication, and adherence to one’s principles can leave a lasting legacy. Bob Knight was not just a coach; he was a force of nature, a titan of college basketball whose impact will be felt for generations to come.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Rep. George Santos Dodges Expulsion, Emphasizing Need for Due Process</title><link href="/politics/2023/11/02/Santos-House-Expulsion-Attempt/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rep. George Santos Dodges Expulsion, Emphasizing Need for Due Process" /><published>2023-11-02T11:34:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-11-02T11:34:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/11/02/Santos-House-Expulsion-Attempt</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/11/02/Santos-House-Expulsion-Attempt/">&lt;p&gt;Rep. George Santos (R-N.Y.) managed to stave off expulsion from the House of Representatives. The scene turned chaotic as Santos engaged in a heated exchange with an anti-Israel protester, showcasing the high tensions surrounding the Congressman.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Santos found himself in the eye of the storm, with a faction of his fellow New York Republicans leading the charge to expel him from the House. Despite the pressure, the final vote tallied at 213-179 against expulsion, with 19 lawmakers choosing to vote “present.” It is crucial to note that expelling a member from the House is an exceptional action, requiring a two-thirds majority of all members present.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, the vote saw 24 Republicans favoring expulsion, while 31 Democrats opted to keep Santos in the House. This vote distribution led Santos to comment on the perceived political landscape, stating, “There’s more Democrats in this body that believe in the rule of law than there are Republicans. That’s what you should know.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Santos, under a cloud of legal troubles, stood his ground, asserting his right to due process. “I am fighting to clear my name. I am fighting for due process,” he emphasized, highlighting the significance of these legal principles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The New York Republicans spearheading the expulsion effort included Anthony D’Esposito, Nick LaLota, and Mike Lawler. Santos, defending himself on the House floor, accused them of overstepping their roles, acting as “judge, jury, and executioner.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Santos’s speech underscored his commitment to proving his innocence against the myriad of charges leveled against him. “Efforts taken by other members in this body to act as jury and executioner are unconscionable and reckless to our Republican system of government and to the integrity of this body,” he proclaimed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite being the sole member of Congress to speak in his defense during the debate, Santos’s words resonated with the need for consistency in upholding constitutional values. He questioned the actions of his peers, urging them to reflect on their commitment to the Constitution while challenging their role in this legal process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Santos’s escape from expulsion does not mark the end of his legal battles, as he faces 23 charges, including conspiracy, wire fraud, making false statements, falsification of records, aggravated identity theft, and credit card fraud. The resolution of these charges will be crucial in determining his political future, but for now, Santos remains a member of the House of Representatives, emphasizing the paramount importance of due process in the American legal system.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Rep. George Santos (R-N.Y.) managed to stave off expulsion from the House of Representatives. The scene turned chaotic as Santos engaged in a heated exchange with an anti-Israel protester, showcasing the high tensions surrounding the Congressman. Santos found himself in the eye of the storm, with a faction of his fellow New York Republicans leading the charge to expel him from the House. Despite the pressure, the final vote tallied at 213-179 against expulsion, with 19 lawmakers choosing to vote “present.” It is crucial to note that expelling a member from the House is an exceptional action, requiring a two-thirds majority of all members present. Interestingly, the vote saw 24 Republicans favoring expulsion, while 31 Democrats opted to keep Santos in the House. This vote distribution led Santos to comment on the perceived political landscape, stating, “There’s more Democrats in this body that believe in the rule of law than there are Republicans. That’s what you should know.” Santos, under a cloud of legal troubles, stood his ground, asserting his right to due process. “I am fighting to clear my name. I am fighting for due process,” he emphasized, highlighting the significance of these legal principles. The New York Republicans spearheading the expulsion effort included Anthony D’Esposito, Nick LaLota, and Mike Lawler. Santos, defending himself on the House floor, accused them of overstepping their roles, acting as “judge, jury, and executioner.” Santos’s speech underscored his commitment to proving his innocence against the myriad of charges leveled against him. “Efforts taken by other members in this body to act as jury and executioner are unconscionable and reckless to our Republican system of government and to the integrity of this body,” he proclaimed. Despite being the sole member of Congress to speak in his defense during the debate, Santos’s words resonated with the need for consistency in upholding constitutional values. He questioned the actions of his peers, urging them to reflect on their commitment to the Constitution while challenging their role in this legal process. Santos’s escape from expulsion does not mark the end of his legal battles, as he faces 23 charges, including conspiracy, wire fraud, making false statements, falsification of records, aggravated identity theft, and credit card fraud. The resolution of these charges will be crucial in determining his political future, but for now, Santos remains a member of the House of Representatives, emphasizing the paramount importance of due process in the American legal system.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Rep. Boebert Stands Firm: ‘No Place in Congress for Anti-Israel Sentiments’</title><link href="/politics/2023/11/02/Boebert-Tlaib-Controversy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rep. Boebert Stands Firm: ‘No Place in Congress for Anti-Israel Sentiments’" /><published>2023-11-02T10:26:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-11-02T10:26:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/11/02/Boebert-Tlaib-Controversy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/11/02/Boebert-Tlaib-Controversy/">&lt;p&gt;Rep. Lauren Boebert (R-Colo.) did not mince words as she declared that there is absolutely no room in Congress for individuals who share the same anti-Israel views as Rep. Rashida Tlaib (D-Mich.). Boebert’s statement comes in the aftermath of a terrorist attack on Israel by Hamas on October 7th, which left over 1,400 Israelis dead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The House of Representatives, caught in the midst of political tumult, witnessed a motion last week by Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene (R-Ga.) seeking to censure Tlaib for her vehement criticism of Israel following the attack. However, this motion was tabled with a vote of 222-186, as 23 Republicans joined Democrats in opposition. Boebert, unwavering in her stance, was not among the dissenters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During her appearance on “Eric Bolling The Balance,” Boebert clearly articulated her viewpoint, stating, “There are lines that members of Congress should not cross, and supporting terrorist groups like Hamas is definitely one of those lines.” She continued by expressing that there is simply no place in Congress for individuals who embody ignorance and hatred to the extent that Tlaib does, voicing her support for the censure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since becoming the first Congress member of Palestinian descent in 2018, Tlaib has been vocal in her critique of Israeli policies, calling for sanctions and accusing Israel of perpetuating apartheid in the Gaza Strip. She maintains this stance despite the Palestinians’ self-governing status in Gaza, a result of electing Hamas to power in 2006.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Boebert did not hold back as she addressed this issue, stating, “There are some [in Congress] who are siding with Hamas during this horrible and brutal attack on Israel, this war that is taking place.” She highlighted that while there are members on the opposite side of the aisle expressing support for Israel, it remains uncertain whether it will translate into concrete action against one of their own.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Emphasizing the strength of the U.S.-Israel alliance, Boebert affirmed, “Israel, our nation’s most trusted ally, has every right to defend itself. And we are here standing in solidarity as Republicans with Israel every step of the way.” She condemned Hamas’ actions as utterly repulsive and expressed her heartfelt prayers for the Israelis and all innocent victims caught in the crossfire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Boebert’s strong, unwavering support for Israel and her call for accountability within Congress reflect the conservative values of standing with allies and ensuring that anti-Israel sentiments do not find a foothold in American politics.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Rep. Lauren Boebert (R-Colo.) did not mince words as she declared that there is absolutely no room in Congress for individuals who share the same anti-Israel views as Rep. Rashida Tlaib (D-Mich.). Boebert’s statement comes in the aftermath of a terrorist attack on Israel by Hamas on October 7th, which left over 1,400 Israelis dead. The House of Representatives, caught in the midst of political tumult, witnessed a motion last week by Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene (R-Ga.) seeking to censure Tlaib for her vehement criticism of Israel following the attack. However, this motion was tabled with a vote of 222-186, as 23 Republicans joined Democrats in opposition. Boebert, unwavering in her stance, was not among the dissenters. During her appearance on “Eric Bolling The Balance,” Boebert clearly articulated her viewpoint, stating, “There are lines that members of Congress should not cross, and supporting terrorist groups like Hamas is definitely one of those lines.” She continued by expressing that there is simply no place in Congress for individuals who embody ignorance and hatred to the extent that Tlaib does, voicing her support for the censure. Since becoming the first Congress member of Palestinian descent in 2018, Tlaib has been vocal in her critique of Israeli policies, calling for sanctions and accusing Israel of perpetuating apartheid in the Gaza Strip. She maintains this stance despite the Palestinians’ self-governing status in Gaza, a result of electing Hamas to power in 2006. Boebert did not hold back as she addressed this issue, stating, “There are some [in Congress] who are siding with Hamas during this horrible and brutal attack on Israel, this war that is taking place.” She highlighted that while there are members on the opposite side of the aisle expressing support for Israel, it remains uncertain whether it will translate into concrete action against one of their own. Emphasizing the strength of the U.S.-Israel alliance, Boebert affirmed, “Israel, our nation’s most trusted ally, has every right to defend itself. And we are here standing in solidarity as Republicans with Israel every step of the way.” She condemned Hamas’ actions as utterly repulsive and expressed her heartfelt prayers for the Israelis and all innocent victims caught in the crossfire. Boebert’s strong, unwavering support for Israel and her call for accountability within Congress reflect the conservative values of standing with allies and ensuring that anti-Israel sentiments do not find a foothold in American politics.</summary></entry></feed>