<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-09-20T19:14:45-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/09/20/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-09-20T19:14:45-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-20T19:14:45-04:00</updated><id>/2023/09/20/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/20/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Texas Representative Takes Stand Against Gun Restrictions</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/20/Protecting-Gun-Rights/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Texas Representative Takes Stand Against Gun Restrictions" /><published>2023-09-20T17:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-20T17:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/20/Protecting-Gun-Rights</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/20/Protecting-Gun-Rights/">&lt;p&gt;In response to what some are calling aggressive moves by the left, Texas Representative Michael Cloud is stepping up to safeguard the rights of gun owners. On Tuesday, he reintroduced the “Protecting the Right To Keep and Bear Arms Act”. This legislation, if passed, would restrict the president and the Department of Health and Human Services (HHS) from using public health emergencies as a means to enforce gun control measures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;second-amendment-under-fire&quot;&gt;Second Amendment Under Fire?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vice President Kamala Harris recently expressed her support for the Second Amendment on “The Jennifer Hudson Show”. However, her endorsement for an assault weapons ban in the same conversation has raised eyebrows among conservatives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, Michael Cloud has expressed concern over the strategies of the ‘radical left’. “For a long time, radical left politicians have been open about their willingness to use executive authority and rob Americans of their Second Amendment rights,” Cloud stated, pointing out the need for his reintroduced bill.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The catalyst for such statements and actions is clear. Last week, New Mexico’s Democratic Governor, Michelle Lujan Grisham, declared gun violence as a public health crisis and attempted to implement a 30-day prohibition on carrying firearms in public spaces and on state-owned properties in Albuquerque. Cloud did not hold back in his criticism, “The Biden administration, Gov. Grisham, and others have exercised extraordinary executive power to push their liberal agenda and expand the power of the government.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-response&quot;&gt;The Response&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Grisham’s bold move faced swift resistance. A judge promptly blocked the proposed 30-day gun ban. In turn, Grisham adjusted her rule to limit firearms at public parks or playgrounds, specifically mentioning areas “where we know we have high risk of kids and families.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many, including Aidan Johnston, director of federal affairs for Gun Owners of America, have voiced their concerns. Johnston noted that Grisham’s utilization of a ‘public health emergency’ to suspend the Second Amendment is a troubling instance of officials potentially misusing ‘emergency powers’ to infringe on constitutional rights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In light of these concerns, Rep. Pete Sessions and Rep. Mary Miller have also shown their support for Cloud’s bill, emphasizing the importance of preserving the rights of gun owners.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-bigger-picture&quot;&gt;The Bigger Picture&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This isn’t the first time gun violence has been referred to as a “public health crisis.” Earlier this year, Health and Human Services Secretary Xavier Becerra used the term after a mass shooting in Atlanta. Prior to that, officials in California had made similar appeals to label gun violence as a public health emergency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a polarized political climate, the debate over gun rights and gun control continues to intensify. With representatives like Michael Cloud taking a stand, the future of the Second Amendment remains a fiercely contested topic in the United States.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In response to what some are calling aggressive moves by the left, Texas Representative Michael Cloud is stepping up to safeguard the rights of gun owners. On Tuesday, he reintroduced the “Protecting the Right To Keep and Bear Arms Act”. This legislation, if passed, would restrict the president and the Department of Health and Human Services (HHS) from using public health emergencies as a means to enforce gun control measures. Second Amendment Under Fire? Vice President Kamala Harris recently expressed her support for the Second Amendment on “The Jennifer Hudson Show”. However, her endorsement for an assault weapons ban in the same conversation has raised eyebrows among conservatives. Meanwhile, Michael Cloud has expressed concern over the strategies of the ‘radical left’. “For a long time, radical left politicians have been open about their willingness to use executive authority and rob Americans of their Second Amendment rights,” Cloud stated, pointing out the need for his reintroduced bill. The catalyst for such statements and actions is clear. Last week, New Mexico’s Democratic Governor, Michelle Lujan Grisham, declared gun violence as a public health crisis and attempted to implement a 30-day prohibition on carrying firearms in public spaces and on state-owned properties in Albuquerque. Cloud did not hold back in his criticism, “The Biden administration, Gov. Grisham, and others have exercised extraordinary executive power to push their liberal agenda and expand the power of the government.” The Response Grisham’s bold move faced swift resistance. A judge promptly blocked the proposed 30-day gun ban. In turn, Grisham adjusted her rule to limit firearms at public parks or playgrounds, specifically mentioning areas “where we know we have high risk of kids and families.” Many, including Aidan Johnston, director of federal affairs for Gun Owners of America, have voiced their concerns. Johnston noted that Grisham’s utilization of a ‘public health emergency’ to suspend the Second Amendment is a troubling instance of officials potentially misusing ‘emergency powers’ to infringe on constitutional rights. In light of these concerns, Rep. Pete Sessions and Rep. Mary Miller have also shown their support for Cloud’s bill, emphasizing the importance of preserving the rights of gun owners. The Bigger Picture This isn’t the first time gun violence has been referred to as a “public health crisis.” Earlier this year, Health and Human Services Secretary Xavier Becerra used the term after a mass shooting in Atlanta. Prior to that, officials in California had made similar appeals to label gun violence as a public health emergency. In a polarized political climate, the debate over gun rights and gun control continues to intensify. With representatives like Michael Cloud taking a stand, the future of the Second Amendment remains a fiercely contested topic in the United States.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hunter Biden Faces Scrutiny Over Federal Gun Charges</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/20/Hunter-Biden-Gun-Charges/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hunter Biden Faces Scrutiny Over Federal Gun Charges" /><published>2023-09-20T16:02:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-20T16:02:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/20/Hunter-Biden-Gun-Charges</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/20/Hunter-Biden-Gun-Charges/">&lt;p&gt;Hunter Biden, son of U.S. President Joe Biden, has recently been caught in the center of a political and legal storm. His lawyers stated on Tuesday that he intends to plead not guilty to federal gun charges recently levied against him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-charges&quot;&gt;The Charges&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These charges, emerging from Special Counsel David Weiss, accuse Biden of:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Making a false statement during the purchase of a firearm&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Providing an inaccurate statement linked to information that federal firearms dealers are mandated to keep&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Being in possession of a firearm while being an unlawful user of or addicted to a controlled substance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though Hunter Biden’s legal team requests his initial court appearance be virtual, they emphasize that Biden isn’t asking for any special treatment. Since his initial plea deal crumbled earlier this year, Biden has complied with all legal conditions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;past-controversies&quot;&gt;Past Controversies&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This isn’t the first time Hunter Biden has faced legal complications. In a previously reported incident from 2018, a gun owned by Hunter was found discarded in a trash can outside a Delaware market. This gun was reportedly thrown away by Hallie Biden, widow of President Biden’s late son, Beau. Notably, Hunter had been romantically linked with Hallie at the time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fox News also revealed that Hunter had answered “no” on a firearm transaction report when queried if he was an “unlawful user of, or addicted to, marijuana or any depressant, stimulant, narcotic drug, or any other controlled substance.” However, it’s essential to recall that Hunter was dismissed from the Navy in 2014 after testing positive for cocaine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-political-storm&quot;&gt;A Political Storm?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hunter’s attorney, Abbe Lowell, stated that this gun-related case poses a greater threat to the justice system than to public safety, hinting at political motivations behind the charges. Lowell declared, “Hunter Biden possessing an unloaded gun for 11 days was not a threat to public safety, but a prosecutor bending to political pressure presents a grave threat to our system of justice.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the legal proceedings unfold, the public and media outlets are keenly observing the case, eager to understand its implications not just for Hunter Biden, but also for the Biden administration as a whole.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Hunter Biden, son of U.S. President Joe Biden, has recently been caught in the center of a political and legal storm. His lawyers stated on Tuesday that he intends to plead not guilty to federal gun charges recently levied against him. The Charges These charges, emerging from Special Counsel David Weiss, accuse Biden of: Making a false statement during the purchase of a firearm Providing an inaccurate statement linked to information that federal firearms dealers are mandated to keep Being in possession of a firearm while being an unlawful user of or addicted to a controlled substance. Though Hunter Biden’s legal team requests his initial court appearance be virtual, they emphasize that Biden isn’t asking for any special treatment. Since his initial plea deal crumbled earlier this year, Biden has complied with all legal conditions. Past Controversies This isn’t the first time Hunter Biden has faced legal complications. In a previously reported incident from 2018, a gun owned by Hunter was found discarded in a trash can outside a Delaware market. This gun was reportedly thrown away by Hallie Biden, widow of President Biden’s late son, Beau. Notably, Hunter had been romantically linked with Hallie at the time. Fox News also revealed that Hunter had answered “no” on a firearm transaction report when queried if he was an “unlawful user of, or addicted to, marijuana or any depressant, stimulant, narcotic drug, or any other controlled substance.” However, it’s essential to recall that Hunter was dismissed from the Navy in 2014 after testing positive for cocaine. A Political Storm? Hunter’s attorney, Abbe Lowell, stated that this gun-related case poses a greater threat to the justice system than to public safety, hinting at political motivations behind the charges. Lowell declared, “Hunter Biden possessing an unloaded gun for 11 days was not a threat to public safety, but a prosecutor bending to political pressure presents a grave threat to our system of justice.” While the legal proceedings unfold, the public and media outlets are keenly observing the case, eager to understand its implications not just for Hunter Biden, but also for the Biden administration as a whole.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Migrant Released by Biden Administration Arrested for Texas Murder</title><link href="/news/2023/09/20/Biden-Release-Texas/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Migrant Released by Biden Administration Arrested for Texas Murder" /><published>2023-09-20T15:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-20T15:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/20/Biden-Release-Texas</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/20/Biden-Release-Texas/">&lt;p&gt;Recent events in Eagle Pass, Texas, are sparking intense debates on border security and migrant release policies. Roberto Emilio Vasquez-Santamaria, a 64-year-old Peruvian migrant who was released by the Biden administration to pursue an asylum claim, is now the primary suspect in a murder case. The victim, a 40-year-old man from Houston, was found beaten to death in a backyard in the Loma Bonita neighborhood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maverick County Sheriff, Tom Schmerber, revealed the disturbing details of the crime scene on Cotorra Street and Progresso Avenue. The chilling incident unfolded on a Monday morning, around 9:30 a.m. While the Sheriff held back from divulging extensive details due to the ongoing investigation, other sources in law enforcement indicated that the property where the crime took place had previous ties to migrant smuggling activities. The exact motive behind the tragic event remains shrouded in mystery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vasquez-Santamaria’s journey to this point is a winding one. After crossing the Rio Grande, he was apprehended by the Border Patrol in Eagle Pass. Rather than being detained, he was processed and then released to a non-governmental shelter by the Biden administration’s directives. Making a choice to remain in the Eagle Pass area, he now finds himself incarcerated in the Maverick County Jail on murder charges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The situation in Eagle Pass grows more complex by the day. The town is currently grappling with a remarkable influx of migrants. On the day of Vasquez-Santamaria’s arrest alone, the Border Patrol apprehended over 1,500 migrants, primarily from Venezuela.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the investigation still in progress under Maverick County Sheriff Schmerber’s guidance, this event stands as a stark reminder of the intricate challenges border towns are confronting, further magnifying the ongoing debate about immigration and national security policies.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Recent events in Eagle Pass, Texas, are sparking intense debates on border security and migrant release policies. Roberto Emilio Vasquez-Santamaria, a 64-year-old Peruvian migrant who was released by the Biden administration to pursue an asylum claim, is now the primary suspect in a murder case. The victim, a 40-year-old man from Houston, was found beaten to death in a backyard in the Loma Bonita neighborhood. Maverick County Sheriff, Tom Schmerber, revealed the disturbing details of the crime scene on Cotorra Street and Progresso Avenue. The chilling incident unfolded on a Monday morning, around 9:30 a.m. While the Sheriff held back from divulging extensive details due to the ongoing investigation, other sources in law enforcement indicated that the property where the crime took place had previous ties to migrant smuggling activities. The exact motive behind the tragic event remains shrouded in mystery. Vasquez-Santamaria’s journey to this point is a winding one. After crossing the Rio Grande, he was apprehended by the Border Patrol in Eagle Pass. Rather than being detained, he was processed and then released to a non-governmental shelter by the Biden administration’s directives. Making a choice to remain in the Eagle Pass area, he now finds himself incarcerated in the Maverick County Jail on murder charges. The situation in Eagle Pass grows more complex by the day. The town is currently grappling with a remarkable influx of migrants. On the day of Vasquez-Santamaria’s arrest alone, the Border Patrol apprehended over 1,500 migrants, primarily from Venezuela. With the investigation still in progress under Maverick County Sheriff Schmerber’s guidance, this event stands as a stark reminder of the intricate challenges border towns are confronting, further magnifying the ongoing debate about immigration and national security policies.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Innovative or Controversial? - AI Chatbot Assists with Abortion Information</title><link href="/news/2023/09/20/AI-Abortion-Chatbot/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Innovative or Controversial? - AI Chatbot Assists with Abortion Information" /><published>2023-09-20T14:02:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-20T14:02:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/20/AI-Abortion-Chatbot</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/20/AI-Abortion-Chatbot/">&lt;p&gt;In a tech-meets-healthcare development, a new AI chatbot named “Charley, The Abortion Chatbot” is designed to guide pregnant women and teens towards abortion services. Developed by Cecile Richards and Tom Subak, two former officials from Planned Parenthood, the chatbot aims to offer private and precise information about abortion, but not without its share of criticisms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Upon visiting the National Women’s Health Network website, users are greeted by Charley saying, “Hi, my name’s Charley. I can help you get an abortion. Let’s get started.” The platform ensures user privacy, requesting only the date of the user’s last menstrual cycle and their state of residence. In its guidance, it covers topics like nearest abortion providers, how minors can seek an abortion without parental consent, and details about mail-order abortion drugs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, not everyone views Charley as a helpful tool. E.V. Osment, the vice president of SBA Pro-Life America, expressed concerns to the Washington Examiner, stating that such platforms could endanger lives and potentially promote illegal activities. A run-through of Charley by the Examiner revealed that it provided out-of-state options with fewer restrictions for users based in Virginia. For Mississippi users, the chatbot even suggested leaving the country or heading to Puerto Rico, a U.S. territory where passports aren’t needed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Co-founders Richards and Subak envision Charley being integrated into various medical and abortion clinic websites across the nation. Nicole Cushman, the content manager for Charley, shed light on their motivation: “Our research showed that people were turning primarily to Google for information about abortion options in the post-Roe landscape and that it was very challenging for abortion seekers to connect to available options.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The rise of Charley underscores a growing intersection of technology and healthcare, with the ongoing debate around abortion only intensifying the scrutiny of such platforms. As with many tools of this nature, the line between empowerment and controversy remains thin.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a tech-meets-healthcare development, a new AI chatbot named “Charley, The Abortion Chatbot” is designed to guide pregnant women and teens towards abortion services. Developed by Cecile Richards and Tom Subak, two former officials from Planned Parenthood, the chatbot aims to offer private and precise information about abortion, but not without its share of criticisms. Upon visiting the National Women’s Health Network website, users are greeted by Charley saying, “Hi, my name’s Charley. I can help you get an abortion. Let’s get started.” The platform ensures user privacy, requesting only the date of the user’s last menstrual cycle and their state of residence. In its guidance, it covers topics like nearest abortion providers, how minors can seek an abortion without parental consent, and details about mail-order abortion drugs. However, not everyone views Charley as a helpful tool. E.V. Osment, the vice president of SBA Pro-Life America, expressed concerns to the Washington Examiner, stating that such platforms could endanger lives and potentially promote illegal activities. A run-through of Charley by the Examiner revealed that it provided out-of-state options with fewer restrictions for users based in Virginia. For Mississippi users, the chatbot even suggested leaving the country or heading to Puerto Rico, a U.S. territory where passports aren’t needed. Co-founders Richards and Subak envision Charley being integrated into various medical and abortion clinic websites across the nation. Nicole Cushman, the content manager for Charley, shed light on their motivation: “Our research showed that people were turning primarily to Google for information about abortion options in the post-Roe landscape and that it was very challenging for abortion seekers to connect to available options.” The rise of Charley underscores a growing intersection of technology and healthcare, with the ongoing debate around abortion only intensifying the scrutiny of such platforms. As with many tools of this nature, the line between empowerment and controversy remains thin.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Vanna White Secures Her Spot - Ryan Seacrest Set to Spin the “Wheel”</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/20/Wheel-of-Fortune/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Vanna White Secures Her Spot - Ryan Seacrest Set to Spin the “Wheel”" /><published>2023-09-20T13:09:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-20T13:09:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/20/Wheel-of-Fortune</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/20/Wheel-of-Fortune/">&lt;p&gt;Vanna White is not leaving her letters just yet! She has renewed her contract with “Wheel of Fortune” for another two years. This extension ensures fans will see her light up the screen until the 2025-26 season.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, Pat Sajak, who’s been charming us with his hosting prowess since 1981, is set to retire in 2024. With his departure, Ryan Seacrest will step in to fill those big shoes, starting from fall 2024. Seacrest, who’s made waves co-hosting “Live with Kelly and Ryan,” expressed his disbelief and excitement about joining this legacy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sajak and White, a duo that has become synonymous with “Wheel of Fortune,” began their journey together in 1982. As Season 41 unfolds, viewers are in for a treat as they’ll see Maggie Sajak, Pat’s daughter, featuring the “Word of the Day” on her European tour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maggie is also upping the ante for the show’s fans. As the show’s Social Media Correspondent, she’s rolling out the “Fan Fridays” sweepstakes, giving fans opportunities to win exciting prizes every week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For Seacrest, joining “Wheel of Fortune” is like a dream come true. He recently shared his enthusiasm and gratitude, mentioning how he looked up to Sajak and is eagerly waiting to meet the contestants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All these new shifts and updates spell out an exciting future for “Wheel of Fortune.” As the show gears up for its next chapter, fans worldwide are ready and waiting to spin into the new era!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Vanna White is not leaving her letters just yet! She has renewed her contract with “Wheel of Fortune” for another two years. This extension ensures fans will see her light up the screen until the 2025-26 season. Meanwhile, Pat Sajak, who’s been charming us with his hosting prowess since 1981, is set to retire in 2024. With his departure, Ryan Seacrest will step in to fill those big shoes, starting from fall 2024. Seacrest, who’s made waves co-hosting “Live with Kelly and Ryan,” expressed his disbelief and excitement about joining this legacy. Sajak and White, a duo that has become synonymous with “Wheel of Fortune,” began their journey together in 1982. As Season 41 unfolds, viewers are in for a treat as they’ll see Maggie Sajak, Pat’s daughter, featuring the “Word of the Day” on her European tour. Maggie is also upping the ante for the show’s fans. As the show’s Social Media Correspondent, she’s rolling out the “Fan Fridays” sweepstakes, giving fans opportunities to win exciting prizes every week. For Seacrest, joining “Wheel of Fortune” is like a dream come true. He recently shared his enthusiasm and gratitude, mentioning how he looked up to Sajak and is eagerly waiting to meet the contestants. All these new shifts and updates spell out an exciting future for “Wheel of Fortune.” As the show gears up for its next chapter, fans worldwide are ready and waiting to spin into the new era!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Biden Under Fire - Voters See Evidence in Impeachment Inquiry</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/20/Biden-Impeachment-Evidence/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Biden Under Fire - Voters See Evidence in Impeachment Inquiry" /><published>2023-09-20T12:03:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-20T12:03:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/20/Biden-Impeachment-Evidence</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/20/Biden-Impeachment-Evidence/">&lt;p&gt;A recent poll has unveiled a startling revelation regarding the ongoing impeachment inquiry into President Joe Biden. Contrary to the assertions of several Democrats and media outlets that there’s no basis for the inquiry, a plurality of voters believe there’s indeed evidence pointing to Biden’s wrongdoing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Public Opinion Speaks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a Morning Consult poll released on Tuesday, a plurality of respondents (43-41 percent) stated that the main thrust behind the impeachment inquiry stems from genuine evidence of Biden’s transgressions. This sentiment isn’t limited to any one demographic; a plurality of independent voters (40-39 percent) share the same viewpoint. Notably, a significant 74 percent of Republican voters agree with the rationale behind the impeachment inquiry, even if just 16 percent of Democrats feel the same way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The findings seem to showcase a predominant narrative – that the GOP is successfully making a case for Biden’s impeachment in the court of public opinion. Statements from the White House, numerous Democrats, and media allies have been outright dismissive of the inquiry, emphasizing a lack of evidence. Yet, House Republicans have spotlighted various alleged pieces of evidence, including photos, videos, texts, and testimonies, implicating Biden in the controversy surrounding his family’s business dealings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Broader Consensus on Impeachment Inquiry&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further dissecting the poll’s data reveals another telling aspect: nearly half of the surveyed voters (48 percent) are in favor of the impeachment inquiry. Meanwhile, 42 percent are against it, and 10 percent remain on the fence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you break it down:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;47 percent of independent voters back the inquiry.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;36 percent of Democrats are in support.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A mere 31 percent of Republicans oppose the inquiry.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The findings indicate a general consensus, even among Democrats, that the impeachment inquiry is at the very least warranted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Implications for Biden and the Democrats&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Morning Consult’s analysis suggests that these findings should ring alarm bells for Biden and the Democratic party. For comparison, Democrats were less resistant to the idea of impeaching President Donald Trump in 2019 regarding his approach to Ukraine. Almost half of the Democrats believe either Biden committed an impeachable offense or he has demonstrated unfitness to serve.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Additionally, the ongoing saga seems to be benefiting Kevin McCarthy, the House speaker, who, despite facing challenges within the GOP, is now in the limelight due to the impeachment proceedings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In summary, the perception of Biden’s impeachment inquiry underscores the prevailing sentiment among voters. While many within the media and the Democratic party may downplay the legitimacy of the inquiry, a significant portion of the electorate feels otherwise. As the proceedings unfold, it remains to be seen how this perception might shape Biden’s presidency and the broader political landscape.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">A recent poll has unveiled a startling revelation regarding the ongoing impeachment inquiry into President Joe Biden. Contrary to the assertions of several Democrats and media outlets that there’s no basis for the inquiry, a plurality of voters believe there’s indeed evidence pointing to Biden’s wrongdoing. Public Opinion Speaks In a Morning Consult poll released on Tuesday, a plurality of respondents (43-41 percent) stated that the main thrust behind the impeachment inquiry stems from genuine evidence of Biden’s transgressions. This sentiment isn’t limited to any one demographic; a plurality of independent voters (40-39 percent) share the same viewpoint. Notably, a significant 74 percent of Republican voters agree with the rationale behind the impeachment inquiry, even if just 16 percent of Democrats feel the same way. The findings seem to showcase a predominant narrative – that the GOP is successfully making a case for Biden’s impeachment in the court of public opinion. Statements from the White House, numerous Democrats, and media allies have been outright dismissive of the inquiry, emphasizing a lack of evidence. Yet, House Republicans have spotlighted various alleged pieces of evidence, including photos, videos, texts, and testimonies, implicating Biden in the controversy surrounding his family’s business dealings. Broader Consensus on Impeachment Inquiry Further dissecting the poll’s data reveals another telling aspect: nearly half of the surveyed voters (48 percent) are in favor of the impeachment inquiry. Meanwhile, 42 percent are against it, and 10 percent remain on the fence. When you break it down: 47 percent of independent voters back the inquiry. 36 percent of Democrats are in support. A mere 31 percent of Republicans oppose the inquiry. The findings indicate a general consensus, even among Democrats, that the impeachment inquiry is at the very least warranted. Implications for Biden and the Democrats Morning Consult’s analysis suggests that these findings should ring alarm bells for Biden and the Democratic party. For comparison, Democrats were less resistant to the idea of impeaching President Donald Trump in 2019 regarding his approach to Ukraine. Almost half of the Democrats believe either Biden committed an impeachable offense or he has demonstrated unfitness to serve. Additionally, the ongoing saga seems to be benefiting Kevin McCarthy, the House speaker, who, despite facing challenges within the GOP, is now in the limelight due to the impeachment proceedings. In summary, the perception of Biden’s impeachment inquiry underscores the prevailing sentiment among voters. While many within the media and the Democratic party may downplay the legitimacy of the inquiry, a significant portion of the electorate feels otherwise. As the proceedings unfold, it remains to be seen how this perception might shape Biden’s presidency and the broader political landscape.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Sudden Loss - Temple University’s Acting President Dies on Stage</title><link href="/news/2023/09/20/Temple-University-Tragedy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sudden Loss - Temple University’s Acting President Dies on Stage" /><published>2023-09-20T11:05:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-20T11:05:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/20/Temple-University-Tragedy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/20/Temple-University-Tragedy/">&lt;p&gt;In a deeply tragic turn of events, JoAnne A. Epps, the acting president of Temple University, collapsed on stage during a memorial service on Tuesday. She was immediately rushed to the hospital but was sadly pronounced dead upon arrival.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Epps, 72, was attending a service in honor of Charles L. Blockson, a significant figure associated with the Blockson Collection at the university. The unexpected incident has sent shockwaves through the Temple University community and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a heartfelt statement released by the university, the extent of her impact was clear. “President Epps was a devoted servant and friend who represented the best parts of Temple. She spent nearly 40 years of her life serving this university, and her loss will reverberate through the community for years to come.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The exact cause of her demise has not been disclosed yet. Temple University Provost, Gregory Mandel, visibly shaken by the event, commented on Epps, saying, “We are all in deep grief and at a loss for words. To know Joanne is to be her friend. She was one of the most remarkably compassionate and caring individuals I’ve ever known.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Epps had a longstanding and influential role within Temple University. Prior to her position as acting president, she served as the dean of the university’s law school and later as provost. Her rise to the role of acting president came in the wake of the resignation of Jason Wingard, Temple’s first Black president. Reflecting on her journey, Epps had shared with local news, “I would never have imagined even becoming a professor at Temple, let alone being in this position.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pennsylvania’s Governor, Josh Shapiro, paid his respects by referring to Epps as a “powerful force and constant ambassador for Temple University for nearly four decades.” Expressing his grief on X (previously known as Twitter), he mentioned how this loss deeply impacts not just the university, but the entire city of Philadelphia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As acting president, Epps had been actively addressing vital concerns, notably focusing on the university’s enrollment and challenges tied to rising crime near the campus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As Temple University, Philadelphia, and the broader academic community grapple with this tragic loss, the legacy and contributions of JoAnne A. Epps will undoubtedly be remembered and cherished.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a deeply tragic turn of events, JoAnne A. Epps, the acting president of Temple University, collapsed on stage during a memorial service on Tuesday. She was immediately rushed to the hospital but was sadly pronounced dead upon arrival. Epps, 72, was attending a service in honor of Charles L. Blockson, a significant figure associated with the Blockson Collection at the university. The unexpected incident has sent shockwaves through the Temple University community and beyond. In a heartfelt statement released by the university, the extent of her impact was clear. “President Epps was a devoted servant and friend who represented the best parts of Temple. She spent nearly 40 years of her life serving this university, and her loss will reverberate through the community for years to come.” The exact cause of her demise has not been disclosed yet. Temple University Provost, Gregory Mandel, visibly shaken by the event, commented on Epps, saying, “We are all in deep grief and at a loss for words. To know Joanne is to be her friend. She was one of the most remarkably compassionate and caring individuals I’ve ever known.” Epps had a longstanding and influential role within Temple University. Prior to her position as acting president, she served as the dean of the university’s law school and later as provost. Her rise to the role of acting president came in the wake of the resignation of Jason Wingard, Temple’s first Black president. Reflecting on her journey, Epps had shared with local news, “I would never have imagined even becoming a professor at Temple, let alone being in this position.” Pennsylvania’s Governor, Josh Shapiro, paid his respects by referring to Epps as a “powerful force and constant ambassador for Temple University for nearly four decades.” Expressing his grief on X (previously known as Twitter), he mentioned how this loss deeply impacts not just the university, but the entire city of Philadelphia. As acting president, Epps had been actively addressing vital concerns, notably focusing on the university’s enrollment and challenges tied to rising crime near the campus. As Temple University, Philadelphia, and the broader academic community grapple with this tragic loss, the legacy and contributions of JoAnne A. Epps will undoubtedly be remembered and cherished.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Seven GOP Contenders Set Eyes on 2nd Debate Stage</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/20/GOP-Debate-Candidates/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Seven GOP Contenders Set Eyes on 2nd Debate Stage" /><published>2023-09-20T10:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-20T10:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/20/GOP-Debate-Candidates</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/20/GOP-Debate-Candidates/">&lt;p&gt;As the Republican primaries heat up, seven GOP candidates have apparently secured their spots for the second presidential debate, slated for September 27. However, all eyes are on former President Donald Trump, who’s choosing to skip the event in favor of addressing striking autoworkers in Michigan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who’s In and Who’s Out?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The debate, hosted at the Ronald Reagan Presidential Library in Simi Valley, California, will likely include a mix of familiar faces and emerging leaders:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Gov. Ron DeSantis (R-FL)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Entrepreneur Vivek Ramaswamy&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Former Gov. Nikki Haley (R-SC)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Former Vice President Mike Pence&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sen. Tim Scott (R-SC)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Former Gov. Chris Christie (R-NJ)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to CBS News politics reporter Aaron Navarro, these candidates have likely satisfied the Republican National Committee’s updated polling and donor prerequisites. However, Gov. Doug Burgum (R-ND) and former Gov. Asa Hutchinson (R-AR), both participants in the first debate, seem to be trailing behind in their bid to join the next round.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Debate Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Candidates looking to step onto the debate stage need to hit certain benchmarks:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Secure three percent or more in two national polls&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Alternatively, obtain at least three percent in one national poll and three percent in two of the initial four early voting states&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All polls considered must be dated August 1 or later. Additionally, hopefuls must also rally a total of 50,000 unique donors, a 10,000 donor increase from the first debate’s requirements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trump’s Counter-Move&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While these candidates are gearing up for a lively debate, Trump is charting his own course. Sources have confirmed that during the debate, Trump plans to engage with members of the United Auto Workers in Detroit, Michigan, who are currently striking against major automakers like General Motors, Ford, and Stellantis. The New York Times has indicated that Trump is set to give a “prime-time speech” to these union members.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This isn’t the first time Trump has opted for a counter-programming strategy. During the first debate, he rivaled the event with a gripping 45-minute interview with Tucker Carlson, which quickly went viral.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the third debate expected in Miami, Florida, in November, it’ll be intriguing to see how the political strategies evolve and what surprises lie ahead in this gripping election season.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">As the Republican primaries heat up, seven GOP candidates have apparently secured their spots for the second presidential debate, slated for September 27. However, all eyes are on former President Donald Trump, who’s choosing to skip the event in favor of addressing striking autoworkers in Michigan. Who’s In and Who’s Out? The debate, hosted at the Ronald Reagan Presidential Library in Simi Valley, California, will likely include a mix of familiar faces and emerging leaders: Gov. Ron DeSantis (R-FL) Entrepreneur Vivek Ramaswamy Former Gov. Nikki Haley (R-SC) Former Vice President Mike Pence Sen. Tim Scott (R-SC) Former Gov. Chris Christie (R-NJ) According to CBS News politics reporter Aaron Navarro, these candidates have likely satisfied the Republican National Committee’s updated polling and donor prerequisites. However, Gov. Doug Burgum (R-ND) and former Gov. Asa Hutchinson (R-AR), both participants in the first debate, seem to be trailing behind in their bid to join the next round. The Debate Requirements Candidates looking to step onto the debate stage need to hit certain benchmarks: Secure three percent or more in two national polls Alternatively, obtain at least three percent in one national poll and three percent in two of the initial four early voting states All polls considered must be dated August 1 or later. Additionally, hopefuls must also rally a total of 50,000 unique donors, a 10,000 donor increase from the first debate’s requirements. Trump’s Counter-Move While these candidates are gearing up for a lively debate, Trump is charting his own course. Sources have confirmed that during the debate, Trump plans to engage with members of the United Auto Workers in Detroit, Michigan, who are currently striking against major automakers like General Motors, Ford, and Stellantis. The New York Times has indicated that Trump is set to give a “prime-time speech” to these union members. This isn’t the first time Trump has opted for a counter-programming strategy. During the first debate, he rivaled the event with a gripping 45-minute interview with Tucker Carlson, which quickly went viral. With the third debate expected in Miami, Florida, in November, it’ll be intriguing to see how the political strategies evolve and what surprises lie ahead in this gripping election season.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A Wrong Turn - Arkansas Trooper Retires After Dramatic Mistake</title><link href="/news/2023/09/20/Arkansas-Trooper-Controversy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Wrong Turn - Arkansas Trooper Retires After Dramatic Mistake" /><published>2023-09-20T09:07:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-20T09:07:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/20/Arkansas-Trooper-Controversy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/20/Arkansas-Trooper-Controversy/">&lt;p&gt;While high-speed pursuits often make for thrilling movie scenes, real-life chases can have dire consequences - especially when mistakes are made. Arkansas recently witnessed such an incident when a state trooper mistakenly targeted the wrong vehicle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On a regular Sunday evening on Interstate 40, an Arkansas State Trooper was in hot pursuit of two vehicles reportedly speeding over 100 mph. One of these was a white sedan. In the midst of this chase, Trooper Cpl. Thomas Hubbard, possibly overwhelmed by the speed and intensity, misidentified a completely unrelated white sedan as the suspect’s car.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Without a moment’s hesitation, Hubbard executed a PIT (precision immobilization technique) maneuver on the innocent vehicle. For those unfamiliar, a PIT maneuver is a tactic used by police to force a fleeing car to lose control and stop. This involves a controlled hit by the police vehicle to the side near a rear wheel of the pursued vehicle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The unsuspecting white sedan, taken off guard, was sent spiraling to the shoulder of the interstate. Dashcam footage vividly captured this entire sequence: the rapid chase, the sedan flashing its brakes, and the subsequent collision.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But what about the occupants of the car? Miraculously, both the driver and the passenger emerged from the crash unscathed. They both declined medical treatment, demonstrating the resilience humans sometimes show in the face of sudden adversity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The aftermath of the incident has led to swift action. Hubbard has since submitted his retirement and remains off duty. The Arkansas State Police initiated an immediate internal review.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet, this isn’t the first time the Arkansas State Police have found themselves under scrutiny for PIT maneuvers. Back in 2021, a woman took legal action against another trooper who “negligently performed” a PIT maneuver, causing her car to overturn at 60 mph. Further investigations by local news revealed that between January 2017 and December 2020, the technique was used a staggering 306 times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But with such a powerful tactic comes grave responsibility. The Washington Post reported that since 2016, at least 30 people have lost their lives due to PIT maneuvers. Eighteen of these were for minor traffic violations, such as speeding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the wake of such statistics and recent incidents, it begs the question: Is it time for a thorough review and possible revision of this pursuit technique?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">While high-speed pursuits often make for thrilling movie scenes, real-life chases can have dire consequences - especially when mistakes are made. Arkansas recently witnessed such an incident when a state trooper mistakenly targeted the wrong vehicle. On a regular Sunday evening on Interstate 40, an Arkansas State Trooper was in hot pursuit of two vehicles reportedly speeding over 100 mph. One of these was a white sedan. In the midst of this chase, Trooper Cpl. Thomas Hubbard, possibly overwhelmed by the speed and intensity, misidentified a completely unrelated white sedan as the suspect’s car. Without a moment’s hesitation, Hubbard executed a PIT (precision immobilization technique) maneuver on the innocent vehicle. For those unfamiliar, a PIT maneuver is a tactic used by police to force a fleeing car to lose control and stop. This involves a controlled hit by the police vehicle to the side near a rear wheel of the pursued vehicle. The unsuspecting white sedan, taken off guard, was sent spiraling to the shoulder of the interstate. Dashcam footage vividly captured this entire sequence: the rapid chase, the sedan flashing its brakes, and the subsequent collision. But what about the occupants of the car? Miraculously, both the driver and the passenger emerged from the crash unscathed. They both declined medical treatment, demonstrating the resilience humans sometimes show in the face of sudden adversity. The aftermath of the incident has led to swift action. Hubbard has since submitted his retirement and remains off duty. The Arkansas State Police initiated an immediate internal review. Yet, this isn’t the first time the Arkansas State Police have found themselves under scrutiny for PIT maneuvers. Back in 2021, a woman took legal action against another trooper who “negligently performed” a PIT maneuver, causing her car to overturn at 60 mph. Further investigations by local news revealed that between January 2017 and December 2020, the technique was used a staggering 306 times. But with such a powerful tactic comes grave responsibility. The Washington Post reported that since 2016, at least 30 people have lost their lives due to PIT maneuvers. Eighteen of these were for minor traffic violations, such as speeding. In the wake of such statistics and recent incidents, it begs the question: Is it time for a thorough review and possible revision of this pursuit technique?</summary></entry></feed>