<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-09-19T09:18:56-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/09/19/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-09-19T09:18:56-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-19T09:18:56-04:00</updated><id>/2023/09/19/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/19/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Halle Berry Calls Out Drake - Unauthorized Use of Her Image</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/19/Halle-Berry-Drake-Dispute/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Halle Berry Calls Out Drake - Unauthorized Use of Her Image" /><published>2023-09-19T09:01:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-19T09:01:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/19/Halle-Berry-Drake-Dispute</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/19/Halle-Berry-Drake-Dispute/">&lt;p&gt;It seems like Catwoman’s not thrilled this time around.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a recent Instagram clash, Hollywood actress Halle Berry voiced her disapproval when rapper Drake and singer SZA used a 2012 photograph of her to promote their fresh track “Slime You Out.” What’s the catch? They did it without asking her first.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-slimy-situation&quot;&gt;The Slimy Situation&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The controversial photo features Berry at the 2012 Nickelodeon Kids’ Choice Awards, where she is seen covered from head to toe in the iconic green slime. As it is customary at the Kids’ Choice Awards, celebrities often end up covered in this playful goop. But for Berry, the problem wasn’t the slime – it was its unexpected and unauthorized use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2023/09/672/378/halle-berry-drake.jpg?ve=1&amp;amp;tl=1&quot; alt=&quot;Halle Berry and Drake&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Halle Berry and Drake, both successful in their respective industries. Photo by Victor VIRGILE/Cole Burston/Getty Images.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earlier this week, both Drake and SZA gave their fans a sneak peek of the song on their Instagram accounts, where they shared the slimed snapshot of Berry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Berry didn’t remain silent. On her own Instagram, she shared a mysterious message: “SOMETIMES YOU HAVE TO BE THE BIGGER GUY…EVEN IF YOU’RE A WOMAN!” Diving into the comments section, Berry further revealed her feelings, saying, “Didn’t get my permission,” and “That’s not cool I thought better of him!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She further emphasized, “When people you admire disappoint you you have to be the bigger person and move on!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-silence-from-the-stars&quot;&gt;The Silence from the Stars&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the controversy, representatives for all three – Berry, Drake, and SZA – haven’t made any public statements addressing the situation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2023/09/672/378/drake-sza.jpg?ve=1&amp;amp;tl=1&quot; alt=&quot;Drake and SZA performing&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Drake and SZA, the artists behind the song “Slime You Out.” Photo by Prince Williams/Andrew Chin/Getty Images.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The song in the midst of this dispute, “Slime You Out,” was launched on September 15. Interestingly, the artwork for the song will also serve as the cover for Drake’s upcoming album, “For All The Dogs.” The rapper has also recently shared that his fans will have to wait a bit longer for his eighth studio album, now set to drop on October 6.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the entertainment world watches, only time will tell how this slimy situation unfolds.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">It seems like Catwoman’s not thrilled this time around. In a recent Instagram clash, Hollywood actress Halle Berry voiced her disapproval when rapper Drake and singer SZA used a 2012 photograph of her to promote their fresh track “Slime You Out.” What’s the catch? They did it without asking her first. The Slimy Situation The controversial photo features Berry at the 2012 Nickelodeon Kids’ Choice Awards, where she is seen covered from head to toe in the iconic green slime. As it is customary at the Kids’ Choice Awards, celebrities often end up covered in this playful goop. But for Berry, the problem wasn’t the slime – it was its unexpected and unauthorized use. Halle Berry and Drake, both successful in their respective industries. Photo by Victor VIRGILE/Cole Burston/Getty Images. Earlier this week, both Drake and SZA gave their fans a sneak peek of the song on their Instagram accounts, where they shared the slimed snapshot of Berry. Berry didn’t remain silent. On her own Instagram, she shared a mysterious message: “SOMETIMES YOU HAVE TO BE THE BIGGER GUY…EVEN IF YOU’RE A WOMAN!” Diving into the comments section, Berry further revealed her feelings, saying, “Didn’t get my permission,” and “That’s not cool I thought better of him!” She further emphasized, “When people you admire disappoint you you have to be the bigger person and move on!” The Silence from the Stars Despite the controversy, representatives for all three – Berry, Drake, and SZA – haven’t made any public statements addressing the situation. Drake and SZA, the artists behind the song “Slime You Out.” Photo by Prince Williams/Andrew Chin/Getty Images. The song in the midst of this dispute, “Slime You Out,” was launched on September 15. Interestingly, the artwork for the song will also serve as the cover for Drake’s upcoming album, “For All The Dogs.” The rapper has also recently shared that his fans will have to wait a bit longer for his eighth studio album, now set to drop on October 6. As the entertainment world watches, only time will tell how this slimy situation unfolds.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Shockwave at the Border - Former CBP Officer Jailed for Cocaine Conspiracy</title><link href="/news/2023/09/19/Cocaine-Trafficking/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Shockwave at the Border - Former CBP Officer Jailed for Cocaine Conspiracy" /><published>2023-09-19T08:05:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-19T08:05:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/19/Cocaine-Trafficking</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/19/Cocaine-Trafficking/">&lt;p&gt;In a stunning revelation, a former officer of the U.S. Customs and Border Protection (CBP) is sentenced to over a decade in prison for his involvement in a drug smuggling scheme. This incident underscores the complex challenges at the U.S. border.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-swift-verdict&quot;&gt;A Swift Verdict&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Juan Posas Jr., 51, stood before U.S. District Judge Micaela Alvarez last week. The outcome? A hefty sentence of 162 months in prison followed by five years of closely watched release. This decision followed a brief trial held on June 27, where a jury took merely two hours to declare Posas guilty of plotting to traffic cocaine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-incident&quot;&gt;The Incident&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On June 6, 2022, Posas met up with Alexis Soria Soria, a 25-year-old living unlawfully in the U.S., in the parking lot of a Home Depot in Weslaco, Texas. There, Soria handed over a box to Posas, which was later discovered to contain 20 kilograms of cocaine. The authorities also acquired recordings that captured the duo conversing about the drug deal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;U.S. Homeland Security Investigations had Posas under their radar for quite some time. They even managed to procure recorded phone calls, revealing Posas discussing drug deals for cash with other parties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, during his trial, Posas offered a surprising defense. He argued that he believed the box merely contained fruit, rather than the illicit drug.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-larger-picture&quot;&gt;The Larger Picture&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The arrest and subsequent sentencing of a former CBP officer expose vulnerabilities and raise pressing questions about the integrity of those tasked with safeguarding the nation’s borders. The Rio Grande Valley remains a hotspot for both drug and human trafficking activities. Posas’ case stands as a stark reminder of the ongoing battle against smuggling and the unexpected actors that can sometimes be found in its web.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a stunning revelation, a former officer of the U.S. Customs and Border Protection (CBP) is sentenced to over a decade in prison for his involvement in a drug smuggling scheme. This incident underscores the complex challenges at the U.S. border. A Swift Verdict Juan Posas Jr., 51, stood before U.S. District Judge Micaela Alvarez last week. The outcome? A hefty sentence of 162 months in prison followed by five years of closely watched release. This decision followed a brief trial held on June 27, where a jury took merely two hours to declare Posas guilty of plotting to traffic cocaine. The Incident On June 6, 2022, Posas met up with Alexis Soria Soria, a 25-year-old living unlawfully in the U.S., in the parking lot of a Home Depot in Weslaco, Texas. There, Soria handed over a box to Posas, which was later discovered to contain 20 kilograms of cocaine. The authorities also acquired recordings that captured the duo conversing about the drug deal. U.S. Homeland Security Investigations had Posas under their radar for quite some time. They even managed to procure recorded phone calls, revealing Posas discussing drug deals for cash with other parties. However, during his trial, Posas offered a surprising defense. He argued that he believed the box merely contained fruit, rather than the illicit drug. The Larger Picture The arrest and subsequent sentencing of a former CBP officer expose vulnerabilities and raise pressing questions about the integrity of those tasked with safeguarding the nation’s borders. The Rio Grande Valley remains a hotspot for both drug and human trafficking activities. Posas’ case stands as a stark reminder of the ongoing battle against smuggling and the unexpected actors that can sometimes be found in its web.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Biden’s Controversial 50-Year Energy Ban in New Mexico</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/19/Biden-Domestic-Energy-Ban/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Biden’s Controversial 50-Year Energy Ban in New Mexico" /><published>2023-09-19T07:02:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-19T07:02:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/19/Biden-Domestic-Energy-Ban</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/19/Biden-Domestic-Energy-Ban/">&lt;p&gt;The Biden administration recently unleashed a proposal to impose a 50-year ban on mining and oil drilling across thousands of acres in New Mexico, citing protection of wildlife, cultural resources, and Native American lands as reasons. But is this truly in the best interest of the American people and domestic energy production?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Shift from Energy Independence&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Located north of Albuquerque in Sandoval County, the affected area spans over 4,200 acres. If this proposal is greenlit, it will not only halt new mining claims and oil and gas development for up to five decades, but it also raises questions on the United States’ commitment to energy independence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interior Secretary Deb Haaland, who previously pushed for similar actions while in Congress, defended the move. “Today we’re responding to calls from Tribes, elected leaders, and community members who want to see these public lands protected,” she commented. Haaland emphasized the importance of these lands for their cultural significance and natural resources.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Real Cost of the Ban&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the protection of natural habitats and historical sites is important, it’s equally crucial to consider the country’s energy needs and the potential economic implications of such bans.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Based on data from the Bureau of Land Management (BLM), the region possesses a high potential for sand and gravel extraction, which plays a pivotal role in infrastructure projects like roads. By sidelining these resources, not only does the country lose out on valuable domestic energy resources, but there’s also a significant economic blow. The Congressional Budget Office reported a projected decrease of $2 million in federal revenue due to this land withdrawal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, as the Biden administration maneuvers to pivot the US away from fossil fuels and towards renewable energy, the tangible impact of these decisions on everyday Americans is profound. With restrictions on domestic energy production, the US could see increased dependence on foreign energy sources, leading to potential vulnerabilities in the nation’s energy security and higher costs for consumers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Question of Priorities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the intent to preserve cultural resources and protect Native American lands is commendable, it’s essential to strike a balance. As we have seen from past actions, including the reversal of Trump-era decisions related to fossil fuel pipelines, the current administration’s approach tends to prioritize global climate ambitions over domestic energy needs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given the importance of energy independence and the role of domestic resources in bolstering the US economy, it’s crucial to reassess the long-term implications of such bans. Finding a middle ground that caters to both environmental and energy concerns could be the way forward, ensuring a more stable future for the American people.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">The Biden administration recently unleashed a proposal to impose a 50-year ban on mining and oil drilling across thousands of acres in New Mexico, citing protection of wildlife, cultural resources, and Native American lands as reasons. But is this truly in the best interest of the American people and domestic energy production? A Shift from Energy Independence Located north of Albuquerque in Sandoval County, the affected area spans over 4,200 acres. If this proposal is greenlit, it will not only halt new mining claims and oil and gas development for up to five decades, but it also raises questions on the United States’ commitment to energy independence. Interior Secretary Deb Haaland, who previously pushed for similar actions while in Congress, defended the move. “Today we’re responding to calls from Tribes, elected leaders, and community members who want to see these public lands protected,” she commented. Haaland emphasized the importance of these lands for their cultural significance and natural resources. The Real Cost of the Ban While the protection of natural habitats and historical sites is important, it’s equally crucial to consider the country’s energy needs and the potential economic implications of such bans. Based on data from the Bureau of Land Management (BLM), the region possesses a high potential for sand and gravel extraction, which plays a pivotal role in infrastructure projects like roads. By sidelining these resources, not only does the country lose out on valuable domestic energy resources, but there’s also a significant economic blow. The Congressional Budget Office reported a projected decrease of $2 million in federal revenue due to this land withdrawal. Furthermore, as the Biden administration maneuvers to pivot the US away from fossil fuels and towards renewable energy, the tangible impact of these decisions on everyday Americans is profound. With restrictions on domestic energy production, the US could see increased dependence on foreign energy sources, leading to potential vulnerabilities in the nation’s energy security and higher costs for consumers. A Question of Priorities While the intent to preserve cultural resources and protect Native American lands is commendable, it’s essential to strike a balance. As we have seen from past actions, including the reversal of Trump-era decisions related to fossil fuel pipelines, the current administration’s approach tends to prioritize global climate ambitions over domestic energy needs. Given the importance of energy independence and the role of domestic resources in bolstering the US economy, it’s crucial to reassess the long-term implications of such bans. Finding a middle ground that caters to both environmental and energy concerns could be the way forward, ensuring a more stable future for the American people.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">GOP Challenges Exorbitant $24 Billion Ukraine Aid Request</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/19/GOP-Ukraine-Aid-Concerns/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="GOP Challenges Exorbitant $24 Billion Ukraine Aid Request" /><published>2023-09-19T06:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-19T06:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/19/GOP-Ukraine-Aid-Concerns</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/19/GOP-Ukraine-Aid-Concerns/">&lt;p&gt;As Ukrainian leader Volodymyr Zelensky gears up to lobby for further aid this Thursday, GOP members of the House are voicing valid concerns about the hefty $24 billion military and economic aid proposal championed by President Joe Biden.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A senior GOP figure has been forthright, indicating a significant lack of Republican support for such a sizable aid package. Their stance underscores a broader GOP viewpoint that emphasizes scrutinizing foreign aid, especially when domestic challenges are looming large.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Putting Americans First?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Richard Stern, the director of the Heritage Foundation’s budget center, underscored the weight of the proposed aid by putting it in relatable terms: the $24 billion aid equates to an alarming $1,100 per American household. To offer some perspective, a 2022 Federal Reserve study found that an unsettling 37% of Americans are ill-equipped to handle a sudden $400 emergency expense. This statistic, up from 32% just a year ago, sheds light on the financial strain many households are experiencing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The decision to allocate such extensive funds to Ukraine becomes even more jarring when considering Biden’s recent pledge to provide a one-time $700 relief payment to Maui fire survivors, which is notably less than the proposed per household aid amount for Ukraine. A recent CNN poll further backs the GOP’s concerns, revealing that 55% of Americans believe Congress should refrain from dispatching additional aid to Ukraine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GOP Voices Grow Louder&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One senior GOP lawmaker expressed skepticism about House Intelligence Committee Chairman Mike Turner’s (R-OH) remarks that Zelensky could sway reluctant Republicans. Dismissing it, the lawmaker humorously stated, “when Turner’s pet unicorn has offspring, I’d like to buy one of the colts,” before getting to the heart of the matter: “We do not have the votes in the Republican conference to do any Ukraine funding.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s also worth noting that while Ukraine seeks more financial assistance, there have been significant internal shakeups, with six of its deputy defense ministers recently being let go after the dismissal of Minister Oleksii Reznikov due to a corruption scandal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In light of such critical domestic financial challenges and the need for accountability in foreign nations seeking assistance, the GOP’s cautious approach to Ukraine’s aid request resonates as both sensible and necessary.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">As Ukrainian leader Volodymyr Zelensky gears up to lobby for further aid this Thursday, GOP members of the House are voicing valid concerns about the hefty $24 billion military and economic aid proposal championed by President Joe Biden. A senior GOP figure has been forthright, indicating a significant lack of Republican support for such a sizable aid package. Their stance underscores a broader GOP viewpoint that emphasizes scrutinizing foreign aid, especially when domestic challenges are looming large. Putting Americans First? Richard Stern, the director of the Heritage Foundation’s budget center, underscored the weight of the proposed aid by putting it in relatable terms: the $24 billion aid equates to an alarming $1,100 per American household. To offer some perspective, a 2022 Federal Reserve study found that an unsettling 37% of Americans are ill-equipped to handle a sudden $400 emergency expense. This statistic, up from 32% just a year ago, sheds light on the financial strain many households are experiencing. The decision to allocate such extensive funds to Ukraine becomes even more jarring when considering Biden’s recent pledge to provide a one-time $700 relief payment to Maui fire survivors, which is notably less than the proposed per household aid amount for Ukraine. A recent CNN poll further backs the GOP’s concerns, revealing that 55% of Americans believe Congress should refrain from dispatching additional aid to Ukraine. GOP Voices Grow Louder One senior GOP lawmaker expressed skepticism about House Intelligence Committee Chairman Mike Turner’s (R-OH) remarks that Zelensky could sway reluctant Republicans. Dismissing it, the lawmaker humorously stated, “when Turner’s pet unicorn has offspring, I’d like to buy one of the colts,” before getting to the heart of the matter: “We do not have the votes in the Republican conference to do any Ukraine funding.” It’s also worth noting that while Ukraine seeks more financial assistance, there have been significant internal shakeups, with six of its deputy defense ministers recently being let go after the dismissal of Minister Oleksii Reznikov due to a corruption scandal. In light of such critical domestic financial challenges and the need for accountability in foreign nations seeking assistance, the GOP’s cautious approach to Ukraine’s aid request resonates as both sensible and necessary.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Shock in Shawnee - Pastor Accused of Attempted Family Murder and Arson</title><link href="/news/2023/09/18/Pastor-Fire-Incident/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Shock in Shawnee - Pastor Accused of Attempted Family Murder and Arson" /><published>2023-09-18T18:02:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-18T18:02:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/18/Pastor-Fire-Incident</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/18/Pastor-Fire-Incident/">&lt;p&gt;Shawnee, a tranquil suburb in Kansas, was rattled by shocking news involving a local youth pastor’s alleged violent actions against his family. Matthew Richards, 41, stands accused of attempting to kill his wife and five children in their home. Following the alleged attack, he is also charged with attempting to set the residence on fire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;disturbing-details&quot;&gt;Disturbing Details&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The harrowing incident occurred on September 16, when emergency services responded to alerts of a disturbance and fire around 3:47 a.m. Upon arriving, firefighters tackled a blaze in the basement of the family home located on Goode Drive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Richards and all the victims were rushed to the hospital. According to the Shawnee Police Department’s press release, the five children and the wife sustained “laceration injuries of varying degrees.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The aftermath has left Richards with five counts of attempted premeditated first-degree murder and one count of aggravated arson with a risk of bodily harm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;an-unexpected-turn&quot;&gt;An Unexpected Turn&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Crossroads Christian Church, where Richards was employed, showcases a heartwarming biography of him on their website. He is described as “a big kid who loves teaching little kids about Jesus.” The biography paints a contrasting picture, highlighting his marriage to Stephanie since 2003, their five children, and the family’s three rules – emphasizing love for God, people, and sports.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In light of the shocking incident, the Senior Pastor of Crossroads Church, Kurt Witten, issued a statement requesting respect for the ongoing investigation and urging prayers for the Richards family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;investigation-and-legal-proceedings&quot;&gt;Investigation and Legal Proceedings&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As investigations proceed, the community struggles to come to terms with the shocking event involving a figure once revered by many. Richards is currently being held on a staggering $5 million bond. The outcome of this situation will be closely watched by many, awaiting to see how justice unfolds.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Shawnee, a tranquil suburb in Kansas, was rattled by shocking news involving a local youth pastor’s alleged violent actions against his family. Matthew Richards, 41, stands accused of attempting to kill his wife and five children in their home. Following the alleged attack, he is also charged with attempting to set the residence on fire. Disturbing Details The harrowing incident occurred on September 16, when emergency services responded to alerts of a disturbance and fire around 3:47 a.m. Upon arriving, firefighters tackled a blaze in the basement of the family home located on Goode Drive. Richards and all the victims were rushed to the hospital. According to the Shawnee Police Department’s press release, the five children and the wife sustained “laceration injuries of varying degrees.” The aftermath has left Richards with five counts of attempted premeditated first-degree murder and one count of aggravated arson with a risk of bodily harm. An Unexpected Turn The Crossroads Christian Church, where Richards was employed, showcases a heartwarming biography of him on their website. He is described as “a big kid who loves teaching little kids about Jesus.” The biography paints a contrasting picture, highlighting his marriage to Stephanie since 2003, their five children, and the family’s three rules – emphasizing love for God, people, and sports. In light of the shocking incident, the Senior Pastor of Crossroads Church, Kurt Witten, issued a statement requesting respect for the ongoing investigation and urging prayers for the Richards family. Investigation and Legal Proceedings As investigations proceed, the community struggles to come to terms with the shocking event involving a figure once revered by many. Richards is currently being held on a staggering $5 million bond. The outcome of this situation will be closely watched by many, awaiting to see how justice unfolds.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump’s Fiery Rebuke - Biden’s $6 Billion ‘Hostage Deal’ with Iran</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/18/Trump-Biden-Iran-Deal/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump’s Fiery Rebuke - Biden’s $6 Billion ‘Hostage Deal’ with Iran" /><published>2023-09-18T17:10:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-18T17:10:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/18/Trump-Biden-Iran-Deal</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/18/Trump-Biden-Iran-Deal/">&lt;p&gt;Former President Donald Trump, known for his candid expressions and unfiltered opinions, blasted President Joe Biden’s recent deal with Iran. Labeled by Trump as a “6 Billion Dollar Hostage Deal,” this agreement has drawn attention and criticism from several corners.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-lopsided-deal&quot;&gt;A Lopsided Deal?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a candid post on Truth Social, Trump declared that this Iran deal has established a “terrible PRECEDENT for the future.” Expressing his concerns, he warned his followers and the general public to “buckle up” for the potential aftermath of such a deal. Highlighting the past reputation of the United States, he remarked that the once “highly respected USA” has now turned into a “laughingstock” globally.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His comments were in light of the recent event where five U.S. citizens were freed from Iranian custody. In exchange, the U.S. released five Iranian prisoners and unfroze $6 billion in Iranian assets that were under U.S. sanctions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;trumps-perspective&quot;&gt;Trump’s Perspective&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Trump did commend the release of the American hostages, he heavily criticized the price at which their freedom came. Comparing this situation with his tenure as President, he boasted of bringing home 58 hostages from various countries, including North Korea, without any ransom payments. He implied that his strong stance made countries rethink their hostage negotiation strategies. “Toward the end, it got so that countries didn’t even start the conversation asking for money, because they knew they would not get it,” Trump stated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Continuing his critique, Trump expressed his apprehension that such deals might pave the way for what he calls “hostage inflation.” According to him, if countries see that the U.S. is willing to pay billions for the safe return of its citizens, more Americans could potentially be taken hostage in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;whats-the-future-hold&quot;&gt;What’s the Future Hold?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The implication of Trump’s statements is clear. He firmly believes that once a precedent of payment is set, the demands will only increase, leading to more Americans at risk overseas. In his signature style, he concluded by labelling President Biden as “Dumb as a ROCK!” and blaming him for this deal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Only time will tell whether Trump’s fears are realized or if this deal will pave the way for smoother international relations. However, his concerns serve as a reminder to always tread cautiously on the international stage.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Former President Donald Trump, known for his candid expressions and unfiltered opinions, blasted President Joe Biden’s recent deal with Iran. Labeled by Trump as a “6 Billion Dollar Hostage Deal,” this agreement has drawn attention and criticism from several corners. A Lopsided Deal? In a candid post on Truth Social, Trump declared that this Iran deal has established a “terrible PRECEDENT for the future.” Expressing his concerns, he warned his followers and the general public to “buckle up” for the potential aftermath of such a deal. Highlighting the past reputation of the United States, he remarked that the once “highly respected USA” has now turned into a “laughingstock” globally. His comments were in light of the recent event where five U.S. citizens were freed from Iranian custody. In exchange, the U.S. released five Iranian prisoners and unfroze $6 billion in Iranian assets that were under U.S. sanctions. Trump’s Perspective While Trump did commend the release of the American hostages, he heavily criticized the price at which their freedom came. Comparing this situation with his tenure as President, he boasted of bringing home 58 hostages from various countries, including North Korea, without any ransom payments. He implied that his strong stance made countries rethink their hostage negotiation strategies. “Toward the end, it got so that countries didn’t even start the conversation asking for money, because they knew they would not get it,” Trump stated. Continuing his critique, Trump expressed his apprehension that such deals might pave the way for what he calls “hostage inflation.” According to him, if countries see that the U.S. is willing to pay billions for the safe return of its citizens, more Americans could potentially be taken hostage in the future. What’s the Future Hold? The implication of Trump’s statements is clear. He firmly believes that once a precedent of payment is set, the demands will only increase, leading to more Americans at risk overseas. In his signature style, he concluded by labelling President Biden as “Dumb as a ROCK!” and blaming him for this deal. Only time will tell whether Trump’s fears are realized or if this deal will pave the way for smoother international relations. However, his concerns serve as a reminder to always tread cautiously on the international stage.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Breaking Point - Eagle Pass Overwhelmed by Migrant Influx</title><link href="/news/2023/09/18/Unsustainable-Border-Crisis/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Breaking Point - Eagle Pass Overwhelmed by Migrant Influx" /><published>2023-09-18T16:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-18T16:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/18/Unsustainable-Border-Crisis</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/18/Unsustainable-Border-Crisis/">&lt;p&gt;EAGLE PASS, Texas — A small town on the border of Texas is facing a dire situation as over 1,500 migrants crossed into Eagle Pass from Mexico in just six hours. This recent influx surpasses the previous record established merely days ago, where 1,300 migrants crossed within a day. A reality check is in order as these numbers raise alarming concerns about the sustainability and effectiveness of U.S. border and immigration policies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Multiple reports have revealed that the local migrant processing center in Eagle Pass, initially designed to hold approximately 1,000 individuals, had to be shut down as it had already tripled its capacity. Officials are now scrambling to make accommodations, resulting in migrants being held outdoors. The rapid increase in numbers only underscores the pressing need for an overhaul in the current system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“This system is broken,” a source within the Customs and Border Protection (CBP) commented.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the weekend, astonishingly, in a single eight-hour shift, over 700 migrants were taken into custody. With the current infrastructure already stretched thin, the ability of border agents to handle the influx efficiently and humanely is called into question. Sadly, as temperatures are projected to soar to the mid-90s, many of these migrants find themselves awaiting processing outdoors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further south, reports from Piedras Negras, Coahuila, noted that Mexican military officials halted another 1,200 migrants from crossing. But it’s only a matter of time before they attempt again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With processing facilities already bursting at the seams, the situation is becoming untenable. By mid-morning, every Border Patrol agent with a commercial driver’s license in the region had been summoned to transport migrants. Yet hundreds still remained by midday, requiring attention from EMT-trained agents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eagle Pass recently witnessed a massive release of migrants into the community due to these constraints. With the processing center running well over its limits, it’s plausible that this trend of mass releases will continue, if not amplify.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sadly, the release isn’t the end of the challenge. Many migrants find themselves stranded in Eagle Pass without funds, relying on the kindness of residents for rides, money, or meals. Some have reported that shelters, such as Mission Border Hope, will only assist those migrants who have the means to buy a bus ticket out of the town. This leaves many to navigate the over 150 miles to cities like San Antonio on their own.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The plight of these migrants underscores the broader issue – a pressing need to address the evident shortcomings in U.S. border and immigration policies. As the streets of Eagle Pass become flooded with hopeful migrants, the sustainability of the current approach is clearly in jeopardy.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">EAGLE PASS, Texas — A small town on the border of Texas is facing a dire situation as over 1,500 migrants crossed into Eagle Pass from Mexico in just six hours. This recent influx surpasses the previous record established merely days ago, where 1,300 migrants crossed within a day. A reality check is in order as these numbers raise alarming concerns about the sustainability and effectiveness of U.S. border and immigration policies. Multiple reports have revealed that the local migrant processing center in Eagle Pass, initially designed to hold approximately 1,000 individuals, had to be shut down as it had already tripled its capacity. Officials are now scrambling to make accommodations, resulting in migrants being held outdoors. The rapid increase in numbers only underscores the pressing need for an overhaul in the current system. “This system is broken,” a source within the Customs and Border Protection (CBP) commented. Over the weekend, astonishingly, in a single eight-hour shift, over 700 migrants were taken into custody. With the current infrastructure already stretched thin, the ability of border agents to handle the influx efficiently and humanely is called into question. Sadly, as temperatures are projected to soar to the mid-90s, many of these migrants find themselves awaiting processing outdoors. Further south, reports from Piedras Negras, Coahuila, noted that Mexican military officials halted another 1,200 migrants from crossing. But it’s only a matter of time before they attempt again. With processing facilities already bursting at the seams, the situation is becoming untenable. By mid-morning, every Border Patrol agent with a commercial driver’s license in the region had been summoned to transport migrants. Yet hundreds still remained by midday, requiring attention from EMT-trained agents. Eagle Pass recently witnessed a massive release of migrants into the community due to these constraints. With the processing center running well over its limits, it’s plausible that this trend of mass releases will continue, if not amplify. Sadly, the release isn’t the end of the challenge. Many migrants find themselves stranded in Eagle Pass without funds, relying on the kindness of residents for rides, money, or meals. Some have reported that shelters, such as Mission Border Hope, will only assist those migrants who have the means to buy a bus ticket out of the town. This leaves many to navigate the over 150 miles to cities like San Antonio on their own. The plight of these migrants underscores the broader issue – a pressing need to address the evident shortcomings in U.S. border and immigration policies. As the streets of Eagle Pass become flooded with hopeful migrants, the sustainability of the current approach is clearly in jeopardy.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Sheryl Crow on Tennessee Move - How Leaving LA ‘Saved My Life’</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/18/Tennessee-Life-Saver/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sheryl Crow on Tennessee Move - How Leaving LA ‘Saved My Life’" /><published>2023-09-18T15:07:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-18T15:07:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/18/Tennessee-Life-Saver</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/18/Tennessee-Life-Saver/">&lt;p&gt;Sheryl Crow, the musician behind hits like “If It Makes You Happy,” recently spoke candidly about how her move from Los Angeles to Nashville, Tennessee, became a lifesaving decision.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-breath-of-fresh-air&quot;&gt;A Breath of Fresh Air&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the 2023 Sea.Hear.Now Music Festival in New Jersey, Crow connected with her audience, many of whom might be navigating through their own challenges. “I know how hard it is for especially young people… but these are some tricky waters to navigate now,” she voiced.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2023/09/720/405/sheryl-crow_04.jpg?ve=1&amp;amp;tl=1&quot; alt=&quot;Sheryl Crow with her guitar&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Sheryl Crow on stage, embracing her love for music. Photo by Astrida Valigorsky/Getty Images.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Revealing a deeply personal insight, she shared, “I’ll just tell you that, for me, getting out in nature really saved my life.” This shift towards a more natural environment led her to buy a farm in Nashville, where she’d sit among the trees, seeking solace and inspiration. It was in this setting that she wrote “Cross Creek Road.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;finding-her-roots&quot;&gt;Finding Her Roots&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sheryl’s relocation to Nashville wasn’t a mere whim. In 2003, she told Rolling Stone that she felt a deep connection to the city, not just because of her friends in the music business, but because of the warmth and simplicity of the people there. The hustle of cities like New York and L.A. paled in comparison to the serenity she felt in Nashville.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moreover, a significant turning point in her life was her breast cancer diagnosis. She revealed to the New York Times that she bought her farm just two weeks post-diagnosis. “I didn’t feel like I had roots anywhere,” Crow reminisced about the time leading up to her move.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2023/09/720/405/sheryl-crow_03.jpg?ve=1&amp;amp;tl=1&quot; alt=&quot;Sheryl Crow in a stylish outfit&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Sheryl Crow at a fashion event. Photo by Gilbert Flores/WWD via Getty Images.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-mother-first&quot;&gt;A Mother First&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apart from finding personal tranquility, Tennessee also provided an ideal environment for raising her two adopted sons, Wyatt and Levi. Living there, Crow shared the benefits of a community-centric upbringing for her kids. It’s a place where they can grow without the constant flash of cameras, where they can understand the value of helping others, and where they won’t be hounded by paparazzi.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In an industry often filled with fleeting glamour, Sheryl Crow’s story is a testament to the healing power of nature, the comfort of community, and the enduring bond of family.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Sheryl Crow, the musician behind hits like “If It Makes You Happy,” recently spoke candidly about how her move from Los Angeles to Nashville, Tennessee, became a lifesaving decision. A Breath of Fresh Air At the 2023 Sea.Hear.Now Music Festival in New Jersey, Crow connected with her audience, many of whom might be navigating through their own challenges. “I know how hard it is for especially young people… but these are some tricky waters to navigate now,” she voiced. Sheryl Crow on stage, embracing her love for music. Photo by Astrida Valigorsky/Getty Images. Revealing a deeply personal insight, she shared, “I’ll just tell you that, for me, getting out in nature really saved my life.” This shift towards a more natural environment led her to buy a farm in Nashville, where she’d sit among the trees, seeking solace and inspiration. It was in this setting that she wrote “Cross Creek Road.” Finding Her Roots Sheryl’s relocation to Nashville wasn’t a mere whim. In 2003, she told Rolling Stone that she felt a deep connection to the city, not just because of her friends in the music business, but because of the warmth and simplicity of the people there. The hustle of cities like New York and L.A. paled in comparison to the serenity she felt in Nashville. Moreover, a significant turning point in her life was her breast cancer diagnosis. She revealed to the New York Times that she bought her farm just two weeks post-diagnosis. “I didn’t feel like I had roots anywhere,” Crow reminisced about the time leading up to her move. Sheryl Crow at a fashion event. Photo by Gilbert Flores/WWD via Getty Images. A Mother First Apart from finding personal tranquility, Tennessee also provided an ideal environment for raising her two adopted sons, Wyatt and Levi. Living there, Crow shared the benefits of a community-centric upbringing for her kids. It’s a place where they can grow without the constant flash of cameras, where they can understand the value of helping others, and where they won’t be hounded by paparazzi. In an industry often filled with fleeting glamour, Sheryl Crow’s story is a testament to the healing power of nature, the comfort of community, and the enduring bond of family.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Soros Funds Biden’s TikTok Strategy - America’s Teens Under Influence?</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/18/Soros-Biden-TikTok-Influence/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Soros Funds Biden’s TikTok Strategy - America’s Teens Under Influence?" /><published>2023-09-18T14:11:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-18T14:11:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/18/Soros-Biden-TikTok-Influence</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/18/Soros-Biden-TikTok-Influence/">&lt;p&gt;George Soros, the billionaire Democrat donor infamous for championing far-left causes, is now funding an initiative to bolster the image of President Joe Biden on TikTok. But why would Soros show interest in a platform popular among American teenagers?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-tiktok-army-and-soros-agenda&quot;&gt;The TikTok Army and Soros’ Agenda&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Documents brought to light by the New York Post indicate that Soros is bankrolling a “TikTok army” composed of Gen-Z social media enthusiasts. Their main task? To disseminate pro-Biden messages and attack conservative views. The platform of choice? TikTok, which already hosts a vast population of American teens, making them a prime target for political influencing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tax filings unveil that Soros’ Open Society Foundation funneled a staggering $5.5 million to Accelerate Action Inc. over 2020 and 2021. Following this, at least $300,000 was directed in 2022 to Gen Z for Change, an organization that flaunts a vast network of “activists, organizers, and creators.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;bidens-social-media-aides&quot;&gt;Biden’s Social Media Aides&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While President Biden occupies the highest office in the land, he’s actively leaning on Gen Z for Change to amplify his policy messages on social media. Not only has Gen Z for Change met with Biden in the famed Oval Office, but they’ve also received briefings from top White House officials, including sessions on the U.S. involvement in Ukraine and discussions with Surgeon General Vivek Murthy on the pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gen Z for Change influencers are not shy about their views. They’ve used their platform to advocate for controversial policies such as abolishing border enforcement, defunding the police, and ending cash bail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;wheres-the-money-flowing&quot;&gt;Where’s the Money Flowing?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A burning question remains: How is Soros’ money being used by these young TikTok influencers? There’s no clarity on how Gen Z for Change allocates the Soros funds among its TikTok squad. What we do know, however, is that their content seems eerily in line with the White House’s talking points.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aidan Kohn-Murphy, the founder of the group, openly advocates for progressive policies such as Medicare for all, the Green New Deal, and Palestinian liberation. With these talking points and a massive platform, he and others are shaping the opinions of countless Gen Z followers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;soros-the-puppet-master&quot;&gt;Soros: The Puppet Master?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s worth noting that Soros isn’t a novice in the world of influencing public opinion. For years, he’s poured funds into left-leaning causes globally via his Open Society Foundation. The recent strategy to tap into TikTok to promote left-wing ideals seems like another feather in his cap of trying to mould public opinion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, is it fair for teens, many of whom are not yet eligible to vote, to be the target of such heavy political messaging? As America’s future voters, they deserve balanced viewpoints rather than a single-sided narrative bankrolled by billionaire agendas.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">George Soros, the billionaire Democrat donor infamous for championing far-left causes, is now funding an initiative to bolster the image of President Joe Biden on TikTok. But why would Soros show interest in a platform popular among American teenagers? The TikTok Army and Soros’ Agenda Documents brought to light by the New York Post indicate that Soros is bankrolling a “TikTok army” composed of Gen-Z social media enthusiasts. Their main task? To disseminate pro-Biden messages and attack conservative views. The platform of choice? TikTok, which already hosts a vast population of American teens, making them a prime target for political influencing. Tax filings unveil that Soros’ Open Society Foundation funneled a staggering $5.5 million to Accelerate Action Inc. over 2020 and 2021. Following this, at least $300,000 was directed in 2022 to Gen Z for Change, an organization that flaunts a vast network of “activists, organizers, and creators.” Biden’s Social Media Aides While President Biden occupies the highest office in the land, he’s actively leaning on Gen Z for Change to amplify his policy messages on social media. Not only has Gen Z for Change met with Biden in the famed Oval Office, but they’ve also received briefings from top White House officials, including sessions on the U.S. involvement in Ukraine and discussions with Surgeon General Vivek Murthy on the pandemic. Gen Z for Change influencers are not shy about their views. They’ve used their platform to advocate for controversial policies such as abolishing border enforcement, defunding the police, and ending cash bail. Where’s the Money Flowing? A burning question remains: How is Soros’ money being used by these young TikTok influencers? There’s no clarity on how Gen Z for Change allocates the Soros funds among its TikTok squad. What we do know, however, is that their content seems eerily in line with the White House’s talking points. Aidan Kohn-Murphy, the founder of the group, openly advocates for progressive policies such as Medicare for all, the Green New Deal, and Palestinian liberation. With these talking points and a massive platform, he and others are shaping the opinions of countless Gen Z followers. Soros: The Puppet Master? It’s worth noting that Soros isn’t a novice in the world of influencing public opinion. For years, he’s poured funds into left-leaning causes globally via his Open Society Foundation. The recent strategy to tap into TikTok to promote left-wing ideals seems like another feather in his cap of trying to mould public opinion. However, is it fair for teens, many of whom are not yet eligible to vote, to be the target of such heavy political messaging? As America’s future voters, they deserve balanced viewpoints rather than a single-sided narrative bankrolled by billionaire agendas.</summary></entry></feed>