<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-10-24T23:16:01-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/24/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-24T23:16:01-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-24T23:16:01-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/24/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/24/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/24/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-24T23:16:01-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-24T23:16:01-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/24/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/24/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/">&lt;p&gt;Recent surprise attacks by Hamas on Israel has fueled ongoing tensions between staunchly conservative commentators and the progressive “Squad” Democrats known for criticizing Israel. The intensity of the backlash highlights the deep political divide over foreign policy in the Middle East.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Hamas’ shocking attack, several members of the “Squad,” including Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.), called for a “ceasefire and de-escalation,” condemning the violence. The absence of a statement from Rep. Rashida Tlaib (D-Mich.) was notably called out by conservative media outlets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;South Carolina GOP Rep. Nancy Mace quickly labeled Ocasio-Cortez a “Hamas apologist” in response to her call for peace and de-escalation. Rep. Ilhan Omar (D-Minn.), no stranger to controversy surrounding her views on Israel, echoed the call for de-escalation and ceasefire. Omar’s prior statements comparing the US and Israel to terrorist groups like Hamas and the Taliban resurfaced in the debate, fueling more criticisms. Omar’s 2019 tweet, where she opined that “Israel has hypnotized the world,” also continues to haunt her political career, often cited by critics to challenge her stance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conservative commentators have been especially vocal. “FOX &amp;amp; Friends Weekend” co-host Rachel Campos-Duffy took aim at Omar, saying she fails to recognize the peace in the Middle East under Trump’s administration. Conservative pundit John Hasson also called out Omar, claiming she insinuated that attacks on IDF forces were acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Massachusetts Democrat Rep. Ayanna Pressley’s concerns over the “devastating attacks on Israelis” were met with skepticism. A prominent conservative online personality, Comfortably Smug, accused the “Squad” of advising Israel to back down after the nation suffered massive attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Jamaal Bowman’s call for an end to the Gaza blockade, in addition to condemning the Hamas attacks, was met with criticism from conservative radio host Jason Rantz. He accused Bowman of pairing his condemnation of terrorism with unwarranted criticisms of Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Cori Bush emphasized the urgent need for a ceasefire, while pushing for an end to “U.S. support for Israeli military occupation and apartheid.” Defense attorney Marina Medvin criticized Bush, suggesting that she equates the death of Palestinian terrorists to the horrific acts committed against Jewish civilians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amidst the political turmoil and intense debate, the attacks have taken a heavy toll. Israeli media report over 300 dead due to the wide-ranging assault. Gaza health officials note that at least 200 Palestinians have perished in the retaliatory Israeli air strikes following the initial Hamas attack. As the situation remains volatile, both sides continue to count their casualties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This divisive issue showcases the challenge America faces in crafting a unified approach to foreign policy, with deeply entrenched political divides at play. As the situation develops, the debate is bound to intensify, shedding light on the complexities of U.S. politics in the global arena.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Former Maryland Gov. Larry Hogan Withdraws from Harvard Fellowships Amid Antisemitic Tensions</title><link href="/news/2023/10/24/Antisemitism-Harvard/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Former Maryland Gov. Larry Hogan Withdraws from Harvard Fellowships Amid Antisemitic Tensions" /><published>2023-10-24T15:24:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-24T15:24:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/24/Antisemitism-Harvard</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/24/Antisemitism-Harvard/">&lt;p&gt;Former Maryland Governor Larry Hogan has taken a firm stance against antisemitism, deciding to withdraw from two esteemed fellowship programs at Harvard University. Hogan, a Republican and a notable figure in American politics, had accepted fellowships at the John F. Kennedy School of Government and the Harvard T.H. Chan School of Public Health months earlier.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hogan’s decision is a direct response to what he describes as “anti-Semitic vitriol” permeating the campus, following the deadly attack by Hamas on Israel on October 7. In a candid letter to Harvard, which Hogan shared on his social media platforms, he expressed his initial excitement about joining the Harvard community and his eagerness to impart leadership lessons to the next generation of leaders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, Hogan’s enthusiasm quickly turned to disappointment as he witnessed the university’s reaction—or lack thereof—to the surge of antisemitic sentiments on campus. Over 30 Harvard student organizations openly blamed Israel for the Hamas-initiated attack, prompting Hogan to reassess his association with the prestigious institution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I cannot condone the dangerous anti-Semitism that has taken root on your campus,” Hogan stated in his letter, highlighting the severity of the attack as the “greatest loss of Jewish life since the Holocaust.” He called for universal condemnation of the attack, emphasizing its fundamentally evil nature.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The student statement, released on the day of the attack, held the Israeli regime entirely responsible for the violence, outlining the longstanding tensions and challenges faced by Palestinians in Gaza. The statement quickly ignited national backlash, with business leaders pledging not to employ the students involved and some even rescinding job offers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Harvard’s administration, led by President Claudine Gay, was quick to denounce Hamas’ violence and clarify that student groups do not speak on behalf of the university. However, Hogan argued that this response was not sufficient, stating that while students have the right to free speech, they should not be allowed to propagate hate speech without challenge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hogan’s withdrawal from the Harvard fellowship programs sends a powerful message about the importance of standing against antisemitism and holding educational institutions accountable for their response to hate speech. As Hogan concludes his letter, he expresses his hope that his decision will prompt Harvard to take meaningful action against antisemitism and uphold the values it should represent to the world.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Former Maryland Governor Larry Hogan has taken a firm stance against antisemitism, deciding to withdraw from two esteemed fellowship programs at Harvard University. Hogan, a Republican and a notable figure in American politics, had accepted fellowships at the John F. Kennedy School of Government and the Harvard T.H. Chan School of Public Health months earlier. Hogan’s decision is a direct response to what he describes as “anti-Semitic vitriol” permeating the campus, following the deadly attack by Hamas on Israel on October 7. In a candid letter to Harvard, which Hogan shared on his social media platforms, he expressed his initial excitement about joining the Harvard community and his eagerness to impart leadership lessons to the next generation of leaders. However, Hogan’s enthusiasm quickly turned to disappointment as he witnessed the university’s reaction—or lack thereof—to the surge of antisemitic sentiments on campus. Over 30 Harvard student organizations openly blamed Israel for the Hamas-initiated attack, prompting Hogan to reassess his association with the prestigious institution. “I cannot condone the dangerous anti-Semitism that has taken root on your campus,” Hogan stated in his letter, highlighting the severity of the attack as the “greatest loss of Jewish life since the Holocaust.” He called for universal condemnation of the attack, emphasizing its fundamentally evil nature. The student statement, released on the day of the attack, held the Israeli regime entirely responsible for the violence, outlining the longstanding tensions and challenges faced by Palestinians in Gaza. The statement quickly ignited national backlash, with business leaders pledging not to employ the students involved and some even rescinding job offers. Harvard’s administration, led by President Claudine Gay, was quick to denounce Hamas’ violence and clarify that student groups do not speak on behalf of the university. However, Hogan argued that this response was not sufficient, stating that while students have the right to free speech, they should not be allowed to propagate hate speech without challenge. Hogan’s withdrawal from the Harvard fellowship programs sends a powerful message about the importance of standing against antisemitism and holding educational institutions accountable for their response to hate speech. As Hogan concludes his letter, he expresses his hope that his decision will prompt Harvard to take meaningful action against antisemitism and uphold the values it should represent to the world.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">DOJ Prosecutors to Address Allegations of Political Bias in Hunter Biden Investigation</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/24/Hunter-Biden-Probe-Questions/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="DOJ Prosecutors to Address Allegations of Political Bias in Hunter Biden Investigation" /><published>2023-10-24T14:06:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-24T14:06:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/24/Hunter-Biden-Probe-Questions</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/24/Hunter-Biden-Probe-Questions/">&lt;p&gt;In a highly anticipated move, federal prosecutors are set to appear for transcribed interviews at the House Judiciary Committee this week, as part of the ongoing investigation into alleged political bias in the Hunter Biden probe. This closed-door session raises significant questions about the integrity of the investigation and the role of politics in judicial proceedings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;U.S. Attorney for the Central District of California, Martin Estrada, is scheduled to be interviewed on Tuesday, followed by DOJ Tax Division attorney Stuart Goldberg on Wednesday. These interviews are a response to allegations of politicization and misconduct at the Justice Department agencies throughout the years-long investigation into President Joe Biden’s son.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The move comes after House Judiciary Committee Chairman Jim Jordan, R-Ohio, has been pushing for months to have federal prosecutors involved in the Biden investigation testify before his committee. These negotiations have been fraught, reflecting the high stakes and political tensions surrounding the investigation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Special Counsel David Weiss, overseeing the government’s investigation into Biden, is also expected to appear for a transcribed interview on Nov. 7, behind closed doors. The Justice Department had initially offered Weiss for public testimony back in July, indicating a preference for transparency, but this closed-door session suggests a more confidential approach is being taken.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The allegations that politics have influenced or hampered prosecutorial decisions in the investigation have led to heightened scrutiny, with Weiss, the U.S. attorney for Delaware, taking on the role of special counsel. He has been leading the Biden investigation since 2018, and his appointment as special counsel aims to address concerns about the impartiality of the investigation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In his first move as special counsel, Weiss charged Hunter Biden with making false statements related to a firearm purchase and possession of a firearm by a person using controlled substances. Biden has pleaded not guilty to all charges, and the investigation continues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This development comes amid House Republicans’ impeachment inquiry against President Biden, adding another layer of complexity to the political landscape. The status of this inquiry remains uncertain following the ouster of Rep. Kevin McCarthy, R-Calif., as House speaker.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the political drama unfolds, the nation’s eyes are on the House Judiciary Committee and the closed-door interviews set to take place this week. The outcomes of these interviews may have significant implications for the Hunter Biden investigation, the integrity of the judicial process, and the broader political discourse in the United States.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a highly anticipated move, federal prosecutors are set to appear for transcribed interviews at the House Judiciary Committee this week, as part of the ongoing investigation into alleged political bias in the Hunter Biden probe. This closed-door session raises significant questions about the integrity of the investigation and the role of politics in judicial proceedings. U.S. Attorney for the Central District of California, Martin Estrada, is scheduled to be interviewed on Tuesday, followed by DOJ Tax Division attorney Stuart Goldberg on Wednesday. These interviews are a response to allegations of politicization and misconduct at the Justice Department agencies throughout the years-long investigation into President Joe Biden’s son. The move comes after House Judiciary Committee Chairman Jim Jordan, R-Ohio, has been pushing for months to have federal prosecutors involved in the Biden investigation testify before his committee. These negotiations have been fraught, reflecting the high stakes and political tensions surrounding the investigation. Special Counsel David Weiss, overseeing the government’s investigation into Biden, is also expected to appear for a transcribed interview on Nov. 7, behind closed doors. The Justice Department had initially offered Weiss for public testimony back in July, indicating a preference for transparency, but this closed-door session suggests a more confidential approach is being taken. The allegations that politics have influenced or hampered prosecutorial decisions in the investigation have led to heightened scrutiny, with Weiss, the U.S. attorney for Delaware, taking on the role of special counsel. He has been leading the Biden investigation since 2018, and his appointment as special counsel aims to address concerns about the impartiality of the investigation. In his first move as special counsel, Weiss charged Hunter Biden with making false statements related to a firearm purchase and possession of a firearm by a person using controlled substances. Biden has pleaded not guilty to all charges, and the investigation continues. This development comes amid House Republicans’ impeachment inquiry against President Biden, adding another layer of complexity to the political landscape. The status of this inquiry remains uncertain following the ouster of Rep. Kevin McCarthy, R-Calif., as House speaker. As the political drama unfolds, the nation’s eyes are on the House Judiciary Committee and the closed-door interviews set to take place this week. The outcomes of these interviews may have significant implications for the Hunter Biden investigation, the integrity of the judicial process, and the broader political discourse in the United States.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Perry Johnson Throws Support Behind Trump for 2024 Presidential Bid</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/24/Perry-Johnson-Trump-Endorsement/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Perry Johnson Throws Support Behind Trump for 2024 Presidential Bid" /><published>2023-10-24T12:57:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-24T12:57:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/24/Perry-Johnson-Trump-Endorsement</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/24/Perry-Johnson-Trump-Endorsement/">&lt;p&gt;Perry Johnson, a self-funded businessman from Michigan who recently suspended his own presidential campaign, has thrown his support behind former President Donald Trump for the 2024 presidential election. Johnson’s endorsement comes as a surprise to many, given his previous criticisms of corruption within the Republican National Committee (RNC).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Johnson made his endorsement public through a statement on social media this Monday, stating, “After suspending my campaign for President on Friday, there is now only one candidate in this race who can provide a solution to our nation’s economic, foreign policy and social crises, and most importantly, beat [President] Joe Biden at the ballot box. That person is Donald Trump.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Emphasizing the need for unity among conservatives, Johnson added, “I look forward to assisting in efforts to elect him next year and uniting with other conservatives to defeat Joe Biden in November.” This statement marks a clear shift in Johnson’s political strategy, aligning himself with Trump’s influential base.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just last week, Johnson expressed his dissatisfaction with the RNC, accusing leaders of corruption and emphasizing the importance of democracy. “The corruption among leaders at the RNC during this process was appalling. I’ve said it before and I’ll say it again, the people should decide the next president of the United States, not the head of the RNC and her cronies,” Johnson remarked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This endorsement is especially noteworthy in light of Johnson’s previous failed attempt to run for governor of Michigan, where he faced legal challenges over the authenticity of signatures on his petition. The court eventually ruled against him, marking a setback in his political career.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, aligning with Trump, Johnson seems poised to reestablish himself in the political arena, contributing to the efforts to unseat President Joe Biden in the upcoming election. This move also highlights the continuing influence of Donald Trump within the Republican Party, as he garners support from former rivals in his pursuit of returning to the White House.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the 2024 presidential race heats up, Johnson’s endorsement of Trump adds an interesting dynamic to the political landscape, emphasizing the high stakes and shifting alliances that define modern American politics. With the nation’s eyes on the Republican Party and its potential candidates, Johnson’s support for Trump is sure to play a significant role in shaping the discourse and strategies leading up to the election.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Perry Johnson, a self-funded businessman from Michigan who recently suspended his own presidential campaign, has thrown his support behind former President Donald Trump for the 2024 presidential election. Johnson’s endorsement comes as a surprise to many, given his previous criticisms of corruption within the Republican National Committee (RNC). Johnson made his endorsement public through a statement on social media this Monday, stating, “After suspending my campaign for President on Friday, there is now only one candidate in this race who can provide a solution to our nation’s economic, foreign policy and social crises, and most importantly, beat [President] Joe Biden at the ballot box. That person is Donald Trump.” Emphasizing the need for unity among conservatives, Johnson added, “I look forward to assisting in efforts to elect him next year and uniting with other conservatives to defeat Joe Biden in November.” This statement marks a clear shift in Johnson’s political strategy, aligning himself with Trump’s influential base. Just last week, Johnson expressed his dissatisfaction with the RNC, accusing leaders of corruption and emphasizing the importance of democracy. “The corruption among leaders at the RNC during this process was appalling. I’ve said it before and I’ll say it again, the people should decide the next president of the United States, not the head of the RNC and her cronies,” Johnson remarked. This endorsement is especially noteworthy in light of Johnson’s previous failed attempt to run for governor of Michigan, where he faced legal challenges over the authenticity of signatures on his petition. The court eventually ruled against him, marking a setback in his political career. Now, aligning with Trump, Johnson seems poised to reestablish himself in the political arena, contributing to the efforts to unseat President Joe Biden in the upcoming election. This move also highlights the continuing influence of Donald Trump within the Republican Party, as he garners support from former rivals in his pursuit of returning to the White House. As the 2024 presidential race heats up, Johnson’s endorsement of Trump adds an interesting dynamic to the political landscape, emphasizing the high stakes and shifting alliances that define modern American politics. With the nation’s eyes on the Republican Party and its potential candidates, Johnson’s support for Trump is sure to play a significant role in shaping the discourse and strategies leading up to the election.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Digital Warfare: Uncovering Iran’s Propaganda Tactics on Chinese TikTok</title><link href="/news/2023/10/24/Iran-TikTok-Propaganda/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Digital Warfare: Uncovering Iran’s Propaganda Tactics on Chinese TikTok" /><published>2023-10-24T11:49:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-24T11:49:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/24/Iran-TikTok-Propaganda</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/24/Iran-TikTok-Propaganda/">&lt;p&gt;The digital space is the new battlefield for geopolitical conflicts, and the latest reports reveal a disturbing trend: Iran is actively using Douyin, the Chinese counterpart of TikTok, to spread propaganda about the ongoing conflict between Hamas and Israel. This move underscores the complexity of modern warfare, where battles are fought not just with weapons but with information and influence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ByteDance, a Beijing-based company, owns Douyin, and it seems to have become a platform for the Iranian embassy in China to express its views and garner support. Newsweek’s recent coverage highlights the embassy’s sympathetic stance toward Hamas, particularly in relation to the Oct. 7 massacre in southern Israel. The embassy’s account goes further to lay blame on the United States and Israel, accusing them of aiming to obliterate Hamas’ control over the Gaza Strip.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since the conflict’s inception, the embassy has strategically used short, impactful videos to draw attention to the destruction in Gaza, attracting hundreds of thousands of views. Some videos explicitly label Israel as a “terrorist” nation, while others share footage of explosion aftermaths, blaming Israel for the devastation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One particular post shared by the embassy features footage from the Anglican Diocese of Jerusalem’s al-Ahli Arab Hospital in Gaza City post-explosion. The embassy attributes the destruction to Israel, despite U.S. intelligence indicating that the damage was actually caused by a failed rocket launch by the Islamic Jihad Movement in Palestine, a group closely aligned with Hamas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a blatant display of antisemitism, another Iranian post on Douyin depicts rockets raining down on Gaza, emanating from the hair of a grotesque caricature of a Jewish person. This sort of hateful content is not only spreading misinformation but also fostering animosity and prejudice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amplifying Iran’s propaganda efforts, Chinese state media outlets have reposted and supported the Iranian embassy’s claims on Sina Weibo, another popular social media platform in China. The concerted efforts of these entities have led to a significant increase in the embassy’s influence on Douyin, now boasting over 1.3 million followers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beijing, while maintaining robust political and trade relationships with Iran, presents itself as a peace broker in the Middle East conflict. However, it’s crucial to highlight that the country has yet to denounce Hamas’ actions or its connections to Iran, as reported by The Wall Street Journal. This silence speaks volumes and raises questions about the role of propaganda in modern geopolitics, as well as the responsibility of social media platforms in curbing the spread of misinformation.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">The digital space is the new battlefield for geopolitical conflicts, and the latest reports reveal a disturbing trend: Iran is actively using Douyin, the Chinese counterpart of TikTok, to spread propaganda about the ongoing conflict between Hamas and Israel. This move underscores the complexity of modern warfare, where battles are fought not just with weapons but with information and influence. ByteDance, a Beijing-based company, owns Douyin, and it seems to have become a platform for the Iranian embassy in China to express its views and garner support. Newsweek’s recent coverage highlights the embassy’s sympathetic stance toward Hamas, particularly in relation to the Oct. 7 massacre in southern Israel. The embassy’s account goes further to lay blame on the United States and Israel, accusing them of aiming to obliterate Hamas’ control over the Gaza Strip. Since the conflict’s inception, the embassy has strategically used short, impactful videos to draw attention to the destruction in Gaza, attracting hundreds of thousands of views. Some videos explicitly label Israel as a “terrorist” nation, while others share footage of explosion aftermaths, blaming Israel for the devastation. One particular post shared by the embassy features footage from the Anglican Diocese of Jerusalem’s al-Ahli Arab Hospital in Gaza City post-explosion. The embassy attributes the destruction to Israel, despite U.S. intelligence indicating that the damage was actually caused by a failed rocket launch by the Islamic Jihad Movement in Palestine, a group closely aligned with Hamas. In a blatant display of antisemitism, another Iranian post on Douyin depicts rockets raining down on Gaza, emanating from the hair of a grotesque caricature of a Jewish person. This sort of hateful content is not only spreading misinformation but also fostering animosity and prejudice. Amplifying Iran’s propaganda efforts, Chinese state media outlets have reposted and supported the Iranian embassy’s claims on Sina Weibo, another popular social media platform in China. The concerted efforts of these entities have led to a significant increase in the embassy’s influence on Douyin, now boasting over 1.3 million followers. Beijing, while maintaining robust political and trade relationships with Iran, presents itself as a peace broker in the Middle East conflict. However, it’s crucial to highlight that the country has yet to denounce Hamas’ actions or its connections to Iran, as reported by The Wall Street Journal. This silence speaks volumes and raises questions about the role of propaganda in modern geopolitics, as well as the responsibility of social media platforms in curbing the spread of misinformation.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Chaos Unleashed: Violent Showdown as Hunt for Georgia Jail Escapees Intensifies</title><link href="/news/2023/10/24/Georgia-Jail-Escapees/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Chaos Unleashed: Violent Showdown as Hunt for Georgia Jail Escapees Intensifies" /><published>2023-10-24T10:34:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-24T10:34:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/24/Georgia-Jail-Escapees</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/24/Georgia-Jail-Escapees/">&lt;p&gt;The search for four escaped Georgia inmates took a violent turn, leading armed law enforcement teams straight to the doorstep of a missing murder suspect, resulting in a confrontation that ended in gunfire. The U.S. Marshals, backed by SWAT teams, experienced gunfire through a closed apartment door, escalating the situation to new heights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Upon breaching the apartment, officers discovered 23-year-old Christian Williams, a suspect in a 2021 murder case who vanished under mysterious circumstances seven months ago. The suspect was found with a self-inflicted gunshot wound and is currently in critical condition at a local hospital. This incident marks the first time Williams has been seen since his reported abduction on March 6, just hours before his scheduled court appearance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Williams is suspected of assisting Joey Fournier (52), Chavis Stokes (29), Marc K. Anderson (24), and Johnifer Barnwell (37) in their escape from Bibbs County Jail. The inmates managed a daring escape, climbing out of a damaged window and cutting through a fence before making their getaway in a blue Dodge Challenger.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The discovery of the suspected getaway vehicle in a parking lot near the jail has not brought the fugitives any closer to capture, as the search continues into its second week. The Bibb County Sheriff’s Office, while releasing few details, has confirmed that Williams’s involvement in the jailbreak is under investigation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His girlfriend, present at the scene, was arrested and charged with felony aiding or permitting another to escape lawful custody or confinement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The current status of the escaped inmates remains uncertain, with the Bibb County Sheriff admitting during a press conference that “They could be anywhere…But how long they stay together or even if they’re together at this point: We don’t know.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Law enforcement has placed a $73,000 reward on the heads of the fugitives, a combination of contributions from the FBI, Macon Regional Crime Stoppers, U.S. Marshals Service, and the Bibb County Sheriff’s Office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This tumultuous incident shines a spotlight on the intricate and often dangerous nature of manhunts, underscoring the lengths to which law enforcement will go to apprehend escapees and solve outstanding cases. As the situation continues to develop, the public and law enforcement alike are left on edge, wondering where the escapees will turn up next and what further revelations this intense manhunt will bring to light.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">The search for four escaped Georgia inmates took a violent turn, leading armed law enforcement teams straight to the doorstep of a missing murder suspect, resulting in a confrontation that ended in gunfire. The U.S. Marshals, backed by SWAT teams, experienced gunfire through a closed apartment door, escalating the situation to new heights. Upon breaching the apartment, officers discovered 23-year-old Christian Williams, a suspect in a 2021 murder case who vanished under mysterious circumstances seven months ago. The suspect was found with a self-inflicted gunshot wound and is currently in critical condition at a local hospital. This incident marks the first time Williams has been seen since his reported abduction on March 6, just hours before his scheduled court appearance. Williams is suspected of assisting Joey Fournier (52), Chavis Stokes (29), Marc K. Anderson (24), and Johnifer Barnwell (37) in their escape from Bibbs County Jail. The inmates managed a daring escape, climbing out of a damaged window and cutting through a fence before making their getaway in a blue Dodge Challenger. The discovery of the suspected getaway vehicle in a parking lot near the jail has not brought the fugitives any closer to capture, as the search continues into its second week. The Bibb County Sheriff’s Office, while releasing few details, has confirmed that Williams’s involvement in the jailbreak is under investigation. His girlfriend, present at the scene, was arrested and charged with felony aiding or permitting another to escape lawful custody or confinement. The current status of the escaped inmates remains uncertain, with the Bibb County Sheriff admitting during a press conference that “They could be anywhere…But how long they stay together or even if they’re together at this point: We don’t know.” Law enforcement has placed a $73,000 reward on the heads of the fugitives, a combination of contributions from the FBI, Macon Regional Crime Stoppers, U.S. Marshals Service, and the Bibb County Sheriff’s Office. This tumultuous incident shines a spotlight on the intricate and often dangerous nature of manhunts, underscoring the lengths to which law enforcement will go to apprehend escapees and solve outstanding cases. As the situation continues to develop, the public and law enforcement alike are left on edge, wondering where the escapees will turn up next and what further revelations this intense manhunt will bring to light.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Exposing Hidden Agendas: Lawsuit Challenges Biden’s DHS over ‘Special Amnesty’ Policy</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/24/Special-Amnesty-Policy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Exposing Hidden Agendas: Lawsuit Challenges Biden’s DHS over ‘Special Amnesty’ Policy" /><published>2023-10-24T09:24:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-24T09:24:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/24/Special-Amnesty-Policy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/24/Special-Amnesty-Policy/">&lt;p&gt;The Immigration Reform Law Institute (IRLI) has filed a lawsuit against the Department of Homeland Security (DHS), led by President Joe Biden. The suit alleges that the DHS is concealing critical details about a policy implemented in July 2021, designed to permit certain deported illegal aliens, particularly those who have served in the U.S. Armed Forces, to return to the United States, despite having been previously expelled due to criminal activities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This controversial policy has sparked fierce debate, as critics argue it exploits the American public’s support for military veterans, while potentially compromising national security by allowing individuals with criminal histories back into the country. The IRLI is pushing back, demanding answers and transparency on this issue, with Executive Director Dale Wilcox stating, “This administration has made clear its desire to keep criminal aliens in the country, and now they are exploiting the American people’s support of military veterans to allow more potentially dangerous aliens to stay.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The lawsuit stems from a Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) request submitted by the IRLI in April of this year, seeking access to all documentation, policies, and case details related to the DHS initiative focusing on the return of deported non-citizen veterans. Despite acknowledgment of the request, the DHS has yet to provide any determination, prompting the IRLI to take legal action.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The lawsuit, filed in the U.S. District Court for the District of Columbia, highlights a critical issue at the intersection of immigration, national security, and transparency. It asks the federal court to mandate the DHS to disclose all relevant information pertaining to this ‘Special Amnesty’ policy, ensuring that the public is fully informed about the actions and intentions of the administration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Director of Investigations at IRLI, Matt O’Brien, emphasizes the need for scrutiny, questioning the appropriateness of a policy that seemingly grants special treatment to foreign criminals, solely based on their brief service in the U.S. military. He raises concerns about the lack of oversight and the potential legal and ethical ramifications of such a policy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the lawsuit progresses, it represents not just a quest for transparency, but also a challenge to the ethical and legal standards of immigration policies. It underscores the need for a balanced approach that honors the service of military veterans while also safeguarding the nation’s security and upholding the rule of law. The outcome of this legal battle could have far-reaching implications, potentially setting precedents for how similar cases are handled in the future and ensuring that the government remains accountable to the people it serves.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">The Immigration Reform Law Institute (IRLI) has filed a lawsuit against the Department of Homeland Security (DHS), led by President Joe Biden. The suit alleges that the DHS is concealing critical details about a policy implemented in July 2021, designed to permit certain deported illegal aliens, particularly those who have served in the U.S. Armed Forces, to return to the United States, despite having been previously expelled due to criminal activities. This controversial policy has sparked fierce debate, as critics argue it exploits the American public’s support for military veterans, while potentially compromising national security by allowing individuals with criminal histories back into the country. The IRLI is pushing back, demanding answers and transparency on this issue, with Executive Director Dale Wilcox stating, “This administration has made clear its desire to keep criminal aliens in the country, and now they are exploiting the American people’s support of military veterans to allow more potentially dangerous aliens to stay.” The lawsuit stems from a Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) request submitted by the IRLI in April of this year, seeking access to all documentation, policies, and case details related to the DHS initiative focusing on the return of deported non-citizen veterans. Despite acknowledgment of the request, the DHS has yet to provide any determination, prompting the IRLI to take legal action. The lawsuit, filed in the U.S. District Court for the District of Columbia, highlights a critical issue at the intersection of immigration, national security, and transparency. It asks the federal court to mandate the DHS to disclose all relevant information pertaining to this ‘Special Amnesty’ policy, ensuring that the public is fully informed about the actions and intentions of the administration. Director of Investigations at IRLI, Matt O’Brien, emphasizes the need for scrutiny, questioning the appropriateness of a policy that seemingly grants special treatment to foreign criminals, solely based on their brief service in the U.S. military. He raises concerns about the lack of oversight and the potential legal and ethical ramifications of such a policy. As the lawsuit progresses, it represents not just a quest for transparency, but also a challenge to the ethical and legal standards of immigration policies. It underscores the need for a balanced approach that honors the service of military veterans while also safeguarding the nation’s security and upholding the rule of law. The outcome of this legal battle could have far-reaching implications, potentially setting precedents for how similar cases are handled in the future and ensuring that the government remains accountable to the people it serves.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Urgent Inquiry: House GOP Seeks Clarification on U.S. Weapons Falling into Hamas’ Hands</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/24/US-Weapons-Hamas/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Urgent Inquiry: House GOP Seeks Clarification on U.S. Weapons Falling into Hamas’ Hands" /><published>2023-10-24T08:14:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-24T08:14:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/24/US-Weapons-Hamas</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/24/US-Weapons-Hamas/">&lt;p&gt;House Republicans have taken a bold step to demand answers regarding the alarming trend of U.S. weaponry ending up in the hands of Hamas, a recognized terrorist organization. In a letter addressed to Defense Secretary Lloyd Austin, the representatives have requested a comprehensive briefing to understand the Department of Defense’s (DoD) monitoring strategies and actions taken to prevent American arms from bolstering terrorist activities against Israel, a key ally.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The letter, penned by House Oversight Committee Chairman James Comer (R-Ky.) and Representative Marjorie Taylor Greene (R-Ga.), highlights the urgency of the matter, calling for Austin’s presence on Capitol Hill next Monday. The representatives express their concerns, citing reports of U.S. arms being redirected from conflict zones in Afghanistan and Ukraine to terrorist groups, specifically Hamas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Washington Examiner reported that the letter explicitly mentions the redistribution and resale of U.S.-manufactured weapons in secondary markets, leading to their acquisition by terrorist entities. Comer and Greene are seeking detailed information on the DoD’s “procedures for preventing, addressing, and mitigating weapon diversion abroad.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recent incidents have underscored the gravity of the situation. The Israel Defense Forces (IDF) shared an image captured on October 5, showcasing a Hamas terrorist wielding an M-16, a weapon of U.S. origin, moments before the IDF neutralized the threat. Additionally, a defense official from Ukraine raised alarms about Russia’s involvement, suggesting that Moscow is supplying Hamas with confiscated U.S. trophy weapons from the Ukrainian battlefield — a tactic aimed at tarnishing Ukraine’s reputation among its Western allies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Marjorie Taylor Greene took to social media on October 8, emphasizing the need for collaborative efforts with Israel to trace U.S. weapons used against them, raising questions about their origins – Afghanistan, Ukraine, or possibly both. She underlines the critical need for accountability and stringent tracking to prevent such security lapses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The backdrop to these developments is the chaotic and much-criticized withdrawal of U.S. forces from Afghanistan in August 2021, during which $7.12 billion worth of military equipment was left behind. This equipment, originally intended for the Afghan National Defense and Security Forces, inadvertently armed the Taliban, effectively transforming them into a potential arms supplier for global terrorist networks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In light of the current geopolitical climate, with over $45 billion in military assistance provided to Ukraine since the Russian invasion, House Republicans are keen to prevent a recurrence of the Afghanistan debacle. The State Department, in a statement to Newsweek in June, assured proactive steps are being taken in cooperation with the Ukrainian government to mitigate the risks of weapon diversion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The letter from Comer and Greene signifies a critical inquiry, as they seek transparency and details on these mitigation strategies, ensuring that American weaponry does not inadvertently empower those with malicious intentions against the U.S. and its allies. The outcomes of this inquiry could have significant implications for future military aid and weapon distribution policies, underlining the importance of robust monitoring and accountability in international military engagements.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">House Republicans have taken a bold step to demand answers regarding the alarming trend of U.S. weaponry ending up in the hands of Hamas, a recognized terrorist organization. In a letter addressed to Defense Secretary Lloyd Austin, the representatives have requested a comprehensive briefing to understand the Department of Defense’s (DoD) monitoring strategies and actions taken to prevent American arms from bolstering terrorist activities against Israel, a key ally. The letter, penned by House Oversight Committee Chairman James Comer (R-Ky.) and Representative Marjorie Taylor Greene (R-Ga.), highlights the urgency of the matter, calling for Austin’s presence on Capitol Hill next Monday. The representatives express their concerns, citing reports of U.S. arms being redirected from conflict zones in Afghanistan and Ukraine to terrorist groups, specifically Hamas. The Washington Examiner reported that the letter explicitly mentions the redistribution and resale of U.S.-manufactured weapons in secondary markets, leading to their acquisition by terrorist entities. Comer and Greene are seeking detailed information on the DoD’s “procedures for preventing, addressing, and mitigating weapon diversion abroad.” Recent incidents have underscored the gravity of the situation. The Israel Defense Forces (IDF) shared an image captured on October 5, showcasing a Hamas terrorist wielding an M-16, a weapon of U.S. origin, moments before the IDF neutralized the threat. Additionally, a defense official from Ukraine raised alarms about Russia’s involvement, suggesting that Moscow is supplying Hamas with confiscated U.S. trophy weapons from the Ukrainian battlefield — a tactic aimed at tarnishing Ukraine’s reputation among its Western allies. Marjorie Taylor Greene took to social media on October 8, emphasizing the need for collaborative efforts with Israel to trace U.S. weapons used against them, raising questions about their origins – Afghanistan, Ukraine, or possibly both. She underlines the critical need for accountability and stringent tracking to prevent such security lapses. The backdrop to these developments is the chaotic and much-criticized withdrawal of U.S. forces from Afghanistan in August 2021, during which $7.12 billion worth of military equipment was left behind. This equipment, originally intended for the Afghan National Defense and Security Forces, inadvertently armed the Taliban, effectively transforming them into a potential arms supplier for global terrorist networks. In light of the current geopolitical climate, with over $45 billion in military assistance provided to Ukraine since the Russian invasion, House Republicans are keen to prevent a recurrence of the Afghanistan debacle. The State Department, in a statement to Newsweek in June, assured proactive steps are being taken in cooperation with the Ukrainian government to mitigate the risks of weapon diversion. The letter from Comer and Greene signifies a critical inquiry, as they seek transparency and details on these mitigation strategies, ensuring that American weaponry does not inadvertently empower those with malicious intentions against the U.S. and its allies. The outcomes of this inquiry could have significant implications for future military aid and weapon distribution policies, underlining the importance of robust monitoring and accountability in international military engagements.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Melody and Machines: Music Publishers File Suit Against AI Startup Anthropic</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/24/Music-Giants-Sue-AI/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Melody and Machines: Music Publishers File Suit Against AI Startup Anthropic" /><published>2023-10-24T07:05:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-24T07:05:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/24/Music-Giants-Sue-AI</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/24/Music-Giants-Sue-AI/">&lt;p&gt;Major players in the music publishing world, including Universal Music, ABKCO, and Concord Publishing, have filed a lawsuit against the artificial intelligence startup Anthropic, putting the tech world on notice. The suit alleges that Anthropic unlawfully utilized copyrighted song lyrics from a variety of artists, from Beyonce to Don McLean, to enhance its chatbot technology, known as Claude.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anthropic’s Claude is a sophisticated chatbot designed to interact with users in a natural and intuitive manner. It was trained on a massive corpus of text from the internet, learning to generate responses to user prompts. However, this lawsuit claims that Anthropic stepped over legal boundaries by incorporating lyrics from over 500 distinct songs without obtaining the necessary permissions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The music publishers point out that Claude doesn’t just reproduce copyrighted lyrics in response to direct requests. Its capabilities extend to generating lyrics in response to a wide array of prompts, such as asking it to create songs, provide chord progressions, or craft poetry in the style of particular artists or songwriters. This, they argue, amounts to an unlawful reproduction of copyrighted material.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For instance, when prompted to write a song about the death of rock pioneer Buddy Holly, Claude reportedly provided lyrics from Don McLean’s “American Pie.” The music publishers’ attorney, Matt Oppenheim, was clear on the legal standpoint: “it’s well-established by copyright law that an entity cannot reproduce, distribute, and display someone else’s copyrighted works to build its own business unless it secures permission from rights holders.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This legal battle draws attention to the increasingly complex interactions between artificial intelligence and copyright law, as AI technologies become more advanced and integrated into various sectors of business and creativity. The outcome of this lawsuit could set a significant precedent for how AI startups and tech companies at large handle copyrighted material in their products and services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, this lawsuit comes at a pivotal moment for Anthropic. The AI startup recently entered into a major investment deal with Amazon, which includes making Amazon its primary cloud computing service and providing access to Amazon’s custom chips for training and deploying its generative AI systems. With such technological advancements on the line, the music industry’s lawsuit adds an extra layer of complexity to Anthropic’s path forward, possibly influencing how other AI companies approach the use of copyrighted material in their technologies.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Major players in the music publishing world, including Universal Music, ABKCO, and Concord Publishing, have filed a lawsuit against the artificial intelligence startup Anthropic, putting the tech world on notice. The suit alleges that Anthropic unlawfully utilized copyrighted song lyrics from a variety of artists, from Beyonce to Don McLean, to enhance its chatbot technology, known as Claude. Anthropic’s Claude is a sophisticated chatbot designed to interact with users in a natural and intuitive manner. It was trained on a massive corpus of text from the internet, learning to generate responses to user prompts. However, this lawsuit claims that Anthropic stepped over legal boundaries by incorporating lyrics from over 500 distinct songs without obtaining the necessary permissions. The music publishers point out that Claude doesn’t just reproduce copyrighted lyrics in response to direct requests. Its capabilities extend to generating lyrics in response to a wide array of prompts, such as asking it to create songs, provide chord progressions, or craft poetry in the style of particular artists or songwriters. This, they argue, amounts to an unlawful reproduction of copyrighted material. For instance, when prompted to write a song about the death of rock pioneer Buddy Holly, Claude reportedly provided lyrics from Don McLean’s “American Pie.” The music publishers’ attorney, Matt Oppenheim, was clear on the legal standpoint: “it’s well-established by copyright law that an entity cannot reproduce, distribute, and display someone else’s copyrighted works to build its own business unless it secures permission from rights holders.” This legal battle draws attention to the increasingly complex interactions between artificial intelligence and copyright law, as AI technologies become more advanced and integrated into various sectors of business and creativity. The outcome of this lawsuit could set a significant precedent for how AI startups and tech companies at large handle copyrighted material in their products and services. Furthermore, this lawsuit comes at a pivotal moment for Anthropic. The AI startup recently entered into a major investment deal with Amazon, which includes making Amazon its primary cloud computing service and providing access to Amazon’s custom chips for training and deploying its generative AI systems. With such technological advancements on the line, the music industry’s lawsuit adds an extra layer of complexity to Anthropic’s path forward, possibly influencing how other AI companies approach the use of copyrighted material in their technologies.</summary></entry></feed>