<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-09-08T13:13:24-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/09/08/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-09-08T13:13:24-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-08T13:13:24-04:00</updated><id>/2023/09/08/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/08/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">California’s Assault on the Second Amendment - Imposing an 11% Gun Tax</title><link href="/news/2023/09/08/Gun-Tax-California/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="California’s Assault on the Second Amendment - Imposing an 11% Gun Tax" /><published>2023-09-08T12:58:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-08T12:58:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/08/Gun-Tax-California</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/08/Gun-Tax-California/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;California’s Unsettling Move: Taxing the Right to Bear Arms&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a move many see as an affront to the Second Amendment, the California Senate audaciously approved an 11% tax on guns and ammunition. This legislation, which now returns to the state assembly for another vote, may soon find its way to Gov. Gavin Newsom’s desk for final approval.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Masked Deterrent to Gun Ownership?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Proposed by Assemblyman Jesse Gabriel, this tax appears to be more than a mere revenue-generating endeavor. On the surface, it is touted as a mechanism to enhance “school safety.” However, the specifics on how this tax directly ensures such safety remain conspicuously ambiguous. The underlying message seems clear: make gun ownership more expensive, thus discouraging citizens from exercising their constitutionally protected right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Concerns Overreach&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While California prides itself on being progressive, there’s a thin line between progression and overreach. The state’s already rigid gun laws restrict K-12 educators from bearing arms for the protection of their students. Additionally, concealed carry permit holders face prohibitions against arming themselves on college campuses. With this tax, is California subtly trying to price out the average citizen’s access to their Second Amendment rights?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;California Rifle and Pistol Association President, Chuck Michel, emphatically voiced his concerns, dubbing the move a “poll tax” and likening it to taxing a fundamental constitutional right. Highlighting the gravity of the issue, Michel declared, “We’re going to have to file a lawsuit to challenge it.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Future Under Threat?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the legislation makes its final journey through the state assembly, it serves as a stark reminder of the continuous challenges faced by the Second Amendment. This isn’t merely a debate about a tax; it’s a dialogue about the sanctity of our constitutional rights. If a foundational right can be taxed, what does that spell for the future of our freedoms?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">California’s Unsettling Move: Taxing the Right to Bear Arms In a move many see as an affront to the Second Amendment, the California Senate audaciously approved an 11% tax on guns and ammunition. This legislation, which now returns to the state assembly for another vote, may soon find its way to Gov. Gavin Newsom’s desk for final approval. A Masked Deterrent to Gun Ownership? Proposed by Assemblyman Jesse Gabriel, this tax appears to be more than a mere revenue-generating endeavor. On the surface, it is touted as a mechanism to enhance “school safety.” However, the specifics on how this tax directly ensures such safety remain conspicuously ambiguous. The underlying message seems clear: make gun ownership more expensive, thus discouraging citizens from exercising their constitutionally protected right. Concerns Overreach While California prides itself on being progressive, there’s a thin line between progression and overreach. The state’s already rigid gun laws restrict K-12 educators from bearing arms for the protection of their students. Additionally, concealed carry permit holders face prohibitions against arming themselves on college campuses. With this tax, is California subtly trying to price out the average citizen’s access to their Second Amendment rights? California Rifle and Pistol Association President, Chuck Michel, emphatically voiced his concerns, dubbing the move a “poll tax” and likening it to taxing a fundamental constitutional right. Highlighting the gravity of the issue, Michel declared, “We’re going to have to file a lawsuit to challenge it.” A Future Under Threat? As the legislation makes its final journey through the state assembly, it serves as a stark reminder of the continuous challenges faced by the Second Amendment. This isn’t merely a debate about a tax; it’s a dialogue about the sanctity of our constitutional rights. If a foundational right can be taxed, what does that spell for the future of our freedoms?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Danny Masterson Faces 30-Year Sentence Amidst Controversy</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/08/Danny-Masterson-Sentenced/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Danny Masterson Faces 30-Year Sentence Amidst Controversy" /><published>2023-09-08T11:45:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-08T11:45:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/08/Danny-Masterson-Sentenced</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/08/Danny-Masterson-Sentenced/">&lt;p&gt;In a case that has caught the attention of the entertainment industry and beyond, ‘That ’70s Show’ star, Danny Masterson, has been sentenced to a substantial 30 years in prison after a conviction on charges of rape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Court sketches depicted an emotional scene as actor and model Bijou Phillips, Masterson’s wife, looked on. Masterson was seen blowing a kiss to her just moments before being escorted away. The verdict came after an eight-day deliberation, where a jury found him guilty of two counts of forcible rape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;maximum-punishment-meted-out&quot;&gt;Maximum Punishment Meted Out&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Los Angeles County Superior Court Judge Charlaine Olmedo handed down the 15 years-to-life imprisonment for each count to be served consecutively. This verdict ensures that Masterson will only be eligible for parole after 25 1/2 years, keeping the possibility open for a lifetime sentence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;District Attorney George Gascón lauded the verdict, citing the challenging journey faced by the victims. In his words, the case against Masterson highlights the often-uneven playing field victims face when challenging influential figures. He hopes the verdict brings solace to the victims and serves as a deterrent to others who might exploit their position of power.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-glimmer-of-hope-for-masterson&quot;&gt;A Glimmer of Hope for Masterson?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the severe sentencing, Masterson’s legal team remains optimistic. They’ve voiced concerns about what they perceive as “substantial” errors during the trial and intend to appeal the court’s decision. Shawn Holley, Masterson’s attorney, stressed their respect for the justice system but emphasized that they believe an incorrect verdict was reached in this case. They are confident in their hopes to overturn the convictions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;scientology-in-the-spotlight&quot;&gt;Scientology in the Spotlight&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The trial has not only shone a spotlight on Masterson but also on the Church of Scientology. Accusations flew regarding the Church’s role in the aftermath of the alleged assaults. Victims claimed reluctance in filing charges, pointing fingers at the Church’s strict internal handling of such issues. The Church, however, refuted these claims, stating their clear policy on adhering to the laws of the land and dispelling rumors of harassment of the accusers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;an-emotional-turmoil&quot;&gt;An Emotional Turmoil&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As statements flowed in from various parties, the impact on the victims became evident. Impact statements delivered in court painted a picture of the trauma and emotional scarring these events have left behind. One of the victims stated, “When you raped me, you stole from me,” describing rape as a “theft of the spirit.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Masterson, once a beloved figure on ‘That ’70s Show’, now faces the reality of his actions. As the entertainment industry reflects on another one of its own falling from grace, the broader conversation around power dynamics, consent, and the role of institutions in such cases continues to evolve.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">In a case that has caught the attention of the entertainment industry and beyond, ‘That ’70s Show’ star, Danny Masterson, has been sentenced to a substantial 30 years in prison after a conviction on charges of rape. Court sketches depicted an emotional scene as actor and model Bijou Phillips, Masterson’s wife, looked on. Masterson was seen blowing a kiss to her just moments before being escorted away. The verdict came after an eight-day deliberation, where a jury found him guilty of two counts of forcible rape. Maximum Punishment Meted Out Los Angeles County Superior Court Judge Charlaine Olmedo handed down the 15 years-to-life imprisonment for each count to be served consecutively. This verdict ensures that Masterson will only be eligible for parole after 25 1/2 years, keeping the possibility open for a lifetime sentence. District Attorney George Gascón lauded the verdict, citing the challenging journey faced by the victims. In his words, the case against Masterson highlights the often-uneven playing field victims face when challenging influential figures. He hopes the verdict brings solace to the victims and serves as a deterrent to others who might exploit their position of power. A Glimmer of Hope for Masterson? Despite the severe sentencing, Masterson’s legal team remains optimistic. They’ve voiced concerns about what they perceive as “substantial” errors during the trial and intend to appeal the court’s decision. Shawn Holley, Masterson’s attorney, stressed their respect for the justice system but emphasized that they believe an incorrect verdict was reached in this case. They are confident in their hopes to overturn the convictions. Scientology in the Spotlight The trial has not only shone a spotlight on Masterson but also on the Church of Scientology. Accusations flew regarding the Church’s role in the aftermath of the alleged assaults. Victims claimed reluctance in filing charges, pointing fingers at the Church’s strict internal handling of such issues. The Church, however, refuted these claims, stating their clear policy on adhering to the laws of the land and dispelling rumors of harassment of the accusers. An Emotional Turmoil As statements flowed in from various parties, the impact on the victims became evident. Impact statements delivered in court painted a picture of the trauma and emotional scarring these events have left behind. One of the victims stated, “When you raped me, you stole from me,” describing rape as a “theft of the spirit.” Masterson, once a beloved figure on ‘That ’70s Show’, now faces the reality of his actions. As the entertainment industry reflects on another one of its own falling from grace, the broader conversation around power dynamics, consent, and the role of institutions in such cases continues to evolve.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Rep. Jim Jordan Fights for Transparency Amid Controversial Attorney Dealings</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/08/Jordan-Seeks-Truth/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rep. Jim Jordan Fights for Transparency Amid Controversial Attorney Dealings" /><published>2023-09-08T10:59:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-08T10:59:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/08/Jordan-Seeks-Truth</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/08/Jordan-Seeks-Truth/">&lt;p&gt;In recent political updates, the House Judiciary Committee, led by Rep. Jim Jordan, R-Ohio, is pushing for more clarity. They’re asking Jack Smith’s office, the special counsel, for more details about their relationship with attorney Stanley Woodward. This move comes right after news outlets shared that Woodward raised concerns over how the prosecution was behaving.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To give a bit of background, Woodward was once the attorney for Yuscil Taveras. Taveras worked in IT at Donald Trump’s Mar-a-Lago estate. Around the same time, Woodward also represented another Mar-a-Lago employee, Walt Nauta. Because of fears that Woodward could be conflicted, the court decided to let Taveras talk to another lawyer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This ended up leading to Taveras agreeing to work with the prosecutors. That didn’t sit well with Woodward, and they parted ways. What’s more, prosecutors are hinting that Taveras might speak out in court, thanks to the agreement. This creates another pickle for Woodward. Why? Well, it means an old client might speak against a current client.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But the story gets deeper. This IT worker, Taveras, had earlier pointed fingers at Trump, Nauta, and another employee, Carlos de Oliveira. This testimony played a big role in more charges against Trump.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On top of all this, Woodward has shared that he felt the heat from a Justice Department official named Jay Bratt. This happened after Woodward mentioned applying for a job at the D.C. superior court. This chat was all about his client, Nauta.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Jim Jordan is stepping up to the plate. He sent a letter on Thursday asking for all talks between Woodward and the prosecutors about Nauta. He also wants to see what top Justice Department officials have said about Woodward’s clients. He’s hoping to get all this info by September 21st.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s clear that Rep. Jim Jordan and the House Judiciary Committee are standing up for justice and transparency. They’re working to make sure everything is above board in these complex legal matters.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In recent political updates, the House Judiciary Committee, led by Rep. Jim Jordan, R-Ohio, is pushing for more clarity. They’re asking Jack Smith’s office, the special counsel, for more details about their relationship with attorney Stanley Woodward. This move comes right after news outlets shared that Woodward raised concerns over how the prosecution was behaving. To give a bit of background, Woodward was once the attorney for Yuscil Taveras. Taveras worked in IT at Donald Trump’s Mar-a-Lago estate. Around the same time, Woodward also represented another Mar-a-Lago employee, Walt Nauta. Because of fears that Woodward could be conflicted, the court decided to let Taveras talk to another lawyer. This ended up leading to Taveras agreeing to work with the prosecutors. That didn’t sit well with Woodward, and they parted ways. What’s more, prosecutors are hinting that Taveras might speak out in court, thanks to the agreement. This creates another pickle for Woodward. Why? Well, it means an old client might speak against a current client. But the story gets deeper. This IT worker, Taveras, had earlier pointed fingers at Trump, Nauta, and another employee, Carlos de Oliveira. This testimony played a big role in more charges against Trump. On top of all this, Woodward has shared that he felt the heat from a Justice Department official named Jay Bratt. This happened after Woodward mentioned applying for a job at the D.C. superior court. This chat was all about his client, Nauta. Rep. Jim Jordan is stepping up to the plate. He sent a letter on Thursday asking for all talks between Woodward and the prosecutors about Nauta. He also wants to see what top Justice Department officials have said about Woodward’s clients. He’s hoping to get all this info by September 21st. It’s clear that Rep. Jim Jordan and the House Judiciary Committee are standing up for justice and transparency. They’re working to make sure everything is above board in these complex legal matters.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Political Playbook? Peter Navarro’s Contempt Conviction Raises Eyebrows</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/08/Navarro-Political-Play/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Political Playbook? Peter Navarro’s Contempt Conviction Raises Eyebrows" /><published>2023-09-08T10:03:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-08T10:03:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/08/Navarro-Political-Play</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/08/Navarro-Political-Play/">&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON, DC: Another chapter in the ongoing investigation by the January 6 Committee seems to reek of political maneuvering. Peter Navarro, former economic adviser to President Trump, was convicted on two counts of criminal contempt of Congress, leading many to question if this is a genuine pursuit of justice or a politically motivated attack on Trump’s closest allies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last year saw Navarro and Dan Scavino, another former White House aide, held in contempt by Congress. This conviction is eerily reminiscent of the trial and subsequent conviction of Steve Bannon, another Trump adviser.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the backdrop of these convictions, Navarro’s perspective on January 6 stands out. He has openly stated in interviews that Trump loyalists aimed to utilize the Capitol’s peaceful protest as leverage. The goal? To pressure Congress and Vice President Mike Pence into rejecting the Electoral College votes from states contested by the Trump campaign. Contrary to the narrative spun by the January 6 Committee, Navarro emphasizes that the unforeseen violence that transpired acted against their intentions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet, the jury’s verdict came swiftly. After just five hours, Navarro was found guilty, with sentencing scheduled for January 12, 2024. The possible consequences? A year behind bars and fines reaching $100,000.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Federal prosecutors were quick to point out the necessity of adhering to congressional subpoenas during their closing arguments, stating, “Our government only works when people play by the rules.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, Navarro’s defense attorney, Stanley Woodward, presented a counter-narrative. He built his case around the terms “accident, mistake, or inadvertence,” hinting that the charges against Navarro lacked substantial evidence. Woodward’s assertion that the government failed to provide adequate proof of Navarro’s deliberate non-compliance was hard-hitting. He concluded with the suggestive remark, “Something stinks.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This case, and others like it, have fueled a growing sentiment that the January 6 Committee’s aggressive probes may be politically charged. Is the aim genuinely to uphold justice, or is there an ulterior motive targeting Trump’s inner circle? As the drama unfolds, the nation watches closely, waiting for clarity.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">WASHINGTON, DC: Another chapter in the ongoing investigation by the January 6 Committee seems to reek of political maneuvering. Peter Navarro, former economic adviser to President Trump, was convicted on two counts of criminal contempt of Congress, leading many to question if this is a genuine pursuit of justice or a politically motivated attack on Trump’s closest allies. Last year saw Navarro and Dan Scavino, another former White House aide, held in contempt by Congress. This conviction is eerily reminiscent of the trial and subsequent conviction of Steve Bannon, another Trump adviser. In the backdrop of these convictions, Navarro’s perspective on January 6 stands out. He has openly stated in interviews that Trump loyalists aimed to utilize the Capitol’s peaceful protest as leverage. The goal? To pressure Congress and Vice President Mike Pence into rejecting the Electoral College votes from states contested by the Trump campaign. Contrary to the narrative spun by the January 6 Committee, Navarro emphasizes that the unforeseen violence that transpired acted against their intentions. Yet, the jury’s verdict came swiftly. After just five hours, Navarro was found guilty, with sentencing scheduled for January 12, 2024. The possible consequences? A year behind bars and fines reaching $100,000. Federal prosecutors were quick to point out the necessity of adhering to congressional subpoenas during their closing arguments, stating, “Our government only works when people play by the rules.” However, Navarro’s defense attorney, Stanley Woodward, presented a counter-narrative. He built his case around the terms “accident, mistake, or inadvertence,” hinting that the charges against Navarro lacked substantial evidence. Woodward’s assertion that the government failed to provide adequate proof of Navarro’s deliberate non-compliance was hard-hitting. He concluded with the suggestive remark, “Something stinks.” This case, and others like it, have fueled a growing sentiment that the January 6 Committee’s aggressive probes may be politically charged. Is the aim genuinely to uphold justice, or is there an ulterior motive targeting Trump’s inner circle? As the drama unfolds, the nation watches closely, waiting for clarity.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">O’Hare Airport - From Busy Hub to Migrant Crisis Epicenter?</title><link href="/news/2023/09/08/Chicago-Migrant-Crisis/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="O’Hare Airport - From Busy Hub to Migrant Crisis Epicenter?" /><published>2023-09-08T09:06:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-08T09:06:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/08/Chicago-Migrant-Crisis</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/08/Chicago-Migrant-Crisis/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Is This the Right Solution? Chicago’s Questionable Move Amidst Soaring Migrant Influx&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The vibrant and bustling O’Hare International Airport, typically known for jet-setters and travel stories, is now a makeshift migrant shelter. A shocking revelation has left many Chicago residents flabbergasted. The city, already grappling with its own challenges, is using one of the nation’s most active airports to house migrants, with numbers increasing from 31 to over 400 in a month.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Befuddled City Leadership?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chicago leaders have made a series of questionable decisions in the recent past, but using O’Hare as a shelter might just top the list. William Kelly, a Chicago reporter, gave a candid account of the situation during his appearance on “Fox &amp;amp; Friends.” Behind the black curtains, far from the public’s view, is a rapidly growing migrant holding area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shockingly, while the city was quick to crack down on its homeless American citizens seeking refuge at the airport, they now seem to be rolling out the red carpet for migrants. As Kelly aptly puts it, the priorities seem misplaced. Mayor Johnson, hailed as “the people’s mayor” during his campaign, appears to have shifted gears, prompting Kelly to dub him “the migrants’ mayor.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Safety, Transparency, and Financial Concerns&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The city’s approach not only raises humanitarian concerns but also logistical and safety ones. Are migrants undergoing the same stringent security checks as American travelers? With Chicago already wrestling with a rising crime rate, and the burdens of post-pandemic recovery, this added layer of complexity could further strain the city’s resources.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kelly highlights the opaque nature of city spending on the crisis, wondering aloud about the trajectory of the “millions upon millions” being spent. Mayor Johnson’s reticence to clarify matters has only fanned the flames of discontent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Broader Citywide Crisis&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kelly’s chilling description of a scene reminiscent of “Mad Max” outside his window speaks volumes about the city’s dire state. With police resources stretched thin, handling both migrants and criminal elements has become a juggling act, putting the safety of Chicago residents at risk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other reports further cement the gravity of the situation. An overwhelming 14,000 migrants have poured into Chicago since August, and the city, despite its 15 asylum seeker shelters, struggles to keep pace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Vianney Marzullo, from the Police Station Response Team, asserts that O’Hare is merely a holding space for incoming flights, one can’t help but question the foresight and planning of city leadership.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With another shelter slated to open next month, one wonders if Chicago is truly prepared to handle its migrant influx while simultaneously addressing the needs and concerns of its citizens.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Is This the Right Solution? Chicago’s Questionable Move Amidst Soaring Migrant Influx The vibrant and bustling O’Hare International Airport, typically known for jet-setters and travel stories, is now a makeshift migrant shelter. A shocking revelation has left many Chicago residents flabbergasted. The city, already grappling with its own challenges, is using one of the nation’s most active airports to house migrants, with numbers increasing from 31 to over 400 in a month. A Befuddled City Leadership? Chicago leaders have made a series of questionable decisions in the recent past, but using O’Hare as a shelter might just top the list. William Kelly, a Chicago reporter, gave a candid account of the situation during his appearance on “Fox &amp;amp; Friends.” Behind the black curtains, far from the public’s view, is a rapidly growing migrant holding area. Shockingly, while the city was quick to crack down on its homeless American citizens seeking refuge at the airport, they now seem to be rolling out the red carpet for migrants. As Kelly aptly puts it, the priorities seem misplaced. Mayor Johnson, hailed as “the people’s mayor” during his campaign, appears to have shifted gears, prompting Kelly to dub him “the migrants’ mayor.” Safety, Transparency, and Financial Concerns The city’s approach not only raises humanitarian concerns but also logistical and safety ones. Are migrants undergoing the same stringent security checks as American travelers? With Chicago already wrestling with a rising crime rate, and the burdens of post-pandemic recovery, this added layer of complexity could further strain the city’s resources. Kelly highlights the opaque nature of city spending on the crisis, wondering aloud about the trajectory of the “millions upon millions” being spent. Mayor Johnson’s reticence to clarify matters has only fanned the flames of discontent. A Broader Citywide Crisis Kelly’s chilling description of a scene reminiscent of “Mad Max” outside his window speaks volumes about the city’s dire state. With police resources stretched thin, handling both migrants and criminal elements has become a juggling act, putting the safety of Chicago residents at risk. Other reports further cement the gravity of the situation. An overwhelming 14,000 migrants have poured into Chicago since August, and the city, despite its 15 asylum seeker shelters, struggles to keep pace. While Vianney Marzullo, from the Police Station Response Team, asserts that O’Hare is merely a holding space for incoming flights, one can’t help but question the foresight and planning of city leadership. With another shelter slated to open next month, one wonders if Chicago is truly prepared to handle its migrant influx while simultaneously addressing the needs and concerns of its citizens.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Another Mar-a-Lago Drama - Real Investigation or Political Theatre?</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/07/Investigation-Theater/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Another Mar-a-Lago Drama - Real Investigation or Political Theatre?" /><published>2023-09-07T19:54:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-07T19:54:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/07/Investigation-Theater</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/07/Investigation-Theater/">&lt;p&gt;Amidst the relentless political theater that has defined much of post-presidential life for Donald Trump, a new act has commenced. CNN reported that Yuscil Taveras, an IT worker from Mar-a-Lago, has agreed to cooperate with special counsel Jack Smith against Trump. Yet, the intricacies of the case and the timing of the investigation leave many observers skeptical.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What we’ve come to understand is that Taveras initially made a statement which eventually led to the indictment of the former President and his close associate, Walt Nauta, concerning alleged mishandling of classified data. But here’s the kicker: Taveras is now exempt from prosecution on perjury charges in exchange for his testimony. The question many are asking is, why the sudden shift?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Taveras’ attorney, Stanley Woodward, who also represents other witnesses in this probe, pointedly remarked on the special treatment for Taveras. “It is telling that the Non-Prosecution Agreement it ultimately offered Trump Employee 4 was not offered before the District Court had agreed to appoint ‘conflict counsel,’” he observed, referencing Taveras.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back in July, the narrative took a turn when Taveras accused the former president of instructing others to request the deletion of certain security footage. Yet, a filing from Smith in August revealed that Taveras had previously “denied or claimed not to recall any contacts or conversations about the security footage at Mar-a-Lago.” It was only after learning he might be the target of a perjury investigation that Taveras reversed course.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stanley Woodward, in light of these developments, stated he “played no role” in Taveras’ choice to cooperate. But one has to wonder: Is this about genuine concerns over national security, or are we watching another high-stakes political game at play?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For many, the ordeal appears as another episode in a series of attempts to undermine the legacy of Trump. And as the case unfolds, the public will be eagerly watching, questioning the true intentions behind this investigation.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Amidst the relentless political theater that has defined much of post-presidential life for Donald Trump, a new act has commenced. CNN reported that Yuscil Taveras, an IT worker from Mar-a-Lago, has agreed to cooperate with special counsel Jack Smith against Trump. Yet, the intricacies of the case and the timing of the investigation leave many observers skeptical. What we’ve come to understand is that Taveras initially made a statement which eventually led to the indictment of the former President and his close associate, Walt Nauta, concerning alleged mishandling of classified data. But here’s the kicker: Taveras is now exempt from prosecution on perjury charges in exchange for his testimony. The question many are asking is, why the sudden shift? Taveras’ attorney, Stanley Woodward, who also represents other witnesses in this probe, pointedly remarked on the special treatment for Taveras. “It is telling that the Non-Prosecution Agreement it ultimately offered Trump Employee 4 was not offered before the District Court had agreed to appoint ‘conflict counsel,’” he observed, referencing Taveras. Back in July, the narrative took a turn when Taveras accused the former president of instructing others to request the deletion of certain security footage. Yet, a filing from Smith in August revealed that Taveras had previously “denied or claimed not to recall any contacts or conversations about the security footage at Mar-a-Lago.” It was only after learning he might be the target of a perjury investigation that Taveras reversed course. Stanley Woodward, in light of these developments, stated he “played no role” in Taveras’ choice to cooperate. But one has to wonder: Is this about genuine concerns over national security, or are we watching another high-stakes political game at play? For many, the ordeal appears as another episode in a series of attempts to undermine the legacy of Trump. And as the case unfolds, the public will be eagerly watching, questioning the true intentions behind this investigation.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Desert Despair - Burning Man Festival Faces Backlash Over Abandoned Cars and Waste</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/07/Burning-Man-Controversy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Desert Despair - Burning Man Festival Faces Backlash Over Abandoned Cars and Waste" /><published>2023-09-07T18:48:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-07T18:48:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/07/Burning-Man-Controversy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/07/Burning-Man-Controversy/">&lt;p&gt;Burning Man, the iconic annual art and music festival held in Nevada’s Black Rock desert, is no stranger to controversy. However, this year’s edition has come under intense scrutiny due to the environmental mess left behind by tens of thousands of attendees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pershing County Sheriff Jerry Allen voiced his disappointment and concern about the piles of trash and numerous abandoned vehicles littering the desert. The attendees reportedly left in haste, trying to escape the harsh desert conditions worsened by an unexpected storm. Allen conveyed his observations to the San Francisco Chronicle, describing the behavior of the departing festival-goers as inconsiderate and even hostile.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sheriff Allen pointed out the irony of the situation, stating that such behavior blatantly contradicts the ten principles of Burning Man, which emphasize community, self-reliance, and leaving no trace. While it’s a known fact that Burning Man occasionally leaves traces of debris stretching to Reno and beyond, the aftermath of this year’s festival has been exceptionally alarming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“This year is a little different in that there are numerous vehicles strewn all throughout the playa for several miles,” Allen commented.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a further indictment, Allen placed a portion of the responsibility on the Burning Man organizers. He believes they should be held accountable for ensuring a thorough cleanup of the area after the event concludes each year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the event’s challenges didn’t end there. The storm at the festival’s peak led to a tragic incident resulting in the death of a 32-year-old man, identified as Leon Reece. While festival and medical personnel tried to resuscitate him, the severe weather conditions delayed authorities’ access to the scene, complicating the situation further.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The unfortunate combination of environmental neglect and a tragic death has cast a shadow over this year’s Burning Man festival. As the aftermath unfolds, it brings to light the essential question of responsibility and sustainability for large-scale events held in fragile environments.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Burning Man, the iconic annual art and music festival held in Nevada’s Black Rock desert, is no stranger to controversy. However, this year’s edition has come under intense scrutiny due to the environmental mess left behind by tens of thousands of attendees. Pershing County Sheriff Jerry Allen voiced his disappointment and concern about the piles of trash and numerous abandoned vehicles littering the desert. The attendees reportedly left in haste, trying to escape the harsh desert conditions worsened by an unexpected storm. Allen conveyed his observations to the San Francisco Chronicle, describing the behavior of the departing festival-goers as inconsiderate and even hostile. Sheriff Allen pointed out the irony of the situation, stating that such behavior blatantly contradicts the ten principles of Burning Man, which emphasize community, self-reliance, and leaving no trace. While it’s a known fact that Burning Man occasionally leaves traces of debris stretching to Reno and beyond, the aftermath of this year’s festival has been exceptionally alarming. “This year is a little different in that there are numerous vehicles strewn all throughout the playa for several miles,” Allen commented. In a further indictment, Allen placed a portion of the responsibility on the Burning Man organizers. He believes they should be held accountable for ensuring a thorough cleanup of the area after the event concludes each year. However, the event’s challenges didn’t end there. The storm at the festival’s peak led to a tragic incident resulting in the death of a 32-year-old man, identified as Leon Reece. While festival and medical personnel tried to resuscitate him, the severe weather conditions delayed authorities’ access to the scene, complicating the situation further. The unfortunate combination of environmental neglect and a tragic death has cast a shadow over this year’s Burning Man festival. As the aftermath unfolds, it brings to light the essential question of responsibility and sustainability for large-scale events held in fragile environments.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Targeting Alito - Democratic Senator’s Controversial Ethics Accusations</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/07/Alito-Under-Fire/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Targeting Alito - Democratic Senator’s Controversial Ethics Accusations" /><published>2023-09-07T17:54:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-07T17:54:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/07/Alito-Under-Fire</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/07/Alito-Under-Fire/">&lt;p&gt;In what some view as a partisan maneuver, Democratic Senator Sheldon Whitehouse has lodged an ethics complaint against esteemed Supreme Court Justice Samuel Alito.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Rhode Island Senator, who chairs the Senate Judiciary Courts Subcommittee, sent a letter to Supreme Court Chief Justice John Roberts. The letter criticizes Justice Alito primarily for his open criticism of Whitehouse’s proposed Supreme Court ethics reform bill.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whitehouse’s letter insinuates, without clear evidence, that Justice Alito might be part of a “coordinated effort” against congressional action. This move has raised eyebrows in political circles and made many wonder about the genuine intent behind such a complaint.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Justice Alito, known for his commitment to justice and the Constitution, categorically denies the allegations. He has unambiguously stated that the Constitution does not give Congress the power to regulate the Supreme Court. Furthermore, he proactively addressed an issue concerning a 2008 fishing trip, with Republican billionaire Paul Singer, clarifying that it did not necessitate any financial disclosure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A concerning point in this episode is the absence of a formal procedure to file complaints against Supreme Court justices, possibly allowing room for politically-motivated maneuvers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whitehouse’s allegations, which carry a discernible partisan tone, suggest Alito might have opined on issues that could come before the Court. Additionally, he hints at the Justice’s alleged acceptance of gifts from conservative billionaires, painting it as a potential ethical issue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The “Supreme Court Ethics, Recusal, and Transparency Act,” S.359, currently under Senate scrutiny, seems to play a central role in this narrative. This bill, seeking to overhaul the Court’s ethical standards, secured a nod from the Senate Judiciary Committee in July.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A ProPublica report, viewed by some as biased against conservative figures, insinuated that Alito may have enjoyed certain privileges, like private jet travels, from particular billionaires. In these divisive times, it remains crucial to evaluate such claims with an unbiased lens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As this situation unfolds, the importance of safeguarding the integrity of the judiciary from potentially politically-driven allegations stands clear, ensuring that our Supreme Court remains an emblem of unbiased justice.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In what some view as a partisan maneuver, Democratic Senator Sheldon Whitehouse has lodged an ethics complaint against esteemed Supreme Court Justice Samuel Alito. The Rhode Island Senator, who chairs the Senate Judiciary Courts Subcommittee, sent a letter to Supreme Court Chief Justice John Roberts. The letter criticizes Justice Alito primarily for his open criticism of Whitehouse’s proposed Supreme Court ethics reform bill. Whitehouse’s letter insinuates, without clear evidence, that Justice Alito might be part of a “coordinated effort” against congressional action. This move has raised eyebrows in political circles and made many wonder about the genuine intent behind such a complaint. Justice Alito, known for his commitment to justice and the Constitution, categorically denies the allegations. He has unambiguously stated that the Constitution does not give Congress the power to regulate the Supreme Court. Furthermore, he proactively addressed an issue concerning a 2008 fishing trip, with Republican billionaire Paul Singer, clarifying that it did not necessitate any financial disclosure. A concerning point in this episode is the absence of a formal procedure to file complaints against Supreme Court justices, possibly allowing room for politically-motivated maneuvers. Whitehouse’s allegations, which carry a discernible partisan tone, suggest Alito might have opined on issues that could come before the Court. Additionally, he hints at the Justice’s alleged acceptance of gifts from conservative billionaires, painting it as a potential ethical issue. The “Supreme Court Ethics, Recusal, and Transparency Act,” S.359, currently under Senate scrutiny, seems to play a central role in this narrative. This bill, seeking to overhaul the Court’s ethical standards, secured a nod from the Senate Judiciary Committee in July. A ProPublica report, viewed by some as biased against conservative figures, insinuated that Alito may have enjoyed certain privileges, like private jet travels, from particular billionaires. In these divisive times, it remains crucial to evaluate such claims with an unbiased lens. As this situation unfolds, the importance of safeguarding the integrity of the judiciary from potentially politically-driven allegations stands clear, ensuring that our Supreme Court remains an emblem of unbiased justice.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump Shows Steadfast Confidence - Ready to Testify in Classified Documents Case</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/07/Trump-Testify/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump Shows Steadfast Confidence - Ready to Testify in Classified Documents Case" /><published>2023-09-07T16:59:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-07T16:59:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/07/Trump-Testify</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/07/Trump-Testify/">&lt;p&gt;In a steadfast show of confidence and transparency, former President Donald Trump recently revealed that he is prepared to testify in his own defense over a controversial trial concerning classified documents. This move, while risky, serves as a testament to Trump’s enduring commitment to clear his name and face his accusers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a conversation with the renowned conservative radio host Hugh Hewitt, Trump declared, “I look forward to testifying.” This powerful statement comes amidst mounting allegations of mishandling sensitive national security documents at his Mar-a-Lago resort post his presidential tenure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The case is one among the four criminal trials that Trump might face in the coming year. Still, the former President remains steadfast in his belief of innocence, denouncing all the charges against him. Not only has he pleaded not guilty to every accusation, but he has also raised concerns about being singled out for political reasons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This isn’t the first time Trump has demonstrated a readiness to stand up and face inquiries head-on. In 2018, he indicated his willingness to communicate under oath with the then U.S. Special Counsel Robert Mueller regarding potential links between his 2016 presidential campaign and the Russian government. Though Trump did not eventually speak with the prosecutors and was exempt from any charges in that investigation, his initial inclination to testify reveals a consistent pattern of his confrontational stance in defending his honor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many would see Trump’s choice to testify as a gamble, given the potential for prosecutors to try and extract compromising information from him under oath. However, in Trump’s perspective, it might be an opportunity to directly challenge the allegations and underscore his claims of a politically motivated agenda against him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the 2024 Presidential race on the horizon and Trump leading as the Republican front-runner, these trials and his decisions could play a pivotal role in the political narrative leading up to the elections.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a steadfast show of confidence and transparency, former President Donald Trump recently revealed that he is prepared to testify in his own defense over a controversial trial concerning classified documents. This move, while risky, serves as a testament to Trump’s enduring commitment to clear his name and face his accusers. In a conversation with the renowned conservative radio host Hugh Hewitt, Trump declared, “I look forward to testifying.” This powerful statement comes amidst mounting allegations of mishandling sensitive national security documents at his Mar-a-Lago resort post his presidential tenure. The case is one among the four criminal trials that Trump might face in the coming year. Still, the former President remains steadfast in his belief of innocence, denouncing all the charges against him. Not only has he pleaded not guilty to every accusation, but he has also raised concerns about being singled out for political reasons. This isn’t the first time Trump has demonstrated a readiness to stand up and face inquiries head-on. In 2018, he indicated his willingness to communicate under oath with the then U.S. Special Counsel Robert Mueller regarding potential links between his 2016 presidential campaign and the Russian government. Though Trump did not eventually speak with the prosecutors and was exempt from any charges in that investigation, his initial inclination to testify reveals a consistent pattern of his confrontational stance in defending his honor. Many would see Trump’s choice to testify as a gamble, given the potential for prosecutors to try and extract compromising information from him under oath. However, in Trump’s perspective, it might be an opportunity to directly challenge the allegations and underscore his claims of a politically motivated agenda against him. With the 2024 Presidential race on the horizon and Trump leading as the Republican front-runner, these trials and his decisions could play a pivotal role in the political narrative leading up to the elections.</summary></entry></feed>