<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-09-14T16:16:11-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/09/14/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-09-14T16:16:11-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-14T16:16:11-04:00</updated><id>/2023/09/14/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/14/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">McCarthy Rallies GOP for Biden Impeachment Inquiry - ‘Logical Next Step’</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/14/McCarthy-Biden-Impeachment/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="McCarthy Rallies GOP for Biden Impeachment Inquiry - ‘Logical Next Step’" /><published>2023-09-14T16:09:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-14T16:09:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/14/McCarthy-Biden-Impeachment</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/14/McCarthy-Biden-Impeachment/">&lt;p&gt;In a significant political move, House Speaker Kevin McCarthy is set to advocate for an impeachment inquiry into President Joe Biden. Labeling it as the “logical next step”, McCarthy aims to rally the GOP’s support in a formal investigation into the numerous allegations against the Biden family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Leadership Meeting to Decide the Path Forward&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During an 8 AM closed-door leadership session scheduled for Thursday, McCarthy will brief fellow House Republicans on the findings by House Oversight Committee Chair Jamie Comer (R-KY) and House Judiciary Committee Chair Jim Jordan (R-OH). These findings, as reported by Punchbowl News, are believed to be substantial enough to warrant a formalized impeachment inquiry to secure the Bidens’ bank records and other pivotal documents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, gaining the necessary 218 House Republicans’ support for this inquiry might be a tall order. Several moderate Republicans, such as Reps. Ken Buck (Colo.) and Don Bacon (Neb.), have voiced their doubts regarding the necessity of an impeachment inquiry. Buck, speaking to MSNBC, stated, “The time for impeachment is the time when there’s evidence linking President Biden — if there’s evidence linking President Biden — to a high crime or misdemeanor. That doesn’t exist right now.” Furthermore, Bacon told Politico, “As of now I don’t support [an impeachment inquiry]. An inquiry should be based on evidence of a crime that points directly to President Biden…”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Growing Support and Allegations&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contrarily, many GOP members appear to be in favor of an impeachment inquiry. As Rep. Nancy Mace (R-SC) pointed out to CNN, the primary purpose of the inquiry would be to gather more evidence. She emphasized the need for transparency, stating, “Any piece of evidence, right or wrong, I want the American people to see all of it, whether it backs us up or not.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The myriad of accusations against Joe Biden range from photographs, texts, videos, audio recordings, and various testimonies. These include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Biden family suspicious activity reports regarding wire transfers.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Numerous pieces of communication, including emails, texts, and WhatsApp messages.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Allegations from former business partners, including references to Joe Biden as the “big guy.”&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A multitude of whistleblower testimonies.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Video clips showcasing Joe Biden discussing the firing of a Ukrainian prosecutor.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Allegations related to Biden family’s financial transactions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recent CNN survey data illustrates a split perception among Americans. 61% believe Joe Biden was involved in his family’s business dealings with China and Ukraine, while only 38% consider him uninvolved. A meager 1% believe he was involved but acted without any wrongdoing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The proposed impeachment inquiry, if green-lighted, is poised to significantly shape the political landscape. Whether it unearths groundbreaking revelations or serves as another political maneuver remains to be seen.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a significant political move, House Speaker Kevin McCarthy is set to advocate for an impeachment inquiry into President Joe Biden. Labeling it as the “logical next step”, McCarthy aims to rally the GOP’s support in a formal investigation into the numerous allegations against the Biden family. Leadership Meeting to Decide the Path Forward During an 8 AM closed-door leadership session scheduled for Thursday, McCarthy will brief fellow House Republicans on the findings by House Oversight Committee Chair Jamie Comer (R-KY) and House Judiciary Committee Chair Jim Jordan (R-OH). These findings, as reported by Punchbowl News, are believed to be substantial enough to warrant a formalized impeachment inquiry to secure the Bidens’ bank records and other pivotal documents. However, gaining the necessary 218 House Republicans’ support for this inquiry might be a tall order. Several moderate Republicans, such as Reps. Ken Buck (Colo.) and Don Bacon (Neb.), have voiced their doubts regarding the necessity of an impeachment inquiry. Buck, speaking to MSNBC, stated, “The time for impeachment is the time when there’s evidence linking President Biden — if there’s evidence linking President Biden — to a high crime or misdemeanor. That doesn’t exist right now.” Furthermore, Bacon told Politico, “As of now I don’t support [an impeachment inquiry]. An inquiry should be based on evidence of a crime that points directly to President Biden…” Growing Support and Allegations Contrarily, many GOP members appear to be in favor of an impeachment inquiry. As Rep. Nancy Mace (R-SC) pointed out to CNN, the primary purpose of the inquiry would be to gather more evidence. She emphasized the need for transparency, stating, “Any piece of evidence, right or wrong, I want the American people to see all of it, whether it backs us up or not.” The myriad of accusations against Joe Biden range from photographs, texts, videos, audio recordings, and various testimonies. These include: Biden family suspicious activity reports regarding wire transfers. Numerous pieces of communication, including emails, texts, and WhatsApp messages. Allegations from former business partners, including references to Joe Biden as the “big guy.” A multitude of whistleblower testimonies. Video clips showcasing Joe Biden discussing the firing of a Ukrainian prosecutor. Allegations related to Biden family’s financial transactions. Recent CNN survey data illustrates a split perception among Americans. 61% believe Joe Biden was involved in his family’s business dealings with China and Ukraine, while only 38% consider him uninvolved. A meager 1% believe he was involved but acted without any wrongdoing. The proposed impeachment inquiry, if green-lighted, is poised to significantly shape the political landscape. Whether it unearths groundbreaking revelations or serves as another political maneuver remains to be seen.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Justin Timberlake and Megan Thee Stallion Spark VMA Buzz - Feud or Friendly Banter?</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/14/Timberlake-Stallion-VMA/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Justin Timberlake and Megan Thee Stallion Spark VMA Buzz - Feud or Friendly Banter?" /><published>2023-09-14T15:02:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-14T15:02:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/14/Timberlake-Stallion-VMA</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/14/Timberlake-Stallion-VMA/">&lt;p&gt;When iconic moments and Hollywood’s brightest stars collide at events like the MTV Video Music Awards, the internet doesn’t stay silent. This year, all eyes (and lenses) were on Justin Timberlake and Megan Thee Stallion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A backstage video, making its rounds on social media, captured Timberlake and Stallion deep in conversation, with Megan’s hand gestures making it a particularly animated chat. This led the rumor mill to spin tales of a possible feud between the two artists.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2023/09/720/405/justin-timberlake-megan-thee-stallion-vmas.jpg?ve=1&amp;amp;tl=1&quot; alt=&quot;Megan and Timberlake at VMAs&quot; /&gt;(Kevin Mazur/Jason Kempin/Getty Images)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But were these speculations accurate?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Insiders quickly debunked the feud theory. A close source clarified to news outlets, “Meg loves Justin. She was excitedly saying they’d never met before.” A simple conversation turned misconstrued, it seems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the age of social media clarity, both artists hopped onto TikTok, where Stallion shared a video of their interaction. Her caption? A light-hearted “I just talk with my hands lol. See ya next time @JustinTimberlake.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The VMAs were not just about this fleeting moment, though. Megan Thee Stallion had two nominations, but the awards evaded her this time around.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But perhaps the most nostalgic and electrifying segment of the night was Timberlake’s reunion with NSYNC, as they presented the best pop video award. Memories of their first VMA win for ‘Bye Bye Bye’ flooded back, as JC Chasez reminisced, “Over 20 years ago, we were just kids when we won.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2023/09/720/405/nsync-vmas.jpg?ve=1&amp;amp;tl=1&quot; alt=&quot;NSYNC Reunion at VMAs&quot; /&gt;(John Shearer/Getty Images for MTV)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The evening culminated with Taylor Swift snagging the coveted Moonman statuette for her track “Anti-Hero.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the glam and glitter of the VMAs, one thing’s for sure: whether it’s addressing rumors or celebrating old memories, music always finds a way to bring people together.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">When iconic moments and Hollywood’s brightest stars collide at events like the MTV Video Music Awards, the internet doesn’t stay silent. This year, all eyes (and lenses) were on Justin Timberlake and Megan Thee Stallion. A backstage video, making its rounds on social media, captured Timberlake and Stallion deep in conversation, with Megan’s hand gestures making it a particularly animated chat. This led the rumor mill to spin tales of a possible feud between the two artists. (Kevin Mazur/Jason Kempin/Getty Images) But were these speculations accurate? Insiders quickly debunked the feud theory. A close source clarified to news outlets, “Meg loves Justin. She was excitedly saying they’d never met before.” A simple conversation turned misconstrued, it seems. In the age of social media clarity, both artists hopped onto TikTok, where Stallion shared a video of their interaction. Her caption? A light-hearted “I just talk with my hands lol. See ya next time @JustinTimberlake.” The VMAs were not just about this fleeting moment, though. Megan Thee Stallion had two nominations, but the awards evaded her this time around. But perhaps the most nostalgic and electrifying segment of the night was Timberlake’s reunion with NSYNC, as they presented the best pop video award. Memories of their first VMA win for ‘Bye Bye Bye’ flooded back, as JC Chasez reminisced, “Over 20 years ago, we were just kids when we won.” (John Shearer/Getty Images for MTV) The evening culminated with Taylor Swift snagging the coveted Moonman statuette for her track “Anti-Hero.” In the glam and glitter of the VMAs, one thing’s for sure: whether it’s addressing rumors or celebrating old memories, music always finds a way to bring people together.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Judge Strikes DACA - Program Faces Legal Peril Once More</title><link href="/news/2023/09/14/DACA-Ruling/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Judge Strikes DACA - Program Faces Legal Peril Once More" /><published>2023-09-14T14:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-14T14:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/14/DACA-Ruling</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/14/DACA-Ruling/">&lt;p&gt;In a momentous decision that could reshape immigration policy, U.S. District Judge Andrew Hanen once again declared the Deferred Action for Childhood Arrivals (DACA) program illegal. This marks the second time Judge Hanen has made such a ruling, reinforcing the belief that the program might soon see its day in the U.S. Supreme Court.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a comprehensive 40-page ruling released on Wednesday, Judge Hanen stated that there existed “no material differences” between the iteration of DACA he deemed illegal in 2021 and the amendments introduced by the Biden administration, as cited by The New York Times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The DACA program, conceived via an executive order by former President Barack Obama in 2012, had been legally contested by Texas and an additional eight states. Their contention lay in the belief that the program circumvented established congressional lawmaking processes, causing the states tangible harm. These grievances ultimately led Judge Hanen to label the program unconstitutional back in 2021 and once more this Wednesday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The individuals protected under the DACA program, colloquially known as “Dreamers”, are safeguarded from potential deportation and can reside within the U.S. borders provided they satisfy specific criteria. These prerequisites, as outlined by the U.S. Citizenship and Immigration Services, include age restrictions, maintenance of a clean criminal record, and specific immigration status as of June 15, 2012.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As of March, NBC DFW highlighted that there were approximately 578,680 individuals enrolled in the DACA program.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the gravity of Wednesday’s ruling, there’s a silver lining. The Biden administration is poised to contest the judgment at the U.S. Supreme Court. Furthermore, Judge Hanen specified that the government retains the authority to process those applicants who secured their initial DACA status before his groundbreaking ruling on July 16, 2021. The catch? The Department of Homeland Security is prohibited from accepting new applications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a bid to clarify his stance, Judge Hanen emphasized, “To be clear, neither this supplemental order of injunction nor the memorandum and order that accompanies it requires DHS or the Department of Justice to take any immigration, deportation, or criminal action against any DACA recipient, applicant, or any other individual.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Hill recounted Judge Hanen’s awareness of the “predicament” DACA participants find themselves embroiled within due to the ongoing legal tussles. Yet, he firmly opined that the remedy to such dilemmas rests with Congress. He emphasized, “While sympathetic to the predicament of DACA recipients and their families, this court has expressed its concerns about the legality of the program for some time… The solution for these deficiencies lies with the legislature, not the executive or judicial branches.”&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a momentous decision that could reshape immigration policy, U.S. District Judge Andrew Hanen once again declared the Deferred Action for Childhood Arrivals (DACA) program illegal. This marks the second time Judge Hanen has made such a ruling, reinforcing the belief that the program might soon see its day in the U.S. Supreme Court. In a comprehensive 40-page ruling released on Wednesday, Judge Hanen stated that there existed “no material differences” between the iteration of DACA he deemed illegal in 2021 and the amendments introduced by the Biden administration, as cited by The New York Times. The DACA program, conceived via an executive order by former President Barack Obama in 2012, had been legally contested by Texas and an additional eight states. Their contention lay in the belief that the program circumvented established congressional lawmaking processes, causing the states tangible harm. These grievances ultimately led Judge Hanen to label the program unconstitutional back in 2021 and once more this Wednesday. The individuals protected under the DACA program, colloquially known as “Dreamers”, are safeguarded from potential deportation and can reside within the U.S. borders provided they satisfy specific criteria. These prerequisites, as outlined by the U.S. Citizenship and Immigration Services, include age restrictions, maintenance of a clean criminal record, and specific immigration status as of June 15, 2012. As of March, NBC DFW highlighted that there were approximately 578,680 individuals enrolled in the DACA program. Despite the gravity of Wednesday’s ruling, there’s a silver lining. The Biden administration is poised to contest the judgment at the U.S. Supreme Court. Furthermore, Judge Hanen specified that the government retains the authority to process those applicants who secured their initial DACA status before his groundbreaking ruling on July 16, 2021. The catch? The Department of Homeland Security is prohibited from accepting new applications. In a bid to clarify his stance, Judge Hanen emphasized, “To be clear, neither this supplemental order of injunction nor the memorandum and order that accompanies it requires DHS or the Department of Justice to take any immigration, deportation, or criminal action against any DACA recipient, applicant, or any other individual.” The Hill recounted Judge Hanen’s awareness of the “predicament” DACA participants find themselves embroiled within due to the ongoing legal tussles. Yet, he firmly opined that the remedy to such dilemmas rests with Congress. He emphasized, “While sympathetic to the predicament of DACA recipients and their families, this court has expressed its concerns about the legality of the program for some time… The solution for these deficiencies lies with the legislature, not the executive or judicial branches.”</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Driven to Despair - Auto Workers Challenge Democratic Priorities</title><link href="/news/2023/09/14/American-Auto-Workers/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Driven to Despair - Auto Workers Challenge Democratic Priorities" /><published>2023-09-14T13:05:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-14T13:05:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/14/American-Auto-Workers</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/14/American-Auto-Workers/">&lt;p&gt;The American automobile industry, a cornerstone of U.S. manufacturing, is undergoing a sea change. With the rapid shift towards green energy, particularly electric vehicles (EVs), there’s a growing discord between auto workers and the Democratic establishment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These workers, many of whom are represented by the United Auto Workers (UAW) union, feel increasingly alienated. According to former UAW President Bob King, the sentiment is clear: “UAW members feel abandoned by the Democratic Party.” His remarks come as the party continues to support what some describe as job-killing free trade and the Biden administration’s Inflation Reduction Act (IRA). The IRA, despite its benign title, is funneling billions from taxpayers to major auto companies and their top tiers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further exacerbating the discontent, Biden’s IRA is providing automakers with considerable tax credits for producing electric vehicles within North America. However, this public investment in transitioning from traditional combustion engines to EVs threatens to sideline millions of American auto jobs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;UAW President Shawn Fain is vocal about the financial imbalance resulting from such policies. His apprehension isn’t without merit – the transition to EVs could jeopardize the livelihoods of 20% of powertrain workers in major auto companies. When discussing the potential fallout, Fain highlighted the stark reality: the transition could cause wages to halve from an average of $32 to $16 per hour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recent insights from a UAW report underscore the depth of this wage decline. It pointed to the General Motors and LG’s EV battery plant in Lordstown, Ohio, as a case in point. While workers at GM’s predecessor plant earned around $30 an hour, their counterparts at the new EV battery plant started with a wage of $16.50, with the prospect of a modest increase to $20 an hour after seven long years. That’s a 45% wage cut for the hard-working individuals of Lordstown.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The UAW, recognizing the gravity of the situation, has already successfully negotiated for wage hikes at the Lordstown plant. But, they’re gearing up for larger battles. There are warnings of potential strikes if auto giants don’t address workers’ demands, especially when considering the ballooning salaries of corporate executives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fain underscores the disparity, “The Big Three CEOs saw their pay increase by 40 percent over the last four years, while our pay only went up by 6 percent.” These figures are even more staggering when juxtaposed with the earnings of General Motors CEO Mary Barra, who in 2022 pocketed almost $29 million – 362 times the median paycheck of an average GM employee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Historically, the gap between executive and employee pay was far narrower. Data from the Economic Policy Institute indicates that in 1965, company executives earned about 20 times their average employee’s paycheck, a figure that has skyrocketed to 399 times in recent years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fain’s message is unambiguous: policies, especially those like Biden’s IRA, cannot perpetuate this widening wage chasm. With billions of taxpayer dollars funding the EV transition, the workforce’s interests should be paramount. As Fain concludes, “workers cannot continue to be left behind in that equation.”&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">The American automobile industry, a cornerstone of U.S. manufacturing, is undergoing a sea change. With the rapid shift towards green energy, particularly electric vehicles (EVs), there’s a growing discord between auto workers and the Democratic establishment. These workers, many of whom are represented by the United Auto Workers (UAW) union, feel increasingly alienated. According to former UAW President Bob King, the sentiment is clear: “UAW members feel abandoned by the Democratic Party.” His remarks come as the party continues to support what some describe as job-killing free trade and the Biden administration’s Inflation Reduction Act (IRA). The IRA, despite its benign title, is funneling billions from taxpayers to major auto companies and their top tiers. Further exacerbating the discontent, Biden’s IRA is providing automakers with considerable tax credits for producing electric vehicles within North America. However, this public investment in transitioning from traditional combustion engines to EVs threatens to sideline millions of American auto jobs. UAW President Shawn Fain is vocal about the financial imbalance resulting from such policies. His apprehension isn’t without merit – the transition to EVs could jeopardize the livelihoods of 20% of powertrain workers in major auto companies. When discussing the potential fallout, Fain highlighted the stark reality: the transition could cause wages to halve from an average of $32 to $16 per hour. Recent insights from a UAW report underscore the depth of this wage decline. It pointed to the General Motors and LG’s EV battery plant in Lordstown, Ohio, as a case in point. While workers at GM’s predecessor plant earned around $30 an hour, their counterparts at the new EV battery plant started with a wage of $16.50, with the prospect of a modest increase to $20 an hour after seven long years. That’s a 45% wage cut for the hard-working individuals of Lordstown. The UAW, recognizing the gravity of the situation, has already successfully negotiated for wage hikes at the Lordstown plant. But, they’re gearing up for larger battles. There are warnings of potential strikes if auto giants don’t address workers’ demands, especially when considering the ballooning salaries of corporate executives. Fain underscores the disparity, “The Big Three CEOs saw their pay increase by 40 percent over the last four years, while our pay only went up by 6 percent.” These figures are even more staggering when juxtaposed with the earnings of General Motors CEO Mary Barra, who in 2022 pocketed almost $29 million – 362 times the median paycheck of an average GM employee. Historically, the gap between executive and employee pay was far narrower. Data from the Economic Policy Institute indicates that in 1965, company executives earned about 20 times their average employee’s paycheck, a figure that has skyrocketed to 399 times in recent years. Fain’s message is unambiguous: policies, especially those like Biden’s IRA, cannot perpetuate this widening wage chasm. With billions of taxpayer dollars funding the EV transition, the workforce’s interests should be paramount. As Fain concludes, “workers cannot continue to be left behind in that equation.”</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">New Hampshire Greenlights Trump’s Ballot Presence Amid 14th Amendment Controversy</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/14/Trump-New-Hampshire-Ballot/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="New Hampshire Greenlights Trump’s Ballot Presence Amid 14th Amendment Controversy" /><published>2023-09-14T12:03:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-14T12:03:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/14/Trump-New-Hampshire-Ballot</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/14/Trump-New-Hampshire-Ballot/">&lt;p&gt;New Hampshire’s primary stage was recently set with a dramatic backdrop, with Secretary of State Dave Scanlan firmly deciding not to block former President Donald Trump from appearing on the presidential primary ballot, despite looming controversies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a Concord news conference, Scanlan detailed the requirements for Trump’s participation — a declaration of candidacy under penalty of perjury and a $1,000 filing fee. He emphasized that the language guiding this decision was unequivocal, leaving no room for discretion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Republican Bryant “Corky” Messner, aided by Trump in securing the 2020 Republican Senate nomination, has been an outspoken critic, even contemplating legal recourse should Trump’s name feature on the ballot. Central to Messner’s argument is Section 3 of the 14th Amendment, which focuses on prohibiting those having engaged in “insurrection or rebellion” from holding office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the wake of Trump’s announcement of a third White House run, this Amendment has increasingly become a central theme. Given recent indictments against Trump in federal court and in Georgia, efforts to invoke the 14th Amendment have intensified.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet, Scanlan was unyielding in his stand. He highlighted that there was no mention in New Hampshire’s statute that permits a presidential primary candidate to be disqualified based on the 14th Amendment, particularly referencing insurrection or rebellion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While most state secretaries have hesitated in removing presidential candidates independently, the final decision might land on the U.S. Supreme Court’s desk, a body that hasn’t adjudicated on the relevant clause in the 14th Amendment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A day before Scanlan’s declaration, a letter from the Trump campaign, backed by numerous Republican state lawmakers, urged Scanlan to disregard what they described as “an absurd conspiracy theory.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The political tapestry further complicates with the Democratic National Committee (DNC) seeking to redefine its 2024 election cycle calendar, a move that threatens New Hampshire’s historic place as the inaugural primary. The DNC’s plan, aiming to reflect more diversity, has encountered stiff resistance in New Hampshire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the pushback, Scanlan remains steadfast, alluding that New Hampshire’s actions will be independent of DNC’s decisions. The repercussions could be significant, with New Hampshire potentially losing half of its delegates to the Democratic presidential nominating convention due to DNC penalties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many Democrats in Iowa and New Hampshire speculate that the calendar reshuffling may be a retaliatory measure, referencing Biden’s underwhelming performance in both states during the 2020 primary season.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Scanlan has only confirmed the filing period, the tentative dates suggest New Hampshire’s primary could be on January 23, just over a week post Iowa’s GOP presidential caucus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For now, New Hampshire’s political battleground remains intense and unpredictable as the primary date approaches.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">New Hampshire’s primary stage was recently set with a dramatic backdrop, with Secretary of State Dave Scanlan firmly deciding not to block former President Donald Trump from appearing on the presidential primary ballot, despite looming controversies. In a Concord news conference, Scanlan detailed the requirements for Trump’s participation — a declaration of candidacy under penalty of perjury and a $1,000 filing fee. He emphasized that the language guiding this decision was unequivocal, leaving no room for discretion. Republican Bryant “Corky” Messner, aided by Trump in securing the 2020 Republican Senate nomination, has been an outspoken critic, even contemplating legal recourse should Trump’s name feature on the ballot. Central to Messner’s argument is Section 3 of the 14th Amendment, which focuses on prohibiting those having engaged in “insurrection or rebellion” from holding office. In the wake of Trump’s announcement of a third White House run, this Amendment has increasingly become a central theme. Given recent indictments against Trump in federal court and in Georgia, efforts to invoke the 14th Amendment have intensified. Yet, Scanlan was unyielding in his stand. He highlighted that there was no mention in New Hampshire’s statute that permits a presidential primary candidate to be disqualified based on the 14th Amendment, particularly referencing insurrection or rebellion. While most state secretaries have hesitated in removing presidential candidates independently, the final decision might land on the U.S. Supreme Court’s desk, a body that hasn’t adjudicated on the relevant clause in the 14th Amendment. A day before Scanlan’s declaration, a letter from the Trump campaign, backed by numerous Republican state lawmakers, urged Scanlan to disregard what they described as “an absurd conspiracy theory.” The political tapestry further complicates with the Democratic National Committee (DNC) seeking to redefine its 2024 election cycle calendar, a move that threatens New Hampshire’s historic place as the inaugural primary. The DNC’s plan, aiming to reflect more diversity, has encountered stiff resistance in New Hampshire. Despite the pushback, Scanlan remains steadfast, alluding that New Hampshire’s actions will be independent of DNC’s decisions. The repercussions could be significant, with New Hampshire potentially losing half of its delegates to the Democratic presidential nominating convention due to DNC penalties. Many Democrats in Iowa and New Hampshire speculate that the calendar reshuffling may be a retaliatory measure, referencing Biden’s underwhelming performance in both states during the 2020 primary season. While Scanlan has only confirmed the filing period, the tentative dates suggest New Hampshire’s primary could be on January 23, just over a week post Iowa’s GOP presidential caucus. For now, New Hampshire’s political battleground remains intense and unpredictable as the primary date approaches.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Fear Grips the Capital - D.C. Residents Change Habits Amid Rising Crime</title><link href="/news/2023/09/14/DC-Crime-Uptick/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Fear Grips the Capital - D.C. Residents Change Habits Amid Rising Crime" /><published>2023-09-14T11:04:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-14T11:04:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/14/DC-Crime-Uptick</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/14/DC-Crime-Uptick/">&lt;p&gt;Washington D.C., once celebrated for its vibrant streets and rich history, is now grappling with an alarming spike in violent crime. The fear is so palpable that some residents have started altering their daily habits, avoiding walking even short distances or going out after dusk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In candid interviews with the &lt;em&gt;Washington Post&lt;/em&gt;, locals depicted a city where the very fabric of daily life is transforming due to safety concerns. Murders in the city have surged by nearly 30 percent, and a staggering increase in robberies, at almost 70 percent from last year, paints a dire picture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For 44-year-old Stephanie Heishman, the choice between convenience and safety is clear. She began driving even for short errands after witnessing a gunfight right outside her apartment in the Adams Morgan area. This personal experience was further exacerbated by the knowledge that three individuals were tragically murdered on her block in August alone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James, another D.C. native, recounts an equally harrowing experience. He and his husband made the significant decision to relocate to Maryland after a violent assault near Dupont Circle. His ordeal didn’t end there, as he later had a bottle hurled at him during a routine trip to Whole Foods.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Safety concerns aren’t limited to newcomers or specific neighborhoods. Ronald Moten, a 53-year-old who has spent his life in D.C., confesses to avoiding trips to his local gas station after dark, fearing the possibility of a robbery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even younger residents aren’t spared. Nora Fanfalone, 28, now uses a service entrance to her apartment, attempting to bypass potential threats or avoid witnessing violent incidents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recent data underlines this grim narrative. Violent crime incidents reported this year in D.C. are approaching a shocking 4,000 – marking an almost 40 percent uptick from 2022. The overall crime rate, too, has leaped by about 30 percent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For a city that stands as the beacon of democracy and power, the rise in crime not only poses a challenge to law enforcement but raises questions on the very essence of the safety and security it represents.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Washington D.C., once celebrated for its vibrant streets and rich history, is now grappling with an alarming spike in violent crime. The fear is so palpable that some residents have started altering their daily habits, avoiding walking even short distances or going out after dusk. In candid interviews with the Washington Post, locals depicted a city where the very fabric of daily life is transforming due to safety concerns. Murders in the city have surged by nearly 30 percent, and a staggering increase in robberies, at almost 70 percent from last year, paints a dire picture. For 44-year-old Stephanie Heishman, the choice between convenience and safety is clear. She began driving even for short errands after witnessing a gunfight right outside her apartment in the Adams Morgan area. This personal experience was further exacerbated by the knowledge that three individuals were tragically murdered on her block in August alone. James, another D.C. native, recounts an equally harrowing experience. He and his husband made the significant decision to relocate to Maryland after a violent assault near Dupont Circle. His ordeal didn’t end there, as he later had a bottle hurled at him during a routine trip to Whole Foods. Safety concerns aren’t limited to newcomers or specific neighborhoods. Ronald Moten, a 53-year-old who has spent his life in D.C., confesses to avoiding trips to his local gas station after dark, fearing the possibility of a robbery. Even younger residents aren’t spared. Nora Fanfalone, 28, now uses a service entrance to her apartment, attempting to bypass potential threats or avoid witnessing violent incidents. Recent data underlines this grim narrative. Violent crime incidents reported this year in D.C. are approaching a shocking 4,000 – marking an almost 40 percent uptick from 2022. The overall crime rate, too, has leaped by about 30 percent. For a city that stands as the beacon of democracy and power, the rise in crime not only poses a challenge to law enforcement but raises questions on the very essence of the safety and security it represents.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Biden Dodges Again - White House’s Evasive Tactics on Impeachment Probe Raise Eyebrows</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/14/Biden-Impeachment-Stance/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Biden Dodges Again - White House’s Evasive Tactics on Impeachment Probe Raise Eyebrows" /><published>2023-09-14T10:14:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-14T10:14:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/14/Biden-Impeachment-Stance</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/14/Biden-Impeachment-Stance/">&lt;p&gt;In a clear display of political sidestepping, White House press secretary Karine Jean-Pierre refused to provide a transparent stance on whether President Joe Biden would fully cooperate with the House’s brewing impeachment inquiry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reports, spearheaded by Breitbart News, highlighted the press secretary’s diplomatic dance. When questioned about Biden’s alleged involvement in “abuse of power, obstruction, and corruption”, Jean-Pierre resorted to obfuscation, claiming, “It’s not in my purview to speculate on what seems to be a baseless inquiry that even the House Republicans struggle to substantiate.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rather than giving a direct answer, she further added, “For specifics, I’ll refer to the wisdom of my White House counsel,” indicating a lack of forthrightness on the issue. Moreover, she sidestepped inquiries aimed at discerning Biden’s reaction to the news of the probe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Supplementing her vague remarks, Jean-Pierre tried to shift the focus, stating, “The Republicans in Congress have consumed the year with a single-minded obsession to investigate the president, a quest that, so far, has found no concrete evidence.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the narrative presented by the House leadership starkly contrasts her portrayal. They underscore suspicious business interactions involving Biden’s son, Hunter Biden, and the president’s suspected ties to purported influence brokering. Allegations suggest that the president might have misused his power during his vice-presidency under Barack Obama, assisting his son in landing lucrative foreign business contracts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the lack of a formal floor vote, House Speaker Kevin McCarthy (R-Calif.) deemed it necessary to initiate the inquiry. Such a decision, though, has been viewed with skepticism by a faction of Republican senators, who believe that the evidence at hand doesn’t warrant progression towards impeachment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Grave concerns surround Biden’s alleged active participation in his son’s engagements with foreign entities. Several lawmakers are raising red flags over the president possibly granting unwarranted favors to his son, especially given the ongoing Justice Department investigation into supposed tax and firearm transgressions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While these allegations simmer, the White House appeared to go on the offensive by issuing “guidance” to mainstream media concerning the new inquiry, urging media houses to turn the tables and scrutinize House Republicans. Ian Sams, representing the White House impeachment war room, penned a letter to premier news institutions, suggesting, “Media outlets ought to ramp up their scrutiny of House Republicans given their baseless impeachment endeavor.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With such a glaring evasion from the White House and a media strategy that seems to deflect rather than address, one can only speculate about the revelations that might come to light in this unfolding political saga.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a clear display of political sidestepping, White House press secretary Karine Jean-Pierre refused to provide a transparent stance on whether President Joe Biden would fully cooperate with the House’s brewing impeachment inquiry. Reports, spearheaded by Breitbart News, highlighted the press secretary’s diplomatic dance. When questioned about Biden’s alleged involvement in “abuse of power, obstruction, and corruption”, Jean-Pierre resorted to obfuscation, claiming, “It’s not in my purview to speculate on what seems to be a baseless inquiry that even the House Republicans struggle to substantiate.” Rather than giving a direct answer, she further added, “For specifics, I’ll refer to the wisdom of my White House counsel,” indicating a lack of forthrightness on the issue. Moreover, she sidestepped inquiries aimed at discerning Biden’s reaction to the news of the probe. Supplementing her vague remarks, Jean-Pierre tried to shift the focus, stating, “The Republicans in Congress have consumed the year with a single-minded obsession to investigate the president, a quest that, so far, has found no concrete evidence.” However, the narrative presented by the House leadership starkly contrasts her portrayal. They underscore suspicious business interactions involving Biden’s son, Hunter Biden, and the president’s suspected ties to purported influence brokering. Allegations suggest that the president might have misused his power during his vice-presidency under Barack Obama, assisting his son in landing lucrative foreign business contracts. Despite the lack of a formal floor vote, House Speaker Kevin McCarthy (R-Calif.) deemed it necessary to initiate the inquiry. Such a decision, though, has been viewed with skepticism by a faction of Republican senators, who believe that the evidence at hand doesn’t warrant progression towards impeachment. Grave concerns surround Biden’s alleged active participation in his son’s engagements with foreign entities. Several lawmakers are raising red flags over the president possibly granting unwarranted favors to his son, especially given the ongoing Justice Department investigation into supposed tax and firearm transgressions. While these allegations simmer, the White House appeared to go on the offensive by issuing “guidance” to mainstream media concerning the new inquiry, urging media houses to turn the tables and scrutinize House Republicans. Ian Sams, representing the White House impeachment war room, penned a letter to premier news institutions, suggesting, “Media outlets ought to ramp up their scrutiny of House Republicans given their baseless impeachment endeavor.” With such a glaring evasion from the White House and a media strategy that seems to deflect rather than address, one can only speculate about the revelations that might come to light in this unfolding political saga.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Great Escape - Fugitive Killer Cavalcante’s Daring Run Ends in Pennsylvania</title><link href="/news/2023/09/14/Escapee-Recapture/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Great Escape - Fugitive Killer Cavalcante’s Daring Run Ends in Pennsylvania" /><published>2023-09-14T09:08:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-14T09:08:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/14/Escapee-Recapture</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/14/Escapee-Recapture/">&lt;p&gt;Pennsylvania’s Chester County, located approximately 30 miles from Philadelphia, was the epicenter of a two-week-long suspenseful manhunt. The fugitive in question? Danelo Cavalcante, a 34-year-old convicted murderer who managed a Hollywood-esque escape from the local prison.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On August 31st, the audacious escape of Cavalcante was caught on camera, showing him crab-walking up a wall to freedom from the Chester County Prison. He was awaiting a transfer to state prison when he made his daring getaway. This set off a massive manhunt, with authorities using every tool at their disposal - mounted units, SWAT teams, and state and local police - scouring the farmlands and woodlands of the county.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cavalcante, originally from Brazil, was no stranger to crime. Convicted for the 2021 murder of his ex-girlfriend, Deborah Brandao, he is also a prime suspect in another homicide from 2017 back in Brazil. His escape had residents on high alert as reports of home break-ins began to surface. Cavalcante stole supplies, altered his appearance, and in one harrowing instance, exchanged gunfire with a homeowner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Images captured six hours post his arrest show a disheveled Cavalcante, barefoot in a hospital robe, displaying the aftermath of his capture. A K-9 bite wound, courtesy of his attempt to escape the arresting officers, had required medical treatment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lt. Col. George Bivens of the Pennsylvania State Police described the arrest, emphasizing the element of surprise. “They were able to move in very quietly,” he reported. Cavalcante, seemingly unaware, was cornered with stolen goods and a rifle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The community can now breathe a sigh of relief. This man, who once crawled his way to freedom and evoked widespread panic, is now back behind bars, awaiting a life sentence for his crimes.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Pennsylvania’s Chester County, located approximately 30 miles from Philadelphia, was the epicenter of a two-week-long suspenseful manhunt. The fugitive in question? Danelo Cavalcante, a 34-year-old convicted murderer who managed a Hollywood-esque escape from the local prison. On August 31st, the audacious escape of Cavalcante was caught on camera, showing him crab-walking up a wall to freedom from the Chester County Prison. He was awaiting a transfer to state prison when he made his daring getaway. This set off a massive manhunt, with authorities using every tool at their disposal - mounted units, SWAT teams, and state and local police - scouring the farmlands and woodlands of the county. Cavalcante, originally from Brazil, was no stranger to crime. Convicted for the 2021 murder of his ex-girlfriend, Deborah Brandao, he is also a prime suspect in another homicide from 2017 back in Brazil. His escape had residents on high alert as reports of home break-ins began to surface. Cavalcante stole supplies, altered his appearance, and in one harrowing instance, exchanged gunfire with a homeowner. Images captured six hours post his arrest show a disheveled Cavalcante, barefoot in a hospital robe, displaying the aftermath of his capture. A K-9 bite wound, courtesy of his attempt to escape the arresting officers, had required medical treatment. Lt. Col. George Bivens of the Pennsylvania State Police described the arrest, emphasizing the element of surprise. “They were able to move in very quietly,” he reported. Cavalcante, seemingly unaware, was cornered with stolen goods and a rifle. The community can now breathe a sigh of relief. This man, who once crawled his way to freedom and evoked widespread panic, is now back behind bars, awaiting a life sentence for his crimes.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump vs. Soros - Epic Showdown Looms Ahead of 2024 Elections</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/14/Trump-Soros-Battle/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump vs. Soros - Epic Showdown Looms Ahead of 2024 Elections" /><published>2023-09-14T08:10:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-14T08:10:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/14/Trump-Soros-Battle</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/14/Trump-Soros-Battle/">&lt;p&gt;Former President Donald Trump, in a fervent call to his supporters, declared that the billionaire activist George Soros and his family are ardently mobilizing resources to derail his potential 2024 bid for the White House. Trump’s sentiments underscore the mounting tension between the Trump and Soros camps, both significant powerhouses in American politics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Citing a headline from the Post Millenium, Trump referenced: “George Soros’ son shifts priorities, resources to focus on defeating MAGA in 2024,” highlighting Soros’s alleged intensified efforts to stifle the “MAGA” movement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The Soros Dynasty is laser-focused on a single mission for 2024: pouring in whatever it takes to ensure the people are deprived of their voice in their homeland,” Trump’s email to his supporters elucidated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The backdrop to Trump’s assertions traces back to a recent op-ed by Alex Soros, son of George Soros and chairman of the Open Society Foundations (OSF). OSF is globally recognized for its stance against Trump’s ‘America First’ agenda during his presidency. In his piece, Alex expressed concern over the potential consequences of a “MAGA-style” Republican triumph in the upcoming U.S. presidential elections, particularly emphasizing its ramifications for the European Union (EU).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Explaining his organization’s strategic pivot, Alex stated, “Given the looming challenges we currently face and the imminent ones awaiting us, we are re-evaluating our European priorities.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adding to the complexity, Trump accentuated Soros’s massive political financial outlays. “Soros has already splurged $50 million with the aim to seize the White House in 2024. Furthermore, an affiliated Soros Super PAC has dished out $75 million. He reigns as the UNDISPUTED BIGGEST DONOR in American politics,” Trump pointed out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Continuing his appeal, Trump stressed, “His son is gearing up to infuse millions more, all in a bid to obstruct our glorious movement. But united, we hold the power to financially outpace Soros and prevent his dynasty from purchasing the White House in 2024.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rounding off his message, Trump reflected on his presidential tenure, crediting himself with destabilizing the established order. He insinuated that this upheaval cemented his position as a thorn in the side of deep-rooted special interests, branding his movement as their “supreme adversary.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the 2024 election edges closer, the mounting tension between these titans promises to keep the political arena bustling with intrigue and fervor.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Former President Donald Trump, in a fervent call to his supporters, declared that the billionaire activist George Soros and his family are ardently mobilizing resources to derail his potential 2024 bid for the White House. Trump’s sentiments underscore the mounting tension between the Trump and Soros camps, both significant powerhouses in American politics. Citing a headline from the Post Millenium, Trump referenced: “George Soros’ son shifts priorities, resources to focus on defeating MAGA in 2024,” highlighting Soros’s alleged intensified efforts to stifle the “MAGA” movement. “The Soros Dynasty is laser-focused on a single mission for 2024: pouring in whatever it takes to ensure the people are deprived of their voice in their homeland,” Trump’s email to his supporters elucidated. The backdrop to Trump’s assertions traces back to a recent op-ed by Alex Soros, son of George Soros and chairman of the Open Society Foundations (OSF). OSF is globally recognized for its stance against Trump’s ‘America First’ agenda during his presidency. In his piece, Alex expressed concern over the potential consequences of a “MAGA-style” Republican triumph in the upcoming U.S. presidential elections, particularly emphasizing its ramifications for the European Union (EU). Explaining his organization’s strategic pivot, Alex stated, “Given the looming challenges we currently face and the imminent ones awaiting us, we are re-evaluating our European priorities.” Adding to the complexity, Trump accentuated Soros’s massive political financial outlays. “Soros has already splurged $50 million with the aim to seize the White House in 2024. Furthermore, an affiliated Soros Super PAC has dished out $75 million. He reigns as the UNDISPUTED BIGGEST DONOR in American politics,” Trump pointed out. Continuing his appeal, Trump stressed, “His son is gearing up to infuse millions more, all in a bid to obstruct our glorious movement. But united, we hold the power to financially outpace Soros and prevent his dynasty from purchasing the White House in 2024.” Rounding off his message, Trump reflected on his presidential tenure, crediting himself with destabilizing the established order. He insinuated that this upheaval cemented his position as a thorn in the side of deep-rooted special interests, branding his movement as their “supreme adversary.” As the 2024 election edges closer, the mounting tension between these titans promises to keep the political arena bustling with intrigue and fervor.</summary></entry></feed>