<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-09-12T06:16:46-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/09/12/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-09-12T06:16:46-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-12T06:16:46-04:00</updated><id>/2023/09/12/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/12/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Communists Attack Freedom of Speech - Jason Aldean’s ‘Try That in a Small Town’ Stands Strong</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/12/Defending-Aldean/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Communists Attack Freedom of Speech - Jason Aldean’s ‘Try That in a Small Town’ Stands Strong" /><published>2023-09-12T06:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-12T06:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/12/Defending-Aldean</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/12/Defending-Aldean/">&lt;p&gt;In an alarming display of extremist fervor, The Revolution Club of Chicago — a self-proclaimed communist group — burned the American flag in protest of country music star Jason Aldean’s hit single, “Try That in a Small Town.” Their blatant disrespect for national symbols and freedom of expression is unsettling to say the least.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Happening outside one of Aldean’s recent concerts in Chicago, the group’s heated demonstration involved vitriolic chants against the U.S. and the artist. Their distorted perception labels the country anthem, which celebrates the core values of America, as “fascist.” It’s a reminder of the far-left’s increasing intolerance towards differing viewpoints and its attempts to stifle voices that challenge their narratives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite such aggressive antics, Jason Aldean remains unfazed, with his song’s popularity soaring to the top of several charts. This is a testament to the song’s resonance with vast sections of the American populace, who identify with its message. It’s ironic that while corporate giants like Paramount-owned CMT chose to censor the song’s music video, the public responded by amplifying its reach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Critics, likely driven by political biases, have wrongfully labelled the song as racist, without providing substantive evidence. Aldean’s track, in reality, critiques the unchecked rioting and lawlessness witnessed in 2020, emphasizing a need for order and respect for community values.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Among the prominent figures defending Aldean’s right to freedom of speech is former President Donald Trump. He lauded the country singer on Truth Social, highlighting Aldean’s genuine talent and urging the public to support him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s clear that while extreme factions like the Revolution Club may shout loudly, their voice doesn’t reflect the majority. Jason Aldean’s music, standing strong amidst the turmoil, is a testament to the enduring power of artistic freedom and its deep roots in American culture.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">In an alarming display of extremist fervor, The Revolution Club of Chicago — a self-proclaimed communist group — burned the American flag in protest of country music star Jason Aldean’s hit single, “Try That in a Small Town.” Their blatant disrespect for national symbols and freedom of expression is unsettling to say the least. Happening outside one of Aldean’s recent concerts in Chicago, the group’s heated demonstration involved vitriolic chants against the U.S. and the artist. Their distorted perception labels the country anthem, which celebrates the core values of America, as “fascist.” It’s a reminder of the far-left’s increasing intolerance towards differing viewpoints and its attempts to stifle voices that challenge their narratives. Despite such aggressive antics, Jason Aldean remains unfazed, with his song’s popularity soaring to the top of several charts. This is a testament to the song’s resonance with vast sections of the American populace, who identify with its message. It’s ironic that while corporate giants like Paramount-owned CMT chose to censor the song’s music video, the public responded by amplifying its reach. Critics, likely driven by political biases, have wrongfully labelled the song as racist, without providing substantive evidence. Aldean’s track, in reality, critiques the unchecked rioting and lawlessness witnessed in 2020, emphasizing a need for order and respect for community values. Among the prominent figures defending Aldean’s right to freedom of speech is former President Donald Trump. He lauded the country singer on Truth Social, highlighting Aldean’s genuine talent and urging the public to support him. It’s clear that while extreme factions like the Revolution Club may shout loudly, their voice doesn’t reflect the majority. Jason Aldean’s music, standing strong amidst the turmoil, is a testament to the enduring power of artistic freedom and its deep roots in American culture.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Unexpected Horror - U.S. Tourists Ambushed by Cartel Near Texas-Mexico Border</title><link href="/news/2023/09/11/Cartel-Attack-Tourists/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Unexpected Horror - U.S. Tourists Ambushed by Cartel Near Texas-Mexico Border" /><published>2023-09-11T18:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-11T18:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/11/Cartel-Attack-Tourists</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/11/Cartel-Attack-Tourists/">&lt;p&gt;The tranquility of a tourist convoy was shattered early Saturday morning when a group of nearly 20 U.S. tourists, fresh from crossing the Texas border into Mexico, faced a harrowing attack by cartel gunmen in the town of Los Guerra, Tamaulipas. This incident underscores the volatile nature of areas along the Mexico-Texas border, particularly amidst ongoing cartel conflicts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Driving through Los Guerra en route to the Mexican state of San Luis Potosi, the tourists were ambushed along the Riberena highway near the El Angel statue. Employing a makeshift armored vehicle, the assailants rammed the cars in the convoy, immediately following which additional gunmen opened fire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The motive? A possible case of mistaken identity. Sources within law enforcement have shared with Breitbart Texas that these Gulf Cartel gunmen likely misconstrued the tourists as rival gang members or police forces encroaching on their territory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The aftermath of this violent encounter left at least seven tourists with varying injuries. Swift action by local authorities ensured these individuals were rushed to the Miguel Aleman-Roma port of entry, where U.S. ambulances promptly transported them to hospitals for medical care.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This incident is an unsettling reminder of the precarious environment near the Tamaulipas border. The Gulf Cartel, embroiled in territorial disputes with opposing factions, has not only been clashing with rivals but has also accrued a dark record of attacking tourists, committing kidnappings, extortions, and executing murders targeting unsuspecting individuals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With such a backdrop of volatility, this episode accentuates the need for heightened caution for those traveling in the region. As investigations proceed, questions abound: Could this have been prevented? And what can be done to ensure the safety of innocent travelers in such high-risk zones?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">The tranquility of a tourist convoy was shattered early Saturday morning when a group of nearly 20 U.S. tourists, fresh from crossing the Texas border into Mexico, faced a harrowing attack by cartel gunmen in the town of Los Guerra, Tamaulipas. This incident underscores the volatile nature of areas along the Mexico-Texas border, particularly amidst ongoing cartel conflicts. Driving through Los Guerra en route to the Mexican state of San Luis Potosi, the tourists were ambushed along the Riberena highway near the El Angel statue. Employing a makeshift armored vehicle, the assailants rammed the cars in the convoy, immediately following which additional gunmen opened fire. The motive? A possible case of mistaken identity. Sources within law enforcement have shared with Breitbart Texas that these Gulf Cartel gunmen likely misconstrued the tourists as rival gang members or police forces encroaching on their territory. The aftermath of this violent encounter left at least seven tourists with varying injuries. Swift action by local authorities ensured these individuals were rushed to the Miguel Aleman-Roma port of entry, where U.S. ambulances promptly transported them to hospitals for medical care. This incident is an unsettling reminder of the precarious environment near the Tamaulipas border. The Gulf Cartel, embroiled in territorial disputes with opposing factions, has not only been clashing with rivals but has also accrued a dark record of attacking tourists, committing kidnappings, extortions, and executing murders targeting unsuspecting individuals. With such a backdrop of volatility, this episode accentuates the need for heightened caution for those traveling in the region. As investigations proceed, questions abound: Could this have been prevented? And what can be done to ensure the safety of innocent travelers in such high-risk zones?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Justice Alito Stands Firm Against Partisan Pressure</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/11/Justice-Alito-Stands-Firm/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Justice Alito Stands Firm Against Partisan Pressure" /><published>2023-09-11T17:07:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-11T17:07:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/11/Justice-Alito-Stands-Firm</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/11/Justice-Alito-Stands-Firm/">&lt;p&gt;In a display of unwavering integrity and dedication to the principles of the American legal system, Justice Samuel Alito firmly dismissed the ill-founded demands of Senate Democrats for his recusal from the upcoming Supreme Court case. Leading the charge, Sen. Dick Durbin, D-Ill., based his feeble argument on a benign interview Alito gave to the Wall Street Journal, where one of the attending journalists, David B. Rivkin, happened to be an attorney involved in the case.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Justice Alito, highlighting the shallow waters in which Durbin’s argument wades, stated unequivocally, “This argument is unsound,” further adding, “There is no valid reason for my recusal in this case.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One cannot ignore the unending pressures from Democrats on the Senate Judiciary Committee, who have been tirelessly targeting Alito and his peers for not adopting their prescribed ethics code. This, despite the ethical quandaries arising from undisclosed trips by justices, which are not exclusive to the conservative members of the bench.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Durbin’s zealous attempt to undermine the integrity of the Supreme Court, he has failed to recognize the clear distinction between professional courtesy and potential conflict of interest. Alito’s interactions with Rivkin were nothing more than a standard journalistic interaction. Suggesting that Alito’s capacity to remain impartial is compromised based on this interaction is not only a stretch but an affront to the dignity of the justice’s position.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Durbin’s accusations are amplified by the alarming assertion that Alito’s views on Congressional authority over the Supreme Court are controversial. Alito’s remarks about Congress lacking the “authority” to regulate the Supreme Court underscores the doctrine of separation of powers – a foundational principle of the U.S. Constitution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In response to the partisan jabs, Justice Alito expertly articulated the complexities and nuances of the Supreme Court’s operations. He explained, “We have no control over the attorneys whom parties select to represent them… If we recused in such cases, we would regularly have less than a full bench, and the Court’s work would be substantially disrupted and distorted.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Justice Alito’s resolute stance against the Democrats’ untenable demands serves as a beacon of hope for many who cherish the sanctity of America’s judicial system. It is paramount for the Supreme Court to remain above the fray of partisan politics, ensuring that justice is dispensed fairly, impartially, and according to the rule of law. Anything less would undermine the very fabric of American democracy.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a display of unwavering integrity and dedication to the principles of the American legal system, Justice Samuel Alito firmly dismissed the ill-founded demands of Senate Democrats for his recusal from the upcoming Supreme Court case. Leading the charge, Sen. Dick Durbin, D-Ill., based his feeble argument on a benign interview Alito gave to the Wall Street Journal, where one of the attending journalists, David B. Rivkin, happened to be an attorney involved in the case. Justice Alito, highlighting the shallow waters in which Durbin’s argument wades, stated unequivocally, “This argument is unsound,” further adding, “There is no valid reason for my recusal in this case.” One cannot ignore the unending pressures from Democrats on the Senate Judiciary Committee, who have been tirelessly targeting Alito and his peers for not adopting their prescribed ethics code. This, despite the ethical quandaries arising from undisclosed trips by justices, which are not exclusive to the conservative members of the bench. In Durbin’s zealous attempt to undermine the integrity of the Supreme Court, he has failed to recognize the clear distinction between professional courtesy and potential conflict of interest. Alito’s interactions with Rivkin were nothing more than a standard journalistic interaction. Suggesting that Alito’s capacity to remain impartial is compromised based on this interaction is not only a stretch but an affront to the dignity of the justice’s position. Durbin’s accusations are amplified by the alarming assertion that Alito’s views on Congressional authority over the Supreme Court are controversial. Alito’s remarks about Congress lacking the “authority” to regulate the Supreme Court underscores the doctrine of separation of powers – a foundational principle of the U.S. Constitution. In response to the partisan jabs, Justice Alito expertly articulated the complexities and nuances of the Supreme Court’s operations. He explained, “We have no control over the attorneys whom parties select to represent them… If we recused in such cases, we would regularly have less than a full bench, and the Court’s work would be substantially disrupted and distorted.” Justice Alito’s resolute stance against the Democrats’ untenable demands serves as a beacon of hope for many who cherish the sanctity of America’s judicial system. It is paramount for the Supreme Court to remain above the fray of partisan politics, ensuring that justice is dispensed fairly, impartially, and according to the rule of law. Anything less would undermine the very fabric of American democracy.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Royal Dissent - Britons Favor Ousting Prince Harry from Throne Succession</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/11/Royal-Dissent/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Royal Dissent - Britons Favor Ousting Prince Harry from Throne Succession" /><published>2023-09-11T16:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-11T16:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/11/Royal-Dissent</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/11/Royal-Dissent/">&lt;p&gt;The tides of popularity have dramatically shifted for Prince Harry in the UK. Recent findings from a Deltapoll conducted for the Daily Mail reveal that an overwhelming 61% of Britons believe that Prince Harry should be excluded from the line to the throne.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prince Harry, once a widely cherished member of the British Royal Family, saw a precipitous drop in his public standing following his marriage to American actress Meghan Markle. Although Harry stepped away from his royal duties to pursue roles in entertainment and activism, he currently stands fifth in the royal line of succession. This sequence places him behind his elder brother Prince William and William’s children, Prince George, Prince Louis, and Princess Charlotte.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, Meghan doesn’t hold a position in the line of succession, similar to her sister-in-law, Kate Middleton, Princess of Wales. However, Meghan’s children with Harry, Prince Archie and Princess Lilibet Mountbatten-Windsor, are presently sixth and seventh in line for the throne.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Harry and Meghan’s reputation has experienced a considerable decline in the UK over recent years. The couple, often described as ‘woke’, have openly expressed their challenges within the Royal Family, making serious accusations, including claims of racism. Such accusations have reportedly strained relations between Prince Harry, King Charles III, and Prince William. Reports even suggested that the couple’s sharp criticisms deeply upset the late Queen Elizabeth II, particularly in the twilight of her life, battling bone marrow cancer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In line with the consensus against Harry’s place in the royal line, the dominant view among the British populace is that Harry and Meghan should not benefit from public funding. This sentiment emerges despite the couple’s reported earnings of around £100 million from media deals since their 2020 move to the United States. Notwithstanding their substantial earnings, Meghan and Harry have sought taxpayer-funded police protection during their visits to the UK.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">The tides of popularity have dramatically shifted for Prince Harry in the UK. Recent findings from a Deltapoll conducted for the Daily Mail reveal that an overwhelming 61% of Britons believe that Prince Harry should be excluded from the line to the throne. Prince Harry, once a widely cherished member of the British Royal Family, saw a precipitous drop in his public standing following his marriage to American actress Meghan Markle. Although Harry stepped away from his royal duties to pursue roles in entertainment and activism, he currently stands fifth in the royal line of succession. This sequence places him behind his elder brother Prince William and William’s children, Prince George, Prince Louis, and Princess Charlotte. Interestingly, Meghan doesn’t hold a position in the line of succession, similar to her sister-in-law, Kate Middleton, Princess of Wales. However, Meghan’s children with Harry, Prince Archie and Princess Lilibet Mountbatten-Windsor, are presently sixth and seventh in line for the throne. Harry and Meghan’s reputation has experienced a considerable decline in the UK over recent years. The couple, often described as ‘woke’, have openly expressed their challenges within the Royal Family, making serious accusations, including claims of racism. Such accusations have reportedly strained relations between Prince Harry, King Charles III, and Prince William. Reports even suggested that the couple’s sharp criticisms deeply upset the late Queen Elizabeth II, particularly in the twilight of her life, battling bone marrow cancer. In line with the consensus against Harry’s place in the royal line, the dominant view among the British populace is that Harry and Meghan should not benefit from public funding. This sentiment emerges despite the couple’s reported earnings of around £100 million from media deals since their 2020 move to the United States. Notwithstanding their substantial earnings, Meghan and Harry have sought taxpayer-funded police protection during their visits to the UK.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Pennsylvania’s Elusive Escapee - How Danelo Cavalcante Outfoxed Authorities</title><link href="/news/2023/09/11/Escaped-Murderer/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Pennsylvania’s Elusive Escapee - How Danelo Cavalcante Outfoxed Authorities" /><published>2023-09-11T15:01:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-11T15:01:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/11/Escaped-Murderer</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/11/Escaped-Murderer/">&lt;p&gt;The community in southeastern Pennsylvania remains on edge as Danelo Souza Cavalcante, an escaped murderer, proves adept at evading authorities. Since his escape from Chester County Prison over a week ago, there have been multiple confirmed sightings of Cavalcante, but he remains at large.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Late Saturday, Pennsylvania State Police provided an update indicating that Cavalcante, who had originally been the focus of a search centered around the Longwood Gardens botanical park, was now seen near Phoenixville in northern Chester County. This location is over 20 miles northeast of the earlier search area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a bid to possibly divert attention and complicate the manhunt, Cavalcante has altered his appearance. He’s now clean-shaven and was last seen wearing a yellow or green hooded sweatshirt, black baseball cap, green prison pants, and white shoes. Additionally, he’s believed to be driving a stolen 2020 White Ford Transit van, which bears a refrigeration unit on top.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reason for Cavalcante’s initial incarceration was a life sentence handed down after he was found guilty of fatally stabbing his ex-girlfriend in 2021. His motivation, prosecutors assert, was to prevent her from revealing to the police that he was a wanted murderer in his home country of Brazil.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The circumstances of his escape raise eyebrows. Cavalcante achieved his freedom by scaling a wall, navigating over razor wire, and eventually jumping off a roof to the ground. What’s astonishing is that his disappearance went unnoticed for over an hour until a routine headcount revealed the discrepancy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A prison tower guard on duty during this escape has since been dismissed. This bold escape, coupled with a manhunt that has attracted international attention, is also making headlines in Brazil. There, Cavalcante is accused of another heinous crime - the “double qualified homicide” of Válter Júnior Moreira dos Reis in 2017, purportedly over a vehicle repair debt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While local festivities, such as the annual mushroom festival in Kennett Square, proceeded as planned, assurances of “all necessary precautions and protocols” couldn’t entirely assuage the heightened anxiety of residents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given Cavalcante’s demonstrated ability to elude capture and the description of him as “extremely dangerous” by authorities, the community is urged to be vigilant. The state police have mobilized a large-scale search operation involving tactical teams, tracking dogs, officers on horseback, and aircraft. A $20,000 reward is now on the table for information leading to his apprehension.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Residents and visitors are encouraged to remain cautious and report any suspicious activities. As the hunt for Cavalcante intensifies, one can only hope for a swift and safe resolution to this unnerving saga.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">The community in southeastern Pennsylvania remains on edge as Danelo Souza Cavalcante, an escaped murderer, proves adept at evading authorities. Since his escape from Chester County Prison over a week ago, there have been multiple confirmed sightings of Cavalcante, but he remains at large. Late Saturday, Pennsylvania State Police provided an update indicating that Cavalcante, who had originally been the focus of a search centered around the Longwood Gardens botanical park, was now seen near Phoenixville in northern Chester County. This location is over 20 miles northeast of the earlier search area. In a bid to possibly divert attention and complicate the manhunt, Cavalcante has altered his appearance. He’s now clean-shaven and was last seen wearing a yellow or green hooded sweatshirt, black baseball cap, green prison pants, and white shoes. Additionally, he’s believed to be driving a stolen 2020 White Ford Transit van, which bears a refrigeration unit on top. The reason for Cavalcante’s initial incarceration was a life sentence handed down after he was found guilty of fatally stabbing his ex-girlfriend in 2021. His motivation, prosecutors assert, was to prevent her from revealing to the police that he was a wanted murderer in his home country of Brazil. The circumstances of his escape raise eyebrows. Cavalcante achieved his freedom by scaling a wall, navigating over razor wire, and eventually jumping off a roof to the ground. What’s astonishing is that his disappearance went unnoticed for over an hour until a routine headcount revealed the discrepancy. A prison tower guard on duty during this escape has since been dismissed. This bold escape, coupled with a manhunt that has attracted international attention, is also making headlines in Brazil. There, Cavalcante is accused of another heinous crime - the “double qualified homicide” of Válter Júnior Moreira dos Reis in 2017, purportedly over a vehicle repair debt. While local festivities, such as the annual mushroom festival in Kennett Square, proceeded as planned, assurances of “all necessary precautions and protocols” couldn’t entirely assuage the heightened anxiety of residents. Given Cavalcante’s demonstrated ability to elude capture and the description of him as “extremely dangerous” by authorities, the community is urged to be vigilant. The state police have mobilized a large-scale search operation involving tactical teams, tracking dogs, officers on horseback, and aircraft. A $20,000 reward is now on the table for information leading to his apprehension. Residents and visitors are encouraged to remain cautious and report any suspicious activities. As the hunt for Cavalcante intensifies, one can only hope for a swift and safe resolution to this unnerving saga.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Scientology Drama Unveiled - Tinseltown’s Most Controversial Faith</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/11/Scientology-Drama-Unveiled/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Scientology Drama Unveiled - Tinseltown’s Most Controversial Faith" /><published>2023-09-11T14:02:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-11T14:02:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/11/Scientology-Drama-Unveiled</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/11/Scientology-Drama-Unveiled/">&lt;p&gt;Hollywood has had a long-standing and complex relationship with Scientology. From its high-profile members to the drama surrounding its practices, the Church of Scientology often finds itself under the Tinseltown spotlight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;danny-masterson-and-scientologys-trial-tangle&quot;&gt;Danny Masterson and Scientology’s Trial Tangle&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Actor Danny Masterson, best known for his role in “That ’70s Show,” recently faced a rape trial where his faith became a significant talking point. Found guilty on two counts of forcible rape, Masterson’s sentencing shed light on the secretive world of Scientology. Though the Church was not directly implicated in the case, the trial proceedings painted a troubling picture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Victims, all members of the Church at the time, were reportedly hesitant to come forward due to the organization’s strict protocols against public involvement with member issues. Deputy District Attorney Ariel Anson told jurors, “The church taught his victims: ‘Rape isn’t rape, you caused this, and above all, you are never allowed to go to law enforcement.’”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a counter-statement, the Church of Scientology stated, “The Church was not a party to this case and religion did not belong in this proceeding as Supreme Court precedent has maintained for centuries.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;leah-remini---from-faithful-follower-to-fierce-critic&quot;&gt;Leah Remini - From Faithful Follower to Fierce Critic&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Former Scientologist Leah Remini has been one of the Church’s most vocal critics since she left in 2013. Celebrating Masterson’s victims for their courage, she commented, “I am relieved that this dangerous rapist will be off the streets and unable to violently assault and rape women with the help of Scientology, a multi-billion-dollar criminal organization with tax-exempt status.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But Remini hasn’t limited her criticisms to this recent trial. In her award-winning documentary series, she delves deep into the Church’s practices, sharing insights and exposing what she believes are its harmful activities. The Church, in response, has dismissed her claims as attempts “to appear relevant again.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tom-cruise---the-poster-boy-of-scientology&quot;&gt;Tom Cruise - The Poster Boy of Scientology&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No discussion of Scientology and Hollywood would be complete without mentioning Tom Cruise. One of the Church’s most high-profile members, Cruise has remained largely loyal to his faith even as controversies raged around him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, his relationships, notably with Nicole Kidman and Katie Holmes, have brought attention to the religion’s influence in personal matters. Remini alluded that Scientology played a role in Cruise’s split with Holmes, citing the Church’s tendency to label detractors as suppressive persons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;scientologys-other-celebrities-and-controversies&quot;&gt;Scientology’s Other Celebrities and Controversies&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other celebrities, such as Kirstie Alley, have praised the Church for its positive impact on their lives. Alley, in particular, credited Scientology with helping her overcome her cocaine addiction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, filmmaker Paul Haggis, a former member, faced legal troubles connected to allegations of rape, with some speculating on the Church’s role in his life and actions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;in-the-spotlight&quot;&gt;In the Spotlight&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While it remains a divisive topic in Hollywood and beyond, Scientology’s association with celebrities ensures it remains in the limelight. As more stories emerge, the relationship between Tinseltown and its most controversial faith continues to intrigue and baffle in equal measure.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Hollywood has had a long-standing and complex relationship with Scientology. From its high-profile members to the drama surrounding its practices, the Church of Scientology often finds itself under the Tinseltown spotlight. Danny Masterson and Scientology’s Trial Tangle Actor Danny Masterson, best known for his role in “That ’70s Show,” recently faced a rape trial where his faith became a significant talking point. Found guilty on two counts of forcible rape, Masterson’s sentencing shed light on the secretive world of Scientology. Though the Church was not directly implicated in the case, the trial proceedings painted a troubling picture. Victims, all members of the Church at the time, were reportedly hesitant to come forward due to the organization’s strict protocols against public involvement with member issues. Deputy District Attorney Ariel Anson told jurors, “The church taught his victims: ‘Rape isn’t rape, you caused this, and above all, you are never allowed to go to law enforcement.’” In a counter-statement, the Church of Scientology stated, “The Church was not a party to this case and religion did not belong in this proceeding as Supreme Court precedent has maintained for centuries.” Leah Remini - From Faithful Follower to Fierce Critic Former Scientologist Leah Remini has been one of the Church’s most vocal critics since she left in 2013. Celebrating Masterson’s victims for their courage, she commented, “I am relieved that this dangerous rapist will be off the streets and unable to violently assault and rape women with the help of Scientology, a multi-billion-dollar criminal organization with tax-exempt status.” But Remini hasn’t limited her criticisms to this recent trial. In her award-winning documentary series, she delves deep into the Church’s practices, sharing insights and exposing what she believes are its harmful activities. The Church, in response, has dismissed her claims as attempts “to appear relevant again.” Tom Cruise - The Poster Boy of Scientology No discussion of Scientology and Hollywood would be complete without mentioning Tom Cruise. One of the Church’s most high-profile members, Cruise has remained largely loyal to his faith even as controversies raged around him. However, his relationships, notably with Nicole Kidman and Katie Holmes, have brought attention to the religion’s influence in personal matters. Remini alluded that Scientology played a role in Cruise’s split with Holmes, citing the Church’s tendency to label detractors as suppressive persons. Scientology’s Other Celebrities and Controversies Other celebrities, such as Kirstie Alley, have praised the Church for its positive impact on their lives. Alley, in particular, credited Scientology with helping her overcome her cocaine addiction. On the other hand, filmmaker Paul Haggis, a former member, faced legal troubles connected to allegations of rape, with some speculating on the Church’s role in his life and actions. In the Spotlight While it remains a divisive topic in Hollywood and beyond, Scientology’s association with celebrities ensures it remains in the limelight. As more stories emerge, the relationship between Tinseltown and its most controversial faith continues to intrigue and baffle in equal measure.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Digital IDs on the Horizon - A Slippery Slope to Surveillance?</title><link href="/news/2023/09/11/Digital-Overreach/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Digital IDs on the Horizon - A Slippery Slope to Surveillance?" /><published>2023-09-11T13:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-11T13:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/11/Digital-Overreach</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/11/Digital-Overreach/">&lt;p&gt;European Commission President Ursula von der Leyen’s recent push for global digital ID systems, akin to coronavirus passports, at the G20 Summit’s “One Future” session has ignited fierce debates. While she touts them as the future of global digital infrastructure, many view these initiatives as a grave step towards omnipresent surveillance, eroding personal freedoms and privacy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The digital era, although prosperous and convenient, comes with significant challenges. One of the most alarming is the potential to turn tools meant for connectivity into tools of control. Von der Leyen’s endorsement of a global regulatory body for Artificial Intelligence (AI) — mirroring the structure of the United Nations’ Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change — raises the question: who gets to set the standards, and how will they be enforced?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;von der Leyen praised the European Union’s development of a coronavirus digital certificate, pointing out its adoption by 51 countries across four continents. While she sees this as a testament to its functionality and trustworthiness, many fear that such widespread adoption of a single digital ID system puts immense power in the hands of few and reduces the anonymity and privacy of individuals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The European Union’s ongoing effort to introduce a “digital identity” app, aiming to consolidate a citizen’s essential data, including passport details, driver’s license, and credit cards, has added fuel to the fire. Given that such information is a treasure trove for cybercriminals, the security implications alone are staggering. But more so, the app’s existence could provide governments with unprecedented access to personal information, raising the specter of an Orwellian future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Romanian MEP Cristian Terhes’s warning earlier this year resounds even more today. He termed the digital ID system push as potentially leading to the “Chinafication” of Europe. Drawing parallels with Communist China’s surveillance mechanisms, Terhes’s statement underscores concerns that Europe might be on a similar trajectory, sacrificing privacy at the altar of supposed convenience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The EU’s plan to potentially introduce a Central Bank Digital Currency (CBDC) further intensifies these apprehensions. Beyond the economic implications, a CBDC could provide an infrastructure for governments to monitor, and possibly control, individual financial transactions, curtailing financial freedom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While digital transformation and global standardization have undeniable merits, the cost of personal freedom and privacy should be paramount. As the line between connectivity and control blurs, one must ask: are we inadvertently laying the foundation for a digital dystopia?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">European Commission President Ursula von der Leyen’s recent push for global digital ID systems, akin to coronavirus passports, at the G20 Summit’s “One Future” session has ignited fierce debates. While she touts them as the future of global digital infrastructure, many view these initiatives as a grave step towards omnipresent surveillance, eroding personal freedoms and privacy. The digital era, although prosperous and convenient, comes with significant challenges. One of the most alarming is the potential to turn tools meant for connectivity into tools of control. Von der Leyen’s endorsement of a global regulatory body for Artificial Intelligence (AI) — mirroring the structure of the United Nations’ Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change — raises the question: who gets to set the standards, and how will they be enforced? von der Leyen praised the European Union’s development of a coronavirus digital certificate, pointing out its adoption by 51 countries across four continents. While she sees this as a testament to its functionality and trustworthiness, many fear that such widespread adoption of a single digital ID system puts immense power in the hands of few and reduces the anonymity and privacy of individuals. The European Union’s ongoing effort to introduce a “digital identity” app, aiming to consolidate a citizen’s essential data, including passport details, driver’s license, and credit cards, has added fuel to the fire. Given that such information is a treasure trove for cybercriminals, the security implications alone are staggering. But more so, the app’s existence could provide governments with unprecedented access to personal information, raising the specter of an Orwellian future. Romanian MEP Cristian Terhes’s warning earlier this year resounds even more today. He termed the digital ID system push as potentially leading to the “Chinafication” of Europe. Drawing parallels with Communist China’s surveillance mechanisms, Terhes’s statement underscores concerns that Europe might be on a similar trajectory, sacrificing privacy at the altar of supposed convenience. The EU’s plan to potentially introduce a Central Bank Digital Currency (CBDC) further intensifies these apprehensions. Beyond the economic implications, a CBDC could provide an infrastructure for governments to monitor, and possibly control, individual financial transactions, curtailing financial freedom. While digital transformation and global standardization have undeniable merits, the cost of personal freedom and privacy should be paramount. As the line between connectivity and control blurs, one must ask: are we inadvertently laying the foundation for a digital dystopia?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Johnson Raises Red Flags - Obama’s Ties to Influence Peddling</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/11/Obama-Influence-Peddling/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Johnson Raises Red Flags - Obama’s Ties to Influence Peddling" /><published>2023-09-11T12:01:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-11T12:01:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/11/Obama-Influence-Peddling</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/11/Obama-Influence-Peddling/">&lt;p&gt;Deepening concerns and raising eyebrows in the corridors of Washington, Sen. Ron Johnson, R-Wis., has cast a shadow over former President Barack Obama’s knowledge of the alleged influence peddling saga. In a revealing conversation, Johnson pulled no punches, stating that Obama was “fully aware of a lot of this.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Underpinning his claim with significant details, Johnson shed light on the fact that the Obama State Department was more than just familiar with the alleged influence peddling associated with Hunter Biden. To add fuel to the fire, Johnson explained, “President Obama was briefed, together with Vice President Biden, by then-CIA Director John Brennan about the scheme that the Hillary Clinton campaign had to accuse the Trump campaign of colluding with Russia.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Making a hard-hitting assertion, Johnson underlined that Obama was in the know about the concocted narrative of Russian collusion. “President Obama knew full well that the Russian collusion scheme false narrative was a hoax,” he stated firmly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reflecting on the steps taken against Michael Flynn, he mentioned, “They certainly set up Michael Flynn so that he would never be involved in the Trump White House because he was just too dangerous. He knew too much.” For Johnson, the Obama administration’s actions toward Flynn smacked of ulterior motives, which he says extends to the broader influence peddling episode.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The National Archives and Records Administration (NARA) recently missed a deadline to turn over documents associated with then-Vice President Joe Biden’s alias email accounts. These records are of particular interest to the House Oversight Committee, which is meticulously combing through the Hunter Biden situation. As it stands, the Biden White House and former President Obama have received the documents, with permission pending for their release to the Oversight Committee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Johnson, expressing his growing exasperation, stated, “Sen. Grassley and I have written multiple letters, three to the White House, starting in the summer of 2021, asking for those same documents.” He emphasized the consistent stonewalling they’ve faced from the current administration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Taking a direct jab at Obama, Johnson remarked, “I don’t know why he’s not allowing to release them now,” hinting at possible inconsistencies in Obama’s approach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Johnson’s revelations point to a possible impeachment inquiry, emphasizing the duty of Congress to maintain constitutional oversight. As the layers of this political drama unfold, Johnson’s words paint a picture that many in Washington would rather remain hidden.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Deepening concerns and raising eyebrows in the corridors of Washington, Sen. Ron Johnson, R-Wis., has cast a shadow over former President Barack Obama’s knowledge of the alleged influence peddling saga. In a revealing conversation, Johnson pulled no punches, stating that Obama was “fully aware of a lot of this.” Underpinning his claim with significant details, Johnson shed light on the fact that the Obama State Department was more than just familiar with the alleged influence peddling associated with Hunter Biden. To add fuel to the fire, Johnson explained, “President Obama was briefed, together with Vice President Biden, by then-CIA Director John Brennan about the scheme that the Hillary Clinton campaign had to accuse the Trump campaign of colluding with Russia.” Making a hard-hitting assertion, Johnson underlined that Obama was in the know about the concocted narrative of Russian collusion. “President Obama knew full well that the Russian collusion scheme false narrative was a hoax,” he stated firmly. Reflecting on the steps taken against Michael Flynn, he mentioned, “They certainly set up Michael Flynn so that he would never be involved in the Trump White House because he was just too dangerous. He knew too much.” For Johnson, the Obama administration’s actions toward Flynn smacked of ulterior motives, which he says extends to the broader influence peddling episode. The National Archives and Records Administration (NARA) recently missed a deadline to turn over documents associated with then-Vice President Joe Biden’s alias email accounts. These records are of particular interest to the House Oversight Committee, which is meticulously combing through the Hunter Biden situation. As it stands, the Biden White House and former President Obama have received the documents, with permission pending for their release to the Oversight Committee. Johnson, expressing his growing exasperation, stated, “Sen. Grassley and I have written multiple letters, three to the White House, starting in the summer of 2021, asking for those same documents.” He emphasized the consistent stonewalling they’ve faced from the current administration. Taking a direct jab at Obama, Johnson remarked, “I don’t know why he’s not allowing to release them now,” hinting at possible inconsistencies in Obama’s approach. Johnson’s revelations point to a possible impeachment inquiry, emphasizing the duty of Congress to maintain constitutional oversight. As the layers of this political drama unfold, Johnson’s words paint a picture that many in Washington would rather remain hidden.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Remembering 9-11 - A Journey from Grief to Purpose</title><link href="/news/2023/09/11/Remembering-9-11/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Remembering 9-11 - A Journey from Grief to Purpose" /><published>2023-09-11T11:11:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-11T11:11:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/11/Remembering-9-11</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/11/Remembering-9-11/">&lt;p&gt;As the 22nd anniversary of the fateful September 11th terror attacks dawns, Pastor Jesse Bradley from Auburn, Washington, underscores the importance of taking a moment to recall the tragic events that reshaped the nation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;reliving-the-past-to-shape-our-future&quot;&gt;Reliving The Past to Shape Our Future&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It is important to pause and remember what happened,” said Pastor Jesse Bradley of Washington. “It shapes our path forward.” The attacks were not just a series of unfortunate events; they altered the course of countless lives, cities, and the nation’s collective consciousness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-legacy-continues&quot;&gt;The Legacy Continues&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two years ago, participants of the 9/11 Promise Run brandished American flags, a stark reminder of the unity and strength the nation exhibited post the attacks. Christopher “Dom” Colasanti, a bond trader at Cantor Fitzgerald, was one of the many who lost their lives during the World Trade Center attack. Bradley remembers him as a teammate from Dartmouth College. He recalls the dedication of the men’s varsity locker room in honor of Colasanti, signifying the bonds and friendships formed there. The legacy of such individuals, characterized by connecting, serving, joy, and love, endures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;sacrifices-and-acts-of-bravery&quot;&gt;Sacrifices and Acts of Bravery&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amid the chaos and devastation, first responders across the country raced into peril, exemplifying bravery and selflessness. Their unflinching commitment serves as a constant source of inspiration. “Love includes sacrifice,” Bradley asserts, urging everyone to read about Todd Beamer’s final moments. Beamer, aboard Flight 93, courageously confronted the hijackers, preventing further potential devastation in the nation’s capital.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Quoting 1 John 3:16, Pastor Bradley emphasizes, “This is how we know what love is: Jesus Christ laid down his life for us. And we ought to lay down our lives for our brothers and sisters.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;trust-healing-and-purpose-in-faith&quot;&gt;Trust, Healing, and Purpose in Faith&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anchoring his message in faith, Bradley references the national motto, “In God We Trust.” A relationship with God, he believes, offers healing, restoration, and an unyielding hope surpassing any sorrow. Echoing Psalm 46:10, he emphasizes, “Be still, and know that I am God; I will be exalted among the nations, I will be exalted in the earth.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The pastor concludes with a powerful call to action, cautioning against complacency and idolatry. He inspires with the words, “If you are overcoming tragedy and trauma, remember that you are loved.” The message is clear: On the anniversary of September 11th and always, “We remember our loved ones,” and we discover peace and profound purpose.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">As the 22nd anniversary of the fateful September 11th terror attacks dawns, Pastor Jesse Bradley from Auburn, Washington, underscores the importance of taking a moment to recall the tragic events that reshaped the nation. Reliving The Past to Shape Our Future “It is important to pause and remember what happened,” said Pastor Jesse Bradley of Washington. “It shapes our path forward.” The attacks were not just a series of unfortunate events; they altered the course of countless lives, cities, and the nation’s collective consciousness. The Legacy Continues Two years ago, participants of the 9/11 Promise Run brandished American flags, a stark reminder of the unity and strength the nation exhibited post the attacks. Christopher “Dom” Colasanti, a bond trader at Cantor Fitzgerald, was one of the many who lost their lives during the World Trade Center attack. Bradley remembers him as a teammate from Dartmouth College. He recalls the dedication of the men’s varsity locker room in honor of Colasanti, signifying the bonds and friendships formed there. The legacy of such individuals, characterized by connecting, serving, joy, and love, endures. Sacrifices and Acts of Bravery Amid the chaos and devastation, first responders across the country raced into peril, exemplifying bravery and selflessness. Their unflinching commitment serves as a constant source of inspiration. “Love includes sacrifice,” Bradley asserts, urging everyone to read about Todd Beamer’s final moments. Beamer, aboard Flight 93, courageously confronted the hijackers, preventing further potential devastation in the nation’s capital. Quoting 1 John 3:16, Pastor Bradley emphasizes, “This is how we know what love is: Jesus Christ laid down his life for us. And we ought to lay down our lives for our brothers and sisters.” Trust, Healing, and Purpose in Faith Anchoring his message in faith, Bradley references the national motto, “In God We Trust.” A relationship with God, he believes, offers healing, restoration, and an unyielding hope surpassing any sorrow. Echoing Psalm 46:10, he emphasizes, “Be still, and know that I am God; I will be exalted among the nations, I will be exalted in the earth.” The pastor concludes with a powerful call to action, cautioning against complacency and idolatry. He inspires with the words, “If you are overcoming tragedy and trauma, remember that you are loved.” The message is clear: On the anniversary of September 11th and always, “We remember our loved ones,” and we discover peace and profound purpose.</summary></entry></feed>