<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-09-08T05:15:01-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/09/08/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-09-08T05:15:01-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-08T05:15:01-04:00</updated><id>/2023/09/08/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/08/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Another Mar-a-Lago Drama - Real Investigation or Political Theatre?</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/07/Investigation-Theater/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Another Mar-a-Lago Drama - Real Investigation or Political Theatre?" /><published>2023-09-07T19:54:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-07T19:54:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/07/Investigation-Theater</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/07/Investigation-Theater/">&lt;p&gt;Amidst the relentless political theater that has defined much of post-presidential life for Donald Trump, a new act has commenced. CNN reported that Yuscil Taveras, an IT worker from Mar-a-Lago, has agreed to cooperate with special counsel Jack Smith against Trump. Yet, the intricacies of the case and the timing of the investigation leave many observers skeptical.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What we’ve come to understand is that Taveras initially made a statement which eventually led to the indictment of the former President and his close associate, Walt Nauta, concerning alleged mishandling of classified data. But here’s the kicker: Taveras is now exempt from prosecution on perjury charges in exchange for his testimony. The question many are asking is, why the sudden shift?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Taveras’ attorney, Stanley Woodward, who also represents other witnesses in this probe, pointedly remarked on the special treatment for Taveras. “It is telling that the Non-Prosecution Agreement it ultimately offered Trump Employee 4 was not offered before the District Court had agreed to appoint ‘conflict counsel,’” he observed, referencing Taveras.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back in July, the narrative took a turn when Taveras accused the former president of instructing others to request the deletion of certain security footage. Yet, a filing from Smith in August revealed that Taveras had previously “denied or claimed not to recall any contacts or conversations about the security footage at Mar-a-Lago.” It was only after learning he might be the target of a perjury investigation that Taveras reversed course.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stanley Woodward, in light of these developments, stated he “played no role” in Taveras’ choice to cooperate. But one has to wonder: Is this about genuine concerns over national security, or are we watching another high-stakes political game at play?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For many, the ordeal appears as another episode in a series of attempts to undermine the legacy of Trump. And as the case unfolds, the public will be eagerly watching, questioning the true intentions behind this investigation.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Amidst the relentless political theater that has defined much of post-presidential life for Donald Trump, a new act has commenced. CNN reported that Yuscil Taveras, an IT worker from Mar-a-Lago, has agreed to cooperate with special counsel Jack Smith against Trump. Yet, the intricacies of the case and the timing of the investigation leave many observers skeptical. What we’ve come to understand is that Taveras initially made a statement which eventually led to the indictment of the former President and his close associate, Walt Nauta, concerning alleged mishandling of classified data. But here’s the kicker: Taveras is now exempt from prosecution on perjury charges in exchange for his testimony. The question many are asking is, why the sudden shift? Taveras’ attorney, Stanley Woodward, who also represents other witnesses in this probe, pointedly remarked on the special treatment for Taveras. “It is telling that the Non-Prosecution Agreement it ultimately offered Trump Employee 4 was not offered before the District Court had agreed to appoint ‘conflict counsel,’” he observed, referencing Taveras. Back in July, the narrative took a turn when Taveras accused the former president of instructing others to request the deletion of certain security footage. Yet, a filing from Smith in August revealed that Taveras had previously “denied or claimed not to recall any contacts or conversations about the security footage at Mar-a-Lago.” It was only after learning he might be the target of a perjury investigation that Taveras reversed course. Stanley Woodward, in light of these developments, stated he “played no role” in Taveras’ choice to cooperate. But one has to wonder: Is this about genuine concerns over national security, or are we watching another high-stakes political game at play? For many, the ordeal appears as another episode in a series of attempts to undermine the legacy of Trump. And as the case unfolds, the public will be eagerly watching, questioning the true intentions behind this investigation.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Desert Despair - Burning Man Festival Faces Backlash Over Abandoned Cars and Waste</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/07/Burning-Man-Controversy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Desert Despair - Burning Man Festival Faces Backlash Over Abandoned Cars and Waste" /><published>2023-09-07T18:48:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-07T18:48:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/07/Burning-Man-Controversy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/07/Burning-Man-Controversy/">&lt;p&gt;Burning Man, the iconic annual art and music festival held in Nevada’s Black Rock desert, is no stranger to controversy. However, this year’s edition has come under intense scrutiny due to the environmental mess left behind by tens of thousands of attendees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pershing County Sheriff Jerry Allen voiced his disappointment and concern about the piles of trash and numerous abandoned vehicles littering the desert. The attendees reportedly left in haste, trying to escape the harsh desert conditions worsened by an unexpected storm. Allen conveyed his observations to the San Francisco Chronicle, describing the behavior of the departing festival-goers as inconsiderate and even hostile.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sheriff Allen pointed out the irony of the situation, stating that such behavior blatantly contradicts the ten principles of Burning Man, which emphasize community, self-reliance, and leaving no trace. While it’s a known fact that Burning Man occasionally leaves traces of debris stretching to Reno and beyond, the aftermath of this year’s festival has been exceptionally alarming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“This year is a little different in that there are numerous vehicles strewn all throughout the playa for several miles,” Allen commented.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a further indictment, Allen placed a portion of the responsibility on the Burning Man organizers. He believes they should be held accountable for ensuring a thorough cleanup of the area after the event concludes each year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the event’s challenges didn’t end there. The storm at the festival’s peak led to a tragic incident resulting in the death of a 32-year-old man, identified as Leon Reece. While festival and medical personnel tried to resuscitate him, the severe weather conditions delayed authorities’ access to the scene, complicating the situation further.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The unfortunate combination of environmental neglect and a tragic death has cast a shadow over this year’s Burning Man festival. As the aftermath unfolds, it brings to light the essential question of responsibility and sustainability for large-scale events held in fragile environments.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Burning Man, the iconic annual art and music festival held in Nevada’s Black Rock desert, is no stranger to controversy. However, this year’s edition has come under intense scrutiny due to the environmental mess left behind by tens of thousands of attendees. Pershing County Sheriff Jerry Allen voiced his disappointment and concern about the piles of trash and numerous abandoned vehicles littering the desert. The attendees reportedly left in haste, trying to escape the harsh desert conditions worsened by an unexpected storm. Allen conveyed his observations to the San Francisco Chronicle, describing the behavior of the departing festival-goers as inconsiderate and even hostile. Sheriff Allen pointed out the irony of the situation, stating that such behavior blatantly contradicts the ten principles of Burning Man, which emphasize community, self-reliance, and leaving no trace. While it’s a known fact that Burning Man occasionally leaves traces of debris stretching to Reno and beyond, the aftermath of this year’s festival has been exceptionally alarming. “This year is a little different in that there are numerous vehicles strewn all throughout the playa for several miles,” Allen commented. In a further indictment, Allen placed a portion of the responsibility on the Burning Man organizers. He believes they should be held accountable for ensuring a thorough cleanup of the area after the event concludes each year. However, the event’s challenges didn’t end there. The storm at the festival’s peak led to a tragic incident resulting in the death of a 32-year-old man, identified as Leon Reece. While festival and medical personnel tried to resuscitate him, the severe weather conditions delayed authorities’ access to the scene, complicating the situation further. The unfortunate combination of environmental neglect and a tragic death has cast a shadow over this year’s Burning Man festival. As the aftermath unfolds, it brings to light the essential question of responsibility and sustainability for large-scale events held in fragile environments.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Targeting Alito - Democratic Senator’s Controversial Ethics Accusations</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/07/Alito-Under-Fire/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Targeting Alito - Democratic Senator’s Controversial Ethics Accusations" /><published>2023-09-07T17:54:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-07T17:54:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/07/Alito-Under-Fire</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/07/Alito-Under-Fire/">&lt;p&gt;In what some view as a partisan maneuver, Democratic Senator Sheldon Whitehouse has lodged an ethics complaint against esteemed Supreme Court Justice Samuel Alito.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Rhode Island Senator, who chairs the Senate Judiciary Courts Subcommittee, sent a letter to Supreme Court Chief Justice John Roberts. The letter criticizes Justice Alito primarily for his open criticism of Whitehouse’s proposed Supreme Court ethics reform bill.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whitehouse’s letter insinuates, without clear evidence, that Justice Alito might be part of a “coordinated effort” against congressional action. This move has raised eyebrows in political circles and made many wonder about the genuine intent behind such a complaint.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Justice Alito, known for his commitment to justice and the Constitution, categorically denies the allegations. He has unambiguously stated that the Constitution does not give Congress the power to regulate the Supreme Court. Furthermore, he proactively addressed an issue concerning a 2008 fishing trip, with Republican billionaire Paul Singer, clarifying that it did not necessitate any financial disclosure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A concerning point in this episode is the absence of a formal procedure to file complaints against Supreme Court justices, possibly allowing room for politically-motivated maneuvers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whitehouse’s allegations, which carry a discernible partisan tone, suggest Alito might have opined on issues that could come before the Court. Additionally, he hints at the Justice’s alleged acceptance of gifts from conservative billionaires, painting it as a potential ethical issue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The “Supreme Court Ethics, Recusal, and Transparency Act,” S.359, currently under Senate scrutiny, seems to play a central role in this narrative. This bill, seeking to overhaul the Court’s ethical standards, secured a nod from the Senate Judiciary Committee in July.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A ProPublica report, viewed by some as biased against conservative figures, insinuated that Alito may have enjoyed certain privileges, like private jet travels, from particular billionaires. In these divisive times, it remains crucial to evaluate such claims with an unbiased lens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As this situation unfolds, the importance of safeguarding the integrity of the judiciary from potentially politically-driven allegations stands clear, ensuring that our Supreme Court remains an emblem of unbiased justice.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In what some view as a partisan maneuver, Democratic Senator Sheldon Whitehouse has lodged an ethics complaint against esteemed Supreme Court Justice Samuel Alito. The Rhode Island Senator, who chairs the Senate Judiciary Courts Subcommittee, sent a letter to Supreme Court Chief Justice John Roberts. The letter criticizes Justice Alito primarily for his open criticism of Whitehouse’s proposed Supreme Court ethics reform bill. Whitehouse’s letter insinuates, without clear evidence, that Justice Alito might be part of a “coordinated effort” against congressional action. This move has raised eyebrows in political circles and made many wonder about the genuine intent behind such a complaint. Justice Alito, known for his commitment to justice and the Constitution, categorically denies the allegations. He has unambiguously stated that the Constitution does not give Congress the power to regulate the Supreme Court. Furthermore, he proactively addressed an issue concerning a 2008 fishing trip, with Republican billionaire Paul Singer, clarifying that it did not necessitate any financial disclosure. A concerning point in this episode is the absence of a formal procedure to file complaints against Supreme Court justices, possibly allowing room for politically-motivated maneuvers. Whitehouse’s allegations, which carry a discernible partisan tone, suggest Alito might have opined on issues that could come before the Court. Additionally, he hints at the Justice’s alleged acceptance of gifts from conservative billionaires, painting it as a potential ethical issue. The “Supreme Court Ethics, Recusal, and Transparency Act,” S.359, currently under Senate scrutiny, seems to play a central role in this narrative. This bill, seeking to overhaul the Court’s ethical standards, secured a nod from the Senate Judiciary Committee in July. A ProPublica report, viewed by some as biased against conservative figures, insinuated that Alito may have enjoyed certain privileges, like private jet travels, from particular billionaires. In these divisive times, it remains crucial to evaluate such claims with an unbiased lens. As this situation unfolds, the importance of safeguarding the integrity of the judiciary from potentially politically-driven allegations stands clear, ensuring that our Supreme Court remains an emblem of unbiased justice.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump Shows Steadfast Confidence - Ready to Testify in Classified Documents Case</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/07/Trump-Testify/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump Shows Steadfast Confidence - Ready to Testify in Classified Documents Case" /><published>2023-09-07T16:59:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-07T16:59:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/07/Trump-Testify</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/07/Trump-Testify/">&lt;p&gt;In a steadfast show of confidence and transparency, former President Donald Trump recently revealed that he is prepared to testify in his own defense over a controversial trial concerning classified documents. This move, while risky, serves as a testament to Trump’s enduring commitment to clear his name and face his accusers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a conversation with the renowned conservative radio host Hugh Hewitt, Trump declared, “I look forward to testifying.” This powerful statement comes amidst mounting allegations of mishandling sensitive national security documents at his Mar-a-Lago resort post his presidential tenure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The case is one among the four criminal trials that Trump might face in the coming year. Still, the former President remains steadfast in his belief of innocence, denouncing all the charges against him. Not only has he pleaded not guilty to every accusation, but he has also raised concerns about being singled out for political reasons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This isn’t the first time Trump has demonstrated a readiness to stand up and face inquiries head-on. In 2018, he indicated his willingness to communicate under oath with the then U.S. Special Counsel Robert Mueller regarding potential links between his 2016 presidential campaign and the Russian government. Though Trump did not eventually speak with the prosecutors and was exempt from any charges in that investigation, his initial inclination to testify reveals a consistent pattern of his confrontational stance in defending his honor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many would see Trump’s choice to testify as a gamble, given the potential for prosecutors to try and extract compromising information from him under oath. However, in Trump’s perspective, it might be an opportunity to directly challenge the allegations and underscore his claims of a politically motivated agenda against him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the 2024 Presidential race on the horizon and Trump leading as the Republican front-runner, these trials and his decisions could play a pivotal role in the political narrative leading up to the elections.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a steadfast show of confidence and transparency, former President Donald Trump recently revealed that he is prepared to testify in his own defense over a controversial trial concerning classified documents. This move, while risky, serves as a testament to Trump’s enduring commitment to clear his name and face his accusers. In a conversation with the renowned conservative radio host Hugh Hewitt, Trump declared, “I look forward to testifying.” This powerful statement comes amidst mounting allegations of mishandling sensitive national security documents at his Mar-a-Lago resort post his presidential tenure. The case is one among the four criminal trials that Trump might face in the coming year. Still, the former President remains steadfast in his belief of innocence, denouncing all the charges against him. Not only has he pleaded not guilty to every accusation, but he has also raised concerns about being singled out for political reasons. This isn’t the first time Trump has demonstrated a readiness to stand up and face inquiries head-on. In 2018, he indicated his willingness to communicate under oath with the then U.S. Special Counsel Robert Mueller regarding potential links between his 2016 presidential campaign and the Russian government. Though Trump did not eventually speak with the prosecutors and was exempt from any charges in that investigation, his initial inclination to testify reveals a consistent pattern of his confrontational stance in defending his honor. Many would see Trump’s choice to testify as a gamble, given the potential for prosecutors to try and extract compromising information from him under oath. However, in Trump’s perspective, it might be an opportunity to directly challenge the allegations and underscore his claims of a politically motivated agenda against him. With the 2024 Presidential race on the horizon and Trump leading as the Republican front-runner, these trials and his decisions could play a pivotal role in the political narrative leading up to the elections.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hollywood Actor Gary Busey - Another Accident Controversy</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/07/Gary-Busey-Investigation/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hollywood Actor Gary Busey - Another Accident Controversy" /><published>2023-09-07T15:49:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-07T15:49:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/07/Gary-Busey-Investigation</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/07/Gary-Busey-Investigation/">&lt;p&gt;Gary Busey, famed for his roles in blockbuster hits like “Lethal Weapon” and “Point Break,” is under the spotlight yet again, this time for his alleged involvement in a hit-and-run car accident.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On a recent August afternoon, while driving his blue Volvo along Malibu’s scenic stretch of the Pacific Coast Highway, Busey reportedly collided with another vehicle. The incident, as described in a report from the Los Angeles County Sheriff’s Department, escalated when the “Point Break” actor allegedly fled the scene without stopping post-impact or providing any proof of registration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The accident’s details are still under official investigation. However, the driver of the vehicle Busey collided with claims to have recognized the actor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;History of Accidents&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Busey’s history with accidents is, unfortunately, not new. In 2015, while backing out of a parking spot in Malibu, Busey accidentally hit and slightly injured a woman. Although he was cited at the time, neither alcohol nor illegal substances were found to have played a part in the accident.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perhaps the most significant and life-altering accident involving Busey occurred in 1988. While riding his motorcycle without a helmet, Busey met with a severe crash that fractured his skull and led to permanent brain damage. Recounting the tragic event to The Guardian in 2020, Busey described a near-death experience that took him to a spiritual realm. The actor views the accident as an essential part of his life’s journey and growth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trials and Tribulations&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Busey’s life post the 1988 accident, though filled with continued professional endeavors, hasn’t been without significant controversies. Last summer, he faced multiple charges, including fourth-degree criminal sexual contact and harassment, after an alleged incident at the DoubleTree Hotel in New Jersey. While Busey denies any wrongdoing, it’s clear that the star’s journey has been a complex blend of highs and lows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As investigations regarding the recent hit-and-run continue, fans and critics alike await more clarity on the incident. Gary Busey’s representative has yet to respond to the allegations.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Gary Busey, famed for his roles in blockbuster hits like “Lethal Weapon” and “Point Break,” is under the spotlight yet again, this time for his alleged involvement in a hit-and-run car accident. On a recent August afternoon, while driving his blue Volvo along Malibu’s scenic stretch of the Pacific Coast Highway, Busey reportedly collided with another vehicle. The incident, as described in a report from the Los Angeles County Sheriff’s Department, escalated when the “Point Break” actor allegedly fled the scene without stopping post-impact or providing any proof of registration. The accident’s details are still under official investigation. However, the driver of the vehicle Busey collided with claims to have recognized the actor. History of Accidents Busey’s history with accidents is, unfortunately, not new. In 2015, while backing out of a parking spot in Malibu, Busey accidentally hit and slightly injured a woman. Although he was cited at the time, neither alcohol nor illegal substances were found to have played a part in the accident. Perhaps the most significant and life-altering accident involving Busey occurred in 1988. While riding his motorcycle without a helmet, Busey met with a severe crash that fractured his skull and led to permanent brain damage. Recounting the tragic event to The Guardian in 2020, Busey described a near-death experience that took him to a spiritual realm. The actor views the accident as an essential part of his life’s journey and growth. Trials and Tribulations Busey’s life post the 1988 accident, though filled with continued professional endeavors, hasn’t been without significant controversies. Last summer, he faced multiple charges, including fourth-degree criminal sexual contact and harassment, after an alleged incident at the DoubleTree Hotel in New Jersey. While Busey denies any wrongdoing, it’s clear that the star’s journey has been a complex blend of highs and lows. As investigations regarding the recent hit-and-run continue, fans and critics alike await more clarity on the incident. Gary Busey’s representative has yet to respond to the allegations.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Rio Grande Barriers Shifted - Compromising Texas’s Border Security?</title><link href="/news/2023/09/07/Texas-Rio-Grande-Barrier/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rio Grande Barriers Shifted - Compromising Texas’s Border Security?" /><published>2023-09-07T14:52:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-07T14:52:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/07/Texas-Rio-Grande-Barrier</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/07/Texas-Rio-Grande-Barrier/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Critical Blow to Texas Border Security Amidst Rising Immigration Concerns&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As Texas grapples with a surging wave of unauthorized border crossings, a recent legal decision is causing ripples of concern among proponents of stringent border security measures. A U.S. judge has called for the relocation of floating buoys in the Rio Grande, key barriers that Texas Governor Greg Abbott had put in place to deter illegal crossings at the U.S.-Mexico border.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Floating Barriers: Essential Defense or Navigational Hazard?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;U.S. District Court Judge David Ezra mandated the removal of these strategically placed buoys from the river’s midpoint to an embankment on the Texan side. The ruling stemmed from a lawsuit initiated by President Joe Biden’s administration, claiming that Texas had placed these barriers unlawfully, potentially disrupting navigation without the explicit permission of the U.S. Army Corps of Engineers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This move raises eyebrows among those who see these barriers as an essential component in the toolkit of border control strategies that Texas has employed under Governor Abbott’s watch. The governor, known for his robust approach to immigration, has not just stopped at floating barriers but also incorporated razor wire coils along the riverbank to ensure the state’s borders remain secure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Judge Ezra’s 42-page order took a rather dismissive tone, emphasizing that Texas failed to ask for the necessary authorization for these barriers. He stated, “Governor Abbott announced that he was not ‘asking for permission’ for Operation Lone Star… Unfortunately for Texas, permission is exactly what federal law requires.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Battle for a Secure Border Continues&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the recent decision, questions are emerging about the potential gaps this could create in the state’s defense against unauthorized crossings, especially given the record numbers of migrants trying to enter the U.S. illegally in recent years. The growing discord between federal stances and state measures on border control highlights the intricate challenges Texas faces in its pursuit to secure its borders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the broader debate on border security persists, many hope Texas will appeal this decision, given the vital role these barriers play in the state’s protective measures. This development underscores the tension and complexity surrounding the task of ensuring both national security and adhering to federal regulations.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Critical Blow to Texas Border Security Amidst Rising Immigration Concerns As Texas grapples with a surging wave of unauthorized border crossings, a recent legal decision is causing ripples of concern among proponents of stringent border security measures. A U.S. judge has called for the relocation of floating buoys in the Rio Grande, key barriers that Texas Governor Greg Abbott had put in place to deter illegal crossings at the U.S.-Mexico border. Floating Barriers: Essential Defense or Navigational Hazard? U.S. District Court Judge David Ezra mandated the removal of these strategically placed buoys from the river’s midpoint to an embankment on the Texan side. The ruling stemmed from a lawsuit initiated by President Joe Biden’s administration, claiming that Texas had placed these barriers unlawfully, potentially disrupting navigation without the explicit permission of the U.S. Army Corps of Engineers. This move raises eyebrows among those who see these barriers as an essential component in the toolkit of border control strategies that Texas has employed under Governor Abbott’s watch. The governor, known for his robust approach to immigration, has not just stopped at floating barriers but also incorporated razor wire coils along the riverbank to ensure the state’s borders remain secure. Judge Ezra’s 42-page order took a rather dismissive tone, emphasizing that Texas failed to ask for the necessary authorization for these barriers. He stated, “Governor Abbott announced that he was not ‘asking for permission’ for Operation Lone Star… Unfortunately for Texas, permission is exactly what federal law requires.” The Battle for a Secure Border Continues With the recent decision, questions are emerging about the potential gaps this could create in the state’s defense against unauthorized crossings, especially given the record numbers of migrants trying to enter the U.S. illegally in recent years. The growing discord between federal stances and state measures on border control highlights the intricate challenges Texas faces in its pursuit to secure its borders. While the broader debate on border security persists, many hope Texas will appeal this decision, given the vital role these barriers play in the state’s protective measures. This development underscores the tension and complexity surrounding the task of ensuring both national security and adhering to federal regulations.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Unveiling the Silent Battle - Bob Barker’s Cause of Death</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/07/Bob-Barker-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Unveiling the Silent Battle - Bob Barker’s Cause of Death" /><published>2023-09-07T13:42:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-07T13:42:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/07/Bob-Barker-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/07/Bob-Barker-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Bob Barker, whose name became synonymous with daytime TV and the ever-entertaining “The Price is Right,” passed away last month. Reports now reveal that the charismatic TV personality had been silently grappling with Alzheimer’s Disease for years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to a death certificate accessed by PEOPLE, Barker’s demise at the venerable age of 99 came after a prolonged battle with this neurodegenerative disorder. The certificate didn’t specify the exact time of diagnosis but confirmed that the beloved game show host had been living with Alzheimer’s Disease for “years.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to Alzheimer’s, other health challenges faced by Barker in his later years included hypertension (high blood pressure), hypothyroidism, and hyperlipidemia (high cholesterol). These were listed as “other significant conditions” that may have contributed to his passing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Barker’s influence on American television is undeniable. From 1972 to 2007, his daily presence on CBS’s “The Price is Right” was a comforting ritual for countless fans, spanning generations. His signature charm and affable demeanor made him a favorite among both housewives and young ones spending a sick day away from school.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Barker’s professional life was filled with accolades and fan adoration, his personal life saw its share of sorrow. His wife, Dorothy Jo, passed away in 1981. The couple had no children, and Barker chose not to remarry, dedicating his later years to various philanthropic efforts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the entertainment industry mourns the loss of one of its brightest stars, Bob Barker’s legacy as a television icon remains indelible. His contribution to the world of entertainment, coupled with the strength he displayed in his personal battles, will be remembered for years to come.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Bob Barker, whose name became synonymous with daytime TV and the ever-entertaining “The Price is Right,” passed away last month. Reports now reveal that the charismatic TV personality had been silently grappling with Alzheimer’s Disease for years. According to a death certificate accessed by PEOPLE, Barker’s demise at the venerable age of 99 came after a prolonged battle with this neurodegenerative disorder. The certificate didn’t specify the exact time of diagnosis but confirmed that the beloved game show host had been living with Alzheimer’s Disease for “years.” In addition to Alzheimer’s, other health challenges faced by Barker in his later years included hypertension (high blood pressure), hypothyroidism, and hyperlipidemia (high cholesterol). These were listed as “other significant conditions” that may have contributed to his passing. Barker’s influence on American television is undeniable. From 1972 to 2007, his daily presence on CBS’s “The Price is Right” was a comforting ritual for countless fans, spanning generations. His signature charm and affable demeanor made him a favorite among both housewives and young ones spending a sick day away from school. While Barker’s professional life was filled with accolades and fan adoration, his personal life saw its share of sorrow. His wife, Dorothy Jo, passed away in 1981. The couple had no children, and Barker chose not to remarry, dedicating his later years to various philanthropic efforts. As the entertainment industry mourns the loss of one of its brightest stars, Bob Barker’s legacy as a television icon remains indelible. His contribution to the world of entertainment, coupled with the strength he displayed in his personal battles, will be remembered for years to come.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Justice on the Horizon - Madison Police Apprehend University Assault Suspect</title><link href="/news/2023/09/07/Madison-Assault-Suspect-Caught/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Justice on the Horizon - Madison Police Apprehend University Assault Suspect" /><published>2023-09-07T12:56:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-07T12:56:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/07/Madison-Assault-Suspect-Caught</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/07/Madison-Assault-Suspect-Caught/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Swift Action Leads to an Important Arrest in Madison&lt;/strong&gt;
In the aftermath of a heinous crime that sent shockwaves through Madison, Wisconsin’s serene streets, justice seems to be on the horizon. The Madison police, in a significant breakthrough, have arrested a suspect believed to be behind the brutal assault on a University of Wisconsin-Madison student.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Arrest in Disturbing Case&lt;/strong&gt;
The city breathed a collective sigh of relief as 26-year-old Brandon A. Thompson was taken into custody. Thompson, a Madison resident, now faces charges of first-degree sexual assault, first-degree reckless injury, and strangulation, as confirmed by Madison police spokeswoman Alyssa Cains.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The student’s life was tragically and abruptly upended in the early hours of a Sunday morning. Discovered near Lake Monona, she was left with life-threatening injuries following a savage sidewalk assault. The nature and brutality of the attack had left the community in palpable fear and uncertainty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Suspect’s Apprehension: A Momentary Respite&lt;/strong&gt;
The arrest of Thompson, particularly given that the assault was believed to be a chance encounter with a stranger, provides a degree of closure and safety to a community grappling with the trauma of the incident. The victim, reports suggest, endured a nightmarish ordeal, having been abducted from the sidewalk and subjected to physical and sexual violence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Looking Ahead: Ensuring Safety in Madison&lt;/strong&gt;
While Thompson’s arrest marks significant progress in this case, Madison stands at an important crossroads. This incident has highlighted the pressing need for reinforced safety measures, more patrolling, and enhanced community vigilance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the suspect in custody, the focus shifts towards healing, community resilience, and fortifying measures to ensure that Madison’s streets remain safe for every resident and student. The unwavering commitment of Madison’s police force combined with a vigilant community will undoubtedly pave the way for a safer tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Swift Action Leads to an Important Arrest in Madison In the aftermath of a heinous crime that sent shockwaves through Madison, Wisconsin’s serene streets, justice seems to be on the horizon. The Madison police, in a significant breakthrough, have arrested a suspect believed to be behind the brutal assault on a University of Wisconsin-Madison student. Key Arrest in Disturbing Case The city breathed a collective sigh of relief as 26-year-old Brandon A. Thompson was taken into custody. Thompson, a Madison resident, now faces charges of first-degree sexual assault, first-degree reckless injury, and strangulation, as confirmed by Madison police spokeswoman Alyssa Cains. The student’s life was tragically and abruptly upended in the early hours of a Sunday morning. Discovered near Lake Monona, she was left with life-threatening injuries following a savage sidewalk assault. The nature and brutality of the attack had left the community in palpable fear and uncertainty. Suspect’s Apprehension: A Momentary Respite The arrest of Thompson, particularly given that the assault was believed to be a chance encounter with a stranger, provides a degree of closure and safety to a community grappling with the trauma of the incident. The victim, reports suggest, endured a nightmarish ordeal, having been abducted from the sidewalk and subjected to physical and sexual violence. Looking Ahead: Ensuring Safety in Madison While Thompson’s arrest marks significant progress in this case, Madison stands at an important crossroads. This incident has highlighted the pressing need for reinforced safety measures, more patrolling, and enhanced community vigilance. With the suspect in custody, the focus shifts towards healing, community resilience, and fortifying measures to ensure that Madison’s streets remain safe for every resident and student. The unwavering commitment of Madison’s police force combined with a vigilant community will undoubtedly pave the way for a safer tomorrow.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump Emphasizes Strong Leadership in Afghanistan Withdrawal</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/07/Trump-Afghanistan-Deal/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump Emphasizes Strong Leadership in Afghanistan Withdrawal" /><published>2023-09-07T11:47:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-07T11:47:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/07/Trump-Afghanistan-Deal</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/07/Trump-Afghanistan-Deal/">&lt;p&gt;Amidst the chaos and questions surrounding the Afghanistan withdrawal, 2024 Republican presidential candidate and former President Donald Trump sets the record straight on his stance and the strategy of his administration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Wednesday’s “Hugh Hewitt Show,” Trump highlighted the distinctive strength and respect commanded by his administration in comparison to the Biden leadership. He discussed his deal with the Taliban, emphasizing that any violation on their part met with serious consequences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The former President stated, “So we [had] a step-by-step agreement. They didn’t fulfill certain steps, and therefore, we knocked the hell out of them. We didn’t lose a soldier in 18 months.” This stands in stark contrast to the violence and instability faced by American troops during the Obama administration, where Taliban snipers were a constant threat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump’s remarks point towards the hands-on, no-nonsense approach that his administration adopted. A significant conversation with Taliban leader Abdul underlined this approach, following which the U.S. didn’t lose a single soldier for a year and a half. Trump reiterated, “They had total respect for us. And we were going to get out, but we were going to get out with dignity and strength.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In drawing this comparison, Trump seems to make a clear distinction between the calculated strategy adopted by his administration and the perceived hastiness and lack of preparedness under Biden. As the 2024 presidential race looms ahead, such reflections provide a glimpse into the leadership styles of the former President, raising important questions about foreign policy strategies and America’s standing on the global stage.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Amidst the chaos and questions surrounding the Afghanistan withdrawal, 2024 Republican presidential candidate and former President Donald Trump sets the record straight on his stance and the strategy of his administration. On Wednesday’s “Hugh Hewitt Show,” Trump highlighted the distinctive strength and respect commanded by his administration in comparison to the Biden leadership. He discussed his deal with the Taliban, emphasizing that any violation on their part met with serious consequences. The former President stated, “So we [had] a step-by-step agreement. They didn’t fulfill certain steps, and therefore, we knocked the hell out of them. We didn’t lose a soldier in 18 months.” This stands in stark contrast to the violence and instability faced by American troops during the Obama administration, where Taliban snipers were a constant threat. Trump’s remarks point towards the hands-on, no-nonsense approach that his administration adopted. A significant conversation with Taliban leader Abdul underlined this approach, following which the U.S. didn’t lose a single soldier for a year and a half. Trump reiterated, “They had total respect for us. And we were going to get out, but we were going to get out with dignity and strength.” In drawing this comparison, Trump seems to make a clear distinction between the calculated strategy adopted by his administration and the perceived hastiness and lack of preparedness under Biden. As the 2024 presidential race looms ahead, such reflections provide a glimpse into the leadership styles of the former President, raising important questions about foreign policy strategies and America’s standing on the global stage.</summary></entry></feed>