<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-09-06T10:14:59-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/09/06/2023-08-10-King-of-the-Hill-Actor-Johnny-Hardwick-Passes/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-09-06T10:14:59-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-06T10:14:59-04:00</updated><id>/2023/09/06/2023-08-10-King-of-the-Hill-Actor-Johnny-Hardwick-Passes</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/06/2023-08-10-King-of-the-Hill-Actor-Johnny-Hardwick-Passes/">&lt;p&gt;The entertainment industry is mourning the loss of Johnny Hardwick, the acclaimed voice actor renowned for his portrayal of Dale Gribble in the popular animated series “King of the Hill.” At the age of 64, Hardwick’s demise has left many in shock.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The distressing news was confirmed by the Austin (Texas) Police Department, which attended a welfare check on Tuesday, leading to the tragic discovery of Hardwick’s lifeless body. While the circumstances surrounding his death are still shrouded in mystery, the Austin police have categorically stated that it isn’t a homicide case. Further details pertaining to the cause will be unveiled once the Travis County Medical Examiner finalizes their findings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hardwick’s role as Dale Gribble began in 1997 with the show’s premiere episode and lasted until its conclusion in 2010, spanning an impressive 259 episodes. His outstanding contribution to “King of the Hill” earned him an Emmy Award in 1999, followed by nominations in 2001 and 2002. The animated masterpiece was the brainchild of creators Mike Judge and Greg Daniels, with a cast ensemble including talents like Judge himself, Kathy Najimy, Stephen Root, and Pamela Adlon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earlier this year, fans rejoiced upon learning about a forthcoming revival of “King of the Hill,” with Hardwick’s involvement confirmed. Craig Erwich, the executive at the helm of ABC Entertainment, Hulu, and Disney Branded Television Streaming Originals, expressed enthusiasm about resuming the show’s narrative to reflect on our contemporary world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond his notable voice acting career, Hardwick was also a gifted stand-up comedian, making a mark in the comedy circuits during the 1990s.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/09/06/2023-08-12-Ian-Watkins-Assault/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-09-06T10:14:59-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-06T10:14:59-04:00</updated><id>/2023/09/06/2023-08-12-Ian-Watkins-Assault</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/06/2023-08-12-Ian-Watkins-Assault/">&lt;p&gt;Ian Watkins, the controversial former lead singer of the rock band Lostprophets, faced a brutal assault inside HMP Wakefield, where he’s currently serving a 29-year sentence for grave child sex crimes. According to sources, Watkins is in critical condition following the incident.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reports from the Mirror shed light on the gruesome nature of the assault. Allegedly, Watkins was accosted and held hostage by three inmates, subjected to hours of physical abuse, and eventually stabbed multiple times. Officers discovered the critically injured singer only hours later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Watkins was held for a lengthy period by the prisoners and endured a severe beating before the stabbing. The entire ordeal is under investigation,” conveyed the officials from HMP Wakefield. Fortunately, in a subsequent update from law enforcement, it was clarified that Watkins’ injuries, while severe, were not life-threatening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lostprophets, active from the late ’90s to the early 2000s, witnessed their downfall following the shocking revelations of Watkins’ depravities. In 2013, he faced charges for thirteen appalling sex offenses against children, which included the attempted rape of a one-year-old girl. The case revealed that Watkins administered drugs to children, plotting their sexual abuse, and even filmed some of his heinous acts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Confronted with overwhelming evidence, Watkins pleaded guilty to multiple counts of rape, sex with minors, and the possession of disturbing explicit content. His conviction in December 2013 led to the disintegration of the Lostprophets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jo Mjadzelics, one of Watkins’ former partners, expressed her shock at the recent attack, stating to the Mirror, “It’s surprising that such a brutal attack took so long, especially in a prison like Wakefield.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The broader implications of the attack on Watkins underline the volatile dynamics within prison systems, especially for individuals convicted of particularly reviled crimes. The repercussions of his crimes, it seems, continue to echo both for Watkins and for those who were once associated with him.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/09/06/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-09-06T10:14:59-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-06T10:14:59-04:00</updated><id>/2023/09/06/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/06/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/09/06/2023-08-29-Consumer-Confidence-Drop/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-09-06T10:14:59-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-06T10:14:59-04:00</updated><id>/2023/09/06/2023-08-29-Consumer-Confidence-Drop</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/06/2023-08-29-Consumer-Confidence-Drop/">&lt;p&gt;As the summer season draws to a close, Americans are beginning to tighten their purse strings, reacting to high prices, surging interest rates, and a potentially cooling job market. Economic indicators released on Tuesday revealed a decline in U.S. job openings, dropping to 8.8 million in July from 9.2 million in June, according to the U.S. Labor Department.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bankrate’s Senior Economic Analyst, Mark Hamrick, remarked to Newsmax Finance, “That translates to roughly 1.5 job openings for every unemployed individual in the U.S. We’ve also observed a reduction in the number and rate of job resignations.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further exacerbating concerns, The Conference Board, a notable business research group, announced that its consumer confidence index plummeted to 106.1 in August, down from July’s revised 114. This dip in confidence has seemingly mirrored the stock market’s own decline during the month, undoing the gains observed in June and July.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The data provides insights into the public’s view on both the present-day economic landscape and their anticipations for the coming half-year, with both dimensions witnessing sharp decreases in August. While the assessment of the current economic climate decreased to 144.8 from 153, the expectations for the future plunged to 80.2 from July’s 88. Historically, any value below 80 in future expectations is a potential harbinger of a recession within the ensuing year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given that consumer spending propels approximately 70% of U.S. economic activities, fluctuations in their sentiment serve as a barometer for the nation’s economic health.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The late spring had witnessed a resurgence in consumer confidence as inflationary pressures eased in light of the Federal Reserve’s 11 consecutive interest rate hikes. However, August’s downturn underscores the prevailing consumer trepidation about purchasing non-essential items, more so if these purchases necessitate the use of high-interest credit cards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The chief economist at The Conference Board, Dana Peterson, shared, “Write-in responses have highlighted a renewed consumer focus on surging prices, particularly in essential sectors such as groceries and gasoline.” Peterson further noted the evident decline in consumer confidence across all demographic groups.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This caution in expenditure is clearly visible in the quarterly reports of numerous renowned retailers. For instance, Target posted its inaugural quarterly sales dip in six years earlier in August, a result of conservative consumer spending. Similarly, Home Depot, America’s premier home improvement retailer, observed persistent sales declines, particularly in high-value items necessitating financing. Furthermore, Best Buy’s recent disclosures reveal reduced sales and profits for Q2, attributing the decline to reduced gadget expenditure, a marked contrast to the pandemic era splurge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though the U.S. economy, the globe’s most substantial, has displayed unexpected resilience despite soaring borrowing costs, with employers registering an impressive 278,000 job additions per month this year, recent indicators suggest a potential shift. As families and individuals recalibrate their budgets for the upcoming school year and in anticipation of the holiday season, the economic trajectory for the remaining year remains uncertain.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/09/06/2023-09-05-Disney-Wokeness/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-09-06T10:14:59-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-06T10:14:59-04:00</updated><id>/2023/09/06/2023-09-05-Disney-Wokeness</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/06/2023-09-05-Disney-Wokeness/">&lt;p&gt;Disney, the once-celebrated beacon of childhood wonder and family entertainment, now seems to be sinking in the quicksand of modern-day “wokeness.” With a series of missteps that some argue deviate from its core values, the entertainment titan is undergoing significant turbulence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From Fairy Tales to Identity Politics&lt;/strong&gt;
For a century, Disney was synonymous with magical adventures and fairy tales. But the present-day Disney appears more engrossed in pushing identity politics and heavy themes of sexuality and gender than in weaving universal tales of wonder. This radical shift from delighting audiences to lecturing them could be the root of their recent challenges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stocks Dive in the Wake of Wokeness&lt;/strong&gt;
If the stock market is any indication, the “woke” direction hasn’t served Disney well. From a prosperous value of around $200 two years ago, the stock has plummeted to a concerning $81.84, marking almost a ten-year low. This decline showcases a clear investor response to the company’s modern-day stances.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disney+ or Disney Minus?&lt;/strong&gt;
The launch of Disney+ promised a new era of streaming, but instead, it seems to have become a showcase for the company’s new “woke” approach. Legal action from investors alleges the company has been less than transparent about its profitability forecasts, with some suggesting that this new content direction is a significant factor in the platform’s economic underperformance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Box Office Reflects the Mood&lt;/strong&gt;
Out of the six major releases this year, five either bombed or missed the mark significantly. When familiar stories are laced with overt political messaging and identity agendas, it’s clear audiences are choosing to stay away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Theme Parks – Lost in Translation?&lt;/strong&gt;
The magic of Disney’s theme parks seems to be fizzling out, with dwindling visitors and a sense that the classic Disney experience is being overshadowed by a more controversial narrative.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Once-Loved Franchises Suffer&lt;/strong&gt;
The new approach has seeped into acquisitions, with giants like Star Wars, Marvel, Indiana Jones, and Pixar facing backlash for their recent content. The magic that once surrounded these franchises is waning, replaced by divisive storylines and characters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Disney’s transformation from an entertainment powerhouse to a platform seemingly more concerned with being “woke” than with universal storytelling is evident. If the recent setbacks are any indication, it might be time for the corporation to reflect on its roots and consider if being “woke” is worth the cost.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Delta’s Poopy Predicament - The Flight That Couldn’t Hold It!</title><link href="/news/2023/09/06/2023-09-06-Delta-Diarrhea-Disaster/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Delta’s Poopy Predicament - The Flight That Couldn’t Hold It!" /><published>2023-09-06T09:45:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-06T09:45:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/06/2023-09-06-Delta-Diarrhea-Disaster</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/06/2023-09-06-Delta-Diarrhea-Disaster/">&lt;p&gt;Ever been in a situation where your stomach lets out a monstrous growl, signaling the imminent approach of a bathroom emergency? Now, imagine that while cruising at 30,000 feet with no escape. One passenger on a Delta flight to Barcelona can attest to this misadventure, proving once and for all that the phrase “shit happens” is not just a metaphor!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To Barcelona, and… Back?&lt;/strong&gt;
Just two hours into its eight-hour transatlantic journey, the Delta flight was forced into a U-turn back to Atlanta. Why, you ask? A diarrhea disaster of epic proportions. As per the official announcement from the cockpit, “This is a biohazard issue.” Well, that’s one way to make a splash on an international flight!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After already enduring a two-hour delay before take-off, this Delta flight couldn’t seem to catch a break. A word of advice? Maybe it’s time to rethink the in-flight menu.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Social Media Flies High on The News&lt;/strong&gt;
As expected, the story quickly took off on the internet, with one Reddit post showcasing the Federal Aviation Administration (FAA) flight strip for Flight DL194 – the infamous diarrhea flight. To no one’s surprise, the plane required a thorough scrub-down before embarking on its doo-doo-free journey to Spain once more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What remained a mystery, however, was whether the “culprit” was aboard the plane for its second attempt. One can only hope that they packed a change of clothes… and maybe some Pepto-Bismol.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Delta’s “Crap-tastic” Week&lt;/strong&gt;
To add to the stink of the situation, this messy incident came right on the heels of another Delta hiccup. Just three days prior, extreme turbulence on a Delta flight from Milan to Atlanta sent 11 passengers to the hospital. Quite the roller-coaster (or should we say, toilet-bowl swirl?) week for Delta!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Delta, ever the professionals, addressed the “doo-doo” incident with an official statement: “Our teams worked as quickly and safely as possible to thoroughly clean the airplane and get our customers to their final destination.” They also expressed their sincere apologies for the “delay and inconvenience to their travel plans.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And to the brave passenger at the center of this incident? Next time, maybe opt for the train. Less air time, and more… restroom options!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Ever been in a situation where your stomach lets out a monstrous growl, signaling the imminent approach of a bathroom emergency? Now, imagine that while cruising at 30,000 feet with no escape. One passenger on a Delta flight to Barcelona can attest to this misadventure, proving once and for all that the phrase “shit happens” is not just a metaphor! To Barcelona, and… Back? Just two hours into its eight-hour transatlantic journey, the Delta flight was forced into a U-turn back to Atlanta. Why, you ask? A diarrhea disaster of epic proportions. As per the official announcement from the cockpit, “This is a biohazard issue.” Well, that’s one way to make a splash on an international flight! After already enduring a two-hour delay before take-off, this Delta flight couldn’t seem to catch a break. A word of advice? Maybe it’s time to rethink the in-flight menu. Social Media Flies High on The News As expected, the story quickly took off on the internet, with one Reddit post showcasing the Federal Aviation Administration (FAA) flight strip for Flight DL194 – the infamous diarrhea flight. To no one’s surprise, the plane required a thorough scrub-down before embarking on its doo-doo-free journey to Spain once more. What remained a mystery, however, was whether the “culprit” was aboard the plane for its second attempt. One can only hope that they packed a change of clothes… and maybe some Pepto-Bismol. Delta’s “Crap-tastic” Week To add to the stink of the situation, this messy incident came right on the heels of another Delta hiccup. Just three days prior, extreme turbulence on a Delta flight from Milan to Atlanta sent 11 passengers to the hospital. Quite the roller-coaster (or should we say, toilet-bowl swirl?) week for Delta! Delta, ever the professionals, addressed the “doo-doo” incident with an official statement: “Our teams worked as quickly and safely as possible to thoroughly clean the airplane and get our customers to their final destination.” They also expressed their sincere apologies for the “delay and inconvenience to their travel plans.” And to the brave passenger at the center of this incident? Next time, maybe opt for the train. Less air time, and more… restroom options!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Crime Spikes in Wisconsin - Liberal Policies to Blame?</title><link href="/news/2023/09/06/2023-09-06-Democrats-Crime-Wisconsin/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Crime Spikes in Wisconsin - Liberal Policies to Blame?" /><published>2023-09-06T08:58:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-06T08:58:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/06/2023-09-06-Democrats-Crime-Wisconsin</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/06/2023-09-06-Democrats-Crime-Wisconsin/">&lt;p&gt;In a chilling reminder of the potential consequences of liberal policies, Madison – Wisconsin’s progressive capital – witnessed a brutal assault on a female student from the University of Wisconsin-Madison, sparking widespread concerns regarding city safety.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;De-funding the Police: A Recipe for Disaster?&lt;/strong&gt;
The unsettling attack occurred shortly after the Badgers football team’s victory, leaving the victim with life-threatening injuries. A mere stone’s throw away from Lake Monona, the attack occurred during the early morning hours at the intersection of South Bedford and West Wilson streets. As the victim fought for her life, one couldn’t help but ponder the repercussions of Madison’s decision to slash police funds in 2020. In a move heralded by many left-leaning activists, Madison reduced the police budget by $2 million, as reported by the city’s weekly newspaper, the Capital Times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The decision, which came in the wake of protests against alleged police brutality, has now left many questioning the Democrats’ approach to community safety. It seems ironic that a city which purportedly championed progressive ideals has now had to increase police patrols in the aftermath of such a heinous act.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Cry for Safety&lt;/strong&gt;
The victim’s ordeal paints a grim picture – abducted off the sidewalk and subjected to unimaginable cruelty. The fact that this took place in a college town, where young minds are expected to pursue their dreams in safety, adds to the tragedy. Police continue their hunt for the perpetrators, urging residents to share any security footage that could provide valuable leads.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But the haunting question remains. Could Madison’s slide into crime have been avoided if the Democrats had adopted a more balanced approach, rather than bowing to pressure and drastically reducing the police budget? The incident calls into sharp focus the wisdom of defunding the police – a move many conservatives argue leaves communities vulnerable and potentially, in harm’s way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reflecting on this incident, one can’t help but remember a post from a concerned young woman on Reddit last year, questioning the safety of walking alone late at night in Madison. The top reply, a simple “No,” now seems prophetic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As Madison grapples with the consequences of its policies, residents are now urged to remain vigilant, avoid walking alone at night, and always stay aware of their surroundings. This incident stands as a testament to the potential dangers of embracing radical reforms without fully considering the potential ramifications for community safety.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a chilling reminder of the potential consequences of liberal policies, Madison – Wisconsin’s progressive capital – witnessed a brutal assault on a female student from the University of Wisconsin-Madison, sparking widespread concerns regarding city safety. De-funding the Police: A Recipe for Disaster? The unsettling attack occurred shortly after the Badgers football team’s victory, leaving the victim with life-threatening injuries. A mere stone’s throw away from Lake Monona, the attack occurred during the early morning hours at the intersection of South Bedford and West Wilson streets. As the victim fought for her life, one couldn’t help but ponder the repercussions of Madison’s decision to slash police funds in 2020. In a move heralded by many left-leaning activists, Madison reduced the police budget by $2 million, as reported by the city’s weekly newspaper, the Capital Times. The decision, which came in the wake of protests against alleged police brutality, has now left many questioning the Democrats’ approach to community safety. It seems ironic that a city which purportedly championed progressive ideals has now had to increase police patrols in the aftermath of such a heinous act. The Cry for Safety The victim’s ordeal paints a grim picture – abducted off the sidewalk and subjected to unimaginable cruelty. The fact that this took place in a college town, where young minds are expected to pursue their dreams in safety, adds to the tragedy. Police continue their hunt for the perpetrators, urging residents to share any security footage that could provide valuable leads. But the haunting question remains. Could Madison’s slide into crime have been avoided if the Democrats had adopted a more balanced approach, rather than bowing to pressure and drastically reducing the police budget? The incident calls into sharp focus the wisdom of defunding the police – a move many conservatives argue leaves communities vulnerable and potentially, in harm’s way. Reflecting on this incident, one can’t help but remember a post from a concerned young woman on Reddit last year, questioning the safety of walking alone late at night in Madison. The top reply, a simple “No,” now seems prophetic. As Madison grapples with the consequences of its policies, residents are now urged to remain vigilant, avoid walking alone at night, and always stay aware of their surroundings. This incident stands as a testament to the potential dangers of embracing radical reforms without fully considering the potential ramifications for community safety.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">McConnell’s Health Under Spotlight - Physician Clears The Air</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/06/2023-09-06-McConnell-Health-Clarification/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="McConnell’s Health Under Spotlight - Physician Clears The Air" /><published>2023-09-06T08:30:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-06T08:30:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/06/2023-09-06-McConnell-Health-Clarification</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/06/2023-09-06-McConnell-Health-Clarification/">&lt;p&gt;In recent days, concerns about Republican Sen. Minority Leader Mitch McConnell’s health were in the limelight after he paused for an extended period during a public address. The Capitol attending physician has now stepped forward to address these concerns, providing a much-needed clarity on the GOP leader’s condition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dr. Brian Monahan, Sen. McConnell’s attending physician, recently issued a comprehensive statement after performing an extensive neurological assessment on the Senator. According to Monahan, various tests, including a brain MRI imaging and an EEG study, showed “no evidence” that the Senator had suffered a stroke, TIA, or any movement disorder such as Parkinson’s disease. Monahan further emphasized that there’s no need to adjust McConnell’s current treatments stemming from his fall in March 2023.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These health concerns took root after an episode last week in Covington, Kentucky. While responding to a reporter’s question on his re-election plans for 2026, Sen. McConnell appeared to lose his train of thought and went silent for over half a minute. This “freeze” was particularly alarming as it came a month after a similar occurrence during a Capitol news conference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, after the episode, a spokesperson for McConnell provided insights into his condition. “Leader McConnell felt momentarily lightheaded and paused during his press conference today,” they said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite these moments of concern, Dr. Monahan gave the go-ahead for the Senator to resume his regular schedule. Commenting on McConnell’s occasional lightheadedness, the physician explained that such symptoms are not uncommon during concussion recovery, suggesting that dehydration might also play a role.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This year has been challenging health-wise for the 81-year-old Senator. Earlier in the year, McConnell had a severe fall in a Washington hotel, resulting in a concussion and a fractured rib. After spending some time in an inpatient rehabilitation facility, he made his return to the Senate. With the recent clarifications, supporters and colleagues hope for McConnell’s continued contribution to the political landscape without further health concerns.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In recent days, concerns about Republican Sen. Minority Leader Mitch McConnell’s health were in the limelight after he paused for an extended period during a public address. The Capitol attending physician has now stepped forward to address these concerns, providing a much-needed clarity on the GOP leader’s condition. Dr. Brian Monahan, Sen. McConnell’s attending physician, recently issued a comprehensive statement after performing an extensive neurological assessment on the Senator. According to Monahan, various tests, including a brain MRI imaging and an EEG study, showed “no evidence” that the Senator had suffered a stroke, TIA, or any movement disorder such as Parkinson’s disease. Monahan further emphasized that there’s no need to adjust McConnell’s current treatments stemming from his fall in March 2023. These health concerns took root after an episode last week in Covington, Kentucky. While responding to a reporter’s question on his re-election plans for 2026, Sen. McConnell appeared to lose his train of thought and went silent for over half a minute. This “freeze” was particularly alarming as it came a month after a similar occurrence during a Capitol news conference. However, after the episode, a spokesperson for McConnell provided insights into his condition. “Leader McConnell felt momentarily lightheaded and paused during his press conference today,” they said. Despite these moments of concern, Dr. Monahan gave the go-ahead for the Senator to resume his regular schedule. Commenting on McConnell’s occasional lightheadedness, the physician explained that such symptoms are not uncommon during concussion recovery, suggesting that dehydration might also play a role. This year has been challenging health-wise for the 81-year-old Senator. Earlier in the year, McConnell had a severe fall in a Washington hotel, resulting in a concussion and a fractured rib. After spending some time in an inpatient rehabilitation facility, he made his return to the Senate. With the recent clarifications, supporters and colleagues hope for McConnell’s continued contribution to the political landscape without further health concerns.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump Sounds the Alarm - Biden’s EV Plans A Gift to China?</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/05/2023-09-05-Trump-UAW-Warning/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump Sounds the Alarm - Biden’s EV Plans A Gift to China?" /><published>2023-09-05T22:20:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-05T22:20:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/05/2023-09-05-Trump-UAW-Warning</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/05/2023-09-05-Trump-UAW-Warning/">&lt;p&gt;In a passionate appeal to United Auto Workers (UAW) members, former President Donald Trump cautioned against President Joe Biden’s vigorous push for electric vehicles (EVs). Trump posited that if Biden’s vision for an all-electric automotive industry materializes, Michigan might bid farewell to its iconic auto industry. But who stands to gain from such a shift? Trump believes China.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On a Labor Day post on Truth Social, Trump minced no words in his warning: “The Great State of Michigan will not have an auto industry anymore if Crooked Joe Biden’s crazed concept of ‘all Electric Cars’ goes into effect.” Trump continued, stating unequivocally, “CHINA WILL TAKE IT ALL, 100%. United Auto Workers, VOTE FOR TRUMP.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump’s concerns echo that of the UAW, which has been vocally critical of Biden’s green energy initiatives. At the heart of their grievance lies the Inflation Reduction Act. Under this legislation, substantial tax credits are offered to major automakers for EVs produced in the United States, Canada, and Mexico. UAW President Shawn Fain expressed the union’s frustrations, noting that while the “Big Three” automakers are capitalizing on billions in government subsidies to pivot to electric, the rewards aren’t trickling down to the workers. In his words, “the corporate elite and the billionaire class, seem to think they can keep calling the shots.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A chilling example of this disconnect is the Lordstown community’s experience in Ohio. After GM shut down its manufacturing plant in Lordstown, resulting in thousands of layoffs, the community had placed its hopes on Ultium Cells, GM’s new EV battery plant venture with LG. However, the reality did not meet expectations. Dave Dellick from UAW Local 1112 shared that while the plant’s inception was anticipated as the “next wave” of manufacturing opportunities, it has been a letdown so far. Fain summed it up by saying that Ultium Cells slashed auto wages by half.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The UAW’s apprehensions about Biden’s push for EVs seem to resonate with their lack of endorsement for his administration. Their stance has been clear: they want unequivocal support from the national leadership before they pledge any allegiance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As Trump courts the UAW with promises of preserving their jobs and expanding choices, Biden’s administration faces the challenge of balancing green initiatives with the immediate needs and concerns of America’s working class.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a passionate appeal to United Auto Workers (UAW) members, former President Donald Trump cautioned against President Joe Biden’s vigorous push for electric vehicles (EVs). Trump posited that if Biden’s vision for an all-electric automotive industry materializes, Michigan might bid farewell to its iconic auto industry. But who stands to gain from such a shift? Trump believes China. On a Labor Day post on Truth Social, Trump minced no words in his warning: “The Great State of Michigan will not have an auto industry anymore if Crooked Joe Biden’s crazed concept of ‘all Electric Cars’ goes into effect.” Trump continued, stating unequivocally, “CHINA WILL TAKE IT ALL, 100%. United Auto Workers, VOTE FOR TRUMP.” Trump’s concerns echo that of the UAW, which has been vocally critical of Biden’s green energy initiatives. At the heart of their grievance lies the Inflation Reduction Act. Under this legislation, substantial tax credits are offered to major automakers for EVs produced in the United States, Canada, and Mexico. UAW President Shawn Fain expressed the union’s frustrations, noting that while the “Big Three” automakers are capitalizing on billions in government subsidies to pivot to electric, the rewards aren’t trickling down to the workers. In his words, “the corporate elite and the billionaire class, seem to think they can keep calling the shots.” A chilling example of this disconnect is the Lordstown community’s experience in Ohio. After GM shut down its manufacturing plant in Lordstown, resulting in thousands of layoffs, the community had placed its hopes on Ultium Cells, GM’s new EV battery plant venture with LG. However, the reality did not meet expectations. Dave Dellick from UAW Local 1112 shared that while the plant’s inception was anticipated as the “next wave” of manufacturing opportunities, it has been a letdown so far. Fain summed it up by saying that Ultium Cells slashed auto wages by half. The UAW’s apprehensions about Biden’s push for EVs seem to resonate with their lack of endorsement for his administration. Their stance has been clear: they want unequivocal support from the national leadership before they pledge any allegiance. As Trump courts the UAW with promises of preserving their jobs and expanding choices, Biden’s administration faces the challenge of balancing green initiatives with the immediate needs and concerns of America’s working class.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Tragic Fall - Atlanta Ramp Accident Claims Lives of 5 Teens</title><link href="/news/2023/09/05/2023-09-05-Atlanta-Interstate-Tragedy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tragic Fall - Atlanta Ramp Accident Claims Lives of 5 Teens" /><published>2023-09-05T21:34:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-05T21:34:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/05/2023-09-05-Atlanta-Interstate-Tragedy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/05/2023-09-05-Atlanta-Interstate-Tragedy/">&lt;p&gt;A somber Labor Day dawned for the city of Atlanta, as a tragic accident claimed the lives of five teenagers and left three others seriously injured.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grim Discovery on I-85&lt;/strong&gt;
Just as the city began to stir in the early hours of Labor Day, a devastating event unfolded on Interstate 85. At about 4 a.m., a 911 call alerted authorities to a horrific accident near Pleasant Hill Rd in Duluth, Georgia. A vehicle had plummeted “over the wall of the raised ramp,” crashing into traffic lanes below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Emergency personnel, upon arriving at the scene, were met with a harrowing sight. Five teenagers, ranging in age from 16 to 19, were pronounced dead at the spot, while three others suffered injuries and were immediately rushed to nearby hospitals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Victims Identified&lt;/strong&gt;
The hearts of many were heavy upon learning the identities of the deceased – Katy Gaitan (17), Ashley Gaitan (16), Coral Lorenzo (17), Hung Nguyen (18), and Abner Santana (19). Tragically, three of them attended the same school, Lakeside High School in DeKalb County.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reconstructing the Events&lt;/strong&gt;
As investigators pieced together the tragic sequence of events, it emerged that two vehicles initially collided on the ramp. This crash sent one of the vehicles soaring over the wall, where it tragically landed on the interstate and was subsequently struck by another car, as per FOX 5 Atlanta.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Following this heartrending incident, traffic diversions were in place, with portions of the interstate, including the SR 316 WB ramps to I85 SB and Pleasant Hill Rd, being closed off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the city mourns the loss of its young souls, questions about ramp safety and vehicular accidents loom large, reminding everyone of the preciousness of life and the unpredictability of fate.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">A somber Labor Day dawned for the city of Atlanta, as a tragic accident claimed the lives of five teenagers and left three others seriously injured. Grim Discovery on I-85 Just as the city began to stir in the early hours of Labor Day, a devastating event unfolded on Interstate 85. At about 4 a.m., a 911 call alerted authorities to a horrific accident near Pleasant Hill Rd in Duluth, Georgia. A vehicle had plummeted “over the wall of the raised ramp,” crashing into traffic lanes below. Emergency personnel, upon arriving at the scene, were met with a harrowing sight. Five teenagers, ranging in age from 16 to 19, were pronounced dead at the spot, while three others suffered injuries and were immediately rushed to nearby hospitals. Victims Identified The hearts of many were heavy upon learning the identities of the deceased – Katy Gaitan (17), Ashley Gaitan (16), Coral Lorenzo (17), Hung Nguyen (18), and Abner Santana (19). Tragically, three of them attended the same school, Lakeside High School in DeKalb County. Reconstructing the Events As investigators pieced together the tragic sequence of events, it emerged that two vehicles initially collided on the ramp. This crash sent one of the vehicles soaring over the wall, where it tragically landed on the interstate and was subsequently struck by another car, as per FOX 5 Atlanta. Following this heartrending incident, traffic diversions were in place, with portions of the interstate, including the SR 316 WB ramps to I85 SB and Pleasant Hill Rd, being closed off. As the city mourns the loss of its young souls, questions about ramp safety and vehicular accidents loom large, reminding everyone of the preciousness of life and the unpredictability of fate.</summary></entry></feed>