<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-09-08T17:12:58-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/09/08/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-09-08T17:12:58-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-08T17:12:58-04:00</updated><id>/2023/09/08/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/08/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Fulton County’s Deadly Crisis - The Jail Where Trump Was Booked Faces Disturbing Death Toll</title><link href="/news/2023/09/08/Trump-Jail-Deaths/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Fulton County’s Deadly Crisis - The Jail Where Trump Was Booked Faces Disturbing Death Toll" /><published>2023-09-08T16:48:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-08T16:48:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/08/Trump-Jail-Deaths</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/08/Trump-Jail-Deaths/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fulton County Jail: A Ground Zero for Presidential Controversies and Grim Realities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the world was preoccupied with the spectacle of former President Donald Trump’s voluntary surrender at Fulton County Jail, a grave and haunting pattern of inmate deaths emerged in the shadows of the facility. Six fatalities have been reported since the end of July, intensifying concerns over the jail’s operations and management.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Presidential Surrender Overshadows a Dire Situation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The jail gained immense attention when Trump turned himself in due to charges stemming from alleged election interference in Georgia. The media fervently covered his booking and that of his 18 co-defendants. However, beneath this high-profile event, the stark reality of life in the jail came into focus with the tragic death of 24-year-old Shawndre Delmore.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DOJ’s Intervention: A Damning Indictment of Jail Conditions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Disturbing incidents, such as the death of 35-year-old Lashawn Thompson caused by apparent severe neglect, have painted a bleak picture of the facility’s conditions. This alarming environment prompted the Department of Justice (DOJ) to launch a civil investigation, addressing growing concerns over violence, deplorable living conditions, and even reports of an inmate’s body found with insect infestation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Series of Troubling Deaths within Jail Walls&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apart from Delmore, several inmates have met untimely deaths within the prison’s confines in recent weeks. Samuel Lawrence, Dayvion Blake, Alexander Hawkins, Christopher Smith, and Montay Stinson all faced tragic ends, with Blake’s fatal stabbing further emphasizing the urgent need for reform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conclusion: The Need for Transparency and Reform&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With a series of tragedies unfolding at Fulton County Jail, it’s paramount that the facility undergoes scrutiny and reforms to prevent further loss of life. While the spotlight may have been on Trump’s booking, the focus should now shift towards ensuring the safety and well-being of the inmates.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Fulton County Jail: A Ground Zero for Presidential Controversies and Grim Realities While the world was preoccupied with the spectacle of former President Donald Trump’s voluntary surrender at Fulton County Jail, a grave and haunting pattern of inmate deaths emerged in the shadows of the facility. Six fatalities have been reported since the end of July, intensifying concerns over the jail’s operations and management. Presidential Surrender Overshadows a Dire Situation The jail gained immense attention when Trump turned himself in due to charges stemming from alleged election interference in Georgia. The media fervently covered his booking and that of his 18 co-defendants. However, beneath this high-profile event, the stark reality of life in the jail came into focus with the tragic death of 24-year-old Shawndre Delmore. DOJ’s Intervention: A Damning Indictment of Jail Conditions Disturbing incidents, such as the death of 35-year-old Lashawn Thompson caused by apparent severe neglect, have painted a bleak picture of the facility’s conditions. This alarming environment prompted the Department of Justice (DOJ) to launch a civil investigation, addressing growing concerns over violence, deplorable living conditions, and even reports of an inmate’s body found with insect infestation. A Series of Troubling Deaths within Jail Walls Apart from Delmore, several inmates have met untimely deaths within the prison’s confines in recent weeks. Samuel Lawrence, Dayvion Blake, Alexander Hawkins, Christopher Smith, and Montay Stinson all faced tragic ends, with Blake’s fatal stabbing further emphasizing the urgent need for reform. Conclusion: The Need for Transparency and Reform With a series of tragedies unfolding at Fulton County Jail, it’s paramount that the facility undergoes scrutiny and reforms to prevent further loss of life. While the spotlight may have been on Trump’s booking, the focus should now shift towards ensuring the safety and well-being of the inmates.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Duggar Divisions - When Reality TV Threatens Family Bonds</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/08/Duggar-Divisions/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Duggar Divisions - When Reality TV Threatens Family Bonds" /><published>2023-09-08T15:37:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-08T15:37:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/08/Duggar-Divisions</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/08/Duggar-Divisions/">&lt;p&gt;Jill Duggar Dillard and her spouse, Derick Dillard, have recently delved into how the TLC reality series “19 Kids and Counting” — and the overbearing influence of patriarch Jim Bob Duggar — almost fragmented their marital bond.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As fans of the show may recall, the Duggar family’s journey to stardom was punctuated with not just the highs of a growing family but also the challenging lows of scandals and internal conflicts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to Jill, 32, and Derick, 34, one of the major hindrances to their marital peace was the extreme expectations surrounding obedience and submission to Jim Bob’s desires. In a heartfelt interview, Jill disclosed, “It definitely got between us… No matter your age, you are to obey your parents’ wishes, and you even have to ask them for their blessing for any major moment in your life.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Derick further recounted instances where Jim Bob allegedly attempted to “weaponize” their relationship, using it as leverage when the couple resisted his plans for the show. He lamented, “He would weaponize the relationship and say, ‘Is this you Jill, or is this you, Derick? Are you leading your wife astray and doing things that are not supportive of marriage?’”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It wasn’t just emotional manipulation that the couple faced; financial matters were also a bone of contention. Jill shed light on the fact that she was paid a mere $175,000 for a decade’s worth of filming, even though the show reportedly raked in over $8 million. The catch? The checks from TLC were directly handed over to Jim Bob.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jim Bob and Michelle Duggar, in a statement, expressed their love for all their children and emphasized their commitment to resolving conflicts honorably. However, they refrained from addressing the claims made by Jill and Derick directly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet, this isn’t the first time the Duggar family name has been steeped in controversy. The show itself was axed from TLC following a molestation scandal linked to Jill’s brother, Josh Duggar, in 2015. Matters further escalated when Josh was sentenced to over a dozen years in prison in December 2022 for child pornography charges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the future remains uncertain for the Duggars, one thing is clear: the allure of reality TV stardom often comes at a price. Whether it’s the strain on relationships, the exposure of personal scandals, or the tug-of-war over control and money, the Dillard couple’s revelations underscore the complexities of life in the limelight.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Jill Duggar Dillard and her spouse, Derick Dillard, have recently delved into how the TLC reality series “19 Kids and Counting” — and the overbearing influence of patriarch Jim Bob Duggar — almost fragmented their marital bond. As fans of the show may recall, the Duggar family’s journey to stardom was punctuated with not just the highs of a growing family but also the challenging lows of scandals and internal conflicts. According to Jill, 32, and Derick, 34, one of the major hindrances to their marital peace was the extreme expectations surrounding obedience and submission to Jim Bob’s desires. In a heartfelt interview, Jill disclosed, “It definitely got between us… No matter your age, you are to obey your parents’ wishes, and you even have to ask them for their blessing for any major moment in your life.” Derick further recounted instances where Jim Bob allegedly attempted to “weaponize” their relationship, using it as leverage when the couple resisted his plans for the show. He lamented, “He would weaponize the relationship and say, ‘Is this you Jill, or is this you, Derick? Are you leading your wife astray and doing things that are not supportive of marriage?’” It wasn’t just emotional manipulation that the couple faced; financial matters were also a bone of contention. Jill shed light on the fact that she was paid a mere $175,000 for a decade’s worth of filming, even though the show reportedly raked in over $8 million. The catch? The checks from TLC were directly handed over to Jim Bob. Jim Bob and Michelle Duggar, in a statement, expressed their love for all their children and emphasized their commitment to resolving conflicts honorably. However, they refrained from addressing the claims made by Jill and Derick directly. Yet, this isn’t the first time the Duggar family name has been steeped in controversy. The show itself was axed from TLC following a molestation scandal linked to Jill’s brother, Josh Duggar, in 2015. Matters further escalated when Josh was sentenced to over a dozen years in prison in December 2022 for child pornography charges. While the future remains uncertain for the Duggars, one thing is clear: the allure of reality TV stardom often comes at a price. Whether it’s the strain on relationships, the exposure of personal scandals, or the tug-of-war over control and money, the Dillard couple’s revelations underscore the complexities of life in the limelight.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Biden on Shaky Ground - Multiple Republicans Surpass Him in Latest Poll</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/08/Biden-GOP-Poll/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Biden on Shaky Ground - Multiple Republicans Surpass Him in Latest Poll" /><published>2023-09-08T14:58:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-08T14:58:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/08/Biden-GOP-Poll</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/08/Biden-GOP-Poll/">&lt;p&gt;CNN’s recent poll has the political scene buzzing, and the numbers don’t bode well for President Joe Biden. Facing off in hypothetical match-ups against a roster of potential GOP contenders, Biden found himself trailing in several instances.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Former President Donald Trump, South Carolina Senator Tim Scott, former Vice President Mike Pence, ex-Governor of South Carolina Nikki Haley, and former New Jersey Governor Chris Christie are some of the Republican names besting Biden in these match-ups.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a narrow contest, Trump just nudges past Biden, gathering 47% to Biden’s 46%. While Trump’s lead is within the poll’s margin of error, it underscores the political duress Biden could face.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet, Trump is not alone in this advantage. Notably, Nikki Haley surpasses Biden with a 49% to 43% lead, clearly sidestepping the poll’s margin of error. Both Pence and Scott find themselves two points ahead, holding 46% to Biden’s 44%. Chris Christie also pushes past Biden by two points, clocking in at 44% versus Biden’s 42%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, Florida Governor Ron DeSantis draws even with Biden, each amassing 47% of the hypothetical vote. Only anti-woke entrepreneur Vivek Ramaswamy seems to be on the back foot, trailing Biden by a single point — 46% to 45%. However, given the poll’s margin of error, even this matchup can be considered a virtual tie.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These numbers spell potential trouble for Biden. As the 2024 elections approach, concerns regarding his age and overall capabilities are becoming more pronounced, even among Democratic ranks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In stark contrast, Trump’s messaging remains confrontational and assertive. The former president, as active as ever on his platform, Truth Social, recently issued stark warnings, promising to address issues from his past term. Trump’s rhetoric focuses on seeking justice for perceived wrongs during his tenure, ranging from impeachment attempts to election controversies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the political scene unravels and contenders firm up their strategies, this latest CNN poll hints at an intense race ahead. Whether Biden can regain momentum remains to be seen. However, one thing is clear: the GOP field is geared up and raring to go.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">CNN’s recent poll has the political scene buzzing, and the numbers don’t bode well for President Joe Biden. Facing off in hypothetical match-ups against a roster of potential GOP contenders, Biden found himself trailing in several instances. Former President Donald Trump, South Carolina Senator Tim Scott, former Vice President Mike Pence, ex-Governor of South Carolina Nikki Haley, and former New Jersey Governor Chris Christie are some of the Republican names besting Biden in these match-ups. In a narrow contest, Trump just nudges past Biden, gathering 47% to Biden’s 46%. While Trump’s lead is within the poll’s margin of error, it underscores the political duress Biden could face. Yet, Trump is not alone in this advantage. Notably, Nikki Haley surpasses Biden with a 49% to 43% lead, clearly sidestepping the poll’s margin of error. Both Pence and Scott find themselves two points ahead, holding 46% to Biden’s 44%. Chris Christie also pushes past Biden by two points, clocking in at 44% versus Biden’s 42%. Interestingly, Florida Governor Ron DeSantis draws even with Biden, each amassing 47% of the hypothetical vote. Only anti-woke entrepreneur Vivek Ramaswamy seems to be on the back foot, trailing Biden by a single point — 46% to 45%. However, given the poll’s margin of error, even this matchup can be considered a virtual tie. These numbers spell potential trouble for Biden. As the 2024 elections approach, concerns regarding his age and overall capabilities are becoming more pronounced, even among Democratic ranks. In stark contrast, Trump’s messaging remains confrontational and assertive. The former president, as active as ever on his platform, Truth Social, recently issued stark warnings, promising to address issues from his past term. Trump’s rhetoric focuses on seeking justice for perceived wrongs during his tenure, ranging from impeachment attempts to election controversies. As the political scene unravels and contenders firm up their strategies, this latest CNN poll hints at an intense race ahead. Whether Biden can regain momentum remains to be seen. However, one thing is clear: the GOP field is geared up and raring to go.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">New Blood for Capitol Hill - Freshman Congressman Takes on Age Limits</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/08/Congress-Age-Limits/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="New Blood for Capitol Hill - Freshman Congressman Takes on Age Limits" /><published>2023-09-08T13:35:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-08T13:35:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/08/Congress-Age-Limits</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/08/Congress-Age-Limits/">&lt;p&gt;The winds of change are blowing on Capitol Hill as freshman House Republican, Rep. John James of Michigan, proposes a groundbreaking resolution. Aimed at establishing an upper age limit for holding federal elected offices, the proposal calls for constitutional amendment considerations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Presently, there are age criteria to meet to run for president, vice president, or Congress. However, these are minimum age requirements. Rep. James’s resolution addresses the other end of the spectrum, stipulating that no one could run for these roles if they would turn 75 or older during their term. The rationale? Adapting to an ever-changing world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“The world’s not getting slower, it’s getting faster. The world’s not getting safer, it’s getting more dangerous,” James shared with Fox News Digital. “We have a lower bound; it just makes sense to have an upper bound.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This proposal comes amid rising concerns regarding the age and health of some prominent politicians. Top names like Senate GOP Leader Mitch McConnell, Sen. Dianne Feinstein, and even President Biden have faced public scrutiny regarding their fitness to serve.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James took a direct stance, expressing concerns not just for internal governance but also for how the nation is perceived externally. “You can’t watch a video of Feinstein or McConnell or Biden and tell me that everything’s OK,” he commented. “America has lost a step.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While many might view this as a controversial move, James points out that the Founding Fathers never envisioned lifetime tenures in the legislature. His perspective echoes a need for periodic refreshment and rejuvenation of the political landscape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s worth noting that implementing such a significant change won’t be easy or swift. Constitutional amendments require broad consensus, needing two-thirds approval from both the House and Senate, followed by ratification from three-fourths of state legislatures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James’s resolution forms part of a broader government accountability package he’s championing. Other propositions include service time caps in Congress and withholding congressional pay during government shutdowns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the future of these resolutions remains uncertain, they surely underscore a fresh wave of thought, emphasizing adaptability, accountability, and the nation’s future preparedness.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">The winds of change are blowing on Capitol Hill as freshman House Republican, Rep. John James of Michigan, proposes a groundbreaking resolution. Aimed at establishing an upper age limit for holding federal elected offices, the proposal calls for constitutional amendment considerations. Presently, there are age criteria to meet to run for president, vice president, or Congress. However, these are minimum age requirements. Rep. James’s resolution addresses the other end of the spectrum, stipulating that no one could run for these roles if they would turn 75 or older during their term. The rationale? Adapting to an ever-changing world. “The world’s not getting slower, it’s getting faster. The world’s not getting safer, it’s getting more dangerous,” James shared with Fox News Digital. “We have a lower bound; it just makes sense to have an upper bound.” This proposal comes amid rising concerns regarding the age and health of some prominent politicians. Top names like Senate GOP Leader Mitch McConnell, Sen. Dianne Feinstein, and even President Biden have faced public scrutiny regarding their fitness to serve. James took a direct stance, expressing concerns not just for internal governance but also for how the nation is perceived externally. “You can’t watch a video of Feinstein or McConnell or Biden and tell me that everything’s OK,” he commented. “America has lost a step.” While many might view this as a controversial move, James points out that the Founding Fathers never envisioned lifetime tenures in the legislature. His perspective echoes a need for periodic refreshment and rejuvenation of the political landscape. It’s worth noting that implementing such a significant change won’t be easy or swift. Constitutional amendments require broad consensus, needing two-thirds approval from both the House and Senate, followed by ratification from three-fourths of state legislatures. James’s resolution forms part of a broader government accountability package he’s championing. Other propositions include service time caps in Congress and withholding congressional pay during government shutdowns. While the future of these resolutions remains uncertain, they surely underscore a fresh wave of thought, emphasizing adaptability, accountability, and the nation’s future preparedness.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">California’s Assault on the Second Amendment - Imposing an 11% Gun Tax</title><link href="/news/2023/09/08/Gun-Tax-California/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="California’s Assault on the Second Amendment - Imposing an 11% Gun Tax" /><published>2023-09-08T12:58:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-08T12:58:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/08/Gun-Tax-California</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/08/Gun-Tax-California/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;California’s Unsettling Move: Taxing the Right to Bear Arms&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a move many see as an affront to the Second Amendment, the California Senate audaciously approved an 11% tax on guns and ammunition. This legislation, which now returns to the state assembly for another vote, may soon find its way to Gov. Gavin Newsom’s desk for final approval.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Masked Deterrent to Gun Ownership?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Proposed by Assemblyman Jesse Gabriel, this tax appears to be more than a mere revenue-generating endeavor. On the surface, it is touted as a mechanism to enhance “school safety.” However, the specifics on how this tax directly ensures such safety remain conspicuously ambiguous. The underlying message seems clear: make gun ownership more expensive, thus discouraging citizens from exercising their constitutionally protected right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Concerns Overreach&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While California prides itself on being progressive, there’s a thin line between progression and overreach. The state’s already rigid gun laws restrict K-12 educators from bearing arms for the protection of their students. Additionally, concealed carry permit holders face prohibitions against arming themselves on college campuses. With this tax, is California subtly trying to price out the average citizen’s access to their Second Amendment rights?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;California Rifle and Pistol Association President, Chuck Michel, emphatically voiced his concerns, dubbing the move a “poll tax” and likening it to taxing a fundamental constitutional right. Highlighting the gravity of the issue, Michel declared, “We’re going to have to file a lawsuit to challenge it.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Future Under Threat?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the legislation makes its final journey through the state assembly, it serves as a stark reminder of the continuous challenges faced by the Second Amendment. This isn’t merely a debate about a tax; it’s a dialogue about the sanctity of our constitutional rights. If a foundational right can be taxed, what does that spell for the future of our freedoms?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">California’s Unsettling Move: Taxing the Right to Bear Arms In a move many see as an affront to the Second Amendment, the California Senate audaciously approved an 11% tax on guns and ammunition. This legislation, which now returns to the state assembly for another vote, may soon find its way to Gov. Gavin Newsom’s desk for final approval. A Masked Deterrent to Gun Ownership? Proposed by Assemblyman Jesse Gabriel, this tax appears to be more than a mere revenue-generating endeavor. On the surface, it is touted as a mechanism to enhance “school safety.” However, the specifics on how this tax directly ensures such safety remain conspicuously ambiguous. The underlying message seems clear: make gun ownership more expensive, thus discouraging citizens from exercising their constitutionally protected right. Concerns Overreach While California prides itself on being progressive, there’s a thin line between progression and overreach. The state’s already rigid gun laws restrict K-12 educators from bearing arms for the protection of their students. Additionally, concealed carry permit holders face prohibitions against arming themselves on college campuses. With this tax, is California subtly trying to price out the average citizen’s access to their Second Amendment rights? California Rifle and Pistol Association President, Chuck Michel, emphatically voiced his concerns, dubbing the move a “poll tax” and likening it to taxing a fundamental constitutional right. Highlighting the gravity of the issue, Michel declared, “We’re going to have to file a lawsuit to challenge it.” A Future Under Threat? As the legislation makes its final journey through the state assembly, it serves as a stark reminder of the continuous challenges faced by the Second Amendment. This isn’t merely a debate about a tax; it’s a dialogue about the sanctity of our constitutional rights. If a foundational right can be taxed, what does that spell for the future of our freedoms?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Danny Masterson Faces 30-Year Sentence Amidst Controversy</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/08/Danny-Masterson-Sentenced/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Danny Masterson Faces 30-Year Sentence Amidst Controversy" /><published>2023-09-08T11:45:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-08T11:45:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/08/Danny-Masterson-Sentenced</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/08/Danny-Masterson-Sentenced/">&lt;p&gt;In a case that has caught the attention of the entertainment industry and beyond, ‘That ’70s Show’ star, Danny Masterson, has been sentenced to a substantial 30 years in prison after a conviction on charges of rape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Court sketches depicted an emotional scene as actor and model Bijou Phillips, Masterson’s wife, looked on. Masterson was seen blowing a kiss to her just moments before being escorted away. The verdict came after an eight-day deliberation, where a jury found him guilty of two counts of forcible rape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;maximum-punishment-meted-out&quot;&gt;Maximum Punishment Meted Out&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Los Angeles County Superior Court Judge Charlaine Olmedo handed down the 15 years-to-life imprisonment for each count to be served consecutively. This verdict ensures that Masterson will only be eligible for parole after 25 1/2 years, keeping the possibility open for a lifetime sentence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;District Attorney George Gascón lauded the verdict, citing the challenging journey faced by the victims. In his words, the case against Masterson highlights the often-uneven playing field victims face when challenging influential figures. He hopes the verdict brings solace to the victims and serves as a deterrent to others who might exploit their position of power.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-glimmer-of-hope-for-masterson&quot;&gt;A Glimmer of Hope for Masterson?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the severe sentencing, Masterson’s legal team remains optimistic. They’ve voiced concerns about what they perceive as “substantial” errors during the trial and intend to appeal the court’s decision. Shawn Holley, Masterson’s attorney, stressed their respect for the justice system but emphasized that they believe an incorrect verdict was reached in this case. They are confident in their hopes to overturn the convictions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;scientology-in-the-spotlight&quot;&gt;Scientology in the Spotlight&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The trial has not only shone a spotlight on Masterson but also on the Church of Scientology. Accusations flew regarding the Church’s role in the aftermath of the alleged assaults. Victims claimed reluctance in filing charges, pointing fingers at the Church’s strict internal handling of such issues. The Church, however, refuted these claims, stating their clear policy on adhering to the laws of the land and dispelling rumors of harassment of the accusers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;an-emotional-turmoil&quot;&gt;An Emotional Turmoil&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As statements flowed in from various parties, the impact on the victims became evident. Impact statements delivered in court painted a picture of the trauma and emotional scarring these events have left behind. One of the victims stated, “When you raped me, you stole from me,” describing rape as a “theft of the spirit.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Masterson, once a beloved figure on ‘That ’70s Show’, now faces the reality of his actions. As the entertainment industry reflects on another one of its own falling from grace, the broader conversation around power dynamics, consent, and the role of institutions in such cases continues to evolve.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">In a case that has caught the attention of the entertainment industry and beyond, ‘That ’70s Show’ star, Danny Masterson, has been sentenced to a substantial 30 years in prison after a conviction on charges of rape. Court sketches depicted an emotional scene as actor and model Bijou Phillips, Masterson’s wife, looked on. Masterson was seen blowing a kiss to her just moments before being escorted away. The verdict came after an eight-day deliberation, where a jury found him guilty of two counts of forcible rape. Maximum Punishment Meted Out Los Angeles County Superior Court Judge Charlaine Olmedo handed down the 15 years-to-life imprisonment for each count to be served consecutively. This verdict ensures that Masterson will only be eligible for parole after 25 1/2 years, keeping the possibility open for a lifetime sentence. District Attorney George Gascón lauded the verdict, citing the challenging journey faced by the victims. In his words, the case against Masterson highlights the often-uneven playing field victims face when challenging influential figures. He hopes the verdict brings solace to the victims and serves as a deterrent to others who might exploit their position of power. A Glimmer of Hope for Masterson? Despite the severe sentencing, Masterson’s legal team remains optimistic. They’ve voiced concerns about what they perceive as “substantial” errors during the trial and intend to appeal the court’s decision. Shawn Holley, Masterson’s attorney, stressed their respect for the justice system but emphasized that they believe an incorrect verdict was reached in this case. They are confident in their hopes to overturn the convictions. Scientology in the Spotlight The trial has not only shone a spotlight on Masterson but also on the Church of Scientology. Accusations flew regarding the Church’s role in the aftermath of the alleged assaults. Victims claimed reluctance in filing charges, pointing fingers at the Church’s strict internal handling of such issues. The Church, however, refuted these claims, stating their clear policy on adhering to the laws of the land and dispelling rumors of harassment of the accusers. An Emotional Turmoil As statements flowed in from various parties, the impact on the victims became evident. Impact statements delivered in court painted a picture of the trauma and emotional scarring these events have left behind. One of the victims stated, “When you raped me, you stole from me,” describing rape as a “theft of the spirit.” Masterson, once a beloved figure on ‘That ’70s Show’, now faces the reality of his actions. As the entertainment industry reflects on another one of its own falling from grace, the broader conversation around power dynamics, consent, and the role of institutions in such cases continues to evolve.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Rep. Jim Jordan Fights for Transparency Amid Controversial Attorney Dealings</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/08/Jordan-Seeks-Truth/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rep. Jim Jordan Fights for Transparency Amid Controversial Attorney Dealings" /><published>2023-09-08T10:59:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-08T10:59:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/08/Jordan-Seeks-Truth</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/08/Jordan-Seeks-Truth/">&lt;p&gt;In recent political updates, the House Judiciary Committee, led by Rep. Jim Jordan, R-Ohio, is pushing for more clarity. They’re asking Jack Smith’s office, the special counsel, for more details about their relationship with attorney Stanley Woodward. This move comes right after news outlets shared that Woodward raised concerns over how the prosecution was behaving.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To give a bit of background, Woodward was once the attorney for Yuscil Taveras. Taveras worked in IT at Donald Trump’s Mar-a-Lago estate. Around the same time, Woodward also represented another Mar-a-Lago employee, Walt Nauta. Because of fears that Woodward could be conflicted, the court decided to let Taveras talk to another lawyer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This ended up leading to Taveras agreeing to work with the prosecutors. That didn’t sit well with Woodward, and they parted ways. What’s more, prosecutors are hinting that Taveras might speak out in court, thanks to the agreement. This creates another pickle for Woodward. Why? Well, it means an old client might speak against a current client.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But the story gets deeper. This IT worker, Taveras, had earlier pointed fingers at Trump, Nauta, and another employee, Carlos de Oliveira. This testimony played a big role in more charges against Trump.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On top of all this, Woodward has shared that he felt the heat from a Justice Department official named Jay Bratt. This happened after Woodward mentioned applying for a job at the D.C. superior court. This chat was all about his client, Nauta.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Jim Jordan is stepping up to the plate. He sent a letter on Thursday asking for all talks between Woodward and the prosecutors about Nauta. He also wants to see what top Justice Department officials have said about Woodward’s clients. He’s hoping to get all this info by September 21st.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s clear that Rep. Jim Jordan and the House Judiciary Committee are standing up for justice and transparency. They’re working to make sure everything is above board in these complex legal matters.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In recent political updates, the House Judiciary Committee, led by Rep. Jim Jordan, R-Ohio, is pushing for more clarity. They’re asking Jack Smith’s office, the special counsel, for more details about their relationship with attorney Stanley Woodward. This move comes right after news outlets shared that Woodward raised concerns over how the prosecution was behaving. To give a bit of background, Woodward was once the attorney for Yuscil Taveras. Taveras worked in IT at Donald Trump’s Mar-a-Lago estate. Around the same time, Woodward also represented another Mar-a-Lago employee, Walt Nauta. Because of fears that Woodward could be conflicted, the court decided to let Taveras talk to another lawyer. This ended up leading to Taveras agreeing to work with the prosecutors. That didn’t sit well with Woodward, and they parted ways. What’s more, prosecutors are hinting that Taveras might speak out in court, thanks to the agreement. This creates another pickle for Woodward. Why? Well, it means an old client might speak against a current client. But the story gets deeper. This IT worker, Taveras, had earlier pointed fingers at Trump, Nauta, and another employee, Carlos de Oliveira. This testimony played a big role in more charges against Trump. On top of all this, Woodward has shared that he felt the heat from a Justice Department official named Jay Bratt. This happened after Woodward mentioned applying for a job at the D.C. superior court. This chat was all about his client, Nauta. Rep. Jim Jordan is stepping up to the plate. He sent a letter on Thursday asking for all talks between Woodward and the prosecutors about Nauta. He also wants to see what top Justice Department officials have said about Woodward’s clients. He’s hoping to get all this info by September 21st. It’s clear that Rep. Jim Jordan and the House Judiciary Committee are standing up for justice and transparency. They’re working to make sure everything is above board in these complex legal matters.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Political Playbook? Peter Navarro’s Contempt Conviction Raises Eyebrows</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/08/Navarro-Political-Play/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Political Playbook? Peter Navarro’s Contempt Conviction Raises Eyebrows" /><published>2023-09-08T10:03:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-08T10:03:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/08/Navarro-Political-Play</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/08/Navarro-Political-Play/">&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON, DC: Another chapter in the ongoing investigation by the January 6 Committee seems to reek of political maneuvering. Peter Navarro, former economic adviser to President Trump, was convicted on two counts of criminal contempt of Congress, leading many to question if this is a genuine pursuit of justice or a politically motivated attack on Trump’s closest allies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last year saw Navarro and Dan Scavino, another former White House aide, held in contempt by Congress. This conviction is eerily reminiscent of the trial and subsequent conviction of Steve Bannon, another Trump adviser.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the backdrop of these convictions, Navarro’s perspective on January 6 stands out. He has openly stated in interviews that Trump loyalists aimed to utilize the Capitol’s peaceful protest as leverage. The goal? To pressure Congress and Vice President Mike Pence into rejecting the Electoral College votes from states contested by the Trump campaign. Contrary to the narrative spun by the January 6 Committee, Navarro emphasizes that the unforeseen violence that transpired acted against their intentions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet, the jury’s verdict came swiftly. After just five hours, Navarro was found guilty, with sentencing scheduled for January 12, 2024. The possible consequences? A year behind bars and fines reaching $100,000.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Federal prosecutors were quick to point out the necessity of adhering to congressional subpoenas during their closing arguments, stating, “Our government only works when people play by the rules.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, Navarro’s defense attorney, Stanley Woodward, presented a counter-narrative. He built his case around the terms “accident, mistake, or inadvertence,” hinting that the charges against Navarro lacked substantial evidence. Woodward’s assertion that the government failed to provide adequate proof of Navarro’s deliberate non-compliance was hard-hitting. He concluded with the suggestive remark, “Something stinks.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This case, and others like it, have fueled a growing sentiment that the January 6 Committee’s aggressive probes may be politically charged. Is the aim genuinely to uphold justice, or is there an ulterior motive targeting Trump’s inner circle? As the drama unfolds, the nation watches closely, waiting for clarity.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">WASHINGTON, DC: Another chapter in the ongoing investigation by the January 6 Committee seems to reek of political maneuvering. Peter Navarro, former economic adviser to President Trump, was convicted on two counts of criminal contempt of Congress, leading many to question if this is a genuine pursuit of justice or a politically motivated attack on Trump’s closest allies. Last year saw Navarro and Dan Scavino, another former White House aide, held in contempt by Congress. This conviction is eerily reminiscent of the trial and subsequent conviction of Steve Bannon, another Trump adviser. In the backdrop of these convictions, Navarro’s perspective on January 6 stands out. He has openly stated in interviews that Trump loyalists aimed to utilize the Capitol’s peaceful protest as leverage. The goal? To pressure Congress and Vice President Mike Pence into rejecting the Electoral College votes from states contested by the Trump campaign. Contrary to the narrative spun by the January 6 Committee, Navarro emphasizes that the unforeseen violence that transpired acted against their intentions. Yet, the jury’s verdict came swiftly. After just five hours, Navarro was found guilty, with sentencing scheduled for January 12, 2024. The possible consequences? A year behind bars and fines reaching $100,000. Federal prosecutors were quick to point out the necessity of adhering to congressional subpoenas during their closing arguments, stating, “Our government only works when people play by the rules.” However, Navarro’s defense attorney, Stanley Woodward, presented a counter-narrative. He built his case around the terms “accident, mistake, or inadvertence,” hinting that the charges against Navarro lacked substantial evidence. Woodward’s assertion that the government failed to provide adequate proof of Navarro’s deliberate non-compliance was hard-hitting. He concluded with the suggestive remark, “Something stinks.” This case, and others like it, have fueled a growing sentiment that the January 6 Committee’s aggressive probes may be politically charged. Is the aim genuinely to uphold justice, or is there an ulterior motive targeting Trump’s inner circle? As the drama unfolds, the nation watches closely, waiting for clarity.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">O’Hare Airport - From Busy Hub to Migrant Crisis Epicenter?</title><link href="/news/2023/09/08/Chicago-Migrant-Crisis/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="O’Hare Airport - From Busy Hub to Migrant Crisis Epicenter?" /><published>2023-09-08T09:06:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-08T09:06:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/08/Chicago-Migrant-Crisis</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/08/Chicago-Migrant-Crisis/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Is This the Right Solution? Chicago’s Questionable Move Amidst Soaring Migrant Influx&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The vibrant and bustling O’Hare International Airport, typically known for jet-setters and travel stories, is now a makeshift migrant shelter. A shocking revelation has left many Chicago residents flabbergasted. The city, already grappling with its own challenges, is using one of the nation’s most active airports to house migrants, with numbers increasing from 31 to over 400 in a month.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Befuddled City Leadership?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chicago leaders have made a series of questionable decisions in the recent past, but using O’Hare as a shelter might just top the list. William Kelly, a Chicago reporter, gave a candid account of the situation during his appearance on “Fox &amp;amp; Friends.” Behind the black curtains, far from the public’s view, is a rapidly growing migrant holding area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shockingly, while the city was quick to crack down on its homeless American citizens seeking refuge at the airport, they now seem to be rolling out the red carpet for migrants. As Kelly aptly puts it, the priorities seem misplaced. Mayor Johnson, hailed as “the people’s mayor” during his campaign, appears to have shifted gears, prompting Kelly to dub him “the migrants’ mayor.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Safety, Transparency, and Financial Concerns&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The city’s approach not only raises humanitarian concerns but also logistical and safety ones. Are migrants undergoing the same stringent security checks as American travelers? With Chicago already wrestling with a rising crime rate, and the burdens of post-pandemic recovery, this added layer of complexity could further strain the city’s resources.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kelly highlights the opaque nature of city spending on the crisis, wondering aloud about the trajectory of the “millions upon millions” being spent. Mayor Johnson’s reticence to clarify matters has only fanned the flames of discontent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Broader Citywide Crisis&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kelly’s chilling description of a scene reminiscent of “Mad Max” outside his window speaks volumes about the city’s dire state. With police resources stretched thin, handling both migrants and criminal elements has become a juggling act, putting the safety of Chicago residents at risk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other reports further cement the gravity of the situation. An overwhelming 14,000 migrants have poured into Chicago since August, and the city, despite its 15 asylum seeker shelters, struggles to keep pace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Vianney Marzullo, from the Police Station Response Team, asserts that O’Hare is merely a holding space for incoming flights, one can’t help but question the foresight and planning of city leadership.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With another shelter slated to open next month, one wonders if Chicago is truly prepared to handle its migrant influx while simultaneously addressing the needs and concerns of its citizens.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Is This the Right Solution? Chicago’s Questionable Move Amidst Soaring Migrant Influx The vibrant and bustling O’Hare International Airport, typically known for jet-setters and travel stories, is now a makeshift migrant shelter. A shocking revelation has left many Chicago residents flabbergasted. The city, already grappling with its own challenges, is using one of the nation’s most active airports to house migrants, with numbers increasing from 31 to over 400 in a month. A Befuddled City Leadership? Chicago leaders have made a series of questionable decisions in the recent past, but using O’Hare as a shelter might just top the list. William Kelly, a Chicago reporter, gave a candid account of the situation during his appearance on “Fox &amp;amp; Friends.” Behind the black curtains, far from the public’s view, is a rapidly growing migrant holding area. Shockingly, while the city was quick to crack down on its homeless American citizens seeking refuge at the airport, they now seem to be rolling out the red carpet for migrants. As Kelly aptly puts it, the priorities seem misplaced. Mayor Johnson, hailed as “the people’s mayor” during his campaign, appears to have shifted gears, prompting Kelly to dub him “the migrants’ mayor.” Safety, Transparency, and Financial Concerns The city’s approach not only raises humanitarian concerns but also logistical and safety ones. Are migrants undergoing the same stringent security checks as American travelers? With Chicago already wrestling with a rising crime rate, and the burdens of post-pandemic recovery, this added layer of complexity could further strain the city’s resources. Kelly highlights the opaque nature of city spending on the crisis, wondering aloud about the trajectory of the “millions upon millions” being spent. Mayor Johnson’s reticence to clarify matters has only fanned the flames of discontent. A Broader Citywide Crisis Kelly’s chilling description of a scene reminiscent of “Mad Max” outside his window speaks volumes about the city’s dire state. With police resources stretched thin, handling both migrants and criminal elements has become a juggling act, putting the safety of Chicago residents at risk. Other reports further cement the gravity of the situation. An overwhelming 14,000 migrants have poured into Chicago since August, and the city, despite its 15 asylum seeker shelters, struggles to keep pace. While Vianney Marzullo, from the Police Station Response Team, asserts that O’Hare is merely a holding space for incoming flights, one can’t help but question the foresight and planning of city leadership. With another shelter slated to open next month, one wonders if Chicago is truly prepared to handle its migrant influx while simultaneously addressing the needs and concerns of its citizens.</summary></entry></feed>