<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-09-11T15:12:10-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/09/11/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-09-11T15:12:10-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-11T15:12:10-04:00</updated><id>/2023/09/11/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/11/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Pennsylvania’s Elusive Escapee - How Danelo Cavalcante Outfoxed Authorities</title><link href="/news/2023/09/11/Escaped-Murderer/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Pennsylvania’s Elusive Escapee - How Danelo Cavalcante Outfoxed Authorities" /><published>2023-09-11T15:01:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-11T15:01:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/11/Escaped-Murderer</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/11/Escaped-Murderer/">&lt;p&gt;The community in southeastern Pennsylvania remains on edge as Danelo Souza Cavalcante, an escaped murderer, proves adept at evading authorities. Since his escape from Chester County Prison over a week ago, there have been multiple confirmed sightings of Cavalcante, but he remains at large.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Late Saturday, Pennsylvania State Police provided an update indicating that Cavalcante, who had originally been the focus of a search centered around the Longwood Gardens botanical park, was now seen near Phoenixville in northern Chester County. This location is over 20 miles northeast of the earlier search area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a bid to possibly divert attention and complicate the manhunt, Cavalcante has altered his appearance. He’s now clean-shaven and was last seen wearing a yellow or green hooded sweatshirt, black baseball cap, green prison pants, and white shoes. Additionally, he’s believed to be driving a stolen 2020 White Ford Transit van, which bears a refrigeration unit on top.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reason for Cavalcante’s initial incarceration was a life sentence handed down after he was found guilty of fatally stabbing his ex-girlfriend in 2021. His motivation, prosecutors assert, was to prevent her from revealing to the police that he was a wanted murderer in his home country of Brazil.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The circumstances of his escape raise eyebrows. Cavalcante achieved his freedom by scaling a wall, navigating over razor wire, and eventually jumping off a roof to the ground. What’s astonishing is that his disappearance went unnoticed for over an hour until a routine headcount revealed the discrepancy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A prison tower guard on duty during this escape has since been dismissed. This bold escape, coupled with a manhunt that has attracted international attention, is also making headlines in Brazil. There, Cavalcante is accused of another heinous crime - the “double qualified homicide” of Válter Júnior Moreira dos Reis in 2017, purportedly over a vehicle repair debt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While local festivities, such as the annual mushroom festival in Kennett Square, proceeded as planned, assurances of “all necessary precautions and protocols” couldn’t entirely assuage the heightened anxiety of residents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given Cavalcante’s demonstrated ability to elude capture and the description of him as “extremely dangerous” by authorities, the community is urged to be vigilant. The state police have mobilized a large-scale search operation involving tactical teams, tracking dogs, officers on horseback, and aircraft. A $20,000 reward is now on the table for information leading to his apprehension.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Residents and visitors are encouraged to remain cautious and report any suspicious activities. As the hunt for Cavalcante intensifies, one can only hope for a swift and safe resolution to this unnerving saga.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">The community in southeastern Pennsylvania remains on edge as Danelo Souza Cavalcante, an escaped murderer, proves adept at evading authorities. Since his escape from Chester County Prison over a week ago, there have been multiple confirmed sightings of Cavalcante, but he remains at large. Late Saturday, Pennsylvania State Police provided an update indicating that Cavalcante, who had originally been the focus of a search centered around the Longwood Gardens botanical park, was now seen near Phoenixville in northern Chester County. This location is over 20 miles northeast of the earlier search area. In a bid to possibly divert attention and complicate the manhunt, Cavalcante has altered his appearance. He’s now clean-shaven and was last seen wearing a yellow or green hooded sweatshirt, black baseball cap, green prison pants, and white shoes. Additionally, he’s believed to be driving a stolen 2020 White Ford Transit van, which bears a refrigeration unit on top. The reason for Cavalcante’s initial incarceration was a life sentence handed down after he was found guilty of fatally stabbing his ex-girlfriend in 2021. His motivation, prosecutors assert, was to prevent her from revealing to the police that he was a wanted murderer in his home country of Brazil. The circumstances of his escape raise eyebrows. Cavalcante achieved his freedom by scaling a wall, navigating over razor wire, and eventually jumping off a roof to the ground. What’s astonishing is that his disappearance went unnoticed for over an hour until a routine headcount revealed the discrepancy. A prison tower guard on duty during this escape has since been dismissed. This bold escape, coupled with a manhunt that has attracted international attention, is also making headlines in Brazil. There, Cavalcante is accused of another heinous crime - the “double qualified homicide” of Válter Júnior Moreira dos Reis in 2017, purportedly over a vehicle repair debt. While local festivities, such as the annual mushroom festival in Kennett Square, proceeded as planned, assurances of “all necessary precautions and protocols” couldn’t entirely assuage the heightened anxiety of residents. Given Cavalcante’s demonstrated ability to elude capture and the description of him as “extremely dangerous” by authorities, the community is urged to be vigilant. The state police have mobilized a large-scale search operation involving tactical teams, tracking dogs, officers on horseback, and aircraft. A $20,000 reward is now on the table for information leading to his apprehension. Residents and visitors are encouraged to remain cautious and report any suspicious activities. As the hunt for Cavalcante intensifies, one can only hope for a swift and safe resolution to this unnerving saga.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Scientology Drama Unveiled - Tinseltown’s Most Controversial Faith</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/11/Scientology-Drama-Unveiled/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Scientology Drama Unveiled - Tinseltown’s Most Controversial Faith" /><published>2023-09-11T14:02:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-11T14:02:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/11/Scientology-Drama-Unveiled</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/11/Scientology-Drama-Unveiled/">&lt;p&gt;Hollywood has had a long-standing and complex relationship with Scientology. From its high-profile members to the drama surrounding its practices, the Church of Scientology often finds itself under the Tinseltown spotlight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;danny-masterson-and-scientologys-trial-tangle&quot;&gt;Danny Masterson and Scientology’s Trial Tangle&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Actor Danny Masterson, best known for his role in “That ’70s Show,” recently faced a rape trial where his faith became a significant talking point. Found guilty on two counts of forcible rape, Masterson’s sentencing shed light on the secretive world of Scientology. Though the Church was not directly implicated in the case, the trial proceedings painted a troubling picture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Victims, all members of the Church at the time, were reportedly hesitant to come forward due to the organization’s strict protocols against public involvement with member issues. Deputy District Attorney Ariel Anson told jurors, “The church taught his victims: ‘Rape isn’t rape, you caused this, and above all, you are never allowed to go to law enforcement.’”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a counter-statement, the Church of Scientology stated, “The Church was not a party to this case and religion did not belong in this proceeding as Supreme Court precedent has maintained for centuries.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;leah-remini---from-faithful-follower-to-fierce-critic&quot;&gt;Leah Remini - From Faithful Follower to Fierce Critic&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Former Scientologist Leah Remini has been one of the Church’s most vocal critics since she left in 2013. Celebrating Masterson’s victims for their courage, she commented, “I am relieved that this dangerous rapist will be off the streets and unable to violently assault and rape women with the help of Scientology, a multi-billion-dollar criminal organization with tax-exempt status.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But Remini hasn’t limited her criticisms to this recent trial. In her award-winning documentary series, she delves deep into the Church’s practices, sharing insights and exposing what she believes are its harmful activities. The Church, in response, has dismissed her claims as attempts “to appear relevant again.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tom-cruise---the-poster-boy-of-scientology&quot;&gt;Tom Cruise - The Poster Boy of Scientology&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No discussion of Scientology and Hollywood would be complete without mentioning Tom Cruise. One of the Church’s most high-profile members, Cruise has remained largely loyal to his faith even as controversies raged around him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, his relationships, notably with Nicole Kidman and Katie Holmes, have brought attention to the religion’s influence in personal matters. Remini alluded that Scientology played a role in Cruise’s split with Holmes, citing the Church’s tendency to label detractors as suppressive persons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;scientologys-other-celebrities-and-controversies&quot;&gt;Scientology’s Other Celebrities and Controversies&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other celebrities, such as Kirstie Alley, have praised the Church for its positive impact on their lives. Alley, in particular, credited Scientology with helping her overcome her cocaine addiction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, filmmaker Paul Haggis, a former member, faced legal troubles connected to allegations of rape, with some speculating on the Church’s role in his life and actions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;in-the-spotlight&quot;&gt;In the Spotlight&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While it remains a divisive topic in Hollywood and beyond, Scientology’s association with celebrities ensures it remains in the limelight. As more stories emerge, the relationship between Tinseltown and its most controversial faith continues to intrigue and baffle in equal measure.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Hollywood has had a long-standing and complex relationship with Scientology. From its high-profile members to the drama surrounding its practices, the Church of Scientology often finds itself under the Tinseltown spotlight. Danny Masterson and Scientology’s Trial Tangle Actor Danny Masterson, best known for his role in “That ’70s Show,” recently faced a rape trial where his faith became a significant talking point. Found guilty on two counts of forcible rape, Masterson’s sentencing shed light on the secretive world of Scientology. Though the Church was not directly implicated in the case, the trial proceedings painted a troubling picture. Victims, all members of the Church at the time, were reportedly hesitant to come forward due to the organization’s strict protocols against public involvement with member issues. Deputy District Attorney Ariel Anson told jurors, “The church taught his victims: ‘Rape isn’t rape, you caused this, and above all, you are never allowed to go to law enforcement.’” In a counter-statement, the Church of Scientology stated, “The Church was not a party to this case and religion did not belong in this proceeding as Supreme Court precedent has maintained for centuries.” Leah Remini - From Faithful Follower to Fierce Critic Former Scientologist Leah Remini has been one of the Church’s most vocal critics since she left in 2013. Celebrating Masterson’s victims for their courage, she commented, “I am relieved that this dangerous rapist will be off the streets and unable to violently assault and rape women with the help of Scientology, a multi-billion-dollar criminal organization with tax-exempt status.” But Remini hasn’t limited her criticisms to this recent trial. In her award-winning documentary series, she delves deep into the Church’s practices, sharing insights and exposing what she believes are its harmful activities. The Church, in response, has dismissed her claims as attempts “to appear relevant again.” Tom Cruise - The Poster Boy of Scientology No discussion of Scientology and Hollywood would be complete without mentioning Tom Cruise. One of the Church’s most high-profile members, Cruise has remained largely loyal to his faith even as controversies raged around him. However, his relationships, notably with Nicole Kidman and Katie Holmes, have brought attention to the religion’s influence in personal matters. Remini alluded that Scientology played a role in Cruise’s split with Holmes, citing the Church’s tendency to label detractors as suppressive persons. Scientology’s Other Celebrities and Controversies Other celebrities, such as Kirstie Alley, have praised the Church for its positive impact on their lives. Alley, in particular, credited Scientology with helping her overcome her cocaine addiction. On the other hand, filmmaker Paul Haggis, a former member, faced legal troubles connected to allegations of rape, with some speculating on the Church’s role in his life and actions. In the Spotlight While it remains a divisive topic in Hollywood and beyond, Scientology’s association with celebrities ensures it remains in the limelight. As more stories emerge, the relationship between Tinseltown and its most controversial faith continues to intrigue and baffle in equal measure.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Digital IDs on the Horizon - A Slippery Slope to Surveillance?</title><link href="/news/2023/09/11/Digital-Overreach/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Digital IDs on the Horizon - A Slippery Slope to Surveillance?" /><published>2023-09-11T13:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-11T13:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/11/Digital-Overreach</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/11/Digital-Overreach/">&lt;p&gt;European Commission President Ursula von der Leyen’s recent push for global digital ID systems, akin to coronavirus passports, at the G20 Summit’s “One Future” session has ignited fierce debates. While she touts them as the future of global digital infrastructure, many view these initiatives as a grave step towards omnipresent surveillance, eroding personal freedoms and privacy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The digital era, although prosperous and convenient, comes with significant challenges. One of the most alarming is the potential to turn tools meant for connectivity into tools of control. Von der Leyen’s endorsement of a global regulatory body for Artificial Intelligence (AI) — mirroring the structure of the United Nations’ Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change — raises the question: who gets to set the standards, and how will they be enforced?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;von der Leyen praised the European Union’s development of a coronavirus digital certificate, pointing out its adoption by 51 countries across four continents. While she sees this as a testament to its functionality and trustworthiness, many fear that such widespread adoption of a single digital ID system puts immense power in the hands of few and reduces the anonymity and privacy of individuals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The European Union’s ongoing effort to introduce a “digital identity” app, aiming to consolidate a citizen’s essential data, including passport details, driver’s license, and credit cards, has added fuel to the fire. Given that such information is a treasure trove for cybercriminals, the security implications alone are staggering. But more so, the app’s existence could provide governments with unprecedented access to personal information, raising the specter of an Orwellian future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Romanian MEP Cristian Terhes’s warning earlier this year resounds even more today. He termed the digital ID system push as potentially leading to the “Chinafication” of Europe. Drawing parallels with Communist China’s surveillance mechanisms, Terhes’s statement underscores concerns that Europe might be on a similar trajectory, sacrificing privacy at the altar of supposed convenience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The EU’s plan to potentially introduce a Central Bank Digital Currency (CBDC) further intensifies these apprehensions. Beyond the economic implications, a CBDC could provide an infrastructure for governments to monitor, and possibly control, individual financial transactions, curtailing financial freedom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While digital transformation and global standardization have undeniable merits, the cost of personal freedom and privacy should be paramount. As the line between connectivity and control blurs, one must ask: are we inadvertently laying the foundation for a digital dystopia?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">European Commission President Ursula von der Leyen’s recent push for global digital ID systems, akin to coronavirus passports, at the G20 Summit’s “One Future” session has ignited fierce debates. While she touts them as the future of global digital infrastructure, many view these initiatives as a grave step towards omnipresent surveillance, eroding personal freedoms and privacy. The digital era, although prosperous and convenient, comes with significant challenges. One of the most alarming is the potential to turn tools meant for connectivity into tools of control. Von der Leyen’s endorsement of a global regulatory body for Artificial Intelligence (AI) — mirroring the structure of the United Nations’ Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change — raises the question: who gets to set the standards, and how will they be enforced? von der Leyen praised the European Union’s development of a coronavirus digital certificate, pointing out its adoption by 51 countries across four continents. While she sees this as a testament to its functionality and trustworthiness, many fear that such widespread adoption of a single digital ID system puts immense power in the hands of few and reduces the anonymity and privacy of individuals. The European Union’s ongoing effort to introduce a “digital identity” app, aiming to consolidate a citizen’s essential data, including passport details, driver’s license, and credit cards, has added fuel to the fire. Given that such information is a treasure trove for cybercriminals, the security implications alone are staggering. But more so, the app’s existence could provide governments with unprecedented access to personal information, raising the specter of an Orwellian future. Romanian MEP Cristian Terhes’s warning earlier this year resounds even more today. He termed the digital ID system push as potentially leading to the “Chinafication” of Europe. Drawing parallels with Communist China’s surveillance mechanisms, Terhes’s statement underscores concerns that Europe might be on a similar trajectory, sacrificing privacy at the altar of supposed convenience. The EU’s plan to potentially introduce a Central Bank Digital Currency (CBDC) further intensifies these apprehensions. Beyond the economic implications, a CBDC could provide an infrastructure for governments to monitor, and possibly control, individual financial transactions, curtailing financial freedom. While digital transformation and global standardization have undeniable merits, the cost of personal freedom and privacy should be paramount. As the line between connectivity and control blurs, one must ask: are we inadvertently laying the foundation for a digital dystopia?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Johnson Raises Red Flags - Obama’s Ties to Influence Peddling</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/11/Obama-Influence-Peddling/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Johnson Raises Red Flags - Obama’s Ties to Influence Peddling" /><published>2023-09-11T12:01:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-11T12:01:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/11/Obama-Influence-Peddling</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/11/Obama-Influence-Peddling/">&lt;p&gt;Deepening concerns and raising eyebrows in the corridors of Washington, Sen. Ron Johnson, R-Wis., has cast a shadow over former President Barack Obama’s knowledge of the alleged influence peddling saga. In a revealing conversation, Johnson pulled no punches, stating that Obama was “fully aware of a lot of this.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Underpinning his claim with significant details, Johnson shed light on the fact that the Obama State Department was more than just familiar with the alleged influence peddling associated with Hunter Biden. To add fuel to the fire, Johnson explained, “President Obama was briefed, together with Vice President Biden, by then-CIA Director John Brennan about the scheme that the Hillary Clinton campaign had to accuse the Trump campaign of colluding with Russia.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Making a hard-hitting assertion, Johnson underlined that Obama was in the know about the concocted narrative of Russian collusion. “President Obama knew full well that the Russian collusion scheme false narrative was a hoax,” he stated firmly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reflecting on the steps taken against Michael Flynn, he mentioned, “They certainly set up Michael Flynn so that he would never be involved in the Trump White House because he was just too dangerous. He knew too much.” For Johnson, the Obama administration’s actions toward Flynn smacked of ulterior motives, which he says extends to the broader influence peddling episode.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The National Archives and Records Administration (NARA) recently missed a deadline to turn over documents associated with then-Vice President Joe Biden’s alias email accounts. These records are of particular interest to the House Oversight Committee, which is meticulously combing through the Hunter Biden situation. As it stands, the Biden White House and former President Obama have received the documents, with permission pending for their release to the Oversight Committee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Johnson, expressing his growing exasperation, stated, “Sen. Grassley and I have written multiple letters, three to the White House, starting in the summer of 2021, asking for those same documents.” He emphasized the consistent stonewalling they’ve faced from the current administration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Taking a direct jab at Obama, Johnson remarked, “I don’t know why he’s not allowing to release them now,” hinting at possible inconsistencies in Obama’s approach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Johnson’s revelations point to a possible impeachment inquiry, emphasizing the duty of Congress to maintain constitutional oversight. As the layers of this political drama unfold, Johnson’s words paint a picture that many in Washington would rather remain hidden.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Deepening concerns and raising eyebrows in the corridors of Washington, Sen. Ron Johnson, R-Wis., has cast a shadow over former President Barack Obama’s knowledge of the alleged influence peddling saga. In a revealing conversation, Johnson pulled no punches, stating that Obama was “fully aware of a lot of this.” Underpinning his claim with significant details, Johnson shed light on the fact that the Obama State Department was more than just familiar with the alleged influence peddling associated with Hunter Biden. To add fuel to the fire, Johnson explained, “President Obama was briefed, together with Vice President Biden, by then-CIA Director John Brennan about the scheme that the Hillary Clinton campaign had to accuse the Trump campaign of colluding with Russia.” Making a hard-hitting assertion, Johnson underlined that Obama was in the know about the concocted narrative of Russian collusion. “President Obama knew full well that the Russian collusion scheme false narrative was a hoax,” he stated firmly. Reflecting on the steps taken against Michael Flynn, he mentioned, “They certainly set up Michael Flynn so that he would never be involved in the Trump White House because he was just too dangerous. He knew too much.” For Johnson, the Obama administration’s actions toward Flynn smacked of ulterior motives, which he says extends to the broader influence peddling episode. The National Archives and Records Administration (NARA) recently missed a deadline to turn over documents associated with then-Vice President Joe Biden’s alias email accounts. These records are of particular interest to the House Oversight Committee, which is meticulously combing through the Hunter Biden situation. As it stands, the Biden White House and former President Obama have received the documents, with permission pending for their release to the Oversight Committee. Johnson, expressing his growing exasperation, stated, “Sen. Grassley and I have written multiple letters, three to the White House, starting in the summer of 2021, asking for those same documents.” He emphasized the consistent stonewalling they’ve faced from the current administration. Taking a direct jab at Obama, Johnson remarked, “I don’t know why he’s not allowing to release them now,” hinting at possible inconsistencies in Obama’s approach. Johnson’s revelations point to a possible impeachment inquiry, emphasizing the duty of Congress to maintain constitutional oversight. As the layers of this political drama unfold, Johnson’s words paint a picture that many in Washington would rather remain hidden.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Remembering 9-11 - A Journey from Grief to Purpose</title><link href="/news/2023/09/11/Remembering-9-11/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Remembering 9-11 - A Journey from Grief to Purpose" /><published>2023-09-11T11:11:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-11T11:11:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/11/Remembering-9-11</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/11/Remembering-9-11/">&lt;p&gt;As the 22nd anniversary of the fateful September 11th terror attacks dawns, Pastor Jesse Bradley from Auburn, Washington, underscores the importance of taking a moment to recall the tragic events that reshaped the nation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;reliving-the-past-to-shape-our-future&quot;&gt;Reliving The Past to Shape Our Future&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It is important to pause and remember what happened,” said Pastor Jesse Bradley of Washington. “It shapes our path forward.” The attacks were not just a series of unfortunate events; they altered the course of countless lives, cities, and the nation’s collective consciousness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-legacy-continues&quot;&gt;The Legacy Continues&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two years ago, participants of the 9/11 Promise Run brandished American flags, a stark reminder of the unity and strength the nation exhibited post the attacks. Christopher “Dom” Colasanti, a bond trader at Cantor Fitzgerald, was one of the many who lost their lives during the World Trade Center attack. Bradley remembers him as a teammate from Dartmouth College. He recalls the dedication of the men’s varsity locker room in honor of Colasanti, signifying the bonds and friendships formed there. The legacy of such individuals, characterized by connecting, serving, joy, and love, endures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;sacrifices-and-acts-of-bravery&quot;&gt;Sacrifices and Acts of Bravery&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amid the chaos and devastation, first responders across the country raced into peril, exemplifying bravery and selflessness. Their unflinching commitment serves as a constant source of inspiration. “Love includes sacrifice,” Bradley asserts, urging everyone to read about Todd Beamer’s final moments. Beamer, aboard Flight 93, courageously confronted the hijackers, preventing further potential devastation in the nation’s capital.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Quoting 1 John 3:16, Pastor Bradley emphasizes, “This is how we know what love is: Jesus Christ laid down his life for us. And we ought to lay down our lives for our brothers and sisters.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;trust-healing-and-purpose-in-faith&quot;&gt;Trust, Healing, and Purpose in Faith&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anchoring his message in faith, Bradley references the national motto, “In God We Trust.” A relationship with God, he believes, offers healing, restoration, and an unyielding hope surpassing any sorrow. Echoing Psalm 46:10, he emphasizes, “Be still, and know that I am God; I will be exalted among the nations, I will be exalted in the earth.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The pastor concludes with a powerful call to action, cautioning against complacency and idolatry. He inspires with the words, “If you are overcoming tragedy and trauma, remember that you are loved.” The message is clear: On the anniversary of September 11th and always, “We remember our loved ones,” and we discover peace and profound purpose.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">As the 22nd anniversary of the fateful September 11th terror attacks dawns, Pastor Jesse Bradley from Auburn, Washington, underscores the importance of taking a moment to recall the tragic events that reshaped the nation. Reliving The Past to Shape Our Future “It is important to pause and remember what happened,” said Pastor Jesse Bradley of Washington. “It shapes our path forward.” The attacks were not just a series of unfortunate events; they altered the course of countless lives, cities, and the nation’s collective consciousness. The Legacy Continues Two years ago, participants of the 9/11 Promise Run brandished American flags, a stark reminder of the unity and strength the nation exhibited post the attacks. Christopher “Dom” Colasanti, a bond trader at Cantor Fitzgerald, was one of the many who lost their lives during the World Trade Center attack. Bradley remembers him as a teammate from Dartmouth College. He recalls the dedication of the men’s varsity locker room in honor of Colasanti, signifying the bonds and friendships formed there. The legacy of such individuals, characterized by connecting, serving, joy, and love, endures. Sacrifices and Acts of Bravery Amid the chaos and devastation, first responders across the country raced into peril, exemplifying bravery and selflessness. Their unflinching commitment serves as a constant source of inspiration. “Love includes sacrifice,” Bradley asserts, urging everyone to read about Todd Beamer’s final moments. Beamer, aboard Flight 93, courageously confronted the hijackers, preventing further potential devastation in the nation’s capital. Quoting 1 John 3:16, Pastor Bradley emphasizes, “This is how we know what love is: Jesus Christ laid down his life for us. And we ought to lay down our lives for our brothers and sisters.” Trust, Healing, and Purpose in Faith Anchoring his message in faith, Bradley references the national motto, “In God We Trust.” A relationship with God, he believes, offers healing, restoration, and an unyielding hope surpassing any sorrow. Echoing Psalm 46:10, he emphasizes, “Be still, and know that I am God; I will be exalted among the nations, I will be exalted in the earth.” The pastor concludes with a powerful call to action, cautioning against complacency and idolatry. He inspires with the words, “If you are overcoming tragedy and trauma, remember that you are loved.” The message is clear: On the anniversary of September 11th and always, “We remember our loved ones,” and we discover peace and profound purpose.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump Sounds the Alarm on Political Indictments</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/11/Defending-Democracy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump Sounds the Alarm on Political Indictments" /><published>2023-09-11T10:06:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-11T10:06:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/11/Defending-Democracy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/11/Defending-Democracy/">&lt;p&gt;At the heart of American democracy, a new challenge arises. Former President Donald Trump, in a charged address to the South Dakota GOP convention, stated unequivocally that his recent indictment is a move by political opponents threatened by his consistent lead in the polls.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With numbers that show him not just leading in the Republican primary but also outpacing incumbent President Joe Biden in a hypothetical general election match-up, Trump emphasized, “They indicted me because I’m in first place.” This is not just a claim of personal targeting, but a grave concern for the integrity of the nation’s political system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump highlighted the peril of his political success, indicating that every surge in his popularity seems to coincide with intensified scrutiny. Expressing his frustration, he mused, “Maybe I should announce, ‘I’m doing horribly; it’s horrible, I’m going to withdraw,” pointing to the irony of his situation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But this isn’t just about one man’s political journey. Trump underscored a systemic issue, indicating that the current strategy of his opponents seems to focus on “interfering with elections” to diminish the chances of Republicans and conservatives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The former President’s call to arms wasn’t limited to his situation. He fervently encouraged congressional Republicans to take decisive actions against these perceived politically-motivated indictments. Drawing attention to Senate Minority Leader Mitch McConnell, R-Ky., Trump urged for more robust action, advocating for the defunding of the DOJ and prosecutors believed to be sidelining conservatives through non-meritorious indictments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump’s message resonates with a vast section of the American populace who believe in the sanctity of fair play in politics. As election fervor picks up, the country watches closely, hoping for a campaign that prioritizes issues over political gamesmanship.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">At the heart of American democracy, a new challenge arises. Former President Donald Trump, in a charged address to the South Dakota GOP convention, stated unequivocally that his recent indictment is a move by political opponents threatened by his consistent lead in the polls. With numbers that show him not just leading in the Republican primary but also outpacing incumbent President Joe Biden in a hypothetical general election match-up, Trump emphasized, “They indicted me because I’m in first place.” This is not just a claim of personal targeting, but a grave concern for the integrity of the nation’s political system. Trump highlighted the peril of his political success, indicating that every surge in his popularity seems to coincide with intensified scrutiny. Expressing his frustration, he mused, “Maybe I should announce, ‘I’m doing horribly; it’s horrible, I’m going to withdraw,” pointing to the irony of his situation. But this isn’t just about one man’s political journey. Trump underscored a systemic issue, indicating that the current strategy of his opponents seems to focus on “interfering with elections” to diminish the chances of Republicans and conservatives. The former President’s call to arms wasn’t limited to his situation. He fervently encouraged congressional Republicans to take decisive actions against these perceived politically-motivated indictments. Drawing attention to Senate Minority Leader Mitch McConnell, R-Ky., Trump urged for more robust action, advocating for the defunding of the DOJ and prosecutors believed to be sidelining conservatives through non-meritorious indictments. Trump’s message resonates with a vast section of the American populace who believe in the sanctity of fair play in politics. As election fervor picks up, the country watches closely, hoping for a campaign that prioritizes issues over political gamesmanship.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Showstopper Illness - Guns N’ Roses Postpones Concert</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/11/Guns-N-Roses-Concert-Postponed/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Showstopper Illness - Guns N’ Roses Postpones Concert" /><published>2023-09-11T09:03:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-11T09:03:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/11/Guns-N-Roses-Concert-Postponed</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/11/Guns-N-Roses-Concert-Postponed/">&lt;p&gt;In an unforeseen twist, rock legends Guns N’ Roses have postponed their highly-anticipated St. Louis concert scheduled for September 9 due to a reported illness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unplugged Due to Illness&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In an official statement shared on their Instagram, the band relayed the unfortunate news, “Gunners, the concert in St. Louis on September 9 stands postponed due to illness. Please hold on to your tickets. Those unable to attend the rescheduled date will receive refunds.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The band rounded off their announcement by expressing gratitude for the continued support from their fans, symbolized with a rose emoji.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unwavering Fan Support&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the unexpected setback, the band’s loyal followers, known endearingly as “Gunners,” flooded the Instagram announcement with messages of goodwill and concern. Comments ranged from fans recalling the band’s memorable New Jersey show to general well wishes, emphasizing health as a priority.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the specific member affected by the illness remains unclear, the band’s iconic frontman, Axl Rose, hinted at health issues earlier in the week. Taking to X, previously known as Twitter, he remarked that he felt “a little horse,” accompanying his statement with a playful picture of a small horse, adding, “Fun night, Great Crowd!! Great Venue!! N’ great to be back!!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;On the Road Again&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The legendary hard rock ensemble began their ambitious Guns N’ Roses World Tour 2023 in Tel Aviv, Israel, this June. After electrifying performances spanning Europe, including shows in countries like Spain, Denmark, Germany, and the U.K., the group commenced their North American leg in August, with a stopover in Moncton, Canada.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the St. Louis concert temporarily on hold, fans eagerly await the band’s next scheduled performance at Thompson-Boling Arena in Knoxville on September 12.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a quick reminder, the current lineup of the iconic group comprises Axl Rose, Slash, Duff McKagan, Dizzy Reed, Richard Fortus, Frank Ferrer, and Melissa Reese.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the “Gunners” out there, remember to stay updated on the band’s official channels for the rescheduled concert date.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">In an unforeseen twist, rock legends Guns N’ Roses have postponed their highly-anticipated St. Louis concert scheduled for September 9 due to a reported illness. Unplugged Due to Illness In an official statement shared on their Instagram, the band relayed the unfortunate news, “Gunners, the concert in St. Louis on September 9 stands postponed due to illness. Please hold on to your tickets. Those unable to attend the rescheduled date will receive refunds.” The band rounded off their announcement by expressing gratitude for the continued support from their fans, symbolized with a rose emoji. Unwavering Fan Support Despite the unexpected setback, the band’s loyal followers, known endearingly as “Gunners,” flooded the Instagram announcement with messages of goodwill and concern. Comments ranged from fans recalling the band’s memorable New Jersey show to general well wishes, emphasizing health as a priority. While the specific member affected by the illness remains unclear, the band’s iconic frontman, Axl Rose, hinted at health issues earlier in the week. Taking to X, previously known as Twitter, he remarked that he felt “a little horse,” accompanying his statement with a playful picture of a small horse, adding, “Fun night, Great Crowd!! Great Venue!! N’ great to be back!!” On the Road Again The legendary hard rock ensemble began their ambitious Guns N’ Roses World Tour 2023 in Tel Aviv, Israel, this June. After electrifying performances spanning Europe, including shows in countries like Spain, Denmark, Germany, and the U.K., the group commenced their North American leg in August, with a stopover in Moncton, Canada. With the St. Louis concert temporarily on hold, fans eagerly await the band’s next scheduled performance at Thompson-Boling Arena in Knoxville on September 12. As a quick reminder, the current lineup of the iconic group comprises Axl Rose, Slash, Duff McKagan, Dizzy Reed, Richard Fortus, Frank Ferrer, and Melissa Reese. For the “Gunners” out there, remember to stay updated on the band’s official channels for the rescheduled concert date.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Defiance Against Tyranny - Albuquerque Stands Tall for Second Amendment</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/11/Defiance-Against-Tyranny/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Defiance Against Tyranny - Albuquerque Stands Tall for Second Amendment" /><published>2023-09-11T08:01:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-11T08:01:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/11/Defiance-Against-Tyranny</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/11/Defiance-Against-Tyranny/">&lt;p&gt;In a triumphant move for American freedoms and rights, Bernalillo County District Attorney Sam Bregman declared on Saturday that he would not enforce New Mexico Gov. Michelle Lujan Grisham’s (D) 30-day ban on concealed carry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This shocking, yet commendable act of defiance came swiftly in response to the ban which had only taken effect on Saturday, September 8, 2023. The hastily-imposed prohibition not only prevents the concealed carrying of handguns but also bars open carry, effectively disarming lawful citizens in places such as Albuquerque, located in Bernalillo County.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Governor Grisham’s rash directive targets even licensed concealed carriers. In an era where citizens are encouraged to be more self-reliant for their safety and well-being, such decrees seem wildly out of touch with the core values upon which the nation was founded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;D.A. Bregman, standing as a beacon for constitutional rights and the Second Amendment, stated, “As an officer of the court, I cannot and will not enforce something that is clearly unconstitutional.” He further emphasized that his office would remain dedicated to pursuing actual criminals who misuse firearms for illegal endeavors, rather than infringing upon law-abiding citizens’ rights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Echoing this sentiment of upholding foundational American rights, New Mexico state rep. John Block (R) fired back at Grisham’s order, rallying for her impeachment and receiving vocal support: “Impeach and remove Lujan Grisham. We even have Elon behind us on this!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adding weight to the collective rejection of this ill-conceived ban, Albuquerque police chief Harold Medina unequivocally stated that he would not be enforcing the governor’s order.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overarching message? The people of Albuquerque, their representatives, and their law enforcement, stand united against what they see as tyranny and infringement on their constitutional rights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, the National Association of Gun Rights is taking the fight directly to the courts, having already filed a lawsuit in a U.S. District Court in New Mexico against the ban. The battle for Second Amendment rights is alive and well, with Albuquerque at its forefront, championing the cause.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a triumphant move for American freedoms and rights, Bernalillo County District Attorney Sam Bregman declared on Saturday that he would not enforce New Mexico Gov. Michelle Lujan Grisham’s (D) 30-day ban on concealed carry. This shocking, yet commendable act of defiance came swiftly in response to the ban which had only taken effect on Saturday, September 8, 2023. The hastily-imposed prohibition not only prevents the concealed carrying of handguns but also bars open carry, effectively disarming lawful citizens in places such as Albuquerque, located in Bernalillo County. Governor Grisham’s rash directive targets even licensed concealed carriers. In an era where citizens are encouraged to be more self-reliant for their safety and well-being, such decrees seem wildly out of touch with the core values upon which the nation was founded. D.A. Bregman, standing as a beacon for constitutional rights and the Second Amendment, stated, “As an officer of the court, I cannot and will not enforce something that is clearly unconstitutional.” He further emphasized that his office would remain dedicated to pursuing actual criminals who misuse firearms for illegal endeavors, rather than infringing upon law-abiding citizens’ rights. Echoing this sentiment of upholding foundational American rights, New Mexico state rep. John Block (R) fired back at Grisham’s order, rallying for her impeachment and receiving vocal support: “Impeach and remove Lujan Grisham. We even have Elon behind us on this!” Adding weight to the collective rejection of this ill-conceived ban, Albuquerque police chief Harold Medina unequivocally stated that he would not be enforcing the governor’s order. The overarching message? The people of Albuquerque, their representatives, and their law enforcement, stand united against what they see as tyranny and infringement on their constitutional rights. Furthermore, the National Association of Gun Rights is taking the fight directly to the courts, having already filed a lawsuit in a U.S. District Court in New Mexico against the ban. The battle for Second Amendment rights is alive and well, with Albuquerque at its forefront, championing the cause.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Military Recruitment Crisis - Beyond the ‘Woke’ Controversy</title><link href="/news/2023/09/11/Military-Recruitment/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Military Recruitment Crisis - Beyond the ‘Woke’ Controversy" /><published>2023-09-11T07:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-11T07:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/11/Military-Recruitment</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/11/Military-Recruitment/">&lt;p&gt;While claims circulate that “woke” Pentagon policies are amplifying the U.S. military’s recruitment challenge, experts suggest that the issue might be deeper and more systemic. The politicization of the military and the current state of the labor market, among other factors, seem to be more significant drivers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;declining-pool-of-potential-recruits&quot;&gt;Declining Pool of Potential Recruits&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Peter Feaver, a distinguished professor at Duke University and ex-member of the National Security Council, points out that concerns about “woke” policies have been overly emphasized. He highlights underlying problems such as the shrinking pool of eligible young Americans. Health issues, drug use, and obesity have led to a reduced pool of potential recruits compared to two years ago.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Feaver’s recent publication, “Thanks For Your Service,” delves into the waning public trust in the military. Despite the military’s 60% public confidence as per a recent Gallup poll, this figure represents the lowest since 1997 and is a disturbing trend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;politics-at-play&quot;&gt;Politics at Play?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Feaver believes that a significant share of the declining confidence can be attributed to politics. Claims of the military becoming “woke” have perhaps added fuel to this fire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Army Secretary Christine Wormuth has voiced concerns over the damaging image the military has received from its critics. Wormuth highlights how criticisms surrounding a “woke military” might have inadvertently influenced recruiting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prominent political figures, such as Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis, have criticized the Pentagon’s newly introduced diversity, equity, and inclusion programs, suggesting that they have resulted in recruitment setbacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-balanced-perspective&quot;&gt;A Balanced Perspective&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it’s essential to strike a balance. Feaver indicates that while some progressive talking points might permeate military training, it’s only a fraction of the military’s overall training focus. The narrative of the military facing a “woke” or extremist issue may not be as pervasive as projected.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Feaver emphasizes the importance of refraining from hyperbole when discussing the military. He suggests granting the military “non-combatant immunity in the culture wars,” allowing for a more nuanced, less politically charged conversation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;looking-forward&quot;&gt;Looking Forward&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Feaver underscores the broader challenges that the military faces in recruitment. The appeal of the civilian job market and the sacrifices associated with military service make recruitment inherently challenging.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But as Feaver notes, politicizing the military only exacerbates an already complex issue. While adjusting rhetoric can help, a holistic approach, understanding the myriad of underlying challenges, will be crucial for the future of U.S. military recruitment.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">While claims circulate that “woke” Pentagon policies are amplifying the U.S. military’s recruitment challenge, experts suggest that the issue might be deeper and more systemic. The politicization of the military and the current state of the labor market, among other factors, seem to be more significant drivers. Declining Pool of Potential Recruits Peter Feaver, a distinguished professor at Duke University and ex-member of the National Security Council, points out that concerns about “woke” policies have been overly emphasized. He highlights underlying problems such as the shrinking pool of eligible young Americans. Health issues, drug use, and obesity have led to a reduced pool of potential recruits compared to two years ago. Feaver’s recent publication, “Thanks For Your Service,” delves into the waning public trust in the military. Despite the military’s 60% public confidence as per a recent Gallup poll, this figure represents the lowest since 1997 and is a disturbing trend. Politics at Play? Feaver believes that a significant share of the declining confidence can be attributed to politics. Claims of the military becoming “woke” have perhaps added fuel to this fire. Army Secretary Christine Wormuth has voiced concerns over the damaging image the military has received from its critics. Wormuth highlights how criticisms surrounding a “woke military” might have inadvertently influenced recruiting. Prominent political figures, such as Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis, have criticized the Pentagon’s newly introduced diversity, equity, and inclusion programs, suggesting that they have resulted in recruitment setbacks. A Balanced Perspective However, it’s essential to strike a balance. Feaver indicates that while some progressive talking points might permeate military training, it’s only a fraction of the military’s overall training focus. The narrative of the military facing a “woke” or extremist issue may not be as pervasive as projected. Feaver emphasizes the importance of refraining from hyperbole when discussing the military. He suggests granting the military “non-combatant immunity in the culture wars,” allowing for a more nuanced, less politically charged conversation. Looking Forward Feaver underscores the broader challenges that the military faces in recruitment. The appeal of the civilian job market and the sacrifices associated with military service make recruitment inherently challenging. But as Feaver notes, politicizing the military only exacerbates an already complex issue. While adjusting rhetoric can help, a holistic approach, understanding the myriad of underlying challenges, will be crucial for the future of U.S. military recruitment.</summary></entry></feed>