<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-10-29T14:18:31-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/29/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-29T14:18:31-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-29T14:18:31-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/29/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/29/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/29/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-29T14:18:31-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-29T14:18:31-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/29/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/29/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/">&lt;p&gt;Recent surprise attacks by Hamas on Israel has fueled ongoing tensions between staunchly conservative commentators and the progressive “Squad” Democrats known for criticizing Israel. The intensity of the backlash highlights the deep political divide over foreign policy in the Middle East.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Hamas’ shocking attack, several members of the “Squad,” including Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.), called for a “ceasefire and de-escalation,” condemning the violence. The absence of a statement from Rep. Rashida Tlaib (D-Mich.) was notably called out by conservative media outlets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;South Carolina GOP Rep. Nancy Mace quickly labeled Ocasio-Cortez a “Hamas apologist” in response to her call for peace and de-escalation. Rep. Ilhan Omar (D-Minn.), no stranger to controversy surrounding her views on Israel, echoed the call for de-escalation and ceasefire. Omar’s prior statements comparing the US and Israel to terrorist groups like Hamas and the Taliban resurfaced in the debate, fueling more criticisms. Omar’s 2019 tweet, where she opined that “Israel has hypnotized the world,” also continues to haunt her political career, often cited by critics to challenge her stance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conservative commentators have been especially vocal. “FOX &amp;amp; Friends Weekend” co-host Rachel Campos-Duffy took aim at Omar, saying she fails to recognize the peace in the Middle East under Trump’s administration. Conservative pundit John Hasson also called out Omar, claiming she insinuated that attacks on IDF forces were acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Massachusetts Democrat Rep. Ayanna Pressley’s concerns over the “devastating attacks on Israelis” were met with skepticism. A prominent conservative online personality, Comfortably Smug, accused the “Squad” of advising Israel to back down after the nation suffered massive attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Jamaal Bowman’s call for an end to the Gaza blockade, in addition to condemning the Hamas attacks, was met with criticism from conservative radio host Jason Rantz. He accused Bowman of pairing his condemnation of terrorism with unwarranted criticisms of Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Cori Bush emphasized the urgent need for a ceasefire, while pushing for an end to “U.S. support for Israeli military occupation and apartheid.” Defense attorney Marina Medvin criticized Bush, suggesting that she equates the death of Palestinian terrorists to the horrific acts committed against Jewish civilians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amidst the political turmoil and intense debate, the attacks have taken a heavy toll. Israeli media report over 300 dead due to the wide-ranging assault. Gaza health officials note that at least 200 Palestinians have perished in the retaliatory Israeli air strikes following the initial Hamas attack. As the situation remains volatile, both sides continue to count their casualties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This divisive issue showcases the challenge America faces in crafting a unified approach to foreign policy, with deeply entrenched political divides at play. As the situation develops, the debate is bound to intensify, shedding light on the complexities of U.S. politics in the global arena.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump’s Pledge of Power: A Commitment to Israel’s Safety and American Strength</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/29/Trump-Israel-Strength/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump’s Pledge of Power: A Commitment to Israel’s Safety and American Strength" /><published>2023-10-29T13:23:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-29T13:23:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/29/Trump-Israel-Strength</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/29/Trump-Israel-Strength/">&lt;p&gt;In a rousing address to the Republican Jewish Coalition on Saturday, former President Donald Trump fiercely criticized President Joe Biden’s foreign policies, accusing him of “weakness” and endangering global stability. Trump vowed a robust American stance against Hamas and any threats to Israel, promising a return to strength and decisiveness if he reclaims the presidency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump’s speech, live-streamed to a nationwide audience, laid out a clear vision for American-Israeli relations, contrasting his administration’s unwavering support for Israel with what he perceives as Biden’s faltering resolve. “When I am back in the White House, the United States will stand with Israel all the way — without hesitation, without qualification, and without apology,” Trump declared, setting a tone of determination and solidarity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This address comes at a critical time, as antisemitic attacks surge globally, and the situation in the Middle East remains volatile. Trump emphasized the need for unequivocal strength, stating, “Evil only respects one thing: unyielding strength. You’ve got to be strong. Otherwise, they’re going to be taking over.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SEO keywords such as “Trump,” “Israel,” “Hamas,” “American strength,” and “presidential commitment” were prominent throughout the speech, reflecting a strategic approach to online visibility and engagement. By aligning his potential future presidency with unwavering support for Israel and a strong retaliatory stance against terrorist attacks, Trump taps into key voter concerns and solidifies his position as a candidate of strength.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump did not hold back in his critique of Biden, blaming the current administration for the recent attack on Israel and the escalation of global tensions. “Joe Biden’s weakness caused the attack on Israel. Pure weakness and incompetence. Everywhere he goes, Biden’s weakness provokes war and death,” Trump asserted, positioning himself as the antidote to perceived current weaknesses in American foreign policy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The former president’s promises extended beyond verbal support, directly addressing the threat posed by Hamas. “When I am back in the White House, America’s enemies will know once again — and they’re going to know it — that if you try to kill our citizens, we kill you. If you spill a drop of American blood, we spill a gallon of yours,” he stated, establishing a clear and unambiguous policy of retaliation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump’s speech serves as a powerful call to action, rallying support for a strong America and a secure Israel. As the country navigates these uncertain times, Trump’s words resonate with those seeking a return to strength and decisiveness on the world stage, positioning him as a key player in the ongoing political narrative. His commitment to Israel and pledge to uphold American strength mark a significant moment in the lead-up to the 2024 presidential election, as voters consider the direction they want for the country and its place in the world.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a rousing address to the Republican Jewish Coalition on Saturday, former President Donald Trump fiercely criticized President Joe Biden’s foreign policies, accusing him of “weakness” and endangering global stability. Trump vowed a robust American stance against Hamas and any threats to Israel, promising a return to strength and decisiveness if he reclaims the presidency. Trump’s speech, live-streamed to a nationwide audience, laid out a clear vision for American-Israeli relations, contrasting his administration’s unwavering support for Israel with what he perceives as Biden’s faltering resolve. “When I am back in the White House, the United States will stand with Israel all the way — without hesitation, without qualification, and without apology,” Trump declared, setting a tone of determination and solidarity. This address comes at a critical time, as antisemitic attacks surge globally, and the situation in the Middle East remains volatile. Trump emphasized the need for unequivocal strength, stating, “Evil only respects one thing: unyielding strength. You’ve got to be strong. Otherwise, they’re going to be taking over.” SEO keywords such as “Trump,” “Israel,” “Hamas,” “American strength,” and “presidential commitment” were prominent throughout the speech, reflecting a strategic approach to online visibility and engagement. By aligning his potential future presidency with unwavering support for Israel and a strong retaliatory stance against terrorist attacks, Trump taps into key voter concerns and solidifies his position as a candidate of strength. Trump did not hold back in his critique of Biden, blaming the current administration for the recent attack on Israel and the escalation of global tensions. “Joe Biden’s weakness caused the attack on Israel. Pure weakness and incompetence. Everywhere he goes, Biden’s weakness provokes war and death,” Trump asserted, positioning himself as the antidote to perceived current weaknesses in American foreign policy. The former president’s promises extended beyond verbal support, directly addressing the threat posed by Hamas. “When I am back in the White House, America’s enemies will know once again — and they’re going to know it — that if you try to kill our citizens, we kill you. If you spill a drop of American blood, we spill a gallon of yours,” he stated, establishing a clear and unambiguous policy of retaliation. Trump’s speech serves as a powerful call to action, rallying support for a strong America and a secure Israel. As the country navigates these uncertain times, Trump’s words resonate with those seeking a return to strength and decisiveness on the world stage, positioning him as a key player in the ongoing political narrative. His commitment to Israel and pledge to uphold American strength mark a significant moment in the lead-up to the 2024 presidential election, as voters consider the direction they want for the country and its place in the world.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Remembering Matthew Perry: A Legacy of Laughter and Struggle</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/29/Matthew-Perry-Tribute/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Remembering Matthew Perry: A Legacy of Laughter and Struggle" /><published>2023-10-29T12:18:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-29T12:18:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/29/Matthew-Perry-Tribute</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/29/Matthew-Perry-Tribute/">&lt;p&gt;Hollywood is in mourning as news breaks of the sudden death of Matthew Perry, a comedic genius who brought laughter to millions as Chandler Bing on the iconic sitcom ‘Friends.’ Perry was found dead at the age of 54 in an L.A.-area home, sparking an outpour of tributes and heartfelt messages from fans and fellow celebrities alike.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Matthew Perry’s portrayal of the sarcastic, quick-witted Chandler Bing made him a household name and solidified his place in the pantheon of television’s greatest actors. For ten seasons, Perry’s impeccable timing and unique delivery brought to life a character that resonated with audiences worldwide, turning ‘Friends’ into a cultural phenomenon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While ‘Friends’ showcased Perry’s comedic prowess, it also masked the personal struggles he faced off-screen. Perry’s battle with addiction was a well-kept secret, a dark contrast to the laughter and joy he brought to living rooms across the globe. In his memoir, “Friends, Lovers and the Big Terrible Thing,” Perry opened up about his addictions and the immense pressure he felt to perform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I felt like I was gonna die if the live audience didn’t laugh, and that’s not healthy for sure,” Perry wrote. His candor and vulnerability in sharing his struggles have been a source of inspiration for many facing similar battles, showcasing the human side of a man who seemed to have it all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perry’s career extended beyond ‘Friends,’ with notable roles in films such as “Fools Rush In” and “The Whole Nine Yards,” as well as a memorable stint on “The West Wing.” Despite his success in various roles, Perry never quite escaped the shadow of Chandler Bing, a testament to the indelible mark he left on the world of television.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As fans and colleagues remember Matthew Perry, they celebrate not just the laughter he brought into their lives, but also his resilience in facing his demons. Perry’s legacy is one of brilliance and bravery, a man who made the world laugh while fighting his own battles in silence. He will be remembered as a comedic icon, a friend to millions, and a brave soul who was unafraid to share his story in the hopes of helping others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world has lost a true legend, but Matthew Perry’s legacy of laughter and strength will live on, a testament to the power of comedy to bring joy even in the darkest of times.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Hollywood is in mourning as news breaks of the sudden death of Matthew Perry, a comedic genius who brought laughter to millions as Chandler Bing on the iconic sitcom ‘Friends.’ Perry was found dead at the age of 54 in an L.A.-area home, sparking an outpour of tributes and heartfelt messages from fans and fellow celebrities alike. Matthew Perry’s portrayal of the sarcastic, quick-witted Chandler Bing made him a household name and solidified his place in the pantheon of television’s greatest actors. For ten seasons, Perry’s impeccable timing and unique delivery brought to life a character that resonated with audiences worldwide, turning ‘Friends’ into a cultural phenomenon. While ‘Friends’ showcased Perry’s comedic prowess, it also masked the personal struggles he faced off-screen. Perry’s battle with addiction was a well-kept secret, a dark contrast to the laughter and joy he brought to living rooms across the globe. In his memoir, “Friends, Lovers and the Big Terrible Thing,” Perry opened up about his addictions and the immense pressure he felt to perform. “I felt like I was gonna die if the live audience didn’t laugh, and that’s not healthy for sure,” Perry wrote. His candor and vulnerability in sharing his struggles have been a source of inspiration for many facing similar battles, showcasing the human side of a man who seemed to have it all. Perry’s career extended beyond ‘Friends,’ with notable roles in films such as “Fools Rush In” and “The Whole Nine Yards,” as well as a memorable stint on “The West Wing.” Despite his success in various roles, Perry never quite escaped the shadow of Chandler Bing, a testament to the indelible mark he left on the world of television. As fans and colleagues remember Matthew Perry, they celebrate not just the laughter he brought into their lives, but also his resilience in facing his demons. Perry’s legacy is one of brilliance and bravery, a man who made the world laugh while fighting his own battles in silence. He will be remembered as a comedic icon, a friend to millions, and a brave soul who was unafraid to share his story in the hopes of helping others. The world has lost a true legend, but Matthew Perry’s legacy of laughter and strength will live on, a testament to the power of comedy to bring joy even in the darkest of times.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">National Security Prioritized: U.S. Halts Most Civilian Firearm Exports</title><link href="/news/2023/10/29/Firearm-Exports-Halted/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="National Security Prioritized: U.S. Halts Most Civilian Firearm Exports" /><published>2023-10-29T11:09:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-29T11:09:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/29/Firearm-Exports-Halted</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/29/Firearm-Exports-Halted/">&lt;p&gt;In a surprise move the U.S. Department of Commerce has announced a 90-day halt on the majority of civilian firearm exports. This temporary freeze is a strategic measure, ensuring that U.S. arms do not inadvertently contribute to regional instability, human rights violations, or criminal activities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The temporary suspension will impact most civilian export licenses, allowing authorities adequate time to assess potential risks and implications associated with firearm exports. This decisive action reflects the government’s dedication to safeguarding national security and promoting global stability. However, it’s crucial to note that the ban does not extend to around 40 countries, including Israel and Ukraine, which have separate export agreements for firearms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;U.S. firearms companies like Sturm Ruger &amp;amp; Co., Vista Outdoor, and Smith &amp;amp; Wesson Brands could feel the impact of this temporary halt, as it could potentially disrupt their international sales and operations. As a significant player in the global arms market, the U.S.’s temporary halt is a clear signal of the government’s willingness to prioritize security over profits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Global government clients seeking to acquire firearms during this period must provide comprehensive details about the end recipients of the firearms. The Commerce Department is standing firm, stating that any government applications lacking explicit end-user details will be returned “without action.” Civilian license applications will also be “held without action,” ensuring a meticulous and accountable process during this critical period.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This temporary halt is a call to arms for responsible trade and accountability in the arms industry. It sends a strong message about the U.S. government’s commitment to preventing the misuse of firearms and ensuring they do not contribute to global instability or human rights abuses. This move is expected to establish a precedent for responsible and secure trade practices in the international arms market, fostering a safer and more stable global environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, the U.S. Department of Commerce’s bold decision to temporarily halt most civilian firearm exports highlights the country’s unwavering commitment to national security and global stability. This strategic pause ensures the U.S. arms exports do not contribute to violence or instability, setting a new standard for responsible governance and secure trade practices in the international arms trade.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a surprise move the U.S. Department of Commerce has announced a 90-day halt on the majority of civilian firearm exports. This temporary freeze is a strategic measure, ensuring that U.S. arms do not inadvertently contribute to regional instability, human rights violations, or criminal activities. The temporary suspension will impact most civilian export licenses, allowing authorities adequate time to assess potential risks and implications associated with firearm exports. This decisive action reflects the government’s dedication to safeguarding national security and promoting global stability. However, it’s crucial to note that the ban does not extend to around 40 countries, including Israel and Ukraine, which have separate export agreements for firearms. U.S. firearms companies like Sturm Ruger &amp;amp; Co., Vista Outdoor, and Smith &amp;amp; Wesson Brands could feel the impact of this temporary halt, as it could potentially disrupt their international sales and operations. As a significant player in the global arms market, the U.S.’s temporary halt is a clear signal of the government’s willingness to prioritize security over profits. Global government clients seeking to acquire firearms during this period must provide comprehensive details about the end recipients of the firearms. The Commerce Department is standing firm, stating that any government applications lacking explicit end-user details will be returned “without action.” Civilian license applications will also be “held without action,” ensuring a meticulous and accountable process during this critical period. This temporary halt is a call to arms for responsible trade and accountability in the arms industry. It sends a strong message about the U.S. government’s commitment to preventing the misuse of firearms and ensuring they do not contribute to global instability or human rights abuses. This move is expected to establish a precedent for responsible and secure trade practices in the international arms market, fostering a safer and more stable global environment. In conclusion, the U.S. Department of Commerce’s bold decision to temporarily halt most civilian firearm exports highlights the country’s unwavering commitment to national security and global stability. This strategic pause ensures the U.S. arms exports do not contribute to violence or instability, setting a new standard for responsible governance and secure trade practices in the international arms trade.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A Call to Action: The Imperative for Strong Borders and an Unyielding Anti-Terror Stance</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/28/Strong-Borders-Anti-Terror-Stance/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Call to Action: The Imperative for Strong Borders and an Unyielding Anti-Terror Stance" /><published>2023-10-28T18:59:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-28T18:59:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/28/Strong-Borders-Anti-Terror-Stance</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/28/Strong-Borders-Anti-Terror-Stance/">&lt;p&gt;In a bold statement Rep. Buddy Carter, R-Ga., underscored the paramount importance of enforcing stringent border security measures and maintaining a relentless stance against terrorism within the halls of Congress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Carter was unequivocal in his message: “Look, if you have ties to terrorist organizations or if you support terrorist organizations, there’s no place for you in the United States Congress, and you don’t need to be there.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The timely conversation comes in the wake of a resounding vote by the House to express steadfast support for Israel and to denounce Hamas in the strongest terms. With a vote tally of 412 in favor, 10 opposed, and 6 abstaining, the resolution was overwhelmingly supported by lawmakers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The resolution firmly positions the House alongside Israel in its defense against “the barbaric war launched by Hamas and other terrorists,” affirming Israel’s right to defend itself. Moreover, it delivers a sharp rebuke to Hamas, calling for an immediate cessation of violence and the release of hostages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Carter did not mince words in expressing his disappointment with the 10 members who chose not to back the resolution. He emphasized the near-unanimity of support, stating, “I’m very, very disappointed that these people who did not support this; this is obvious. It was overwhelming with only just a few of them who didn’t. … If you support terrorism, if you have ties to terrorism, there’s no place for you in the United States.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Addressing the issue of border security, Carter drew a direct connection to national security, expressing alarm at the ease with which individuals are currently able to cross the U.S.-Mexico border. He highlighted the potential for terrorists to exploit this vulnerability, stating, “Oh, no question about it. Listen, that is a porous border. I mean, people are crossing that; and we would be naive to think that they’re not terrorists who are coming across that border with the intention of hurting us.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He reinforced the idea that the primary responsibility of the federal government is to protect American soil, a task he believes can only be accomplished through robust and secure borders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Carter did not hold back in his critique of the current administration’s approach to border security, asserting, “This administration is just ridiculous in what they’re doing right now. They are not doing anything at all to protect us, and we’re just welcoming in people who truly do want to hurt us.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He concluded with a call to action, underscoring the urgency of strengthening our borders to ensure the safety and security of the United States.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a bold statement Rep. Buddy Carter, R-Ga., underscored the paramount importance of enforcing stringent border security measures and maintaining a relentless stance against terrorism within the halls of Congress. Carter was unequivocal in his message: “Look, if you have ties to terrorist organizations or if you support terrorist organizations, there’s no place for you in the United States Congress, and you don’t need to be there.” The timely conversation comes in the wake of a resounding vote by the House to express steadfast support for Israel and to denounce Hamas in the strongest terms. With a vote tally of 412 in favor, 10 opposed, and 6 abstaining, the resolution was overwhelmingly supported by lawmakers. The resolution firmly positions the House alongside Israel in its defense against “the barbaric war launched by Hamas and other terrorists,” affirming Israel’s right to defend itself. Moreover, it delivers a sharp rebuke to Hamas, calling for an immediate cessation of violence and the release of hostages. Carter did not mince words in expressing his disappointment with the 10 members who chose not to back the resolution. He emphasized the near-unanimity of support, stating, “I’m very, very disappointed that these people who did not support this; this is obvious. It was overwhelming with only just a few of them who didn’t. … If you support terrorism, if you have ties to terrorism, there’s no place for you in the United States.” Addressing the issue of border security, Carter drew a direct connection to national security, expressing alarm at the ease with which individuals are currently able to cross the U.S.-Mexico border. He highlighted the potential for terrorists to exploit this vulnerability, stating, “Oh, no question about it. Listen, that is a porous border. I mean, people are crossing that; and we would be naive to think that they’re not terrorists who are coming across that border with the intention of hurting us.” He reinforced the idea that the primary responsibility of the federal government is to protect American soil, a task he believes can only be accomplished through robust and secure borders. Carter did not hold back in his critique of the current administration’s approach to border security, asserting, “This administration is just ridiculous in what they’re doing right now. They are not doing anything at all to protect us, and we’re just welcoming in people who truly do want to hurt us.” He concluded with a call to action, underscoring the urgency of strengthening our borders to ensure the safety and security of the United States.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Shocking Revelation: The Hidden Costs of Electric Vehicles Unveiled</title><link href="/news/2023/10/28/Electric-Vehicle-True-Costs/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Shocking Revelation: The Hidden Costs of Electric Vehicles Unveiled" /><published>2023-10-28T17:52:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-28T17:52:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/28/Electric-Vehicle-True-Costs</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/28/Electric-Vehicle-True-Costs/">&lt;p&gt;In a ground-breaking study recently released by the Texas Public Policy Foundation, researchers have exposed what they believe to be the true costs of fueling electric vehicles (EVs), significantly challenging the popular narratives surrounding the cost-effectiveness of EVs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Authored by Brent Bennett and Jason Isaac, the report titled “Overcharged Expectations: Unmasking the True Costs of Electric Vehicles,” delves deep into the direct and indirect costs associated with EV ownership. While many EV advocates loudly proclaim the affordability of electric vehicles, citing costs equivalent to $1.21 per gallon of gasoline, this study brings to light a startlingly different picture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The authors argue that when you factor in the cost of charging equipment and losses over a period of 10 years and 120,000 miles, an additional $1.38 per gallon equivalent needs to be added. Furthermore, when the costs of subsidies are included, the actual cost of fueling an electric vehicle skyrockets to a staggering $17.33 per gallon of gasoline equivalent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The study scrutinizes the role of U.S. government regulations, such as the Corporate Average Fuel Economy (CAFE) and Greenhouse Gas (GHG) emissions standards, in indirectly financing the growth of the EV market. Automakers are left with no choice but to conform to these standards, often resulting in a push towards manufacturing more EVs, or purchasing credits from compliant companies. This scenario introduces hidden costs to traditional gasoline and diesel vehicles, which the study argues are often overlooked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The authors pose a crucial question: “When an EV owner connects to the electric grid, how much are they paying for the extra generation, transmission, and distribution costs that they are imposing on the grid, and will those embedded costs rise over time?” They conclude that the EV industry, buoyed by federal government support and regulations pushing for more EV production, is masking the true costs of EV ownership.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In summary, the study provides a conservative estimate that the average EV accrues $48,698 in subsidies and an additional $4,569 in charging and electricity costs over a decade. This results in a total cost of $53,267, equating to $16.12 per gallon of gasoline equivalent. The stark reality, according to the authors, is that without continued and substantial government support, electric vehicles will remain more expensive than internal combustion engine vehicles for many years to come.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This eye-opening report urges consumers, policymakers, and industry stakeholders to reevaluate the true costs of electric vehicle ownership, ensuring that decisions are made based on comprehensive and transparent information.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a ground-breaking study recently released by the Texas Public Policy Foundation, researchers have exposed what they believe to be the true costs of fueling electric vehicles (EVs), significantly challenging the popular narratives surrounding the cost-effectiveness of EVs. Authored by Brent Bennett and Jason Isaac, the report titled “Overcharged Expectations: Unmasking the True Costs of Electric Vehicles,” delves deep into the direct and indirect costs associated with EV ownership. While many EV advocates loudly proclaim the affordability of electric vehicles, citing costs equivalent to $1.21 per gallon of gasoline, this study brings to light a startlingly different picture. The authors argue that when you factor in the cost of charging equipment and losses over a period of 10 years and 120,000 miles, an additional $1.38 per gallon equivalent needs to be added. Furthermore, when the costs of subsidies are included, the actual cost of fueling an electric vehicle skyrockets to a staggering $17.33 per gallon of gasoline equivalent. The study scrutinizes the role of U.S. government regulations, such as the Corporate Average Fuel Economy (CAFE) and Greenhouse Gas (GHG) emissions standards, in indirectly financing the growth of the EV market. Automakers are left with no choice but to conform to these standards, often resulting in a push towards manufacturing more EVs, or purchasing credits from compliant companies. This scenario introduces hidden costs to traditional gasoline and diesel vehicles, which the study argues are often overlooked. The authors pose a crucial question: “When an EV owner connects to the electric grid, how much are they paying for the extra generation, transmission, and distribution costs that they are imposing on the grid, and will those embedded costs rise over time?” They conclude that the EV industry, buoyed by federal government support and regulations pushing for more EV production, is masking the true costs of EV ownership. In summary, the study provides a conservative estimate that the average EV accrues $48,698 in subsidies and an additional $4,569 in charging and electricity costs over a decade. This results in a total cost of $53,267, equating to $16.12 per gallon of gasoline equivalent. The stark reality, according to the authors, is that without continued and substantial government support, electric vehicles will remain more expensive than internal combustion engine vehicles for many years to come. This eye-opening report urges consumers, policymakers, and industry stakeholders to reevaluate the true costs of electric vehicle ownership, ensuring that decisions are made based on comprehensive and transparent information.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Uncovering the Truth: House Speaker Johnson Takes Charge in Biden Impeachment Inquiry</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/28/House-Speaker-Johnson-Biden-Impeachment/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Uncovering the Truth: House Speaker Johnson Takes Charge in Biden Impeachment Inquiry" /><published>2023-10-28T16:47:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-28T16:47:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/28/House-Speaker-Johnson-Biden-Impeachment</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/28/House-Speaker-Johnson-Biden-Impeachment/">&lt;p&gt;In a powerful move this week, newly elected House Speaker Mike Johnson declared a steadfast commitment to transparency and the rule of law, as he announced the continuation of the impeachment inquiry against President Joe Biden. This bold assertion comes amidst growing concerns over the President’s cognitive abilities and his alleged involvement in Hunter Biden’s business transactions, bringing the nation’s attention to Capitol Hill.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaker Johnson, a respected constitutional lawyer and Louisiana Republican, has stepped into his new role with a determination to uphold the integrity of the Congressional investigation. “We are the rule of law team,” he stated, emphasizing the need for a methodical approach to the ongoing impeachment inquiry initiated by his predecessor, Kevin McCarthy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The focus of the investigation surrounds President Biden’s potential cover-up of his involvement in Hunter Biden’s business dealings, a matter that has drawn significant public interest and raised questions about the ethical standards of the nation’s highest office. Speaker Johnson, with his legal background and experience on the House Judiciary Committee, brings a critical eye to the proceedings, ensuring a thorough and unbiased exploration of the facts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the impeachment inquiry unfolds, House Republicans are diligently collecting evidence and following leads, with Johnson highlighting the importance of bank records in uncovering the truth. “Bank records don’t lie,” he noted, underscoring the importance of financial transparency in the investigation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Speaker’s commitment to accountability resonates with many Americans, as he assures the public that the process will be conducted in an “appropriate and constitutional manner.” Johnson’s role in the impeachment defense team for former President Trump in 2020 further positions him as a key figure in the political landscape, with firsthand experience of the challenges and responsibilities that come with such high-stakes investigations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the midst of these serious allegations and the ongoing inquiry, Johnson maintains a professional rapport with President Biden, emphasizing that the investigation is not a personal vendetta but a necessary pursuit of truth and accountability. The American people, he believes, deserve nothing less.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The House Speaker’s strong stance and dedication to due process have set the stage for a comprehensive investigation, with Johnson at the helm, guiding the inquiry with a steady hand and a commitment to uncovering the truth. As the nation watches, the Speaker’s actions and decisions in the coming weeks will be crucial in shaping the course of this high-profile investigation and ensuring that justice is served.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Biden impeachment inquiry, led by key figures such as House Judiciary Committee Chairman Jim Jordan, Oversight Committee Chairman James Comer, and Ways &amp;amp; Means Committee Chairman Jason Smith, is a pivotal moment in American politics. With Speaker Johnson’s leadership, the investigation is poised to be a thorough and transparent examination of the facts, bringing clarity to the allegations against President Biden and upholding the principles of accountability and justice.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a powerful move this week, newly elected House Speaker Mike Johnson declared a steadfast commitment to transparency and the rule of law, as he announced the continuation of the impeachment inquiry against President Joe Biden. This bold assertion comes amidst growing concerns over the President’s cognitive abilities and his alleged involvement in Hunter Biden’s business transactions, bringing the nation’s attention to Capitol Hill. Speaker Johnson, a respected constitutional lawyer and Louisiana Republican, has stepped into his new role with a determination to uphold the integrity of the Congressional investigation. “We are the rule of law team,” he stated, emphasizing the need for a methodical approach to the ongoing impeachment inquiry initiated by his predecessor, Kevin McCarthy. The focus of the investigation surrounds President Biden’s potential cover-up of his involvement in Hunter Biden’s business dealings, a matter that has drawn significant public interest and raised questions about the ethical standards of the nation’s highest office. Speaker Johnson, with his legal background and experience on the House Judiciary Committee, brings a critical eye to the proceedings, ensuring a thorough and unbiased exploration of the facts. As the impeachment inquiry unfolds, House Republicans are diligently collecting evidence and following leads, with Johnson highlighting the importance of bank records in uncovering the truth. “Bank records don’t lie,” he noted, underscoring the importance of financial transparency in the investigation. The Speaker’s commitment to accountability resonates with many Americans, as he assures the public that the process will be conducted in an “appropriate and constitutional manner.” Johnson’s role in the impeachment defense team for former President Trump in 2020 further positions him as a key figure in the political landscape, with firsthand experience of the challenges and responsibilities that come with such high-stakes investigations. In the midst of these serious allegations and the ongoing inquiry, Johnson maintains a professional rapport with President Biden, emphasizing that the investigation is not a personal vendetta but a necessary pursuit of truth and accountability. The American people, he believes, deserve nothing less. The House Speaker’s strong stance and dedication to due process have set the stage for a comprehensive investigation, with Johnson at the helm, guiding the inquiry with a steady hand and a commitment to uncovering the truth. As the nation watches, the Speaker’s actions and decisions in the coming weeks will be crucial in shaping the course of this high-profile investigation and ensuring that justice is served. The Biden impeachment inquiry, led by key figures such as House Judiciary Committee Chairman Jim Jordan, Oversight Committee Chairman James Comer, and Ways &amp;amp; Means Committee Chairman Jason Smith, is a pivotal moment in American politics. With Speaker Johnson’s leadership, the investigation is poised to be a thorough and transparent examination of the facts, bringing clarity to the allegations against President Biden and upholding the principles of accountability and justice.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Kanye West Demands Jewish Adidas Executive to Kiss Hitler Photo: Inside the Disturbing Partnership</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/28/Kanye-West-Adidas-Controversy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Kanye West Demands Jewish Adidas Executive to Kiss Hitler Photo: Inside the Disturbing Partnership" /><published>2023-10-28T15:36:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-28T15:36:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/28/Kanye-West-Adidas-Controversy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/28/Kanye-West-Adidas-Controversy/">&lt;p&gt;Kanye West, also known as Ye, has been a dominant figure in the music and fashion industries, with his unique style and outspoken personality capturing the public’s attention. However, a new report from the New York Times has brought to light a darker side of the rapper’s actions, particularly during his partnership with Adidas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The report details disturbing incidents, including West’s demand for a Jewish Adidas executive to kiss a photo of Adolf Hitler. This revelation adds another layer to the understanding of why Adidas decided to sever ties with the artist last year, initially thought to be a response to his public antisemitic outbursts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kanye’s partnership with Adidas, which began in 2013, was mutually beneficial for a time, with soaring profits and West’s brand Yeezys contributing significantly to his billionaire status. However, the report reveals that the company had been dealing with West’s erratic and troubling behavior for nearly a decade, often adapting to his demands and mood swings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the most alarming revelations is an incident in 2013, where West, during a meeting at Adidas headquarters in Germany, drew a swastika on an Adidas sketch and told a Jewish executive to kiss a portrait of Hitler daily. He also expressed admiration for Hitler’s command of propaganda to Adidas employees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The report, based on interviews with current and former employees and a review of internal documents, paints a picture of a company struggling to manage their star partner’s behavior while reaping the financial rewards of the partnership. Top executives and managers reportedly had a group chat named “Yzy hotline” to discuss how to handle any chaos caused by West, comparing their strategy to firefighting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As Adidas grew more reliant on the Yeezy brand, West benefited significantly, receiving a 15 percent royalty on net sales, $15 million upfront, millions in company stock annually, and a $100 million annual fund for Yeezy marketing starting in 2019.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, when the partnership ended last year amidst public backlash against West’s actions, Adidas projected its first annual loss in decades, and West’s net worth took a hit. Despite this, Adidas and West had one more financial interaction, as Adidas released the remaining $1.3 billion worth of Yeezys, with a portion of the proceeds going to charity, but most of the money going back to Adidas and royalties to West.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This report highlights the complex and often troubling nature of celebrity partnerships, raising questions about the responsibility of companies to take a stand against harmful behavior, even when there are significant financial incentives at play.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Kanye West, also known as Ye, has been a dominant figure in the music and fashion industries, with his unique style and outspoken personality capturing the public’s attention. However, a new report from the New York Times has brought to light a darker side of the rapper’s actions, particularly during his partnership with Adidas. The report details disturbing incidents, including West’s demand for a Jewish Adidas executive to kiss a photo of Adolf Hitler. This revelation adds another layer to the understanding of why Adidas decided to sever ties with the artist last year, initially thought to be a response to his public antisemitic outbursts. Kanye’s partnership with Adidas, which began in 2013, was mutually beneficial for a time, with soaring profits and West’s brand Yeezys contributing significantly to his billionaire status. However, the report reveals that the company had been dealing with West’s erratic and troubling behavior for nearly a decade, often adapting to his demands and mood swings. One of the most alarming revelations is an incident in 2013, where West, during a meeting at Adidas headquarters in Germany, drew a swastika on an Adidas sketch and told a Jewish executive to kiss a portrait of Hitler daily. He also expressed admiration for Hitler’s command of propaganda to Adidas employees. The report, based on interviews with current and former employees and a review of internal documents, paints a picture of a company struggling to manage their star partner’s behavior while reaping the financial rewards of the partnership. Top executives and managers reportedly had a group chat named “Yzy hotline” to discuss how to handle any chaos caused by West, comparing their strategy to firefighting. As Adidas grew more reliant on the Yeezy brand, West benefited significantly, receiving a 15 percent royalty on net sales, $15 million upfront, millions in company stock annually, and a $100 million annual fund for Yeezy marketing starting in 2019. However, when the partnership ended last year amidst public backlash against West’s actions, Adidas projected its first annual loss in decades, and West’s net worth took a hit. Despite this, Adidas and West had one more financial interaction, as Adidas released the remaining $1.3 billion worth of Yeezys, with a portion of the proceeds going to charity, but most of the money going back to Adidas and royalties to West. This report highlights the complex and often troubling nature of celebrity partnerships, raising questions about the responsibility of companies to take a stand against harmful behavior, even when there are significant financial incentives at play.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Concerns Raised: Speaker Johnson Questions Biden’s Cognitive Abilities</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/28/Bidens-Cognitive-State/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Concerns Raised: Speaker Johnson Questions Biden’s Cognitive Abilities" /><published>2023-10-28T14:21:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-28T14:21:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/28/Bidens-Cognitive-State</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/28/Bidens-Cognitive-State/">&lt;p&gt;In a candid interview with Fox News, House Speaker Mike Johnson, R-La., has raised concerns about President Joe Biden’s cognitive abilities, sparking a nationwide conversation on the matter. Johnson’s comments follow his inaugural meeting with the President since taking up the role of House Speaker, setting a serious tone for their working relationship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Johnson, when asked by Fox News host Sean Hannity, did not shy away from admitting his concerns. “I do. I think most of us do,” he said, adding that his observations were not meant as a personal criticism but were based on noticeable changes in Biden’s speech patterns and abilities over the years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“This is not a personal slight to him. It has to do with age and acumen, and everyone’s different. Everyone ages differently,” Johnson emphasized, underlining the reality that cognitive abilities can vary from person to person, and change over time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To illustrate his point, Johnson compared Biden’s past performances in Senate Judiciary Committee speeches to his current speeches, highlighting a clear contrast. “Clearly, if you look at a tape of Joe Biden making an argument in the Senate Judiciary Committee a few years ago and you see a speech that he delivers now, there’s a difference,” he stated. “Again, it’s not a personal insult to him. It’s just reality.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the midst of discussing national security funding requests for Ukraine, Israel, and other initiatives with President Biden and House Minority Leader Hakeem Jeffries, D-N.Y., Johnson underscored the importance of separate appropriations bills. He also voiced the opposition of his caucus to bundling foreign aid, recalling their vote against a $40 billion aid package last year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While expressing his commitment to countering Russian President Vladimir Putin’s actions in Eastern Europe, Johnson remained skeptical of the proposed humanitarian aid to Gaza, controlled by Hamas, questioning the integrity of its use. “They use the Palestinians as shields; they don’t even provide the people with clean drinking water. We’re supposed to believe they’re going to use U.S. aid for humanitarian purposes. Count me as a skeptic,” he remarked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite his concerns about Biden’s cognitive state and skepticism over the proposed aid, Johnson maintained a respectful stance towards the President. “I have no problem with President Biden as an individual,” he told Hannity. “You respect the office: It’s a biblical admonition that you give honor where honor is due.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The conversation initiated by Johnson goes beyond political lines, touching on sensitive topics of age, cognitive abilities, and the expectations placed on public officials. As the nation grapples with these issues, the importance of respectful discourse and careful consideration becomes all the more evident.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a candid interview with Fox News, House Speaker Mike Johnson, R-La., has raised concerns about President Joe Biden’s cognitive abilities, sparking a nationwide conversation on the matter. Johnson’s comments follow his inaugural meeting with the President since taking up the role of House Speaker, setting a serious tone for their working relationship. Johnson, when asked by Fox News host Sean Hannity, did not shy away from admitting his concerns. “I do. I think most of us do,” he said, adding that his observations were not meant as a personal criticism but were based on noticeable changes in Biden’s speech patterns and abilities over the years. “This is not a personal slight to him. It has to do with age and acumen, and everyone’s different. Everyone ages differently,” Johnson emphasized, underlining the reality that cognitive abilities can vary from person to person, and change over time. To illustrate his point, Johnson compared Biden’s past performances in Senate Judiciary Committee speeches to his current speeches, highlighting a clear contrast. “Clearly, if you look at a tape of Joe Biden making an argument in the Senate Judiciary Committee a few years ago and you see a speech that he delivers now, there’s a difference,” he stated. “Again, it’s not a personal insult to him. It’s just reality.” In the midst of discussing national security funding requests for Ukraine, Israel, and other initiatives with President Biden and House Minority Leader Hakeem Jeffries, D-N.Y., Johnson underscored the importance of separate appropriations bills. He also voiced the opposition of his caucus to bundling foreign aid, recalling their vote against a $40 billion aid package last year. While expressing his commitment to countering Russian President Vladimir Putin’s actions in Eastern Europe, Johnson remained skeptical of the proposed humanitarian aid to Gaza, controlled by Hamas, questioning the integrity of its use. “They use the Palestinians as shields; they don’t even provide the people with clean drinking water. We’re supposed to believe they’re going to use U.S. aid for humanitarian purposes. Count me as a skeptic,” he remarked. Despite his concerns about Biden’s cognitive state and skepticism over the proposed aid, Johnson maintained a respectful stance towards the President. “I have no problem with President Biden as an individual,” he told Hannity. “You respect the office: It’s a biblical admonition that you give honor where honor is due.” The conversation initiated by Johnson goes beyond political lines, touching on sensitive topics of age, cognitive abilities, and the expectations placed on public officials. As the nation grapples with these issues, the importance of respectful discourse and careful consideration becomes all the more evident.</summary></entry></feed>