<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-11-01T22:22:01-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/11/01/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-11-01T22:22:01-04:00</published><updated>2023-11-01T22:22:01-04:00</updated><id>/2023/11/01/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/11/01/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/11/01/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-11-01T22:22:01-04:00</published><updated>2023-11-01T22:22:01-04:00</updated><id>/2023/11/01/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/11/01/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/">&lt;p&gt;Recent surprise attacks by Hamas on Israel has fueled ongoing tensions between staunchly conservative commentators and the progressive “Squad” Democrats known for criticizing Israel. The intensity of the backlash highlights the deep political divide over foreign policy in the Middle East.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Hamas’ shocking attack, several members of the “Squad,” including Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.), called for a “ceasefire and de-escalation,” condemning the violence. The absence of a statement from Rep. Rashida Tlaib (D-Mich.) was notably called out by conservative media outlets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;South Carolina GOP Rep. Nancy Mace quickly labeled Ocasio-Cortez a “Hamas apologist” in response to her call for peace and de-escalation. Rep. Ilhan Omar (D-Minn.), no stranger to controversy surrounding her views on Israel, echoed the call for de-escalation and ceasefire. Omar’s prior statements comparing the US and Israel to terrorist groups like Hamas and the Taliban resurfaced in the debate, fueling more criticisms. Omar’s 2019 tweet, where she opined that “Israel has hypnotized the world,” also continues to haunt her political career, often cited by critics to challenge her stance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conservative commentators have been especially vocal. “FOX &amp;amp; Friends Weekend” co-host Rachel Campos-Duffy took aim at Omar, saying she fails to recognize the peace in the Middle East under Trump’s administration. Conservative pundit John Hasson also called out Omar, claiming she insinuated that attacks on IDF forces were acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Massachusetts Democrat Rep. Ayanna Pressley’s concerns over the “devastating attacks on Israelis” were met with skepticism. A prominent conservative online personality, Comfortably Smug, accused the “Squad” of advising Israel to back down after the nation suffered massive attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Jamaal Bowman’s call for an end to the Gaza blockade, in addition to condemning the Hamas attacks, was met with criticism from conservative radio host Jason Rantz. He accused Bowman of pairing his condemnation of terrorism with unwarranted criticisms of Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Cori Bush emphasized the urgent need for a ceasefire, while pushing for an end to “U.S. support for Israeli military occupation and apartheid.” Defense attorney Marina Medvin criticized Bush, suggesting that she equates the death of Palestinian terrorists to the horrific acts committed against Jewish civilians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amidst the political turmoil and intense debate, the attacks have taken a heavy toll. Israeli media report over 300 dead due to the wide-ranging assault. Gaza health officials note that at least 200 Palestinians have perished in the retaliatory Israeli air strikes following the initial Hamas attack. As the situation remains volatile, both sides continue to count their casualties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This divisive issue showcases the challenge America faces in crafting a unified approach to foreign policy, with deeply entrenched political divides at play. As the situation develops, the debate is bound to intensify, shedding light on the complexities of U.S. politics in the global arena.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">BLM Organizer Sentenced: A Tale of Deceit and Misused Funds</title><link href="/news/2023/11/01/Activist-Fraud-Exposed/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="BLM Organizer Sentenced: A Tale of Deceit and Misused Funds" /><published>2023-11-01T18:12:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-11-01T18:12:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/11/01/Activist-Fraud-Exposed</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/11/01/Activist-Fraud-Exposed/">&lt;p&gt;Xahra Saleem, a leading figure in the Black Lives Matter (BLM) movement and the 2020 Bristol protests, has been justly sentenced to two and a half years in prison for her fraudulent misappropriation of charity funds. Saleem, who played a pivotal role in orchestrating the protest that led to the dismantling of Sir Edward Colston’s statue, faced the court and was convicted of stealing over £32,000.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saleem, also known under the alias Yvonne Maina and a founder of the All Black Lives Bristol group, deceitfully established fundraising pages, claiming to support a local children’s group, Changing Your Mindset. The supposed intention was to finance a trip to Africa for disadvantaged children. However, she exploited the funds for her own indulgence, splurging on an array of personal items, including an iPhone, a computer, fast food, beauty products, and an exorbitant £5,800 on Uber rides within an 11-month timeframe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The court proceedings laid bare her egregious breach of trust, with the judge emphasizing the severe damage inflicted upon the victims. Saleem attempted to justify her refusal to release the donations with a series of unconvincing excuses, eventually admitting her guilt and expressing remorse for her actions. Nonetheless, her apologies and admission of guilt came too late for the charity, which was forced to shut down as a result of her selfish actions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saleem’s arrest by Avon and Somerset Police in July 2021 marked a pivotal moment, bringing her deceitful practices to an end. However, the fallout from her actions had already caused irreversible damage to the community. The charity’s closure left a void, and tragically, a young individual connected to Saleem and supported by the charity lost his life to violence. Representatives from Changing Your Mindset believe this loss could have been avoided had the charity remained operational.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saleem’s sentencing brings to light the need for greater accountability and transparency within activist movements and charitable organizations. Her actions serve as a stark reminder that not all those who claim to champion social justice are acting in good faith. It underscores the importance of vigilance and due diligence to ensure that funds intended for community betterment are used appropriately. The community, now left to pick up the pieces, must remain vigilant and demand accountability to prevent such egregious breaches of trust in the future.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Xahra Saleem, a leading figure in the Black Lives Matter (BLM) movement and the 2020 Bristol protests, has been justly sentenced to two and a half years in prison for her fraudulent misappropriation of charity funds. Saleem, who played a pivotal role in orchestrating the protest that led to the dismantling of Sir Edward Colston’s statue, faced the court and was convicted of stealing over £32,000. Saleem, also known under the alias Yvonne Maina and a founder of the All Black Lives Bristol group, deceitfully established fundraising pages, claiming to support a local children’s group, Changing Your Mindset. The supposed intention was to finance a trip to Africa for disadvantaged children. However, she exploited the funds for her own indulgence, splurging on an array of personal items, including an iPhone, a computer, fast food, beauty products, and an exorbitant £5,800 on Uber rides within an 11-month timeframe. The court proceedings laid bare her egregious breach of trust, with the judge emphasizing the severe damage inflicted upon the victims. Saleem attempted to justify her refusal to release the donations with a series of unconvincing excuses, eventually admitting her guilt and expressing remorse for her actions. Nonetheless, her apologies and admission of guilt came too late for the charity, which was forced to shut down as a result of her selfish actions. Saleem’s arrest by Avon and Somerset Police in July 2021 marked a pivotal moment, bringing her deceitful practices to an end. However, the fallout from her actions had already caused irreversible damage to the community. The charity’s closure left a void, and tragically, a young individual connected to Saleem and supported by the charity lost his life to violence. Representatives from Changing Your Mindset believe this loss could have been avoided had the charity remained operational. Saleem’s sentencing brings to light the need for greater accountability and transparency within activist movements and charitable organizations. Her actions serve as a stark reminder that not all those who claim to champion social justice are acting in good faith. It underscores the importance of vigilance and due diligence to ensure that funds intended for community betterment are used appropriately. The community, now left to pick up the pieces, must remain vigilant and demand accountability to prevent such egregious breaches of trust in the future.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Tragedy Strikes Kentucky: A Call for Unity and Support in the Wake of Coal Plant Collapse</title><link href="/news/2023/11/01/Kentucky-Coal-Plant-Collapse/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tragedy Strikes Kentucky: A Call for Unity and Support in the Wake of Coal Plant Collapse" /><published>2023-11-01T16:57:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-11-01T16:57:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/11/01/Kentucky-Coal-Plant-Collapse</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/11/01/Kentucky-Coal-Plant-Collapse/">&lt;p&gt;Kentucky has been thrust into the national spotlight following the catastrophic collapse of a coal preparation plant in Martin County, resulting in a tragic loss of life and leaving another worker trapped amidst the rubble. Governor Andy Beshear has declared a state of emergency, mobilizing state resources and shining a light on the gravity of the situation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The collapse, which occurred late Tuesday, has sent shockwaves throughout the community and the state at large. Governor Beshear, taking to social media, urged the people of Kentucky to unite in prayer and support for the victims, their families, and the brave first responders working tirelessly at the scene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“One worker has lost their life, and another remains trapped. We are doing everything we can, and I urge you all to keep them in your thoughts and prayers,” Governor Beshear stated solemnly. This tragedy hits close to home for many in Kentucky, a state with deep roots in the coal industry, and it serves as a stark reminder of the inherent dangers faced by those working in this critical sector of our economy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Martin County Sheriff’s Office and multiple other agencies are on-site, navigating the challenging and dangerous conditions in a race against time to rescue the trapped worker. “This is a complex and delicate operation. We are pouring all of our resources into the rescue efforts, but we need the community’s support and prayers more than ever,” shared Martin County Sheriff John Kirk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The coal preparation plant, which had been out of commission for several years, was in the process of being dismantled when the unthinkable happened. “These workers were doing their job, preparing the structure for demolition when the building collapsed. It’s a tragic accident, and our hearts go out to all those affected,” explained Sheriff Kirk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Governor Beshear’s swift response, declaring a state of emergency, ensures that all necessary resources are made available to aid in the rescue efforts. Kentucky Attorney General Daniel Cameron also took to social media, calling for prayers and support for the trapped workers and the first responders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The tragedy in Martin County serves as a somber reminder of the risks associated with the coal industry, and it highlights the need for continued attention to worker safety and structural integrity. As Kentucky grapples with this disaster, the unity and strength of its people will be paramount.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Governor Beshear’s message is clear: “In these trying times, we must come together as a community, as a state, and support one another. We are Kentucky strong, and we will get through this together.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the rescue operations continue, the eyes of the nation are on Kentucky, hoping and praying for a miracle amidst the devastation. The people of Kentucky, resilient and united, stand ready to support the victims, their families, and the brave men and women on the front lines of this disaster.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Kentucky has been thrust into the national spotlight following the catastrophic collapse of a coal preparation plant in Martin County, resulting in a tragic loss of life and leaving another worker trapped amidst the rubble. Governor Andy Beshear has declared a state of emergency, mobilizing state resources and shining a light on the gravity of the situation. The collapse, which occurred late Tuesday, has sent shockwaves throughout the community and the state at large. Governor Beshear, taking to social media, urged the people of Kentucky to unite in prayer and support for the victims, their families, and the brave first responders working tirelessly at the scene. “One worker has lost their life, and another remains trapped. We are doing everything we can, and I urge you all to keep them in your thoughts and prayers,” Governor Beshear stated solemnly. This tragedy hits close to home for many in Kentucky, a state with deep roots in the coal industry, and it serves as a stark reminder of the inherent dangers faced by those working in this critical sector of our economy. The Martin County Sheriff’s Office and multiple other agencies are on-site, navigating the challenging and dangerous conditions in a race against time to rescue the trapped worker. “This is a complex and delicate operation. We are pouring all of our resources into the rescue efforts, but we need the community’s support and prayers more than ever,” shared Martin County Sheriff John Kirk. The coal preparation plant, which had been out of commission for several years, was in the process of being dismantled when the unthinkable happened. “These workers were doing their job, preparing the structure for demolition when the building collapsed. It’s a tragic accident, and our hearts go out to all those affected,” explained Sheriff Kirk. Governor Beshear’s swift response, declaring a state of emergency, ensures that all necessary resources are made available to aid in the rescue efforts. Kentucky Attorney General Daniel Cameron also took to social media, calling for prayers and support for the trapped workers and the first responders. The tragedy in Martin County serves as a somber reminder of the risks associated with the coal industry, and it highlights the need for continued attention to worker safety and structural integrity. As Kentucky grapples with this disaster, the unity and strength of its people will be paramount. Governor Beshear’s message is clear: “In these trying times, we must come together as a community, as a state, and support one another. We are Kentucky strong, and we will get through this together.” As the rescue operations continue, the eyes of the nation are on Kentucky, hoping and praying for a miracle amidst the devastation. The people of Kentucky, resilient and united, stand ready to support the victims, their families, and the brave men and women on the front lines of this disaster.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Elon Musk Exposes George Soros: The Architect of Social Decay</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/11/01/Soros-Humanity-Crisis/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Elon Musk Exposes George Soros: The Architect of Social Decay" /><published>2023-11-01T15:48:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-11-01T15:48:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/11/01/Soros-Humanity-Crisis</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/11/01/Soros-Humanity-Crisis/">&lt;p&gt;Tesla CEO and renowned entrepreneur, Elon Musk, has recently taken a bold stance against billionaire Democrat donor George Soros, accusing him of ‘eroding the fabric of civilization’ and harboring a deep-seated hatred for humanity. During an appearance on the Joe Rogan Show, Musk did not hold back his criticisms, expressing his concerns about the detrimental impact Soros is having on society at large.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Soros, a name synonymous with political donations and controversial global influence, has long been a divisive figure in American politics. Musk’s assertion that Soros is actively contributing to the decline of civilization aligns with the sentiments of many conservatives who have scrutinized Soros’s funding of progressive district attorneys and his role in shaping policy at the local level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Musk emphasized Soros’s cunning ability to exploit loopholes and manipulate systems for personal and ideological gain. He highlighted Soros’s history of financial maneuvers, including his infamous shorting of the British pound, drawing parallels between his financial strategies and political machinations. Soros’s ability to spot ‘value for money’ in local races, Musk argues, allows him to exert influence in a way that is both cost-effective and insidiously impactful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Elon Musk, a figure admired by many for his entrepreneurial spirit and his willingness to challenge the status quo, is using his platform to shine a light on what he sees as a grave threat to the values and institutions that uphold society. His message is clear: George Soros’s actions and the ideologies he funds are contributing to a degradation of law and order, and his influence needs to be critically examined.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Soros’s contributions to the Democratic party, his funding of progressive district attorneys, and his influence on local elections represent a challenge to conservative values and the rule of law. Musk’s conversation with Rogan serves as a stark reminder of the need for vigilance and the importance of holding those with power and influence accountable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the fight for the soul of America, voices like Musk’s are invaluable. They serve as a counterpoint to the narratives pushed by those who seek to undermine the fabric of society for ideological gain. As we navigate these turbulent times, it is crucial to remain informed, stay engaged, and stand up for the values that make America great.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By highlighting Soros’s influence and the risks it poses, Musk has once again proven himself to be a thought leader unafraid to tackle the tough issues and speak out against those he believes are harming humanity. The conservative audience, ever watchful for threats to their values and way of life, will no doubt take Musk’s words to heart, fueling the ongoing debate about George Soros’s role in American politics and the broader global stage.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Tesla CEO and renowned entrepreneur, Elon Musk, has recently taken a bold stance against billionaire Democrat donor George Soros, accusing him of ‘eroding the fabric of civilization’ and harboring a deep-seated hatred for humanity. During an appearance on the Joe Rogan Show, Musk did not hold back his criticisms, expressing his concerns about the detrimental impact Soros is having on society at large. Soros, a name synonymous with political donations and controversial global influence, has long been a divisive figure in American politics. Musk’s assertion that Soros is actively contributing to the decline of civilization aligns with the sentiments of many conservatives who have scrutinized Soros’s funding of progressive district attorneys and his role in shaping policy at the local level. Musk emphasized Soros’s cunning ability to exploit loopholes and manipulate systems for personal and ideological gain. He highlighted Soros’s history of financial maneuvers, including his infamous shorting of the British pound, drawing parallels between his financial strategies and political machinations. Soros’s ability to spot ‘value for money’ in local races, Musk argues, allows him to exert influence in a way that is both cost-effective and insidiously impactful. Elon Musk, a figure admired by many for his entrepreneurial spirit and his willingness to challenge the status quo, is using his platform to shine a light on what he sees as a grave threat to the values and institutions that uphold society. His message is clear: George Soros’s actions and the ideologies he funds are contributing to a degradation of law and order, and his influence needs to be critically examined. Soros’s contributions to the Democratic party, his funding of progressive district attorneys, and his influence on local elections represent a challenge to conservative values and the rule of law. Musk’s conversation with Rogan serves as a stark reminder of the need for vigilance and the importance of holding those with power and influence accountable. In the fight for the soul of America, voices like Musk’s are invaluable. They serve as a counterpoint to the narratives pushed by those who seek to undermine the fabric of society for ideological gain. As we navigate these turbulent times, it is crucial to remain informed, stay engaged, and stand up for the values that make America great. By highlighting Soros’s influence and the risks it poses, Musk has once again proven himself to be a thought leader unafraid to tackle the tough issues and speak out against those he believes are harming humanity. The conservative audience, ever watchful for threats to their values and way of life, will no doubt take Musk’s words to heart, fueling the ongoing debate about George Soros’s role in American politics and the broader global stage.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Biden allegedly received $40K in laundered money: Unraveling the Tangled Web of China Money</title><link href="/politics/2023/11/01/Biden-China-Money-Scandal/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Biden allegedly received $40K in laundered money: Unraveling the Tangled Web of China Money" /><published>2023-11-01T14:24:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-11-01T14:24:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/11/01/Biden-China-Money-Scandal</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/11/01/Biden-China-Money-Scandal/">&lt;p&gt;House Oversight Committee Chairman James Comer has accused President Joe Biden of receiving $40,000 in ‘laundered China money’ from his brother James Biden back in 2017. This bombshell assertion raises numerous questions about the integrity of Biden’s financial dealings and his potential vulnerability to foreign influence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The money, allegedly originating from China’s CEFC and channeled through Hunter Biden, was described as a ‘loan repayment’ from James to Joe Biden. However, this transaction raises alarm bells considering the close ties between the Biden family and Chinese Communist Party-linked entities. Comer’s investigation, rooted in bank records and a meticulous following of the money trail, exposes a complex web of transactions designed to benefit the Biden family financially.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The accusation that money from a Chinese company ended up in the personal account of Joe Biden is not just a financial scandal; it is potentially a significant national security threat. Comer suggests that Biden has “exposed himself to future blackmail” from Beijing, putting America’s interests at risk. The Biden family’s business dealings with China have long been a subject of contention and criticism, and this latest development only adds fuel to the fire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Oversight Committee’s relentless pursuit of the truth has revealed more than just this single transaction. Comer asserts that the Biden family, their business associates, and related companies have received over $24 million from entities in China, Russia, Ukraine, Kazakhstan, and Romania between 2014 and 2019. This international money trail, benefiting from Joe Biden’s political clout, is a concerning pattern that warrants thorough investigation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For conservatives and many Americans concerned about transparency and accountability, these revelations are a stark reminder of the need for vigilance. The Biden family’s financial dealings with foreign entities, especially those linked to adversarial governments, are a matter of national concern.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this era of political turmoil and distrust, getting to the bottom of these allegations is not just about partisan politics; it is about safeguarding the integrity of American democracy and ensuring that no individual, regardless of their position, is above the law.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The White House has attempted to downplay these allegations, emphasizing Biden’s status as a private citizen during the time of these transactions. However, the American people deserve a clear and transparent investigation to ensure that their leaders are acting in the best interests of the nation, free from foreign influence and financial entanglements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As we await further developments in this investigation, it is crucial for the media, lawmakers, and the public to remain vigilant and demand transparency and accountability. The future of American democracy may well depend on it.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">House Oversight Committee Chairman James Comer has accused President Joe Biden of receiving $40,000 in ‘laundered China money’ from his brother James Biden back in 2017. This bombshell assertion raises numerous questions about the integrity of Biden’s financial dealings and his potential vulnerability to foreign influence. The money, allegedly originating from China’s CEFC and channeled through Hunter Biden, was described as a ‘loan repayment’ from James to Joe Biden. However, this transaction raises alarm bells considering the close ties between the Biden family and Chinese Communist Party-linked entities. Comer’s investigation, rooted in bank records and a meticulous following of the money trail, exposes a complex web of transactions designed to benefit the Biden family financially. The accusation that money from a Chinese company ended up in the personal account of Joe Biden is not just a financial scandal; it is potentially a significant national security threat. Comer suggests that Biden has “exposed himself to future blackmail” from Beijing, putting America’s interests at risk. The Biden family’s business dealings with China have long been a subject of contention and criticism, and this latest development only adds fuel to the fire. The Oversight Committee’s relentless pursuit of the truth has revealed more than just this single transaction. Comer asserts that the Biden family, their business associates, and related companies have received over $24 million from entities in China, Russia, Ukraine, Kazakhstan, and Romania between 2014 and 2019. This international money trail, benefiting from Joe Biden’s political clout, is a concerning pattern that warrants thorough investigation. For conservatives and many Americans concerned about transparency and accountability, these revelations are a stark reminder of the need for vigilance. The Biden family’s financial dealings with foreign entities, especially those linked to adversarial governments, are a matter of national concern. In this era of political turmoil and distrust, getting to the bottom of these allegations is not just about partisan politics; it is about safeguarding the integrity of American democracy and ensuring that no individual, regardless of their position, is above the law. The White House has attempted to downplay these allegations, emphasizing Biden’s status as a private citizen during the time of these transactions. However, the American people deserve a clear and transparent investigation to ensure that their leaders are acting in the best interests of the nation, free from foreign influence and financial entanglements. As we await further developments in this investigation, it is crucial for the media, lawmakers, and the public to remain vigilant and demand transparency and accountability. The future of American democracy may well depend on it.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Downfall of San Francisco: Bank Closures as a Symptom of Democrat-led Disorder</title><link href="/news/2023/11/01/Bank-Closures-San-Francisco/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Downfall of San Francisco: Bank Closures as a Symptom of Democrat-led Disorder" /><published>2023-11-01T13:16:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-11-01T13:16:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/11/01/Bank-Closures-San-Francisco</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/11/01/Bank-Closures-San-Francisco/">&lt;p&gt;San Francisco, once a booming city of prosperity, now faces a devastating economic decline. Local bank branches are shuttering across the city at an alarming rate, with 20 branches closing their doors through Oct. 28 this year alone. This trend is not just a local issue; it’s part of a nationwide crisis where financial institutions are vanishing, leaving residents without essential services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The city’s descent into chaos, marked by crime, homelessness, and a drug epidemic, has created a hostile environment for businesses. The Democratic policies that dominate San Francisco’s political landscape have only exacerbated these issues, leading to a surge in crime rates and creating an unsafe atmosphere that has driven businesses away. As a result, many banks have been forced to close, often without warning, leaving residents and local businesses scrambling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to data from the U.S. Office of the Comptroller of the Currency, the closures in San Francisco this year surpass the total number of closures from the previous two years combined. It’s a shocking trend that speaks volumes about the dire state of the city’s economy and safety. From the central Richmond District to Bayview, no area has been spared, underscoring the pervasive nature of this crisis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;California as a whole is not faring much better, with 277 bank branches closing statewide so far this year, a number second only to the record set in 2020 when 325 branches shuttered. These closures are a stark contrast to the mere eight branch openings that have occurred statewide this year, painting a grim picture of the financial landscape in California.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While some of these closures can be attributed to the move to online banking and industry-wide consolidation, many are directly tied to the city’s ongoing exodus of retail businesses, a situation worsened by persistent shoplifting problems and the inability of local authorities to address these issues effectively. The commercial center of San Francisco, once bustling with activity, is now struggling to recover from the impact of the coronavirus pandemic and the shift to remote work, further hampered by the Democrat-led city’s failure to address the rising crime rates and create a safe and secure environment for businesses and residents alike.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This alarming trend of bank closures is a clear indication that the policies of the Democrat-led city are failing its residents. The lack of action to address the rising crime rates, combined with the economic fallout from the pandemic, has created a perfect storm that is driving businesses away and leaving the city in disarray. As conservatives, we must stand firm in our commitment to law and order, economic prosperity, and the well-being of our communities, and hold those in power accountable for their failure to uphold these principles.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">San Francisco, once a booming city of prosperity, now faces a devastating economic decline. Local bank branches are shuttering across the city at an alarming rate, with 20 branches closing their doors through Oct. 28 this year alone. This trend is not just a local issue; it’s part of a nationwide crisis where financial institutions are vanishing, leaving residents without essential services. The city’s descent into chaos, marked by crime, homelessness, and a drug epidemic, has created a hostile environment for businesses. The Democratic policies that dominate San Francisco’s political landscape have only exacerbated these issues, leading to a surge in crime rates and creating an unsafe atmosphere that has driven businesses away. As a result, many banks have been forced to close, often without warning, leaving residents and local businesses scrambling. According to data from the U.S. Office of the Comptroller of the Currency, the closures in San Francisco this year surpass the total number of closures from the previous two years combined. It’s a shocking trend that speaks volumes about the dire state of the city’s economy and safety. From the central Richmond District to Bayview, no area has been spared, underscoring the pervasive nature of this crisis. California as a whole is not faring much better, with 277 bank branches closing statewide so far this year, a number second only to the record set in 2020 when 325 branches shuttered. These closures are a stark contrast to the mere eight branch openings that have occurred statewide this year, painting a grim picture of the financial landscape in California. While some of these closures can be attributed to the move to online banking and industry-wide consolidation, many are directly tied to the city’s ongoing exodus of retail businesses, a situation worsened by persistent shoplifting problems and the inability of local authorities to address these issues effectively. The commercial center of San Francisco, once bustling with activity, is now struggling to recover from the impact of the coronavirus pandemic and the shift to remote work, further hampered by the Democrat-led city’s failure to address the rising crime rates and create a safe and secure environment for businesses and residents alike. This alarming trend of bank closures is a clear indication that the policies of the Democrat-led city are failing its residents. The lack of action to address the rising crime rates, combined with the economic fallout from the pandemic, has created a perfect storm that is driving businesses away and leaving the city in disarray. As conservatives, we must stand firm in our commitment to law and order, economic prosperity, and the well-being of our communities, and hold those in power accountable for their failure to uphold these principles.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Accountability Looms: The Unraveling of Rep. George Santos</title><link href="/politics/2023/11/01/George-Santos-Ethics-Investigation/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Accountability Looms: The Unraveling of Rep. George Santos" /><published>2023-11-01T12:10:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-11-01T12:10:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/11/01/George-Santos-Ethics-Investigation</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/11/01/George-Santos-Ethics-Investigation/">&lt;p&gt;The walls are closing in on New York Republican Rep. George Santos as the House Ethics Committee promises a decision by November 17th on the “next course of action” for the beleaguered congressman. Santos, drowning in a sea of federal charges and bipartisan disdain, faces the stark reality of his actions catching up with him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amidst the possibility of a House vote on a resolution for his expulsion, Santos finds himself at the center of a whirlwind investigation. The Ethics Committee, diligently led by Michael Guest and top Democrat Susan Wild, has tirelessly reached out to around 40 witnesses, sifted through over 170,000 pages of documents, and approved 37 subpoenas to uncover the truth behind Santos’s murky dealings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With accusations ranging from identity theft of campaign donors, unauthorized credit card charges, falsification of campaign finance reports, to money laundering, the list of federal charges against Santos totals a staggering 23. Yet, despite these serious allegations, Santos remains defiant, pleading not guilty and refusing to step down. His resistance is in stark contrast to the calls for resignation from both sides of the aisle, reflecting a blatant disregard for accountability and the values we hold dear as Republicans.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Several New York Republicans, unwilling to let this blatant misconduct slide, are fervently pushing for a resolution to expel Santos from Congress. The urgency of the situation is palpable, with a potential vote to oust him being considered as early as Wednesday. The gravity of this action cannot be understated - expelling a member from the House requires a two-thirds majority vote, a clear indication that this is not a decision taken lightly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rewind to May, and we saw House Republicans blocking a Democrat-led initiative to expel Santos, opting instead to entrust the Ethics Committee with deciding his fate. This decision, made in the spirit of due process, now culminates in the impending announcement from the committee, a moment that will undoubtedly be a turning point in this saga.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As we await the committee’s decision, it is crucial to reflect on the values that define us as Republicans and as Americans. Accountability, integrity, and a commitment to the truth are non-negotiable, and Santos’s actions stand in stark contradiction to these principles. The time for accountability is now, and as the committee prepares to make its announcement, the nation watches, expecting nothing less than a firm stand against misconduct and a resounding affirmation of our commitment to integrity and justice.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">The walls are closing in on New York Republican Rep. George Santos as the House Ethics Committee promises a decision by November 17th on the “next course of action” for the beleaguered congressman. Santos, drowning in a sea of federal charges and bipartisan disdain, faces the stark reality of his actions catching up with him. Amidst the possibility of a House vote on a resolution for his expulsion, Santos finds himself at the center of a whirlwind investigation. The Ethics Committee, diligently led by Michael Guest and top Democrat Susan Wild, has tirelessly reached out to around 40 witnesses, sifted through over 170,000 pages of documents, and approved 37 subpoenas to uncover the truth behind Santos’s murky dealings. With accusations ranging from identity theft of campaign donors, unauthorized credit card charges, falsification of campaign finance reports, to money laundering, the list of federal charges against Santos totals a staggering 23. Yet, despite these serious allegations, Santos remains defiant, pleading not guilty and refusing to step down. His resistance is in stark contrast to the calls for resignation from both sides of the aisle, reflecting a blatant disregard for accountability and the values we hold dear as Republicans. Several New York Republicans, unwilling to let this blatant misconduct slide, are fervently pushing for a resolution to expel Santos from Congress. The urgency of the situation is palpable, with a potential vote to oust him being considered as early as Wednesday. The gravity of this action cannot be understated - expelling a member from the House requires a two-thirds majority vote, a clear indication that this is not a decision taken lightly. Rewind to May, and we saw House Republicans blocking a Democrat-led initiative to expel Santos, opting instead to entrust the Ethics Committee with deciding his fate. This decision, made in the spirit of due process, now culminates in the impending announcement from the committee, a moment that will undoubtedly be a turning point in this saga. As we await the committee’s decision, it is crucial to reflect on the values that define us as Republicans and as Americans. Accountability, integrity, and a commitment to the truth are non-negotiable, and Santos’s actions stand in stark contradiction to these principles. The time for accountability is now, and as the committee prepares to make its announcement, the nation watches, expecting nothing less than a firm stand against misconduct and a resounding affirmation of our commitment to integrity and justice.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Golden Age Star Joan Evans: A Tribute to Her Illustrious Career</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/11/01/Hollywood-Legend-Joan-Evans-Passes-Away/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Golden Age Star Joan Evans: A Tribute to Her Illustrious Career" /><published>2023-11-01T11:03:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-11-01T11:03:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/11/01/Hollywood-Legend-Joan-Evans-Passes-Away</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/11/01/Hollywood-Legend-Joan-Evans-Passes-Away/">&lt;p&gt;Joan Evans, a luminary of the Hollywood’s Golden Age and star of classics such as “On the Loose” and “Skirts Ahoy!,” has passed away at the venerable age of 89. The actress’s son, John Weatherly, confirmed her passing, which occurred at her home in Henderson, Nevada on October 21.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Evans’ journey in the entertainment world was nothing short of remarkable. As the goddaughter of the legendary Joan Crawford, she was destined for stardom from a young age. Her parents, Dale Eunson and Katherine Albert, were both well-established screenwriters, penning the script for “On the Loose,” one of Evans’ most memorable films.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 1950s saw Evans rise to prominence, starring alongside Esther Williams in the 1952 musical hit “Skirts Ahoy!” and delivering compelling performances in “Edge of Doom,” “Our Very Own,” “Column South,” and “No Name on the Bullet.” Her acting prowess and on-screen charm captivated audiences, making her a household name and a beloved figure in Hollywood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Born in New York in 1934, Evans’ mother served as a Hollywood reporter for Photoplay magazine, often covering Crawford’s rising career. This close-knit relationship between Evans’ family and Crawford played a significant role in shaping her life and career. “They were best friends,” Evans recalled in a 2013 interview with Foster Hirsch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Evans’ journey, however, was not without its trials. She shared a harrowing experience from the set of “Roseanna McCoy” in 1948, where she was accidentally shot in the arm, requiring emergency surgery and a hospital stay. This incident, while traumatic, showcased Evans’ resilience and determination, traits that defined her both on and off the screen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Evans’ personal life was as captivating as her film career. At a dinner party hosted by Crawford, she and Kirby Weatherly decided to tie the knot, a spontaneous decision that resulted in a midnight wedding officiated by a judge Crawford had called over. Evans and Weatherly’s marriage stood the test of time, lasting until his death on January 1, 2023.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reflecting on her relationship with Crawford, Evans spoke warmly of the star, remembering her as a “wonderful, darling friend” and debunking the myth of the diva actress. The bond between Evans and Crawford remained strong until Crawford’s death in 1977, a testament to their enduring friendship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Joan Evans leaves behind a legacy of cinematic excellence, personal resilience, and a life well-lived. She is survived by her son, John, daughter, Dale, and grandson, Chris. As we bid farewell to this Golden Age icon, we celebrate her contributions to the world of film and remember her as a shining star in Hollywood’s illustrious history.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Joan Evans, a luminary of the Hollywood’s Golden Age and star of classics such as “On the Loose” and “Skirts Ahoy!,” has passed away at the venerable age of 89. The actress’s son, John Weatherly, confirmed her passing, which occurred at her home in Henderson, Nevada on October 21. Evans’ journey in the entertainment world was nothing short of remarkable. As the goddaughter of the legendary Joan Crawford, she was destined for stardom from a young age. Her parents, Dale Eunson and Katherine Albert, were both well-established screenwriters, penning the script for “On the Loose,” one of Evans’ most memorable films. The 1950s saw Evans rise to prominence, starring alongside Esther Williams in the 1952 musical hit “Skirts Ahoy!” and delivering compelling performances in “Edge of Doom,” “Our Very Own,” “Column South,” and “No Name on the Bullet.” Her acting prowess and on-screen charm captivated audiences, making her a household name and a beloved figure in Hollywood. Born in New York in 1934, Evans’ mother served as a Hollywood reporter for Photoplay magazine, often covering Crawford’s rising career. This close-knit relationship between Evans’ family and Crawford played a significant role in shaping her life and career. “They were best friends,” Evans recalled in a 2013 interview with Foster Hirsch. Evans’ journey, however, was not without its trials. She shared a harrowing experience from the set of “Roseanna McCoy” in 1948, where she was accidentally shot in the arm, requiring emergency surgery and a hospital stay. This incident, while traumatic, showcased Evans’ resilience and determination, traits that defined her both on and off the screen. Evans’ personal life was as captivating as her film career. At a dinner party hosted by Crawford, she and Kirby Weatherly decided to tie the knot, a spontaneous decision that resulted in a midnight wedding officiated by a judge Crawford had called over. Evans and Weatherly’s marriage stood the test of time, lasting until his death on January 1, 2023. Reflecting on her relationship with Crawford, Evans spoke warmly of the star, remembering her as a “wonderful, darling friend” and debunking the myth of the diva actress. The bond between Evans and Crawford remained strong until Crawford’s death in 1977, a testament to their enduring friendship. Joan Evans leaves behind a legacy of cinematic excellence, personal resilience, and a life well-lived. She is survived by her son, John, daughter, Dale, and grandson, Chris. As we bid farewell to this Golden Age icon, we celebrate her contributions to the world of film and remember her as a shining star in Hollywood’s illustrious history.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Decoding the Biden Family Saga: Business or Benefaction?</title><link href="/politics/2023/11/01/Biden-Family-Business-Dealings/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Decoding the Biden Family Saga: Business or Benefaction?" /><published>2023-11-01T08:51:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-11-01T08:51:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/11/01/Biden-Family-Business-Dealings</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/11/01/Biden-Family-Business-Dealings/">&lt;p&gt;In an era where transparency in politics is more crucial than ever, the Biden family’s financial dealings have come under intense scrutiny. Large sums of money changing hands within the family, coupled with President Biden’s denial of involvement in his son’s international business dealings, have raised eyebrows and serious questions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The financial tapestry woven by the Biden family includes a questionable $200,000 payment received by Joe Biden from his brother, James Biden, following a loan of the same amount granted to James by a health care company he was affiliated with. The exchange was purportedly for access and influence, a claim that brings into question the ethics of the family’s dealings. This is not an isolated incident; it’s part of a pattern that has persisted over the years, with the family using loans and other financial mechanisms to maneuver money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the labyrinth of the Biden family’s finances, the use of over 20 shell companies to move money discreetly has also come to light. This, coupled with the ‘loans’ used to facilitate the transfer of funds between family members, paints a picture of complexity and secrecy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As we dig deeper, another layer of this financial web reveals itself. In 2020, Hollywood attorney Kevin Morris cleared a $2 million unpaid tax liability for Hunter Biden. Initially labeled as a ‘loan,’ the paperwork supporting this claim seemed to materialize only after the IRS began raising suspicions, casting further doubt on the nature of the transaction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These financial intricacies demand transparency and scrutiny, especially when they involve individuals in the highest offices of the land. The House of Representatives has taken up the mantle to investigate, ensuring that those in power are held accountable and are not using their positions for personal gain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whistleblowers from the IRS have also come forward, alleging that the Biden Justice Department obstructed investigations into potential campaign finance violations involving the Biden presidential campaign. This accusation adds another layer of complexity to the situation, emphasizing the need for a thorough and impartial investigation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the House delves into these so-called ‘loans’ and financial dealings, the American people watch closely, with polls indicating that nearly half of the adult population believes President Biden may have been involved in illegal activities concerning his son. The trust in our institutions and in our leaders is at stake, and it is incumbent upon Congress to uncover the truth, wherever it may lead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In these trying times, our democracy demands diligence, transparency, and accountability from its leaders. The ongoing inquiry into the Biden family’s business dealings is not just about financial transactions; it’s about upholding the values that our nation holds dear and ensuring that those in power are serving the American people, and not their own interests.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In an era where transparency in politics is more crucial than ever, the Biden family’s financial dealings have come under intense scrutiny. Large sums of money changing hands within the family, coupled with President Biden’s denial of involvement in his son’s international business dealings, have raised eyebrows and serious questions. The financial tapestry woven by the Biden family includes a questionable $200,000 payment received by Joe Biden from his brother, James Biden, following a loan of the same amount granted to James by a health care company he was affiliated with. The exchange was purportedly for access and influence, a claim that brings into question the ethics of the family’s dealings. This is not an isolated incident; it’s part of a pattern that has persisted over the years, with the family using loans and other financial mechanisms to maneuver money. In the labyrinth of the Biden family’s finances, the use of over 20 shell companies to move money discreetly has also come to light. This, coupled with the ‘loans’ used to facilitate the transfer of funds between family members, paints a picture of complexity and secrecy. As we dig deeper, another layer of this financial web reveals itself. In 2020, Hollywood attorney Kevin Morris cleared a $2 million unpaid tax liability for Hunter Biden. Initially labeled as a ‘loan,’ the paperwork supporting this claim seemed to materialize only after the IRS began raising suspicions, casting further doubt on the nature of the transaction. These financial intricacies demand transparency and scrutiny, especially when they involve individuals in the highest offices of the land. The House of Representatives has taken up the mantle to investigate, ensuring that those in power are held accountable and are not using their positions for personal gain. Whistleblowers from the IRS have also come forward, alleging that the Biden Justice Department obstructed investigations into potential campaign finance violations involving the Biden presidential campaign. This accusation adds another layer of complexity to the situation, emphasizing the need for a thorough and impartial investigation. As the House delves into these so-called ‘loans’ and financial dealings, the American people watch closely, with polls indicating that nearly half of the adult population believes President Biden may have been involved in illegal activities concerning his son. The trust in our institutions and in our leaders is at stake, and it is incumbent upon Congress to uncover the truth, wherever it may lead. In these trying times, our democracy demands diligence, transparency, and accountability from its leaders. The ongoing inquiry into the Biden family’s business dealings is not just about financial transactions; it’s about upholding the values that our nation holds dear and ensuring that those in power are serving the American people, and not their own interests.</summary></entry></feed>