<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-10-11T10:16:04-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/11/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-11T10:16:04-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-11T10:16:04-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/11/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/11/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/11/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-11T10:16:04-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-11T10:16:04-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/11/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/11/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/">&lt;p&gt;Recent surprise attacks by Hamas on Israel has fueled ongoing tensions between staunchly conservative commentators and the progressive “Squad” Democrats known for criticizing Israel. The intensity of the backlash highlights the deep political divide over foreign policy in the Middle East.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Hamas’ shocking attack, several members of the “Squad,” including Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.), called for a “ceasefire and de-escalation,” condemning the violence. The absence of a statement from Rep. Rashida Tlaib (D-Mich.) was notably called out by conservative media outlets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;South Carolina GOP Rep. Nancy Mace quickly labeled Ocasio-Cortez a “Hamas apologist” in response to her call for peace and de-escalation. Rep. Ilhan Omar (D-Minn.), no stranger to controversy surrounding her views on Israel, echoed the call for de-escalation and ceasefire. Omar’s prior statements comparing the US and Israel to terrorist groups like Hamas and the Taliban resurfaced in the debate, fueling more criticisms. Omar’s 2019 tweet, where she opined that “Israel has hypnotized the world,” also continues to haunt her political career, often cited by critics to challenge her stance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conservative commentators have been especially vocal. “FOX &amp;amp; Friends Weekend” co-host Rachel Campos-Duffy took aim at Omar, saying she fails to recognize the peace in the Middle East under Trump’s administration. Conservative pundit John Hasson also called out Omar, claiming she insinuated that attacks on IDF forces were acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Massachusetts Democrat Rep. Ayanna Pressley’s concerns over the “devastating attacks on Israelis” were met with skepticism. A prominent conservative online personality, Comfortably Smug, accused the “Squad” of advising Israel to back down after the nation suffered massive attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Jamaal Bowman’s call for an end to the Gaza blockade, in addition to condemning the Hamas attacks, was met with criticism from conservative radio host Jason Rantz. He accused Bowman of pairing his condemnation of terrorism with unwarranted criticisms of Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Cori Bush emphasized the urgent need for a ceasefire, while pushing for an end to “U.S. support for Israeli military occupation and apartheid.” Defense attorney Marina Medvin criticized Bush, suggesting that she equates the death of Palestinian terrorists to the horrific acts committed against Jewish civilians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amidst the political turmoil and intense debate, the attacks have taken a heavy toll. Israeli media report over 300 dead due to the wide-ranging assault. Gaza health officials note that at least 200 Palestinians have perished in the retaliatory Israeli air strikes following the initial Hamas attack. As the situation remains volatile, both sides continue to count their casualties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This divisive issue showcases the challenge America faces in crafting a unified approach to foreign policy, with deeply entrenched political divides at play. As the situation develops, the debate is bound to intensify, shedding light on the complexities of U.S. politics in the global arena.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Utah Takes on TikTok: State Sues Over Child Addiction Concerns</title><link href="/news/2023/10/11/TikTok-Lawsuit-Utah/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Utah Takes on TikTok: State Sues Over Child Addiction Concerns" /><published>2023-10-11T09:20:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-11T09:20:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/11/TikTok-Lawsuit-Utah</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/11/TikTok-Lawsuit-Utah/">&lt;p&gt;In a bold move against social media titan TikTok, the state of Utah has launched a lawsuit, accusing the platform of creating and promoting addictive behaviors among its younger users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Highlighting the significant role social media plays in the lives of the youth, the lawsuit, announced on Tuesday, asserts that TikTok is deliberately “baiting” children into unhealthy, prolonged usage habits. These alleged deceptive strategies not only encompass content delivery but also misrepresentation about the app’s affiliation with its parent company, ByteDance, based in China.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Utah Governor Spencer Cox emphasized the state’s commitment to safeguarding its children from potentially harmful social media practices, stating, “We will not stand by while these companies fail to take adequate, meaningful action to protect our children.” This lawsuit, filed in Salt Lake City’s state court, builds on similar legal actions initiated by Arkansas and Indiana. Meanwhile, the broader implications of state-driven social media regulations are slated for consideration by the U.S. Supreme Court.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Key elements of the Utah lawsuit revolve around public health concerns. The suit references various studies, pointing out that children dedicating more than three hours daily to social media platforms are more susceptible to mental health issues, such as anxiety and depression.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sean Reyes, Utah’s Attorney General, likened TikTok’s algorithm to a “cruel slot machine,” purposefully designed to capture and retain children’s attention. The main objective of this lawsuit is not only to drive TikTok towards more responsible behavior but also to secure penalties and fines. These funds would be directed towards educational initiatives and other mechanisms that could address the alleged harm caused to Utah’s younger demographic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TikTok’s response to this lawsuit is yet awaited, with spokesperson Hilary McQuaide not immediately providing any comment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, Utah has been at the forefront of driving regulations around children’s social media usage. Earlier in the year, the state passed pioneering laws to curtail children and teen engagement with apps like TikTok. These new regulations, set to be effective from next year, entail a digital curfew for individuals under 18. Further, they enforce parental consent requirements for minor sign-ups and age verification for all Utah-based users. Additionally, tech firms would be mandated to grant parents access to their children’s private accounts, a move which has stirred concerns about infringing on children’s privacy rights, especially for those in the LGBTQ+ community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the battle lines are drawn between state authorities and tech giants, the focal point remains the welfare and protection of young users in an increasingly digital age.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a bold move against social media titan TikTok, the state of Utah has launched a lawsuit, accusing the platform of creating and promoting addictive behaviors among its younger users. Highlighting the significant role social media plays in the lives of the youth, the lawsuit, announced on Tuesday, asserts that TikTok is deliberately “baiting” children into unhealthy, prolonged usage habits. These alleged deceptive strategies not only encompass content delivery but also misrepresentation about the app’s affiliation with its parent company, ByteDance, based in China. Utah Governor Spencer Cox emphasized the state’s commitment to safeguarding its children from potentially harmful social media practices, stating, “We will not stand by while these companies fail to take adequate, meaningful action to protect our children.” This lawsuit, filed in Salt Lake City’s state court, builds on similar legal actions initiated by Arkansas and Indiana. Meanwhile, the broader implications of state-driven social media regulations are slated for consideration by the U.S. Supreme Court. Key elements of the Utah lawsuit revolve around public health concerns. The suit references various studies, pointing out that children dedicating more than three hours daily to social media platforms are more susceptible to mental health issues, such as anxiety and depression. Sean Reyes, Utah’s Attorney General, likened TikTok’s algorithm to a “cruel slot machine,” purposefully designed to capture and retain children’s attention. The main objective of this lawsuit is not only to drive TikTok towards more responsible behavior but also to secure penalties and fines. These funds would be directed towards educational initiatives and other mechanisms that could address the alleged harm caused to Utah’s younger demographic. TikTok’s response to this lawsuit is yet awaited, with spokesperson Hilary McQuaide not immediately providing any comment. Interestingly, Utah has been at the forefront of driving regulations around children’s social media usage. Earlier in the year, the state passed pioneering laws to curtail children and teen engagement with apps like TikTok. These new regulations, set to be effective from next year, entail a digital curfew for individuals under 18. Further, they enforce parental consent requirements for minor sign-ups and age verification for all Utah-based users. Additionally, tech firms would be mandated to grant parents access to their children’s private accounts, a move which has stirred concerns about infringing on children’s privacy rights, especially for those in the LGBTQ+ community. As the battle lines are drawn between state authorities and tech giants, the focal point remains the welfare and protection of young users in an increasingly digital age.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Bomb Threat Shuts Down Santa Monica Pier: Ferris Wheel Drama Ends Peacefully</title><link href="/news/2023/10/11/Bomb-Threat-Santa-Monica/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bomb Threat Shuts Down Santa Monica Pier: Ferris Wheel Drama Ends Peacefully" /><published>2023-10-11T08:17:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-11T08:17:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/11/Bomb-Threat-Santa-Monica</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/11/Bomb-Threat-Santa-Monica/">&lt;p&gt;In a shocking turn of events, a man scaled the Ferris wheel at Santa Monica Pier on Monday, causing a major scare by claiming he possessed a bomb. The iconic tourist destination was swiftly evacuated amidst the growing alarm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Early in the afternoon, onlookers watched in a mix of horror and curiosity as the man climbed the famed Ferris wheel. Witnesses reported overhearing the man’s bomb claims, prompting immediate action by local authorities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Santa Monica Police Department’s Crisis Negotiation Team was promptly dispatched to the scene. As a precaution, both the pier and its adjoining amusement park were cleared of all visitors. Police took to social media to confirm the incident, underscoring the serious nature of the threat and the immediate actions taken.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The standoff reached its conclusion around 4:15 p.m., with police taking the man into custody. Authorities thoroughly inspected the scene and, much to everyone’s relief, announced that no bomb or other explosive device was discovered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Several bystanders captured the event on their mobile devices, and footage revealed officers tackling the man as he descended from the Ferris wheel. These visuals quickly made their way to social media platforms and news outlets, amplifying the tension and drama of the situation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adding to the tension, dozens of visitors were left stranded on the Ferris wheel during the crisis. Their prolonged wait in the gondolas only added to the palpable anxiety of the situation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This incident, while thankfully resolved without any injuries or actual threats, underscores the vulnerabilities of public spaces and the challenges law enforcement agencies face. Vigilance and quick response from both the public and authorities were critical in ensuring that the situation didn’t escalate further.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Santa Monica Pier, a symbol of joy and recreation for many, became the center of a tense showdown, reminding all of the unpredictabilities of public spaces and the importance of safety protocols.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a shocking turn of events, a man scaled the Ferris wheel at Santa Monica Pier on Monday, causing a major scare by claiming he possessed a bomb. The iconic tourist destination was swiftly evacuated amidst the growing alarm. Early in the afternoon, onlookers watched in a mix of horror and curiosity as the man climbed the famed Ferris wheel. Witnesses reported overhearing the man’s bomb claims, prompting immediate action by local authorities. The Santa Monica Police Department’s Crisis Negotiation Team was promptly dispatched to the scene. As a precaution, both the pier and its adjoining amusement park were cleared of all visitors. Police took to social media to confirm the incident, underscoring the serious nature of the threat and the immediate actions taken. The standoff reached its conclusion around 4:15 p.m., with police taking the man into custody. Authorities thoroughly inspected the scene and, much to everyone’s relief, announced that no bomb or other explosive device was discovered. Several bystanders captured the event on their mobile devices, and footage revealed officers tackling the man as he descended from the Ferris wheel. These visuals quickly made their way to social media platforms and news outlets, amplifying the tension and drama of the situation. Adding to the tension, dozens of visitors were left stranded on the Ferris wheel during the crisis. Their prolonged wait in the gondolas only added to the palpable anxiety of the situation. This incident, while thankfully resolved without any injuries or actual threats, underscores the vulnerabilities of public spaces and the challenges law enforcement agencies face. Vigilance and quick response from both the public and authorities were critical in ensuring that the situation didn’t escalate further. The Santa Monica Pier, a symbol of joy and recreation for many, became the center of a tense showdown, reminding all of the unpredictabilities of public spaces and the importance of safety protocols.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Silent Stars: Top Celebrities Stay Mum on Israel Amidst Hamas Attacks</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/11/Celebrity-Instagram-Stance/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Silent Stars: Top Celebrities Stay Mum on Israel Amidst Hamas Attacks" /><published>2023-10-11T07:09:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-11T07:09:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/11/Celebrity-Instagram-Stance</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/11/Celebrity-Instagram-Stance/">&lt;p&gt;In the wake of recent violent attacks by Hamas on Israel, resulting in over 1,100 Israeli casualties, top-tier celebrities on Instagram have been surprisingly quiet. An observation made just four days post the bloody events reveals that none of the ten most-followed celebrity Instagram accounts have expressed their support for Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyonce, Dwayne “The Rock” Johnson, and notable members of the Kardashian family, among others, have kept their opinions about the situation under wraps. The exception being Kylie Jenner who briefly posted a pro-Israel message, but quickly retracted and deleted it after a wave of negative responses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Top celebrities like Selena Gomez, Ariana Grande, and football sensations Cristiano Ronaldo and Lionel Messi have also refrained from commenting on the situation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This lack of response might reflect a complex PR landscape for celebrities. Taking a stance on the Israel-Palestine issue can potentially alienate certain fanbases or invite media scrutiny, especially since mainstream news often leans anti-Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, these celebrities had been rather vocal when it came to supporting the Black Lives Matter movement in the past, even though it’s polarizing within the U.S. populace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recall Beyonce dedicating her 2020 BET Humanitarian Award to BLM supporters, Dwayne Johnson’s vocal support on Twitter alongside a critique of then-President Donald Trump, or Ariana Grande joining a BLM protest march in Los Angeles. Additionally, Selena Gomez expressed her solidarity with the BLM movement on Instagram, and both Kim Kardashian and Kylie Jenner contributed monetary donations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently, the Chicago chapter of BLM voiced their support for Palestinians over Israel. Their post included a graphic illustrating a Hamas terrorist in a paragliding attack — mirroring the very tactic used against Israelis during a music festival on the weekend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, some celebrities have bucked the trend. Noteworthy figures like Debra Messing, Amy Schumer, Mark Hamill, Jamie Lee Curtis, and Israeli natives Gal Gadot and Natalie Portman have been openly supportive of Israel during these trying times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As tensions continue, the entertainment world’s response—or lack thereof—offers a fascinating glimpse into the intricate dance between celebrity influence and international politics.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">In the wake of recent violent attacks by Hamas on Israel, resulting in over 1,100 Israeli casualties, top-tier celebrities on Instagram have been surprisingly quiet. An observation made just four days post the bloody events reveals that none of the ten most-followed celebrity Instagram accounts have expressed their support for Israel. Beyonce, Dwayne “The Rock” Johnson, and notable members of the Kardashian family, among others, have kept their opinions about the situation under wraps. The exception being Kylie Jenner who briefly posted a pro-Israel message, but quickly retracted and deleted it after a wave of negative responses. Top celebrities like Selena Gomez, Ariana Grande, and football sensations Cristiano Ronaldo and Lionel Messi have also refrained from commenting on the situation. This lack of response might reflect a complex PR landscape for celebrities. Taking a stance on the Israel-Palestine issue can potentially alienate certain fanbases or invite media scrutiny, especially since mainstream news often leans anti-Israel. However, these celebrities had been rather vocal when it came to supporting the Black Lives Matter movement in the past, even though it’s polarizing within the U.S. populace. Recall Beyonce dedicating her 2020 BET Humanitarian Award to BLM supporters, Dwayne Johnson’s vocal support on Twitter alongside a critique of then-President Donald Trump, or Ariana Grande joining a BLM protest march in Los Angeles. Additionally, Selena Gomez expressed her solidarity with the BLM movement on Instagram, and both Kim Kardashian and Kylie Jenner contributed monetary donations. Recently, the Chicago chapter of BLM voiced their support for Palestinians over Israel. Their post included a graphic illustrating a Hamas terrorist in a paragliding attack — mirroring the very tactic used against Israelis during a music festival on the weekend. However, some celebrities have bucked the trend. Noteworthy figures like Debra Messing, Amy Schumer, Mark Hamill, Jamie Lee Curtis, and Israeli natives Gal Gadot and Natalie Portman have been openly supportive of Israel during these trying times. As tensions continue, the entertainment world’s response—or lack thereof—offers a fascinating glimpse into the intricate dance between celebrity influence and international politics.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">GOP Tensions Rise: Dueling Proposals Highlight Speaker Selection Struggle</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/11/House-Speaker-Debate/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="GOP Tensions Rise: Dueling Proposals Highlight Speaker Selection Struggle" /><published>2023-10-11T06:05:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-11T06:05:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/11/House-Speaker-Debate</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/11/House-Speaker-Debate/">&lt;p&gt;House Republicans are in a heated debate, introducing competing amendments to the House GOP rules, underlining the division within the party as they gear up to elect their new speaker.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the heart of the matter, Rep. Chip Roy proposed an amendment that raises the bar for nominating a speaker candidate, setting the requirement at 217 votes – equivalent to a House majority. This initiative comes in light of the memory of Former Speaker Kevin McCarthy’s lengthy 15-round election journey to acquire the gavel earlier in the year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Supporters of this amendment argue its merit, suggesting that it’s a pivotal step towards preventing future internal battles from taking the center stage, and ensuring greater unity within the House GOP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the rule hasn’t been met with unanimous approval. Rep. Tom McClintock, another significant Republican figure, labeled Roy’s proposal as “an absurdity on its face.” He emphasized the flaw in the existing process of ousting a speaker, which allows for the removal of the chosen speaker by merely a handful of disgruntled members. McClintock voiced his concern in strong terms, stating that such a system amounts to “childish despotism and utter nonsense.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In response, McClintock proposed an alternative: any member going against the collective decision of the conference on procedural matters, including speaker votes and rule changes, should face expulsion. To readmit such an expelled member, a two-thirds majority of the conference would have to vote in favor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, amidst these swirling controversies, there have been calls to bring back McCarthy as the speaker. However, the chances of that happening seem slim, given McCarthy’s own expressed disinclination to reclaim the position.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As of now, all eyes are on Majority Leader Steve Scalise and Judiciary Chair Jim Jordan, the two major contenders for the speaker’s position. House Republicans are geared up to hear their pitches and are expected to convene again to finalize their decision on the next speaker.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ongoing disagreements underscore the challenges that lie ahead for the GOP as they attempt to showcase unity and strength in these politically tumultuous times.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">House Republicans are in a heated debate, introducing competing amendments to the House GOP rules, underlining the division within the party as they gear up to elect their new speaker. At the heart of the matter, Rep. Chip Roy proposed an amendment that raises the bar for nominating a speaker candidate, setting the requirement at 217 votes – equivalent to a House majority. This initiative comes in light of the memory of Former Speaker Kevin McCarthy’s lengthy 15-round election journey to acquire the gavel earlier in the year. Supporters of this amendment argue its merit, suggesting that it’s a pivotal step towards preventing future internal battles from taking the center stage, and ensuring greater unity within the House GOP. However, the rule hasn’t been met with unanimous approval. Rep. Tom McClintock, another significant Republican figure, labeled Roy’s proposal as “an absurdity on its face.” He emphasized the flaw in the existing process of ousting a speaker, which allows for the removal of the chosen speaker by merely a handful of disgruntled members. McClintock voiced his concern in strong terms, stating that such a system amounts to “childish despotism and utter nonsense.” In response, McClintock proposed an alternative: any member going against the collective decision of the conference on procedural matters, including speaker votes and rule changes, should face expulsion. To readmit such an expelled member, a two-thirds majority of the conference would have to vote in favor. Interestingly, amidst these swirling controversies, there have been calls to bring back McCarthy as the speaker. However, the chances of that happening seem slim, given McCarthy’s own expressed disinclination to reclaim the position. As of now, all eyes are on Majority Leader Steve Scalise and Judiciary Chair Jim Jordan, the two major contenders for the speaker’s position. House Republicans are geared up to hear their pitches and are expected to convene again to finalize their decision on the next speaker. The ongoing disagreements underscore the challenges that lie ahead for the GOP as they attempt to showcase unity and strength in these politically tumultuous times.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Heart Alert: The New Syndrome Affecting 1 in 3 Americans</title><link href="/news/2023/10/10/Heart-Syndrome-Diagnosis/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Heart Alert: The New Syndrome Affecting 1 in 3 Americans" /><published>2023-10-10T15:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-10T15:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/10/Heart-Syndrome-Diagnosis</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/10/Heart-Syndrome-Diagnosis/">&lt;p&gt;A groundbreaking discovery by the American Heart Association has revealed a new medical syndrome, named Cardiovascular-Kidney-Metabolic Syndrome (CKM). This syndrome accentuates the strong link between obesity, heart disease, and kidney disorders. The main aim behind identifying CKM? To diagnose those most vulnerable to fatal cardiovascular diseases at the earliest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to Dr. Chiadi Ndumele, the advisory’s chief author and the director of obesity and cardiometabolic research at Johns Hopkins University, the core objective is “reducing the pipeline of individuals progressing toward heart disease.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Diving deep into the intricacies of CKM, research shows metabolic risk factors like abdominal fat, elevated blood pressure, heightened cholesterol, and increased blood sugar can adversely affect our vital organs. Dr. Pam Taub, a renowned cardiologist from the UC San Diego School of Medicine, considers CKM identification a pivotal moment for patients with high risks. The early detection and subsequent treatment of affected organs have resulted in a notable reduction in cardiovascular events.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CKM detection not only allows professionals to understand the interplay between organs but also paves the way for early diagnosis, preventing heart-wrenching cardiovascular outcomes. There’s a silver lining too: individuals diagnosed with this newly recognized condition can show improvement if it’s identified timely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For an efficient diagnosis process, Dr. Ndumele’s team has crafted a comprehensive four-stage system:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stage 0&lt;/strong&gt;: No discernible risk factors.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stage 1&lt;/strong&gt;: Targets those overweight or with signs of pre-diabetes. Recommendations include healthy lifestyle changes aiming for a minimum 5% weight reduction.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stage 2&lt;/strong&gt;: Focuses on individuals with Type 2 diabetes, kidney disease, high triglycerides, or increased blood pressure. Treatment may encompass medications controlling blood pressure, blood sugar, and cholesterol.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stage 3&lt;/strong&gt;: Individuals with metabolic risk factors but remain asymptomatic. Intervention might involve heart medicines and arterial examinations.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stage 4&lt;/strong&gt;: Persons diagnosed with heart disease or associated conditions. Treatment is devised based on the specific condition and associated symptoms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The numbers are staggering. Dr. Ndumele approximates a whopping 90% of U.S. adults lie somewhere on the CKM spectrum, attributable to the alarming rates of obesity and Type 2 diabetes observed in both adults and young ones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To put it in perspective, per the American Heart Association’s presidential advisory, every third adult in the U.S. showcases three or more risk elements, predisposing them to cardiovascular disease, metabolic disorders, or kidney ailments. CKM’s clasp is vast, impacting major organs including the heart, brain, kidney, and liver. Yet, its most profound influence is observed on the cardiovascular system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This breakthrough is bound to redefine medical paradigms. As Dr. Ndumele aptly put it, “Screening for kidney and metabolic disease will help us start protective therapies earlier, paving the way to more effectively prevent heart disease and manage existing ones.”&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">A groundbreaking discovery by the American Heart Association has revealed a new medical syndrome, named Cardiovascular-Kidney-Metabolic Syndrome (CKM). This syndrome accentuates the strong link between obesity, heart disease, and kidney disorders. The main aim behind identifying CKM? To diagnose those most vulnerable to fatal cardiovascular diseases at the earliest. According to Dr. Chiadi Ndumele, the advisory’s chief author and the director of obesity and cardiometabolic research at Johns Hopkins University, the core objective is “reducing the pipeline of individuals progressing toward heart disease.” Diving deep into the intricacies of CKM, research shows metabolic risk factors like abdominal fat, elevated blood pressure, heightened cholesterol, and increased blood sugar can adversely affect our vital organs. Dr. Pam Taub, a renowned cardiologist from the UC San Diego School of Medicine, considers CKM identification a pivotal moment for patients with high risks. The early detection and subsequent treatment of affected organs have resulted in a notable reduction in cardiovascular events. CKM detection not only allows professionals to understand the interplay between organs but also paves the way for early diagnosis, preventing heart-wrenching cardiovascular outcomes. There’s a silver lining too: individuals diagnosed with this newly recognized condition can show improvement if it’s identified timely. For an efficient diagnosis process, Dr. Ndumele’s team has crafted a comprehensive four-stage system: Stage 0: No discernible risk factors. Stage 1: Targets those overweight or with signs of pre-diabetes. Recommendations include healthy lifestyle changes aiming for a minimum 5% weight reduction. Stage 2: Focuses on individuals with Type 2 diabetes, kidney disease, high triglycerides, or increased blood pressure. Treatment may encompass medications controlling blood pressure, blood sugar, and cholesterol. Stage 3: Individuals with metabolic risk factors but remain asymptomatic. Intervention might involve heart medicines and arterial examinations. Stage 4: Persons diagnosed with heart disease or associated conditions. Treatment is devised based on the specific condition and associated symptoms. The numbers are staggering. Dr. Ndumele approximates a whopping 90% of U.S. adults lie somewhere on the CKM spectrum, attributable to the alarming rates of obesity and Type 2 diabetes observed in both adults and young ones. To put it in perspective, per the American Heart Association’s presidential advisory, every third adult in the U.S. showcases three or more risk elements, predisposing them to cardiovascular disease, metabolic disorders, or kidney ailments. CKM’s clasp is vast, impacting major organs including the heart, brain, kidney, and liver. Yet, its most profound influence is observed on the cardiovascular system. This breakthrough is bound to redefine medical paradigms. As Dr. Ndumele aptly put it, “Screening for kidney and metabolic disease will help us start protective therapies earlier, paving the way to more effectively prevent heart disease and manage existing ones.”</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Amazon’s Alexa Makes Stolen Election Claims</title><link href="/news/2023/10/10/Amazon-Alexa-Claims/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Amazon’s Alexa Makes Stolen Election Claims" /><published>2023-10-10T14:01:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-10T14:01:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/10/Amazon-Alexa-Claims</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/10/Amazon-Alexa-Claims/">&lt;p&gt;In a startling revelation, Amazon’s widely-used voice assistant, Alexa, reportedly claimed that the 2020 U.S. presidential election was “stolen by a massive amount of election fraud.” The election saw a contest between former President Donald Trump and President Joe Biden.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Washington Post, a leading newspaper, reported that Alexa provided users with information suggesting that the 2020 presidential election had been “stolen.” While details about the specific Alexa version tested weren’t mentioned, the assistant’s source for the claim was cited as Rumble. For those unaware, Rumble serves as an alternative video streaming platform to Google’s YouTube.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, Alexa was reported to inform users that the 2020 election was characterized by “many incidents of irregularities and indications pointing to electoral fraud occurring in major metro centers.” Interestingly, the voice assistant also referenced the newsletter service, Substack, as its source.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Such assertions from a leading tech giant’s voice assistant understandably raise eyebrows, given the broader conversations around misinformation and the role of technology platforms in curating content. Addressing the issue, Amazon promptly responded to the Washington Post, clarifying that the claims were an error. An Amazon spokesperson stated, “These responses were errors that were delivered a small number of times, and quickly fixed when brought to our attention.” Amazon emphasizes its commitment to accuracy by continually auditing and refining systems in place to detect and prevent inaccurate content dissemination.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, following the issue being flagged and Amazon’s statement, Alexa, when posed with questions regarding the legitimacy of the 2020 U.S. presidential election, began abstaining from answering, as noted by the Washington Post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As voice assistants become an integral part of daily life, influencing decisions from shopping to news consumption, the accuracy of the information they provide becomes paramount. With Alexa’s reach in numerous households, claims like these highlight the significance of ensuring accurate and unbiased content delivery. As the world navigates the challenges of misinformation in the digital age, the role of tech giants like Amazon becomes ever crucial in shaping informed societies.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a startling revelation, Amazon’s widely-used voice assistant, Alexa, reportedly claimed that the 2020 U.S. presidential election was “stolen by a massive amount of election fraud.” The election saw a contest between former President Donald Trump and President Joe Biden. The Washington Post, a leading newspaper, reported that Alexa provided users with information suggesting that the 2020 presidential election had been “stolen.” While details about the specific Alexa version tested weren’t mentioned, the assistant’s source for the claim was cited as Rumble. For those unaware, Rumble serves as an alternative video streaming platform to Google’s YouTube. Furthermore, Alexa was reported to inform users that the 2020 election was characterized by “many incidents of irregularities and indications pointing to electoral fraud occurring in major metro centers.” Interestingly, the voice assistant also referenced the newsletter service, Substack, as its source. Such assertions from a leading tech giant’s voice assistant understandably raise eyebrows, given the broader conversations around misinformation and the role of technology platforms in curating content. Addressing the issue, Amazon promptly responded to the Washington Post, clarifying that the claims were an error. An Amazon spokesperson stated, “These responses were errors that were delivered a small number of times, and quickly fixed when brought to our attention.” Amazon emphasizes its commitment to accuracy by continually auditing and refining systems in place to detect and prevent inaccurate content dissemination. Interestingly, following the issue being flagged and Amazon’s statement, Alexa, when posed with questions regarding the legitimacy of the 2020 U.S. presidential election, began abstaining from answering, as noted by the Washington Post. As voice assistants become an integral part of daily life, influencing decisions from shopping to news consumption, the accuracy of the information they provide becomes paramount. With Alexa’s reach in numerous households, claims like these highlight the significance of ensuring accurate and unbiased content delivery. As the world navigates the challenges of misinformation in the digital age, the role of tech giants like Amazon becomes ever crucial in shaping informed societies.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Massive Walgreens Walkout: Pharmacy Workers Demand Better Working Conditions</title><link href="/news/2023/10/10/Walgreens-Walkout/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Massive Walgreens Walkout: Pharmacy Workers Demand Better Working Conditions" /><published>2023-10-10T13:07:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-10T13:07:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/10/Walgreens-Walkout</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/10/Walgreens-Walkout/">&lt;p&gt;Walgreens, a major pharmacy chain in the U.S., is facing a significant disruption in its operations as hundreds of employees across numerous stores stage walkouts. The primary reason behind this wave of protests? Alarming working conditions that employees claim jeopardize both their well-being and the safety of customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to inside sources who spoke with CNN, over 500 of Walgreens’ approximately 9,000 locations — a staggering 5.5 percent — have shown interest in participating in the strike, scheduled from Monday to Wednesday. As a result, many pharmacies in states like Arizona, Washington, Massachusetts, and Oregon have temporarily ceased operations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stores that remain operational are grappling with acute staff shortages as a large fraction of workers abstain from showing up. Some Walgreens outlets are striving to keep their drive-through services running, while others contemplate shutting their doors temporarily.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, what’s driving these pharmacy workers to take such drastic measures? The grievances listed are manifold: an uptick in responsibilities like vaccinations, coupled with confronting hostile customers and dealing with various forms of harassment. Amanda Applegate, interim executive director of the Kansas Pharmacists Association, described the plight of the pharmacists, likening them to ATMs, where the emphasis on volume trumps quality of service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The grassroots nature of this protest is evident. Without a central union leader orchestrating the demonstrations, the movement gains traction through word-of-mouth, social media, and even fliers. Under the hashtag “#OperationSpotlight,” pharmacy employees voice their concerns and frustrations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One striking visual that resonates with the sentiment of these workers is a placard outside a Walgreens store that reads: “Dear Public, There is NOT a Shortage of Pharmacists, Technicians. There is a shortage of pharmacy employees willing to work in conditions which put their lives and your life in danger!!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the outcry and visible impact on store operations, Walgreens’ corporate response seems underplayed. Although they acknowledge “some activity,” the company’s statement to CNN emphasizes that the “vast majority of pharmacies are operating across the country.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This wave of protests and the spotlight on working conditions come amidst another challenge retail stores face: increasing thefts. CVS, another pharmaceutical retail giant, announced plans to close around 900 of its stores by 2024 due to a spike in shoplifting incidents. Similarly, multiple CVS stores in Kansas City, Missouri, have had to close their doors for weeks owing to employee walkouts, echoing concerns about a “dangerous environment.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a country that heavily relies on retail pharmacies like Walgreens and CVS for their healthcare and medicinal needs, these walkouts are a wakeup call. The message from employees is clear: prioritize their safety and well-being for better services and a safer community.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Walgreens, a major pharmacy chain in the U.S., is facing a significant disruption in its operations as hundreds of employees across numerous stores stage walkouts. The primary reason behind this wave of protests? Alarming working conditions that employees claim jeopardize both their well-being and the safety of customers. According to inside sources who spoke with CNN, over 500 of Walgreens’ approximately 9,000 locations — a staggering 5.5 percent — have shown interest in participating in the strike, scheduled from Monday to Wednesday. As a result, many pharmacies in states like Arizona, Washington, Massachusetts, and Oregon have temporarily ceased operations. Stores that remain operational are grappling with acute staff shortages as a large fraction of workers abstain from showing up. Some Walgreens outlets are striving to keep their drive-through services running, while others contemplate shutting their doors temporarily. So, what’s driving these pharmacy workers to take such drastic measures? The grievances listed are manifold: an uptick in responsibilities like vaccinations, coupled with confronting hostile customers and dealing with various forms of harassment. Amanda Applegate, interim executive director of the Kansas Pharmacists Association, described the plight of the pharmacists, likening them to ATMs, where the emphasis on volume trumps quality of service. The grassroots nature of this protest is evident. Without a central union leader orchestrating the demonstrations, the movement gains traction through word-of-mouth, social media, and even fliers. Under the hashtag “#OperationSpotlight,” pharmacy employees voice their concerns and frustrations. One striking visual that resonates with the sentiment of these workers is a placard outside a Walgreens store that reads: “Dear Public, There is NOT a Shortage of Pharmacists, Technicians. There is a shortage of pharmacy employees willing to work in conditions which put their lives and your life in danger!!” Despite the outcry and visible impact on store operations, Walgreens’ corporate response seems underplayed. Although they acknowledge “some activity,” the company’s statement to CNN emphasizes that the “vast majority of pharmacies are operating across the country.” This wave of protests and the spotlight on working conditions come amidst another challenge retail stores face: increasing thefts. CVS, another pharmaceutical retail giant, announced plans to close around 900 of its stores by 2024 due to a spike in shoplifting incidents. Similarly, multiple CVS stores in Kansas City, Missouri, have had to close their doors for weeks owing to employee walkouts, echoing concerns about a “dangerous environment.” In a country that heavily relies on retail pharmacies like Walgreens and CVS for their healthcare and medicinal needs, these walkouts are a wakeup call. The message from employees is clear: prioritize their safety and well-being for better services and a safer community.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Virginia Man Faces Dual Life Sentences Over Fatal Assault on Toddler</title><link href="/news/2023/10/10/Child-Tragedy-Virginia/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Virginia Man Faces Dual Life Sentences Over Fatal Assault on Toddler" /><published>2023-10-10T11:45:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-10T11:45:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/10/Child-Tragedy-Virginia</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/10/Child-Tragedy-Virginia/">&lt;p&gt;In a tragic event that has shaken the state of Virginia, a man has been sentenced to two life terms after being found guilty of fatally attacking a 2-year-old toddler and later neglecting to provide her with the needed medical care, which led to her unfortunate demise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The assailant, 37-year-old Andrew Byrd, was convicted in March on multiple counts, including aggravated murder and aggravated malicious wounding, for the 2020 assault on Harper Mitchell, his girlfriend’s young daughter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chris Rehak, the Commonwealth’s Attorney, shared his sentiments on the case, noting that it was one of the gravest crimes on record. The horrific details paint a clear picture of a brutal attack on an innocent child, with Rehak stating, “&lt;em&gt;This defendant tortured that poor little girl.&lt;/em&gt;”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The incident occurred on April 16 in Byrd’s Roanoke residence. The child’s mother, Amanda Mitchell, was away at work, leaving Harper and her siblings under Byrd’s supervision. Upon her return, Amanda found Harper in a distressing state — bruised, cold, and unresponsive. However, Byrd’s violent tendencies did not end there. As Mitchell tried to seek medical help, Byrd stopped her, going as far as threatening the life of her other children, the local media sources reported.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Roanoke Times described how Byrd prioritized his drug habits over the life of the young child, with Rehak mentioning that Byrd’s primary concern that fateful night was “&lt;em&gt;getting high&lt;/em&gt;”. It was only the following morning that Mitchell could reach out to Byrd’s mother, leading to a 911 call. Although Harper was immediately rushed to a hospital, she could not be saved. The extent of her injuries, as described by medical examiner Dr. Amy Tharp, resembled those sustained in a severe car accident. The cause of death: blunt-force trauma to the head.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the defense tried to protect Byrd by pointing out the lack of eyewitnesses and highlighting his history with substance abuse, their arguments did not hold up against the overwhelming evidence. Byrd had previously attempted to justify Harper’s injuries by suggesting she might have fallen down stairs or off a four-wheeler. Commonwealth’s Attorney Rehak didn’t mince words in court, describing Byrd as a “&lt;em&gt;dangerous, violent liar&lt;/em&gt;”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a moving statement during the sentencing, the child’s father, TJ Mitchell, expressed the deep void left behind by Harper’s tragic passing. Circuit Judge Joey Showalter emphasized that no individual, especially an innocent child, should ever face such brutality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the case unfolds further, Amanda Mitchell faces her own legal battles with charges of child abuse, cruelty, and drug possession. Byrd also has additional charges to answer for, related to the alleged abuse of Mitchell’s sons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a world where child abuse continues to be a haunting reality, Harper Mitchell’s story serves as a heartbreaking reminder of the need for continued vigilance, protection, and justice for the most vulnerable.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a tragic event that has shaken the state of Virginia, a man has been sentenced to two life terms after being found guilty of fatally attacking a 2-year-old toddler and later neglecting to provide her with the needed medical care, which led to her unfortunate demise. The assailant, 37-year-old Andrew Byrd, was convicted in March on multiple counts, including aggravated murder and aggravated malicious wounding, for the 2020 assault on Harper Mitchell, his girlfriend’s young daughter. Chris Rehak, the Commonwealth’s Attorney, shared his sentiments on the case, noting that it was one of the gravest crimes on record. The horrific details paint a clear picture of a brutal attack on an innocent child, with Rehak stating, “This defendant tortured that poor little girl.” The incident occurred on April 16 in Byrd’s Roanoke residence. The child’s mother, Amanda Mitchell, was away at work, leaving Harper and her siblings under Byrd’s supervision. Upon her return, Amanda found Harper in a distressing state — bruised, cold, and unresponsive. However, Byrd’s violent tendencies did not end there. As Mitchell tried to seek medical help, Byrd stopped her, going as far as threatening the life of her other children, the local media sources reported. The Roanoke Times described how Byrd prioritized his drug habits over the life of the young child, with Rehak mentioning that Byrd’s primary concern that fateful night was “getting high”. It was only the following morning that Mitchell could reach out to Byrd’s mother, leading to a 911 call. Although Harper was immediately rushed to a hospital, she could not be saved. The extent of her injuries, as described by medical examiner Dr. Amy Tharp, resembled those sustained in a severe car accident. The cause of death: blunt-force trauma to the head. While the defense tried to protect Byrd by pointing out the lack of eyewitnesses and highlighting his history with substance abuse, their arguments did not hold up against the overwhelming evidence. Byrd had previously attempted to justify Harper’s injuries by suggesting she might have fallen down stairs or off a four-wheeler. Commonwealth’s Attorney Rehak didn’t mince words in court, describing Byrd as a “dangerous, violent liar”. In a moving statement during the sentencing, the child’s father, TJ Mitchell, expressed the deep void left behind by Harper’s tragic passing. Circuit Judge Joey Showalter emphasized that no individual, especially an innocent child, should ever face such brutality. As the case unfolds further, Amanda Mitchell faces her own legal battles with charges of child abuse, cruelty, and drug possession. Byrd also has additional charges to answer for, related to the alleged abuse of Mitchell’s sons. In a world where child abuse continues to be a haunting reality, Harper Mitchell’s story serves as a heartbreaking reminder of the need for continued vigilance, protection, and justice for the most vulnerable.</summary></entry></feed>