<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-11-01T09:18:32-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/11/01/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-11-01T09:18:32-04:00</published><updated>2023-11-01T09:18:32-04:00</updated><id>/2023/11/01/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/11/01/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/11/01/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-11-01T09:18:32-04:00</published><updated>2023-11-01T09:18:32-04:00</updated><id>/2023/11/01/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/11/01/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/">&lt;p&gt;Recent surprise attacks by Hamas on Israel has fueled ongoing tensions between staunchly conservative commentators and the progressive “Squad” Democrats known for criticizing Israel. The intensity of the backlash highlights the deep political divide over foreign policy in the Middle East.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Hamas’ shocking attack, several members of the “Squad,” including Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.), called for a “ceasefire and de-escalation,” condemning the violence. The absence of a statement from Rep. Rashida Tlaib (D-Mich.) was notably called out by conservative media outlets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;South Carolina GOP Rep. Nancy Mace quickly labeled Ocasio-Cortez a “Hamas apologist” in response to her call for peace and de-escalation. Rep. Ilhan Omar (D-Minn.), no stranger to controversy surrounding her views on Israel, echoed the call for de-escalation and ceasefire. Omar’s prior statements comparing the US and Israel to terrorist groups like Hamas and the Taliban resurfaced in the debate, fueling more criticisms. Omar’s 2019 tweet, where she opined that “Israel has hypnotized the world,” also continues to haunt her political career, often cited by critics to challenge her stance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conservative commentators have been especially vocal. “FOX &amp;amp; Friends Weekend” co-host Rachel Campos-Duffy took aim at Omar, saying she fails to recognize the peace in the Middle East under Trump’s administration. Conservative pundit John Hasson also called out Omar, claiming she insinuated that attacks on IDF forces were acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Massachusetts Democrat Rep. Ayanna Pressley’s concerns over the “devastating attacks on Israelis” were met with skepticism. A prominent conservative online personality, Comfortably Smug, accused the “Squad” of advising Israel to back down after the nation suffered massive attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Jamaal Bowman’s call for an end to the Gaza blockade, in addition to condemning the Hamas attacks, was met with criticism from conservative radio host Jason Rantz. He accused Bowman of pairing his condemnation of terrorism with unwarranted criticisms of Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Cori Bush emphasized the urgent need for a ceasefire, while pushing for an end to “U.S. support for Israeli military occupation and apartheid.” Defense attorney Marina Medvin criticized Bush, suggesting that she equates the death of Palestinian terrorists to the horrific acts committed against Jewish civilians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amidst the political turmoil and intense debate, the attacks have taken a heavy toll. Israeli media report over 300 dead due to the wide-ranging assault. Gaza health officials note that at least 200 Palestinians have perished in the retaliatory Israeli air strikes following the initial Hamas attack. As the situation remains volatile, both sides continue to count their casualties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This divisive issue showcases the challenge America faces in crafting a unified approach to foreign policy, with deeply entrenched political divides at play. As the situation develops, the debate is bound to intensify, shedding light on the complexities of U.S. politics in the global arena.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Decoding the Biden Family Saga: Business or Benefaction?</title><link href="/politics/2023/11/01/Biden-Family-Business-Dealings/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Decoding the Biden Family Saga: Business or Benefaction?" /><published>2023-11-01T08:51:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-11-01T08:51:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/11/01/Biden-Family-Business-Dealings</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/11/01/Biden-Family-Business-Dealings/">&lt;p&gt;In an era where transparency in politics is more crucial than ever, the Biden family’s financial dealings have come under intense scrutiny. Large sums of money changing hands within the family, coupled with President Biden’s denial of involvement in his son’s international business dealings, have raised eyebrows and serious questions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The financial tapestry woven by the Biden family includes a questionable $200,000 payment received by Joe Biden from his brother, James Biden, following a loan of the same amount granted to James by a health care company he was affiliated with. The exchange was purportedly for access and influence, a claim that brings into question the ethics of the family’s dealings. This is not an isolated incident; it’s part of a pattern that has persisted over the years, with the family using loans and other financial mechanisms to maneuver money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the labyrinth of the Biden family’s finances, the use of over 20 shell companies to move money discreetly has also come to light. This, coupled with the ‘loans’ used to facilitate the transfer of funds between family members, paints a picture of complexity and secrecy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As we dig deeper, another layer of this financial web reveals itself. In 2020, Hollywood attorney Kevin Morris cleared a $2 million unpaid tax liability for Hunter Biden. Initially labeled as a ‘loan,’ the paperwork supporting this claim seemed to materialize only after the IRS began raising suspicions, casting further doubt on the nature of the transaction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These financial intricacies demand transparency and scrutiny, especially when they involve individuals in the highest offices of the land. The House of Representatives has taken up the mantle to investigate, ensuring that those in power are held accountable and are not using their positions for personal gain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whistleblowers from the IRS have also come forward, alleging that the Biden Justice Department obstructed investigations into potential campaign finance violations involving the Biden presidential campaign. This accusation adds another layer of complexity to the situation, emphasizing the need for a thorough and impartial investigation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the House delves into these so-called ‘loans’ and financial dealings, the American people watch closely, with polls indicating that nearly half of the adult population believes President Biden may have been involved in illegal activities concerning his son. The trust in our institutions and in our leaders is at stake, and it is incumbent upon Congress to uncover the truth, wherever it may lead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In these trying times, our democracy demands diligence, transparency, and accountability from its leaders. The ongoing inquiry into the Biden family’s business dealings is not just about financial transactions; it’s about upholding the values that our nation holds dear and ensuring that those in power are serving the American people, and not their own interests.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In an era where transparency in politics is more crucial than ever, the Biden family’s financial dealings have come under intense scrutiny. Large sums of money changing hands within the family, coupled with President Biden’s denial of involvement in his son’s international business dealings, have raised eyebrows and serious questions. The financial tapestry woven by the Biden family includes a questionable $200,000 payment received by Joe Biden from his brother, James Biden, following a loan of the same amount granted to James by a health care company he was affiliated with. The exchange was purportedly for access and influence, a claim that brings into question the ethics of the family’s dealings. This is not an isolated incident; it’s part of a pattern that has persisted over the years, with the family using loans and other financial mechanisms to maneuver money. In the labyrinth of the Biden family’s finances, the use of over 20 shell companies to move money discreetly has also come to light. This, coupled with the ‘loans’ used to facilitate the transfer of funds between family members, paints a picture of complexity and secrecy. As we dig deeper, another layer of this financial web reveals itself. In 2020, Hollywood attorney Kevin Morris cleared a $2 million unpaid tax liability for Hunter Biden. Initially labeled as a ‘loan,’ the paperwork supporting this claim seemed to materialize only after the IRS began raising suspicions, casting further doubt on the nature of the transaction. These financial intricacies demand transparency and scrutiny, especially when they involve individuals in the highest offices of the land. The House of Representatives has taken up the mantle to investigate, ensuring that those in power are held accountable and are not using their positions for personal gain. Whistleblowers from the IRS have also come forward, alleging that the Biden Justice Department obstructed investigations into potential campaign finance violations involving the Biden presidential campaign. This accusation adds another layer of complexity to the situation, emphasizing the need for a thorough and impartial investigation. As the House delves into these so-called ‘loans’ and financial dealings, the American people watch closely, with polls indicating that nearly half of the adult population believes President Biden may have been involved in illegal activities concerning his son. The trust in our institutions and in our leaders is at stake, and it is incumbent upon Congress to uncover the truth, wherever it may lead. In these trying times, our democracy demands diligence, transparency, and accountability from its leaders. The ongoing inquiry into the Biden family’s business dealings is not just about financial transactions; it’s about upholding the values that our nation holds dear and ensuring that those in power are serving the American people, and not their own interests.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Biden’s Hidden Agenda: Paving the Way for White Collar Migration</title><link href="/news/2023/10/31/Biden-White-Collar-Migration/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Biden’s Hidden Agenda: Paving the Way for White Collar Migration" /><published>2023-10-31T15:36:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-31T15:36:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/31/Biden-White-Collar-Migration</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/31/Biden-White-Collar-Migration/">&lt;p&gt;In a recent maneuver that has left many scratching their heads, President Joe Biden has unabashedly opened the floodgates for more white-collar migration into the United States, specifically targeting the jobs that our own debt-ridden graduates so desperately need. This bold move has been neatly packaged in the “Executive Order on Safe, Secure, and Trustworthy Artificial Intelligence,” a directive that on the surface promises innovation and progress but delves deeper into a sea of questionable decisions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those unacquainted with the notorious H-1B visa program, it is a gateway for approximately 200,000 foreign graduates annually, promising them a slice of the American Dream. However, critics like Kevin Lynn, founder of U.S. TechWorkers, are calling out Biden’s decision, likening it to setting up a new era of indentured servitude. The program is not just a vessel for top-tier talent as it’s often portrayed but has become a tool for corporations to displace American workers, holding their foreign employees’ futures hostage with the dangling carrot of a green card.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With over 1.5 million visa workers already saturating various sectors of the U.S. job market, the expansion of this program only stands to exacerbate the issue. The Biden administration, backed by Fortune 500 lobbyists and investors, is pushing this agenda forward, indifferent to the potential career derailment for skilled American graduates. Employers are quick to cash in on this opportunity, leaving American workers in the dust.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Divyansh Kaushik, an imported Indian immigrant and representative of a white-collar employers lobby group, has already laid out a comprehensive list of ‘benefits’ this executive order brings to the table. From easier visa renewals to fast-tracked green cards for favored foreigners, it’s a shopping list designed to serve employers, not employees. This, while native STEM graduates are left grappling with a saturated job market, as highlighted by a 2021 Census Bureau report.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s most troubling is the sheer volume of technically skilled American graduates being flushed out of their careers, especially as they age. The displacement does not just impact individual careers but has far-reaching implications on national competitiveness and innovation. While Biden’s directive promises growth and leadership in innovation, it simultaneously undermines the very workforce capable of driving that progress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Critics argue that the issue at hand is not migration itself, but the insatiable hunger of Wall Street for short-term profits, a hunger that seems to be dictating policy decisions. The Biden administration’s plan, veiled as a step towards innovation, is a dangerous dance with economic instability, sidelining American workers in favor of short-term corporate gains.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As we navigate through this sea of contradictions and questionable policy decisions, one thing is clear: the American worker deserves better. The Biden administration’s directive is a stark reminder of the urgent need for policies that prioritize the American workforce, ensuring a future where innovation and progress are driven by the very people who call this nation home.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a recent maneuver that has left many scratching their heads, President Joe Biden has unabashedly opened the floodgates for more white-collar migration into the United States, specifically targeting the jobs that our own debt-ridden graduates so desperately need. This bold move has been neatly packaged in the “Executive Order on Safe, Secure, and Trustworthy Artificial Intelligence,” a directive that on the surface promises innovation and progress but delves deeper into a sea of questionable decisions. For those unacquainted with the notorious H-1B visa program, it is a gateway for approximately 200,000 foreign graduates annually, promising them a slice of the American Dream. However, critics like Kevin Lynn, founder of U.S. TechWorkers, are calling out Biden’s decision, likening it to setting up a new era of indentured servitude. The program is not just a vessel for top-tier talent as it’s often portrayed but has become a tool for corporations to displace American workers, holding their foreign employees’ futures hostage with the dangling carrot of a green card. With over 1.5 million visa workers already saturating various sectors of the U.S. job market, the expansion of this program only stands to exacerbate the issue. The Biden administration, backed by Fortune 500 lobbyists and investors, is pushing this agenda forward, indifferent to the potential career derailment for skilled American graduates. Employers are quick to cash in on this opportunity, leaving American workers in the dust. Divyansh Kaushik, an imported Indian immigrant and representative of a white-collar employers lobby group, has already laid out a comprehensive list of ‘benefits’ this executive order brings to the table. From easier visa renewals to fast-tracked green cards for favored foreigners, it’s a shopping list designed to serve employers, not employees. This, while native STEM graduates are left grappling with a saturated job market, as highlighted by a 2021 Census Bureau report. What’s most troubling is the sheer volume of technically skilled American graduates being flushed out of their careers, especially as they age. The displacement does not just impact individual careers but has far-reaching implications on national competitiveness and innovation. While Biden’s directive promises growth and leadership in innovation, it simultaneously undermines the very workforce capable of driving that progress. Critics argue that the issue at hand is not migration itself, but the insatiable hunger of Wall Street for short-term profits, a hunger that seems to be dictating policy decisions. The Biden administration’s plan, veiled as a step towards innovation, is a dangerous dance with economic instability, sidelining American workers in favor of short-term corporate gains. As we navigate through this sea of contradictions and questionable policy decisions, one thing is clear: the American worker deserves better. The Biden administration’s directive is a stark reminder of the urgent need for policies that prioritize the American workforce, ensuring a future where innovation and progress are driven by the very people who call this nation home.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Biden’s Golden Boy: How SEC Chairman Gensler’s Fortune Flourished in Public Service</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/31/Biden-Gensler-SEC-Wealth-Growth/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Biden’s Golden Boy: How SEC Chairman Gensler’s Fortune Flourished in Public Service" /><published>2023-10-31T14:23:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-31T14:23:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/31/Biden-Gensler-SEC-Wealth-Growth</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/31/Biden-Gensler-SEC-Wealth-Growth/">&lt;p&gt;Gary Gensler, the man appointed by President Biden to lead the nation’s top financial regulator - the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), seems to have struck gold during his years in public service. His net worth has reportedly skyrocketed by an astounding 650% over the last decade, raising eyebrows and questions about the ethics of wealth accumulation while in government roles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gensler, who took the reins of the SEC in 2021, has watched his fortune grow from between $15.5 million and $61.8 million in 2009, to a staggering $40 million to $116.2 million as of his most recent financial disclosure. These figures, revealed through financial filings obtained by Fox News Digital, shed light on the opulence that can be amassed even while serving in lead public-service roles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gensler’s portfolio is diverse, with substantial investments in exchange-traded funds (ETFs) and a considerable property in Maryland. His largest investment lies in Vanguard’s Total Market Index Fund ETF, valued between $25 million and $50 million, while his second-largest is a stake in Vanguard’s European Stock Index Fund ETF, worth between $5 million and $25 million.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Critics argue that such wealth accumulation while in public service raises serious questions about the integrity of our government officials. The revelation of Gensler’s financial prosperity comes at a time when bipartisan lawmakers are pressing for reforms on federal officials’ stock market trading activities, aiming to ensure that those in power are not profiting at the expense of the American public.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Senator Josh Hawley has been vocal about this issue, stating, “Politicians and civil servants shouldn’t spend their time day trading and trying to make a profit at the expense of the American public.” His sentiments are echoed by Senator Kirsten Gillibrand, emphasizing the need for transparency and integrity among government officials.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gensler’s journey to affluence has predominantly been through public service roles, including his tenure as the chair of the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) during the Obama administration, his leadership at the Maryland Financial Consumer Protection Commission, and various advisory positions. His lucrative positions and investments raise questions about the potential conflicts of interest and the moral responsibility of public servants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This issue of wealth accumulation in public service is not isolated to Gensler alone. Other prominent figures, such as Dr. Anthony Fauci and numerous congressional members, have also seen their net worths burgeon while serving the public. This pattern necessitates a reevaluation of the systems in place, ensuring that those entrusted with the nation’s welfare are held to the highest standards of integrity and transparency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In an era where trust in government is at a premium, the story of Gary Gensler serves as a stark reminder of the work that needs to be done to restore faith in our public institutions. As we navigate these challenging times, it is imperative that we demand accountability and transparency from our leaders, ensuring that public service remains a noble calling, free from the allure of personal financial gain.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Gary Gensler, the man appointed by President Biden to lead the nation’s top financial regulator - the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), seems to have struck gold during his years in public service. His net worth has reportedly skyrocketed by an astounding 650% over the last decade, raising eyebrows and questions about the ethics of wealth accumulation while in government roles. Gensler, who took the reins of the SEC in 2021, has watched his fortune grow from between $15.5 million and $61.8 million in 2009, to a staggering $40 million to $116.2 million as of his most recent financial disclosure. These figures, revealed through financial filings obtained by Fox News Digital, shed light on the opulence that can be amassed even while serving in lead public-service roles. Gensler’s portfolio is diverse, with substantial investments in exchange-traded funds (ETFs) and a considerable property in Maryland. His largest investment lies in Vanguard’s Total Market Index Fund ETF, valued between $25 million and $50 million, while his second-largest is a stake in Vanguard’s European Stock Index Fund ETF, worth between $5 million and $25 million. Critics argue that such wealth accumulation while in public service raises serious questions about the integrity of our government officials. The revelation of Gensler’s financial prosperity comes at a time when bipartisan lawmakers are pressing for reforms on federal officials’ stock market trading activities, aiming to ensure that those in power are not profiting at the expense of the American public. Senator Josh Hawley has been vocal about this issue, stating, “Politicians and civil servants shouldn’t spend their time day trading and trying to make a profit at the expense of the American public.” His sentiments are echoed by Senator Kirsten Gillibrand, emphasizing the need for transparency and integrity among government officials. Gensler’s journey to affluence has predominantly been through public service roles, including his tenure as the chair of the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) during the Obama administration, his leadership at the Maryland Financial Consumer Protection Commission, and various advisory positions. His lucrative positions and investments raise questions about the potential conflicts of interest and the moral responsibility of public servants. This issue of wealth accumulation in public service is not isolated to Gensler alone. Other prominent figures, such as Dr. Anthony Fauci and numerous congressional members, have also seen their net worths burgeon while serving the public. This pattern necessitates a reevaluation of the systems in place, ensuring that those entrusted with the nation’s welfare are held to the highest standards of integrity and transparency. In an era where trust in government is at a premium, the story of Gary Gensler serves as a stark reminder of the work that needs to be done to restore faith in our public institutions. As we navigate these challenging times, it is imperative that we demand accountability and transparency from our leaders, ensuring that public service remains a noble calling, free from the allure of personal financial gain.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Bidenflation Bites: McDonald’s Profits Soar as Burger Prices Skyrocket</title><link href="/news/2023/10/31/Bidenflation-Boosts-Burger-Prices/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bidenflation Bites: McDonald’s Profits Soar as Burger Prices Skyrocket" /><published>2023-10-31T13:12:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-31T13:12:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/31/Bidenflation-Boosts-Burger-Prices</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/31/Bidenflation-Boosts-Burger-Prices/">&lt;p&gt;In an era of skyrocketing prices and economic uncertainty, McDonald’s has found a way to turn the tide in its favor, reporting soaring profits and sales in the third quarter. The culprit? None other than the ominous Bidenflation, as rising burger prices contribute to the fast-food giant’s unexpected financial upswing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company’s profits and sales have beaten all estimates, pushing shares higher and leaving investors satisfied. However, this leaves the average American grappling with the reality of rising costs and a strained budget. Revenue shot up by 14 percent, reaching an astounding $6.69 billion, surpassing the expected $6.56 billion. Comparable store sales grew by 8.8 percent, leaving analysts’ 8.0 percent increase prediction in the dust.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chris Kempczinski, McDonald’s Chief Executive, confidently stated, “The macroeconomic environment is unfolding in line with our expectations for the year, and we continued to deliver convenience and value for our customers.” But at what cost?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the U.S. alone, comparable store sales witnessed an 8.1 percent increase, outpacing the forecasted 7.5 percent growth. “Comparable sales results benefited from strong average check growth driven by strategic menu price increases,” McDonald’s admitted. The stark reality is that these “strategic” price hikes are a direct result of the rampant inflation under the Biden administration, coined as Bidenflation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The increase in prices did manage to counteract a noticeable decline in foot traffic to McDonald’s locations. Yet, this reveals a concerning trend: higher costs are driving customers away, particularly those in lower income brackets. Kempczinski noted, “One of the things that we saw industry-wide is that that low-income consumer, which we would say is $45,000 and under, was negative from an industry standpoint.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Net income saw a boost, rising to $2.32 billion, or $3.17 a share, a significant increase from the previous year’s $1.98 billion, or $2.68 a share. Adjusted earnings per share settled at $3.19, surpassing the estimated $3.00 per share.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While McDonald’s might be reveling in its financial success, the harsh reality of Bidenflation looms large, with everyday Americans bearing the brunt of rising prices and a cost of living crisis. The fast-food giant’s prosperity serves as a stark reminder of the urgent need for economic reform and relief from the financial strain imposed by the current administration. It’s high time for a change, and the American people deserve nothing less.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In an era of skyrocketing prices and economic uncertainty, McDonald’s has found a way to turn the tide in its favor, reporting soaring profits and sales in the third quarter. The culprit? None other than the ominous Bidenflation, as rising burger prices contribute to the fast-food giant’s unexpected financial upswing. The company’s profits and sales have beaten all estimates, pushing shares higher and leaving investors satisfied. However, this leaves the average American grappling with the reality of rising costs and a strained budget. Revenue shot up by 14 percent, reaching an astounding $6.69 billion, surpassing the expected $6.56 billion. Comparable store sales grew by 8.8 percent, leaving analysts’ 8.0 percent increase prediction in the dust. Chris Kempczinski, McDonald’s Chief Executive, confidently stated, “The macroeconomic environment is unfolding in line with our expectations for the year, and we continued to deliver convenience and value for our customers.” But at what cost? In the U.S. alone, comparable store sales witnessed an 8.1 percent increase, outpacing the forecasted 7.5 percent growth. “Comparable sales results benefited from strong average check growth driven by strategic menu price increases,” McDonald’s admitted. The stark reality is that these “strategic” price hikes are a direct result of the rampant inflation under the Biden administration, coined as Bidenflation. The increase in prices did manage to counteract a noticeable decline in foot traffic to McDonald’s locations. Yet, this reveals a concerning trend: higher costs are driving customers away, particularly those in lower income brackets. Kempczinski noted, “One of the things that we saw industry-wide is that that low-income consumer, which we would say is $45,000 and under, was negative from an industry standpoint.” Net income saw a boost, rising to $2.32 billion, or $3.17 a share, a significant increase from the previous year’s $1.98 billion, or $2.68 a share. Adjusted earnings per share settled at $3.19, surpassing the estimated $3.00 per share. While McDonald’s might be reveling in its financial success, the harsh reality of Bidenflation looms large, with everyday Americans bearing the brunt of rising prices and a cost of living crisis. The fast-food giant’s prosperity serves as a stark reminder of the urgent need for economic reform and relief from the financial strain imposed by the current administration. It’s high time for a change, and the American people deserve nothing less.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Phil Murphy’s Pricey Party: Taxpayer Dollars at a Taylor Swift Concert</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/31/Phil-Murphy-Taylor-Swift-Concert/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Phil Murphy’s Pricey Party: Taxpayer Dollars at a Taylor Swift Concert" /><published>2023-10-31T11:53:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-31T11:53:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/31/Phil-Murphy-Taylor-Swift-Concert</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/31/Phil-Murphy-Taylor-Swift-Concert/">&lt;p&gt;Governor Phil Murphy has come under intense scrutiny for his extravagant spending of taxpayer money. Shockingly, Murphy used a whopping $12,000 in state funds to revel in food and drinks at a Taylor Swift concert and various other stadium events, as initially reported by Politico.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Governor Murphy’s indiscretions were exposed when his office revealed that it had dipped into a $95,000 personal expense account, which is explicitly set up for “Official Receptions, Official Residence, and Other Official Expenses.” The guidelines are clear – these funds are not to be used for personal purposes. Yet, Murphy saw fit to spend lavishly on his own enjoyment, leaving taxpayers to foot the bill for his entertainment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When confronted with this gross misuse of funds, Murphy’s office hastily claimed that they intended for the state Democratic Party to cover the costs and that they are now “pursuing reimbursement” for the expenses incurred at MetLife Stadium. But the question remains: Why did the Governor believe it was appropriate to use taxpayer money for his personal partying in the first place?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jennifer Sciortino, a spokeswoman for Murphy, tried to justify the expenditures by stating, “Once it was clear that there were outstanding bills that had not been paid, the state stepped up to meet this responsibility.” However, this statement does little to appease the rightly angered public who are tired of politicians misusing their hard-earned money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What makes this situation even more galling is the fact that former New Jersey Governor Chris Christie, a Republican, found himself in a similar situation but chose to have the state Republican Party reimburse the approximately $82,000 spent at MetLife Stadium. Christie’s actions demonstrate a level of accountability and responsibility that Murphy seems to lack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Public records have laid bare the extent of Murphy’s frivolous spending, including nearly $1,000 at a Taylor Swift concert in 2018 and thousands more at various sporting events. This level of extravagance is unacceptable, especially when it is funded by the taxpayer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the Governor’s office scrambles to do damage control, it is clear that Phil Murphy has shown a blatant disregard for the responsible use of taxpayer money. New Jersey residents deserve better than a Governor who parties on their dime, and it is time for Murphy to be held accountable for his actions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a state already grappling with its share of political scandals, including charges against Senator Bob Menendez for acting as a foreign agent, Murphy’s lavish spending adds insult to injury. New Jerseyans are left wondering: when will enough be enough?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Governor Phil Murphy has come under intense scrutiny for his extravagant spending of taxpayer money. Shockingly, Murphy used a whopping $12,000 in state funds to revel in food and drinks at a Taylor Swift concert and various other stadium events, as initially reported by Politico. Governor Murphy’s indiscretions were exposed when his office revealed that it had dipped into a $95,000 personal expense account, which is explicitly set up for “Official Receptions, Official Residence, and Other Official Expenses.” The guidelines are clear – these funds are not to be used for personal purposes. Yet, Murphy saw fit to spend lavishly on his own enjoyment, leaving taxpayers to foot the bill for his entertainment. When confronted with this gross misuse of funds, Murphy’s office hastily claimed that they intended for the state Democratic Party to cover the costs and that they are now “pursuing reimbursement” for the expenses incurred at MetLife Stadium. But the question remains: Why did the Governor believe it was appropriate to use taxpayer money for his personal partying in the first place? Jennifer Sciortino, a spokeswoman for Murphy, tried to justify the expenditures by stating, “Once it was clear that there were outstanding bills that had not been paid, the state stepped up to meet this responsibility.” However, this statement does little to appease the rightly angered public who are tired of politicians misusing their hard-earned money. What makes this situation even more galling is the fact that former New Jersey Governor Chris Christie, a Republican, found himself in a similar situation but chose to have the state Republican Party reimburse the approximately $82,000 spent at MetLife Stadium. Christie’s actions demonstrate a level of accountability and responsibility that Murphy seems to lack. Public records have laid bare the extent of Murphy’s frivolous spending, including nearly $1,000 at a Taylor Swift concert in 2018 and thousands more at various sporting events. This level of extravagance is unacceptable, especially when it is funded by the taxpayer. As the Governor’s office scrambles to do damage control, it is clear that Phil Murphy has shown a blatant disregard for the responsible use of taxpayer money. New Jersey residents deserve better than a Governor who parties on their dime, and it is time for Murphy to be held accountable for his actions. In a state already grappling with its share of political scandals, including charges against Senator Bob Menendez for acting as a foreign agent, Murphy’s lavish spending adds insult to injury. New Jerseyans are left wondering: when will enough be enough?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Amy Schumer Boldly Stands for Israel: Losing Friends but Gaining Freedom</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/31/Amy-Schumer-Support-Israel/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Amy Schumer Boldly Stands for Israel: Losing Friends but Gaining Freedom" /><published>2023-10-31T10:44:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-31T10:44:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/31/Amy-Schumer-Support-Israel</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/31/Amy-Schumer-Support-Israel/">&lt;p&gt;Comedian Amy Schumer has recently come forward, sharing the personal sacrifices she has made due to her staunch support for Israel. Despite facing backlash and losing friends, Schumer stands firm, embracing her identity and her right to voice her opinions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a heartfelt Instagram post, Schumer, known for her roles in hit films like “Trainwreck,” expressed her unwavering support for Israel, particularly in light of the recent violent escalations with Hamas. “I’m a proud Jewish woman and have every right to be,” she affirmed, reflecting her commitment to her heritage and her beliefs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Schumer didn’t shy away from addressing the cost of her stance, acknowledging the loss of many friends in recent weeks. However, she emphasizes feeling “powerful and free,” deriving strength from standing up for what she believes to be the truth. Her post sheds light on the ongoing conflict between Israel and Hamas, bringing attention to the grim realities, including the Israeli hostages still in captivity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The comedian’s bold position has not been without controversy, as she faces severe criticism from her fellow leftists. Schumer’s adamant support for Israel’s right to defend itself against Hamas’ aggression has made her a target of vicious attacks. A senior advisor to a Los Angeles City Councilman recently resigned after making Holocaust-themed jokes about Schumer, highlighting the intense polarization and animosity stemming from her stance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Schumer’s critique extends beyond social circles; she has boldly challenged major news outlets, accusing them of spreading Hamas propaganda. She demanded accountability and the resignation of senior editors at the New York Times and CNN, showcasing her readiness to hold powerful entities to account.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In taking such a public and firm stance, Schumer sets an example of resilience and the importance of standing up for one’s beliefs, even in the face of personal loss and public scrutiny. Her story underscores the complexities and personal toll of the Israel-Hamas conflict, illustrating how these global issues ripple through individual lives, influencing relationships, and shaping public discourse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amy Schumer’s narrative serves as a powerful reminder that voicing support for what one believes to be just and true may come at a significant personal cost, but it also brings a sense of empowerment and freedom that is irreplaceable.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Comedian Amy Schumer has recently come forward, sharing the personal sacrifices she has made due to her staunch support for Israel. Despite facing backlash and losing friends, Schumer stands firm, embracing her identity and her right to voice her opinions. In a heartfelt Instagram post, Schumer, known for her roles in hit films like “Trainwreck,” expressed her unwavering support for Israel, particularly in light of the recent violent escalations with Hamas. “I’m a proud Jewish woman and have every right to be,” she affirmed, reflecting her commitment to her heritage and her beliefs. Schumer didn’t shy away from addressing the cost of her stance, acknowledging the loss of many friends in recent weeks. However, she emphasizes feeling “powerful and free,” deriving strength from standing up for what she believes to be the truth. Her post sheds light on the ongoing conflict between Israel and Hamas, bringing attention to the grim realities, including the Israeli hostages still in captivity. The comedian’s bold position has not been without controversy, as she faces severe criticism from her fellow leftists. Schumer’s adamant support for Israel’s right to defend itself against Hamas’ aggression has made her a target of vicious attacks. A senior advisor to a Los Angeles City Councilman recently resigned after making Holocaust-themed jokes about Schumer, highlighting the intense polarization and animosity stemming from her stance. Schumer’s critique extends beyond social circles; she has boldly challenged major news outlets, accusing them of spreading Hamas propaganda. She demanded accountability and the resignation of senior editors at the New York Times and CNN, showcasing her readiness to hold powerful entities to account. In taking such a public and firm stance, Schumer sets an example of resilience and the importance of standing up for one’s beliefs, even in the face of personal loss and public scrutiny. Her story underscores the complexities and personal toll of the Israel-Hamas conflict, illustrating how these global issues ripple through individual lives, influencing relationships, and shaping public discourse. Amy Schumer’s narrative serves as a powerful reminder that voicing support for what one believes to be just and true may come at a significant personal cost, but it also brings a sense of empowerment and freedom that is irreplaceable.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Comedian Jim Gaffigan Stands with Jewish Community Amid Rising Anti-Semitism</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/31/Jim-Gaffigan-Anti-Semitism/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Comedian Jim Gaffigan Stands with Jewish Community Amid Rising Anti-Semitism" /><published>2023-10-31T09:32:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-31T09:32:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/31/Jim-Gaffigan-Anti-Semitism</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/31/Jim-Gaffigan-Anti-Semitism/">&lt;p&gt;Renowned comedian Jim Gaffigan has recently voiced his concern and support for the Jewish community, addressing the alarming surge in anti-Semitic incidents occurring in major cities and college campuses. With a reputation for his candid and thoughtful commentary, Gaffigan has made it clear that the fears and concerns of the Jewish people are not unfounded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Monday, Gaffigan, who practices Catholicism, took to social media to express his sentiments. His message was straightforward and impactful, acknowledging the long-standing stereotype of paranoia within the Jewish community, often perpetuated by comedians themselves. Gaffigan’s recognition of the severity of the current situation marks a significant moment, challenging existing stereotypes and urging for a reevaluation of the narratives we create and propagate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In recent weeks, cities governed by Democratic leadership and various college campuses, including prestigious Ivy League institutions, have witnessed a noticeable uptick in anti-Semitic incidents. This includes public demonstrations expressing support for Hamas, a Palestinian organization designated as a terrorist group by multiple countries, including the United States. The blatant hatred directed at Jewish people during these events has been disturbing, prompting major donors to retract their financial support from affected institutions, such as the University of Pennsylvania.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gaffigan’s voice joins a chorus of individuals from various political and entertainment spheres who are speaking out against this wave of anti-Semitism. Interestingly, Gaffigan, a self-identified member of the left-wing community, is calling attention to the issue within his own political alignment, echoing sentiments previously expressed by comedian Amy Schumer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Schumer, who is Jewish, has been vocal in her support for Israel and her condemnation of Hamas, as well as the left’s apparent growing support for the organization. She has also criticized major news outlets, including the New York Times and CNN, demanding accountability and the resignation of senior editors involved in spreading what she identifies as Hamas propaganda.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As anti-Semitic incidents continue to rise, the need for voices like Gaffigan’s becomes increasingly crucial. His decision to speak out not only provides support to the Jewish community but also encourages others to reflect on their own biases and the narratives they contribute to. In doing so, Gaffigan exemplifies the role that individuals, particularly those with public platforms, can play in challenging harmful stereotypes and advocating for change.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Renowned comedian Jim Gaffigan has recently voiced his concern and support for the Jewish community, addressing the alarming surge in anti-Semitic incidents occurring in major cities and college campuses. With a reputation for his candid and thoughtful commentary, Gaffigan has made it clear that the fears and concerns of the Jewish people are not unfounded. On Monday, Gaffigan, who practices Catholicism, took to social media to express his sentiments. His message was straightforward and impactful, acknowledging the long-standing stereotype of paranoia within the Jewish community, often perpetuated by comedians themselves. Gaffigan’s recognition of the severity of the current situation marks a significant moment, challenging existing stereotypes and urging for a reevaluation of the narratives we create and propagate. In recent weeks, cities governed by Democratic leadership and various college campuses, including prestigious Ivy League institutions, have witnessed a noticeable uptick in anti-Semitic incidents. This includes public demonstrations expressing support for Hamas, a Palestinian organization designated as a terrorist group by multiple countries, including the United States. The blatant hatred directed at Jewish people during these events has been disturbing, prompting major donors to retract their financial support from affected institutions, such as the University of Pennsylvania. Gaffigan’s voice joins a chorus of individuals from various political and entertainment spheres who are speaking out against this wave of anti-Semitism. Interestingly, Gaffigan, a self-identified member of the left-wing community, is calling attention to the issue within his own political alignment, echoing sentiments previously expressed by comedian Amy Schumer. Schumer, who is Jewish, has been vocal in her support for Israel and her condemnation of Hamas, as well as the left’s apparent growing support for the organization. She has also criticized major news outlets, including the New York Times and CNN, demanding accountability and the resignation of senior editors involved in spreading what she identifies as Hamas propaganda. As anti-Semitic incidents continue to rise, the need for voices like Gaffigan’s becomes increasingly crucial. His decision to speak out not only provides support to the Jewish community but also encourages others to reflect on their own biases and the narratives they contribute to. In doing so, Gaffigan exemplifies the role that individuals, particularly those with public platforms, can play in challenging harmful stereotypes and advocating for change.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Unspoken Truth About Vice President Kamala Harris</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/31/Kamala-Harris-Disaster/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Unspoken Truth About Vice President Kamala Harris" /><published>2023-10-31T08:23:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-31T08:23:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/31/Kamala-Harris-Disaster</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/31/Kamala-Harris-Disaster/">&lt;p&gt;Whispers of discontent within the Democratic Party are starting to become audible as party members begin to voice their concerns about Vice President Kamala Harris. For a long time, the criticism surrounding Harris’s capabilities and performance has been a topic of discussion on conservative platforms, but it appears the skepticism is now making its way into Democratic circles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vice President Harris has been in the political spotlight since her nomination, with expectations sky-high due to her historical position as the first female Vice President and the highest-ranking female official in U.S. history. However, her time in office has been anything but smooth, with numerous instances of questionable competence and lack of leadership. Her handling of the border crisis and inability to provide clear answers in interviews have left both the public and her colleagues doubting her readiness for such a high-stakes role.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The “60 Minutes” interview served as a catalyst, bringing to light the growing unease among Democrat donors and party members about Harris’s potential to lead the nation if the need arises. The Vice President’s performance during the interview, marked by her signature laughter at inappropriate times and inability to address the questions head-on, did little to assuage the concerns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her track record speaks volumes, polling at less than 1% in the Democratic primary, yet she was chosen as Biden’s running mate. Critics argue this decision was based more on checking diversity boxes than on her actual merit or capabilities, a move that may have seemed beneficial at the time but is now coming back to haunt the Democratic Party.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The possibility of California Governor Gavin Newsom stepping up as a 2024 contender adds another layer of complexity to the situation. While some may see him as a fresh alternative, his leadership in California has been far from exemplary, with the state facing a multitude of issues, from homelessness to mismanagement of resources. The American people are wary of importing California’s failed policies to the rest of the country, and Newsom’s association with these failures makes him a less-than-ideal candidate for the Democrats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the 2024 elections draw nearer, the Democratic Party finds itself at a crossroads. Acknowledging the elephant in the room – Vice President Harris’s inadequacies – is a step in the right direction, but it also raises the question: who is the right person to lead the Democrats and potentially the country? The conservatives have been saying it all along, and now, it seems, the Democrats are starting to listen.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Whispers of discontent within the Democratic Party are starting to become audible as party members begin to voice their concerns about Vice President Kamala Harris. For a long time, the criticism surrounding Harris’s capabilities and performance has been a topic of discussion on conservative platforms, but it appears the skepticism is now making its way into Democratic circles. Vice President Harris has been in the political spotlight since her nomination, with expectations sky-high due to her historical position as the first female Vice President and the highest-ranking female official in U.S. history. However, her time in office has been anything but smooth, with numerous instances of questionable competence and lack of leadership. Her handling of the border crisis and inability to provide clear answers in interviews have left both the public and her colleagues doubting her readiness for such a high-stakes role. The “60 Minutes” interview served as a catalyst, bringing to light the growing unease among Democrat donors and party members about Harris’s potential to lead the nation if the need arises. The Vice President’s performance during the interview, marked by her signature laughter at inappropriate times and inability to address the questions head-on, did little to assuage the concerns. Her track record speaks volumes, polling at less than 1% in the Democratic primary, yet she was chosen as Biden’s running mate. Critics argue this decision was based more on checking diversity boxes than on her actual merit or capabilities, a move that may have seemed beneficial at the time but is now coming back to haunt the Democratic Party. The possibility of California Governor Gavin Newsom stepping up as a 2024 contender adds another layer of complexity to the situation. While some may see him as a fresh alternative, his leadership in California has been far from exemplary, with the state facing a multitude of issues, from homelessness to mismanagement of resources. The American people are wary of importing California’s failed policies to the rest of the country, and Newsom’s association with these failures makes him a less-than-ideal candidate for the Democrats. As the 2024 elections draw nearer, the Democratic Party finds itself at a crossroads. Acknowledging the elephant in the room – Vice President Harris’s inadequacies – is a step in the right direction, but it also raises the question: who is the right person to lead the Democrats and potentially the country? The conservatives have been saying it all along, and now, it seems, the Democrats are starting to listen.</summary></entry></feed>