<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-10-09T16:15:09-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/09/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-09T16:15:09-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-09T16:15:09-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/09/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/09/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/09/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-09T16:15:09-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-09T16:15:09-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/09/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/09/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/">&lt;p&gt;Recent surprise attacks by Hamas on Israel has fueled ongoing tensions between staunchly conservative commentators and the progressive “Squad” Democrats known for criticizing Israel. The intensity of the backlash highlights the deep political divide over foreign policy in the Middle East.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Hamas’ shocking attack, several members of the “Squad,” including Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.), called for a “ceasefire and de-escalation,” condemning the violence. The absence of a statement from Rep. Rashida Tlaib (D-Mich.) was notably called out by conservative media outlets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;South Carolina GOP Rep. Nancy Mace quickly labeled Ocasio-Cortez a “Hamas apologist” in response to her call for peace and de-escalation. Rep. Ilhan Omar (D-Minn.), no stranger to controversy surrounding her views on Israel, echoed the call for de-escalation and ceasefire. Omar’s prior statements comparing the US and Israel to terrorist groups like Hamas and the Taliban resurfaced in the debate, fueling more criticisms. Omar’s 2019 tweet, where she opined that “Israel has hypnotized the world,” also continues to haunt her political career, often cited by critics to challenge her stance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conservative commentators have been especially vocal. “FOX &amp;amp; Friends Weekend” co-host Rachel Campos-Duffy took aim at Omar, saying she fails to recognize the peace in the Middle East under Trump’s administration. Conservative pundit John Hasson also called out Omar, claiming she insinuated that attacks on IDF forces were acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Massachusetts Democrat Rep. Ayanna Pressley’s concerns over the “devastating attacks on Israelis” were met with skepticism. A prominent conservative online personality, Comfortably Smug, accused the “Squad” of advising Israel to back down after the nation suffered massive attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Jamaal Bowman’s call for an end to the Gaza blockade, in addition to condemning the Hamas attacks, was met with criticism from conservative radio host Jason Rantz. He accused Bowman of pairing his condemnation of terrorism with unwarranted criticisms of Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Cori Bush emphasized the urgent need for a ceasefire, while pushing for an end to “U.S. support for Israeli military occupation and apartheid.” Defense attorney Marina Medvin criticized Bush, suggesting that she equates the death of Palestinian terrorists to the horrific acts committed against Jewish civilians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amidst the political turmoil and intense debate, the attacks have taken a heavy toll. Israeli media report over 300 dead due to the wide-ranging assault. Gaza health officials note that at least 200 Palestinians have perished in the retaliatory Israeli air strikes following the initial Hamas attack. As the situation remains volatile, both sides continue to count their casualties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This divisive issue showcases the challenge America faces in crafting a unified approach to foreign policy, with deeply entrenched political divides at play. As the situation develops, the debate is bound to intensify, shedding light on the complexities of U.S. politics in the global arena.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Hamas-Israel Crisis: A Tug-of-War in the House Speaker Race</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/09/Israel-Hamas-Impact-on-Speaker-Race/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hamas-Israel Crisis: A Tug-of-War in the House Speaker Race" /><published>2023-10-09T15:45:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-09T15:45:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/09/Israel-Hamas-Impact-on-Speaker-Race</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/09/Israel-Hamas-Impact-on-Speaker-Race/">&lt;p&gt;The recent brutal Hamas attack on Israel has ignited an unexpected wrinkle in the already-tense race for the US House Speaker position. This international crisis, which has many looking to the US for a response, comes at a time when Republicans are pressing for a prompt installment of a new leader to address these global challenges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the House of Representatives currently missing a Speaker, it’s been hamstrung in its ability to swiftly tackle the situation, even as the crisis escalates. This gap in leadership has been acutely felt, given that President Joe Biden has not sought a formal request from Congress and the Senate remains in recess.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the urgency, the White House has remained relatively quiet on the issue. Monday morning saw a lid called, meaning no public comments from President Biden until at least Tuesday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Acting with limited authority is Speaker Pro Tem Patrick McHenry (R-NC), whose role is based on rules established post 9/11. However, his recent actions suggest a readiness to stretch these powers, evidenced by his recent eviction of Reps. Nancy Pelosi (D-CA) and Steny Hoyer (R-MD) from prime Capitol office space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The absence of a solid leader has led to a legislative standstill. While House Foreign Affairs Committee Chairman Michael McCaul (R-TX) and ranking Democrat Gregory Meeks (D-NY) have drafted a pro-Israel resolution, real legislative actions remain stagnant. This standstill is even more pronounced when considering that some members of the political sphere, like members of the Squad, have been vocally critical of the US-Israel relationship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is also a keen awareness among Republicans about the missed political opportunities this presents. Without clear leadership, they’re unable to effectively address divisive issues within their own ranks or capitalize on differences among Democrats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the situation in Israel becomes more volatile, it’s evident that both parties are feeling the heat to move quickly. Potential contenders for the Speaker position include Reps. Steve Scalise (R-LA) and Jim Jordan (R-OH). With the next potential Speaker vote expected as early as Thursday, Republicans are under pressure to choose their candidate wisely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As political maneuvers continue, there’s a looming need to address other urgent matters, including funding decisions with the November 17 deadline approaching. With the ousting of McCarthy, these timelines are under scrutiny.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In essence, the sudden Hamas-Israel crisis has added another layer of complexity to an already heated political atmosphere in the US. If a decision isn’t reached promptly about the Speaker’s position, and the global situation continues to worsen, Republicans might need to resort to unconventional measures.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">The recent brutal Hamas attack on Israel has ignited an unexpected wrinkle in the already-tense race for the US House Speaker position. This international crisis, which has many looking to the US for a response, comes at a time when Republicans are pressing for a prompt installment of a new leader to address these global challenges. With the House of Representatives currently missing a Speaker, it’s been hamstrung in its ability to swiftly tackle the situation, even as the crisis escalates. This gap in leadership has been acutely felt, given that President Joe Biden has not sought a formal request from Congress and the Senate remains in recess. Despite the urgency, the White House has remained relatively quiet on the issue. Monday morning saw a lid called, meaning no public comments from President Biden until at least Tuesday. Acting with limited authority is Speaker Pro Tem Patrick McHenry (R-NC), whose role is based on rules established post 9/11. However, his recent actions suggest a readiness to stretch these powers, evidenced by his recent eviction of Reps. Nancy Pelosi (D-CA) and Steny Hoyer (R-MD) from prime Capitol office space. The absence of a solid leader has led to a legislative standstill. While House Foreign Affairs Committee Chairman Michael McCaul (R-TX) and ranking Democrat Gregory Meeks (D-NY) have drafted a pro-Israel resolution, real legislative actions remain stagnant. This standstill is even more pronounced when considering that some members of the political sphere, like members of the Squad, have been vocally critical of the US-Israel relationship. There is also a keen awareness among Republicans about the missed political opportunities this presents. Without clear leadership, they’re unable to effectively address divisive issues within their own ranks or capitalize on differences among Democrats. As the situation in Israel becomes more volatile, it’s evident that both parties are feeling the heat to move quickly. Potential contenders for the Speaker position include Reps. Steve Scalise (R-LA) and Jim Jordan (R-OH). With the next potential Speaker vote expected as early as Thursday, Republicans are under pressure to choose their candidate wisely. As political maneuvers continue, there’s a looming need to address other urgent matters, including funding decisions with the November 17 deadline approaching. With the ousting of McCarthy, these timelines are under scrutiny. In essence, the sudden Hamas-Israel crisis has added another layer of complexity to an already heated political atmosphere in the US. If a decision isn’t reached promptly about the Speaker’s position, and the global situation continues to worsen, Republicans might need to resort to unconventional measures.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">President Biden Under Fire for Hosting BBQ Amidst Hamas Crisis</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/09/Biden-BBQ-Controversy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="President Biden Under Fire for Hosting BBQ Amidst Hamas Crisis" /><published>2023-10-09T14:03:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-09T14:03:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/09/Biden-BBQ-Controversy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/09/Biden-BBQ-Controversy/">&lt;p&gt;In a surprising turn of events, President Joe Biden and his administration have come under heavy criticism for reportedly hosting a barbecue at the White House. This criticism is deeply intertwined with the grave news of Americans being killed or taken hostage during Hamas’ unexpected attack on Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Sunday, the White House National Security Council made an official announcement confirming the unfortunate loss of multiple American lives during this assault. The timing of this announcement is particularly poignant, as a memo about a scheduled White House barbecue surfaced the very next day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to the memo, “The President and First Lady are hosting a barbecue for White House Executive Residence staff and their families.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The confluence of these two events — the barbecue and the news of the Hamas attack — ignited a storm of outrage. Critics and commentators from various political backgrounds voiced their concerns, with many pointing out the seemingly inconsiderate juxtaposition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Republican Sen. Josh Hawley of Missouri, for instance, took to his platform to express his dismay, stating, “While Hamas holds Americans hostage, Joe Biden is enjoying a picnic with a live band.” Similarly, reporter Jennie Taer commented on the disconcerting situation, citing that a war was unfolding in the Middle East involving US citizens, all while the president and the First Lady were hosting a BBQ.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Political commentators and former White House officials also voiced their opinions. Katie Pavlich, a conservative commentator, and Brilyn Hollyhand, a political commentator, both highlighted the tragedy of American citizens being impacted by the conflict and juxtaposed it with the president’s decision to host a BBQ. Karoline Leavitt, a MAGA Inc. spokeswoman, contrasted Biden’s actions with those of former President Trump, suggesting the latter would’ve been more responsive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Several other individuals, from journalists to commentators, also expressed their deep concerns and frustrations, with some using the tagline, “BBQ First, America Last” to summarize their sentiments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the backdrop of this controversy, it’s important to note that the Hamas attack over the weekend resulted in the tragic loss of American lives. Confirmations from the Israeli Ambassador to the U.S., Mike Herzog, and Israeli Minister for Strategic Affairs, Ron Dermer, further highlighted that American citizens were among the hostages taken to Gaza by Hamas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the situation continues to evolve, the decisions and actions of the Biden administration remain under intense scrutiny by both the American public and global onlookers.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a surprising turn of events, President Joe Biden and his administration have come under heavy criticism for reportedly hosting a barbecue at the White House. This criticism is deeply intertwined with the grave news of Americans being killed or taken hostage during Hamas’ unexpected attack on Israel. On Sunday, the White House National Security Council made an official announcement confirming the unfortunate loss of multiple American lives during this assault. The timing of this announcement is particularly poignant, as a memo about a scheduled White House barbecue surfaced the very next day. According to the memo, “The President and First Lady are hosting a barbecue for White House Executive Residence staff and their families.” The confluence of these two events — the barbecue and the news of the Hamas attack — ignited a storm of outrage. Critics and commentators from various political backgrounds voiced their concerns, with many pointing out the seemingly inconsiderate juxtaposition. Republican Sen. Josh Hawley of Missouri, for instance, took to his platform to express his dismay, stating, “While Hamas holds Americans hostage, Joe Biden is enjoying a picnic with a live band.” Similarly, reporter Jennie Taer commented on the disconcerting situation, citing that a war was unfolding in the Middle East involving US citizens, all while the president and the First Lady were hosting a BBQ. Political commentators and former White House officials also voiced their opinions. Katie Pavlich, a conservative commentator, and Brilyn Hollyhand, a political commentator, both highlighted the tragedy of American citizens being impacted by the conflict and juxtaposed it with the president’s decision to host a BBQ. Karoline Leavitt, a MAGA Inc. spokeswoman, contrasted Biden’s actions with those of former President Trump, suggesting the latter would’ve been more responsive. Several other individuals, from journalists to commentators, also expressed their deep concerns and frustrations, with some using the tagline, “BBQ First, America Last” to summarize their sentiments. In the backdrop of this controversy, it’s important to note that the Hamas attack over the weekend resulted in the tragic loss of American lives. Confirmations from the Israeli Ambassador to the U.S., Mike Herzog, and Israeli Minister for Strategic Affairs, Ron Dermer, further highlighted that American citizens were among the hostages taken to Gaza by Hamas. As the situation continues to evolve, the decisions and actions of the Biden administration remain under intense scrutiny by both the American public and global onlookers.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">New Jersey Republicans Call for Independent Probe into Sen. Menendez’s Alleged Bribery Scheme</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/09/New-Jersey-Menendez-Probe/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="New Jersey Republicans Call for Independent Probe into Sen. Menendez’s Alleged Bribery Scheme" /><published>2023-10-09T12:10:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-09T12:10:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/09/New-Jersey-Menendez-Probe</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/09/New-Jersey-Menendez-Probe/">&lt;p&gt;In light of the recent indictment of Democratic U.S. Sen. Bob Menendez, a robust group of New Jersey state Senate Republicans is pushing to empower the judiciary committee with investigatory and subpoena capabilities. The goal? To deeply probe allegations suggesting the New Jersey Office of Attorney General may have been influenced by Menendez’s federal bribery scandal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Republican leader Sen. Anthony Bucco, at the forefront of this group, emphasizes the necessity of this move. The indictment against Menendez not only accuses the Senator of pressuring officials to dismiss criminal cases but also brings to light concerns about the integrity of officials at the New Jersey Office of Attorney General. Questions arise if they were potentially involved in the senator’s alleged crimes or if there were lapses in safeguarding protocols against such public corruption.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2023/09/720/405/AP23270448628318.jpg?ve=1&amp;amp;tl=1&quot; alt=&quot;Democratic U.S. Sen. Bob Menendez&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Democratic U.S. Sen. Bob Menendez of New Jersey arriving at the federal courthouse in New York, Sept. 27, 2023.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A core segment of the indictment zeroes in on a disturbing narrative involving Menendez, his wife, and three New Jersey businessmen. One of these businessmen, Jose Uribe, reportedly purchased a Mercedes-Benz convertible, valued over $60,000, for Menendez and his wife, following a tragic incident where she accidentally struck a pedestrian. The indictment then insinuates that in return, Menendez attempted to intervene in an investigation against Uribe, conducted by the New Jersey attorney general’s office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite these serious allegations and their potential ramifications on state governance, any decision to grant the judiciary committee subpoena power would have to be collectively approved by the full state Senate. Key figures, including New Jersey Senate President Nicholas Scutari and judiciary committee chairman, Brian Stack, both Democrats, would also need to greenlight the initiative.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;State Senate Republicans have made their stance clear. While they do not wish to impede the federal investigation into Menendez, the claims associated with the state’s attorney general office are squarely within the domain of the New Jersey Legislature. Their objective? To fulfill their constitutional responsibility by investigating and implementing any reforms deemed necessary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a comprehensive search conducted in June 2022 at Menendez’s residence, the FBI discovered a plethora of assets - from cold hard cash to luxurious items. The evidence, as per prosecutors, links Menendez to businessman Fred Daibes, another principal figure in the purported bribery scheme.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It remains to be seen how this political saga will unfold. But one thing is clear: the issue has resonated deeply in New Jersey politics, with potential nationwide implications.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In light of the recent indictment of Democratic U.S. Sen. Bob Menendez, a robust group of New Jersey state Senate Republicans is pushing to empower the judiciary committee with investigatory and subpoena capabilities. The goal? To deeply probe allegations suggesting the New Jersey Office of Attorney General may have been influenced by Menendez’s federal bribery scandal. Republican leader Sen. Anthony Bucco, at the forefront of this group, emphasizes the necessity of this move. The indictment against Menendez not only accuses the Senator of pressuring officials to dismiss criminal cases but also brings to light concerns about the integrity of officials at the New Jersey Office of Attorney General. Questions arise if they were potentially involved in the senator’s alleged crimes or if there were lapses in safeguarding protocols against such public corruption. Democratic U.S. Sen. Bob Menendez of New Jersey arriving at the federal courthouse in New York, Sept. 27, 2023. A core segment of the indictment zeroes in on a disturbing narrative involving Menendez, his wife, and three New Jersey businessmen. One of these businessmen, Jose Uribe, reportedly purchased a Mercedes-Benz convertible, valued over $60,000, for Menendez and his wife, following a tragic incident where she accidentally struck a pedestrian. The indictment then insinuates that in return, Menendez attempted to intervene in an investigation against Uribe, conducted by the New Jersey attorney general’s office. Despite these serious allegations and their potential ramifications on state governance, any decision to grant the judiciary committee subpoena power would have to be collectively approved by the full state Senate. Key figures, including New Jersey Senate President Nicholas Scutari and judiciary committee chairman, Brian Stack, both Democrats, would also need to greenlight the initiative. State Senate Republicans have made their stance clear. While they do not wish to impede the federal investigation into Menendez, the claims associated with the state’s attorney general office are squarely within the domain of the New Jersey Legislature. Their objective? To fulfill their constitutional responsibility by investigating and implementing any reforms deemed necessary. In a comprehensive search conducted in June 2022 at Menendez’s residence, the FBI discovered a plethora of assets - from cold hard cash to luxurious items. The evidence, as per prosecutors, links Menendez to businessman Fred Daibes, another principal figure in the purported bribery scheme. It remains to be seen how this political saga will unfold. But one thing is clear: the issue has resonated deeply in New Jersey politics, with potential nationwide implications.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Newsom Hits Pause on Psychedelic Decriminalization in California</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/09/Newsom-Psychedelic-Veto/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Newsom Hits Pause on Psychedelic Decriminalization in California" /><published>2023-10-09T10:45:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-09T10:45:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/09/Newsom-Psychedelic-Veto</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/09/Newsom-Psychedelic-Veto/">&lt;p&gt;In a bold move, California’s Governor Gavin Newsom vetoed legislation intended to decriminalize psychedelic mushrooms and other hallucinogens, sparking mixed reactions across the state and country.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the proposed bill had aimed to decriminalize the possession and personal use of these substances for adults over 21, Newsom expressed reservations. His stance is surprising, especially given his supportive history toward cannabis legalization back in 2016.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bill, designed to take effect in 2025, emphasized the non-commercial nature of decriminalization. It would have only applied to personal use, excluding the selling of these substances, and would’ve ensured that individuals possessing limited amounts of such hallucinogens would not face prosecution or arrest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Newsom, in his official statement, conveyed the need for regulated treatment guidelines, ensuring therapeutic and safety standards before such a move. The legislation’s objective also included instructing the California Health and Human Services Agency to delve deeper into the therapeutic use of psychedelics and provide insights to lawmakers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With psychedelics gaining momentum as potential treatment options for various mental health conditions, it’s a hot topic. For instance, the Federal Drug Administration (FDA) recognized psilocybin as a breakthrough therapy for treatment-resistant depression as recently as 2019.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many proponents, including combat veterans and emergency responders, tout the benefits of psychedelics for trauma treatment. Joe McKay, a firefighter who worked during the devastating 9/11 attacks, is an example, having publicly expressed how psilocybin transformed his life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, not everyone is on board. Concerns range from the potential ease of access for younger individuals to the currently uncharted benefits and risks of these substances. The California Coalition for Psychedelic Safety and Education, which opposed the bill, emphasized the need for more safety measures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;State Sen. Scott Wiener, the bill’s author, expressed disappointment in the veto, advocating for the numerous Californians who’ve found solace in these substances. Wiener emphasized the evident drawbacks of criminalizing such substances and hinted at revisiting the topic with future legislation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, other states and cities have shown progressive stances on this issue. Oregon and Colorado have made strides toward decriminalizing psychedelics, and cities like Oakland and San Francisco in California have already decriminalized certain natural psychedelics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It remains to be seen how this veto will shape the future of psychedelic decriminalization in California. With potential ballot initiatives slated for 2024, Californians may get another shot at making their voices heard on this divisive issue.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a bold move, California’s Governor Gavin Newsom vetoed legislation intended to decriminalize psychedelic mushrooms and other hallucinogens, sparking mixed reactions across the state and country. While the proposed bill had aimed to decriminalize the possession and personal use of these substances for adults over 21, Newsom expressed reservations. His stance is surprising, especially given his supportive history toward cannabis legalization back in 2016. The bill, designed to take effect in 2025, emphasized the non-commercial nature of decriminalization. It would have only applied to personal use, excluding the selling of these substances, and would’ve ensured that individuals possessing limited amounts of such hallucinogens would not face prosecution or arrest. Newsom, in his official statement, conveyed the need for regulated treatment guidelines, ensuring therapeutic and safety standards before such a move. The legislation’s objective also included instructing the California Health and Human Services Agency to delve deeper into the therapeutic use of psychedelics and provide insights to lawmakers. With psychedelics gaining momentum as potential treatment options for various mental health conditions, it’s a hot topic. For instance, the Federal Drug Administration (FDA) recognized psilocybin as a breakthrough therapy for treatment-resistant depression as recently as 2019. Many proponents, including combat veterans and emergency responders, tout the benefits of psychedelics for trauma treatment. Joe McKay, a firefighter who worked during the devastating 9/11 attacks, is an example, having publicly expressed how psilocybin transformed his life. However, not everyone is on board. Concerns range from the potential ease of access for younger individuals to the currently uncharted benefits and risks of these substances. The California Coalition for Psychedelic Safety and Education, which opposed the bill, emphasized the need for more safety measures. State Sen. Scott Wiener, the bill’s author, expressed disappointment in the veto, advocating for the numerous Californians who’ve found solace in these substances. Wiener emphasized the evident drawbacks of criminalizing such substances and hinted at revisiting the topic with future legislation. Interestingly, other states and cities have shown progressive stances on this issue. Oregon and Colorado have made strides toward decriminalizing psychedelics, and cities like Oakland and San Francisco in California have already decriminalized certain natural psychedelics. It remains to be seen how this veto will shape the future of psychedelic decriminalization in California. With potential ballot initiatives slated for 2024, Californians may get another shot at making their voices heard on this divisive issue.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Elon Musk’s Twitter Misstep: Promotes Pro-Hamas Accounts</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/09/Elon-Musk-Tweet-Controversy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Elon Musk’s Twitter Misstep: Promotes Pro-Hamas Accounts" /><published>2023-10-09T09:20:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-09T09:20:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/09/Elon-Musk-Tweet-Controversy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/09/Elon-Musk-Tweet-Controversy/">&lt;p&gt;In a surprising Twitter blunder, tech mogul Elon Musk faced backlash after promoting two accounts associated with pro-Hamas sentiments, especially during a sensitive time when the terrorist organization Hamas launched attacks on Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Elon Musk, the mastermind behind Tesla and SpaceX, known for his outspoken nature on Twitter, recommended accounts @WarMonitors and @sentdefender as reliable sources for real-time updates. However, his recommendations were quickly contested when several users pointed out that @WarMonitor had previously labeled Hamas as “resistance fighters” and utilized derogatory language targeting Jewish individuals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Upon realization or after receiving feedback, Musk swiftly deleted his initial tweets. In a subsequent post, the billionaire entrepreneur emphasized the importance of truth and reducing noise in information dissemination. He mentioned, “This platform aspires to maximize signal/noise of the human collective.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the damage was done. Media outlets such as Mediaite were quick to highlight the problematic nature of Musk’s endorsements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To provide context, this incident occurred amid a massive offensive from the Palestinian militant group Hamas against Israel, a move that the Israeli Prime Minister, Benjamin Netanyahu, declared as an act of ‘war.’ According to reports, the attack resulted in significant casualties on both sides. Over 700 Israelis lost their lives, and many were wounded. In response, Israel’s military operation, named ‘Operation Sword of Iron,’ also inflicted considerable damage, with Palestinian casualties reaching close to 200 and many more injured.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The intense situation further escalated on the Jewish holiday of Shemini Atzeret, making it an extremely delicate and tumultuous period for both parties involved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given Musk’s vast influence and the global reach of his tweets, the oversight serves as a stark reminder of the responsibilities that come with such a platform. Promoting accounts without thorough background checks, especially during tense geopolitical events, can lead to significant repercussions. It’s evident that even figures as influential as Musk are not immune to errors, highlighting the need for vigilance and accuracy in today’s fast-paced information age.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">In a surprising Twitter blunder, tech mogul Elon Musk faced backlash after promoting two accounts associated with pro-Hamas sentiments, especially during a sensitive time when the terrorist organization Hamas launched attacks on Israel. Elon Musk, the mastermind behind Tesla and SpaceX, known for his outspoken nature on Twitter, recommended accounts @WarMonitors and @sentdefender as reliable sources for real-time updates. However, his recommendations were quickly contested when several users pointed out that @WarMonitor had previously labeled Hamas as “resistance fighters” and utilized derogatory language targeting Jewish individuals. Upon realization or after receiving feedback, Musk swiftly deleted his initial tweets. In a subsequent post, the billionaire entrepreneur emphasized the importance of truth and reducing noise in information dissemination. He mentioned, “This platform aspires to maximize signal/noise of the human collective.” However, the damage was done. Media outlets such as Mediaite were quick to highlight the problematic nature of Musk’s endorsements. To provide context, this incident occurred amid a massive offensive from the Palestinian militant group Hamas against Israel, a move that the Israeli Prime Minister, Benjamin Netanyahu, declared as an act of ‘war.’ According to reports, the attack resulted in significant casualties on both sides. Over 700 Israelis lost their lives, and many were wounded. In response, Israel’s military operation, named ‘Operation Sword of Iron,’ also inflicted considerable damage, with Palestinian casualties reaching close to 200 and many more injured. The intense situation further escalated on the Jewish holiday of Shemini Atzeret, making it an extremely delicate and tumultuous period for both parties involved. Given Musk’s vast influence and the global reach of his tweets, the oversight serves as a stark reminder of the responsibilities that come with such a platform. Promoting accounts without thorough background checks, especially during tense geopolitical events, can lead to significant repercussions. It’s evident that even figures as influential as Musk are not immune to errors, highlighting the need for vigilance and accuracy in today’s fast-paced information age.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Court Drama: ‘Rust’ Producers to Release Documents in Baldwin Case</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/09/Rust-Production-Documents/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Court Drama: ‘Rust’ Producers to Release Documents in Baldwin Case" /><published>2023-10-09T08:16:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-09T08:16:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/09/Rust-Production-Documents</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/09/Rust-Production-Documents/">&lt;p&gt;A new chapter unfolds in the high-profile ‘Rust’ case, with a New Mexico judge recently demanding that film producers provide critical documents that may further implicate actor Alec Baldwin in the tragic on-set death of cinematographer Halyna Hutchins in 2021.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The western movie’s production company, Rust Movie Productions, is under intense scrutiny after the accidental shooting. Their reluctance to share requested documents has heightened suspicions. According to an L.A. Times report, the production company had opposed a subpoena that sought documents, including Baldwin’s contract.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Attorney Abigail R. Wolberg, representing Rust Movie Productions, voiced concerns about the nature of these demands, noting, “The state has made it very clear in its statements that it’s still considering bringing charges against Alec Baldwin.” On the other hand, special prosecutor Kari T. Morrissey countered, emphasizing how Rust Productions “cut corners every chance they could”, jeopardizing crew members’ safety.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The pivotal focus now is on the extent of Baldwin’s role as a producer. State officials aim to ascertain his knowledge about the film’s budgetary constraints and crew management. The underlying concern revolves around the alleged unsafe atmosphere on set, possibly stemming from cost-cutting measures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An ongoing debate centers around Hannah Gutierrez-Reed, the film’s armorer. She has claimed that the movie’s producers declined her proposal for extended firearm training for Baldwin. Such training would have covered the usage of the .45 Colt pistol that was central to the fatal incident. The requested documents would likely shed light on Baldwin’s actions leading up to the unfortunate event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, internal communication has revealed that Gutierrez-Reed was stretched thin, juggling dual roles as both the armorer and props assistant. Morrissey alleged that cost-cutting motives influenced this decision, explaining, “We have a situation where Rust Production is doing everything it can to keep costs low so that it can keep profits high.” With Baldwin as one of the film’s producers, he would potentially benefit from these cost-saving actions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another contentious point raised by Morrissey is the rapid involvement of Rust Productions’ legal counsel following the accident, suggesting that potential witnesses were approached by a company lawyer almost immediately after the shooting, possibly even before the police could intervene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although manslaughter charges against Baldwin were dropped earlier this year, the case remains very much active, with potential for further developments. The tragic accident in October 2021 resulted from a real bullet mistakenly loaded into a prop gun handed to Baldwin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As investigations continue, the entertainment world and fans globally await more revelations on this heartbreaking incident.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">A new chapter unfolds in the high-profile ‘Rust’ case, with a New Mexico judge recently demanding that film producers provide critical documents that may further implicate actor Alec Baldwin in the tragic on-set death of cinematographer Halyna Hutchins in 2021. The western movie’s production company, Rust Movie Productions, is under intense scrutiny after the accidental shooting. Their reluctance to share requested documents has heightened suspicions. According to an L.A. Times report, the production company had opposed a subpoena that sought documents, including Baldwin’s contract. Attorney Abigail R. Wolberg, representing Rust Movie Productions, voiced concerns about the nature of these demands, noting, “The state has made it very clear in its statements that it’s still considering bringing charges against Alec Baldwin.” On the other hand, special prosecutor Kari T. Morrissey countered, emphasizing how Rust Productions “cut corners every chance they could”, jeopardizing crew members’ safety. The pivotal focus now is on the extent of Baldwin’s role as a producer. State officials aim to ascertain his knowledge about the film’s budgetary constraints and crew management. The underlying concern revolves around the alleged unsafe atmosphere on set, possibly stemming from cost-cutting measures. An ongoing debate centers around Hannah Gutierrez-Reed, the film’s armorer. She has claimed that the movie’s producers declined her proposal for extended firearm training for Baldwin. Such training would have covered the usage of the .45 Colt pistol that was central to the fatal incident. The requested documents would likely shed light on Baldwin’s actions leading up to the unfortunate event. Furthermore, internal communication has revealed that Gutierrez-Reed was stretched thin, juggling dual roles as both the armorer and props assistant. Morrissey alleged that cost-cutting motives influenced this decision, explaining, “We have a situation where Rust Production is doing everything it can to keep costs low so that it can keep profits high.” With Baldwin as one of the film’s producers, he would potentially benefit from these cost-saving actions. Another contentious point raised by Morrissey is the rapid involvement of Rust Productions’ legal counsel following the accident, suggesting that potential witnesses were approached by a company lawyer almost immediately after the shooting, possibly even before the police could intervene. Although manslaughter charges against Baldwin were dropped earlier this year, the case remains very much active, with potential for further developments. The tragic accident in October 2021 resulted from a real bullet mistakenly loaded into a prop gun handed to Baldwin. As investigations continue, the entertainment world and fans globally await more revelations on this heartbreaking incident.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Turbulence in the Capitol: Republicans Scramble for New Speaker Amidst Israel Crisis</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/09/Republican-Crisis-House-Speaker/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Turbulence in the Capitol: Republicans Scramble for New Speaker Amidst Israel Crisis" /><published>2023-10-09T07:07:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-09T07:07:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/09/Republican-Crisis-House-Speaker</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/09/Republican-Crisis-House-Speaker/">&lt;p&gt;As Israel grapples with a massive surprise attack by Hamas militants, House Republicans back home are facing their own battle: the unexpected ouster of former House Speaker Kevin McCarthy and the ensuing leadership vacuum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Mike Lawler, R-N.Y., didn’t hold back, taking to social media to vent his frustration: “This is why you don’t remove a Speaker mid-term without cause. What an unmitigated s— show.” Lawler underscored the need for stability and direction, especially given the escalating situation in Israel. He emphasized, “We need to elect a Speaker.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the face of adversity, Israel’s Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu has displayed determination, vowing to eliminate threats posed by Hamas. “All of the places which Hamas is deployed, hiding, and operating in that wicked city, we will turn them into rubble,” Netanyahu warned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet, in stark contrast, the political landscape within the U.S. House of Representatives is marked by uncertainty and disarray. For the first time in U.S. history, a House Speaker has been removed, paralyzing Congress’s decision-making abilities during a pivotal international crisis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;House Financial Services Chairman Patrick McHenry, R-N.C., has taken the reins as interim speaker, but his true extent of power remains uncertain. Traditionally, the Speaker is a key part of the “Gang of Eight”, a select group of top congressional leaders privy to classified intelligence briefings. Without a definitive Speaker, there’s a possible intelligence gap during this delicate period.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Former House Speaker Kevin McCarthy raised similar concerns in a recent interview, “There is nothing the House can do until they elect a speaker… why would you ever remove a speaker during a term to raise doubt around the world?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the search for a new leader intensifies, House Majority Leader Steve Scalise, R-La., and Judiciary Chairman Jim Jordan, R-Ohio, have emerged as frontrunners. Kevin Hern, R-Okla., who previously contemplated running, urged the party to swiftly come together, emphasizing the urgency of the situation, “We cannot allow the narrative to be chaos and confusion on Capitol Hill.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Marc Molinaro echoed the sentiments, emphasizing the immediate need for a permanent speaker. “Israel is at war [and] its people are being terrorized. We cannot let uncertainty in the Capitol get in the way of helping Israel. There’s no time to waste,” he asserted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;House Republicans are expected to make a decisive move in the coming days, with speaker elections scheduled for Wednesday, following pivotal meetings early in the week. As the world watches the Israeli conflict unfold, the pressure is on for House Republicans to unite, lead, and address the pressing matters at hand.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">As Israel grapples with a massive surprise attack by Hamas militants, House Republicans back home are facing their own battle: the unexpected ouster of former House Speaker Kevin McCarthy and the ensuing leadership vacuum. Rep. Mike Lawler, R-N.Y., didn’t hold back, taking to social media to vent his frustration: “This is why you don’t remove a Speaker mid-term without cause. What an unmitigated s— show.” Lawler underscored the need for stability and direction, especially given the escalating situation in Israel. He emphasized, “We need to elect a Speaker.” In the face of adversity, Israel’s Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu has displayed determination, vowing to eliminate threats posed by Hamas. “All of the places which Hamas is deployed, hiding, and operating in that wicked city, we will turn them into rubble,” Netanyahu warned. Yet, in stark contrast, the political landscape within the U.S. House of Representatives is marked by uncertainty and disarray. For the first time in U.S. history, a House Speaker has been removed, paralyzing Congress’s decision-making abilities during a pivotal international crisis. House Financial Services Chairman Patrick McHenry, R-N.C., has taken the reins as interim speaker, but his true extent of power remains uncertain. Traditionally, the Speaker is a key part of the “Gang of Eight”, a select group of top congressional leaders privy to classified intelligence briefings. Without a definitive Speaker, there’s a possible intelligence gap during this delicate period. Former House Speaker Kevin McCarthy raised similar concerns in a recent interview, “There is nothing the House can do until they elect a speaker… why would you ever remove a speaker during a term to raise doubt around the world?” As the search for a new leader intensifies, House Majority Leader Steve Scalise, R-La., and Judiciary Chairman Jim Jordan, R-Ohio, have emerged as frontrunners. Kevin Hern, R-Okla., who previously contemplated running, urged the party to swiftly come together, emphasizing the urgency of the situation, “We cannot allow the narrative to be chaos and confusion on Capitol Hill.” Rep. Marc Molinaro echoed the sentiments, emphasizing the immediate need for a permanent speaker. “Israel is at war [and] its people are being terrorized. We cannot let uncertainty in the Capitol get in the way of helping Israel. There’s no time to waste,” he asserted. House Republicans are expected to make a decisive move in the coming days, with speaker elections scheduled for Wednesday, following pivotal meetings early in the week. As the world watches the Israeli conflict unfold, the pressure is on for House Republicans to unite, lead, and address the pressing matters at hand.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Israel’s Struggle: The Low Private Gun Ownership Debate</title><link href="/news/2023/10/09/Israel-Gun-Ownership/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Israel’s Struggle: The Low Private Gun Ownership Debate" /><published>2023-10-09T06:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-09T06:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/09/Israel-Gun-Ownership</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/09/Israel-Gun-Ownership/">&lt;p&gt;With rising tensions and violent attacks witnessed in Israel, particularly from groups like Hamas, it brings to the forefront a pressing debate on private gun ownership. Unlike the United States, which boasts of the Second Amendment that champions an individual’s right to bear arms, Israel’s private gun ownership landscape paints a starkly different picture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As per reports from the BC, merely 2% of the Israeli population own guns. This is a far cry from the United States, where a study from Rutgers University’s New Jersey Gun Violence Research Center posits that approximately six in ten Americans are gun owners.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The primary distinguishing factor here is the Second Amendment in the U.S. Constitution. This amendment safeguards an American’s right to gun ownership from birth. In stark contrast, Israelis can own firearms only to the extent permitted by their government. Not just this, Israel sets strict limits on the type of firearms and the amount of ammunition one can possess. To put it into perspective, while an Israeli might typically be permitted a pistol with a cap of 50 bullets, Americans, depending on the state they reside in, can own a plethora of guns and amass as much ammunition as their pockets allow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Highlighting the sheer volume of firearms in America, it’s estimated that nearly 25 million semi-automatic rifles, such as the AR-15s and AK-47s, are in circulation. This statistic means there are more of these firearms in the U.S. than “Ford F-Series trucks on the road.” Summing up all firearm categories, America sees an astounding figure of over 434 million privately-owned guns. Meanwhile, Israel’s limitations confine citizens mostly to handguns with limited bullets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the debate rages on, the University of Sydney’s Gun Policy center has underlined that unlike the U.S., Israel does not legally guarantee the right to private gun ownership. However, in the face of increasing threats, there’s been a notable surge in the number of Israelis seeking gun licenses. From 19,000 applications in 2021, the figure jumped to 42,236 the following year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a bid to counteract terrorism and bolster civilian safety, earlier this year, Israel’s security cabinet endorsed measures that streamline the process for civilians to carry firearms. The changes even encompassed rescinding the residency and citizenship of identified terrorists. Sources indicate that the high-level security cabinet is mulling over augmenting the response mechanisms against terrorism. This might include enhancing the funding for firearm purchases and fast-tracking the issuance of gun licenses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the wake of recent events, some analysts speculate that Israeli authorities could potentially expand the gamut of weapons that its citizens can privately own. Whether this shift would significantly alter the security landscape of the nation remains to be seen. But one thing’s for certain, as terror threats loom large, Israel’s gun ownership policies are under intense scrutiny, and changes, if any, will reverberate on the global stage.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">With rising tensions and violent attacks witnessed in Israel, particularly from groups like Hamas, it brings to the forefront a pressing debate on private gun ownership. Unlike the United States, which boasts of the Second Amendment that champions an individual’s right to bear arms, Israel’s private gun ownership landscape paints a starkly different picture. As per reports from the BC, merely 2% of the Israeli population own guns. This is a far cry from the United States, where a study from Rutgers University’s New Jersey Gun Violence Research Center posits that approximately six in ten Americans are gun owners. The primary distinguishing factor here is the Second Amendment in the U.S. Constitution. This amendment safeguards an American’s right to gun ownership from birth. In stark contrast, Israelis can own firearms only to the extent permitted by their government. Not just this, Israel sets strict limits on the type of firearms and the amount of ammunition one can possess. To put it into perspective, while an Israeli might typically be permitted a pistol with a cap of 50 bullets, Americans, depending on the state they reside in, can own a plethora of guns and amass as much ammunition as their pockets allow. Highlighting the sheer volume of firearms in America, it’s estimated that nearly 25 million semi-automatic rifles, such as the AR-15s and AK-47s, are in circulation. This statistic means there are more of these firearms in the U.S. than “Ford F-Series trucks on the road.” Summing up all firearm categories, America sees an astounding figure of over 434 million privately-owned guns. Meanwhile, Israel’s limitations confine citizens mostly to handguns with limited bullets. As the debate rages on, the University of Sydney’s Gun Policy center has underlined that unlike the U.S., Israel does not legally guarantee the right to private gun ownership. However, in the face of increasing threats, there’s been a notable surge in the number of Israelis seeking gun licenses. From 19,000 applications in 2021, the figure jumped to 42,236 the following year. In a bid to counteract terrorism and bolster civilian safety, earlier this year, Israel’s security cabinet endorsed measures that streamline the process for civilians to carry firearms. The changes even encompassed rescinding the residency and citizenship of identified terrorists. Sources indicate that the high-level security cabinet is mulling over augmenting the response mechanisms against terrorism. This might include enhancing the funding for firearm purchases and fast-tracking the issuance of gun licenses. In the wake of recent events, some analysts speculate that Israeli authorities could potentially expand the gamut of weapons that its citizens can privately own. Whether this shift would significantly alter the security landscape of the nation remains to be seen. But one thing’s for certain, as terror threats loom large, Israel’s gun ownership policies are under intense scrutiny, and changes, if any, will reverberate on the global stage.</summary></entry></feed>