<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-09-20T10:15:36-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/09/20/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-09-20T10:15:36-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-20T10:15:36-04:00</updated><id>/2023/09/20/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/20/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Seven GOP Contenders Set Eyes on 2nd Debate Stage</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/20/GOP-Debate-Candidates/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Seven GOP Contenders Set Eyes on 2nd Debate Stage" /><published>2023-09-20T10:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-20T10:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/20/GOP-Debate-Candidates</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/20/GOP-Debate-Candidates/">&lt;p&gt;As the Republican primaries heat up, seven GOP candidates have apparently secured their spots for the second presidential debate, slated for September 27. However, all eyes are on former President Donald Trump, who’s choosing to skip the event in favor of addressing striking autoworkers in Michigan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who’s In and Who’s Out?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The debate, hosted at the Ronald Reagan Presidential Library in Simi Valley, California, will likely include a mix of familiar faces and emerging leaders:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Gov. Ron DeSantis (R-FL)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Entrepreneur Vivek Ramaswamy&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Former Gov. Nikki Haley (R-SC)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Former Vice President Mike Pence&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sen. Tim Scott (R-SC)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Former Gov. Chris Christie (R-NJ)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to CBS News politics reporter Aaron Navarro, these candidates have likely satisfied the Republican National Committee’s updated polling and donor prerequisites. However, Gov. Doug Burgum (R-ND) and former Gov. Asa Hutchinson (R-AR), both participants in the first debate, seem to be trailing behind in their bid to join the next round.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Debate Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Candidates looking to step onto the debate stage need to hit certain benchmarks:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Secure three percent or more in two national polls&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Alternatively, obtain at least three percent in one national poll and three percent in two of the initial four early voting states&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All polls considered must be dated August 1 or later. Additionally, hopefuls must also rally a total of 50,000 unique donors, a 10,000 donor increase from the first debate’s requirements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trump’s Counter-Move&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While these candidates are gearing up for a lively debate, Trump is charting his own course. Sources have confirmed that during the debate, Trump plans to engage with members of the United Auto Workers in Detroit, Michigan, who are currently striking against major automakers like General Motors, Ford, and Stellantis. The New York Times has indicated that Trump is set to give a “prime-time speech” to these union members.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This isn’t the first time Trump has opted for a counter-programming strategy. During the first debate, he rivaled the event with a gripping 45-minute interview with Tucker Carlson, which quickly went viral.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the third debate expected in Miami, Florida, in November, it’ll be intriguing to see how the political strategies evolve and what surprises lie ahead in this gripping election season.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">As the Republican primaries heat up, seven GOP candidates have apparently secured their spots for the second presidential debate, slated for September 27. However, all eyes are on former President Donald Trump, who’s choosing to skip the event in favor of addressing striking autoworkers in Michigan. Who’s In and Who’s Out? The debate, hosted at the Ronald Reagan Presidential Library in Simi Valley, California, will likely include a mix of familiar faces and emerging leaders: Gov. Ron DeSantis (R-FL) Entrepreneur Vivek Ramaswamy Former Gov. Nikki Haley (R-SC) Former Vice President Mike Pence Sen. Tim Scott (R-SC) Former Gov. Chris Christie (R-NJ) According to CBS News politics reporter Aaron Navarro, these candidates have likely satisfied the Republican National Committee’s updated polling and donor prerequisites. However, Gov. Doug Burgum (R-ND) and former Gov. Asa Hutchinson (R-AR), both participants in the first debate, seem to be trailing behind in their bid to join the next round. The Debate Requirements Candidates looking to step onto the debate stage need to hit certain benchmarks: Secure three percent or more in two national polls Alternatively, obtain at least three percent in one national poll and three percent in two of the initial four early voting states All polls considered must be dated August 1 or later. Additionally, hopefuls must also rally a total of 50,000 unique donors, a 10,000 donor increase from the first debate’s requirements. Trump’s Counter-Move While these candidates are gearing up for a lively debate, Trump is charting his own course. Sources have confirmed that during the debate, Trump plans to engage with members of the United Auto Workers in Detroit, Michigan, who are currently striking against major automakers like General Motors, Ford, and Stellantis. The New York Times has indicated that Trump is set to give a “prime-time speech” to these union members. This isn’t the first time Trump has opted for a counter-programming strategy. During the first debate, he rivaled the event with a gripping 45-minute interview with Tucker Carlson, which quickly went viral. With the third debate expected in Miami, Florida, in November, it’ll be intriguing to see how the political strategies evolve and what surprises lie ahead in this gripping election season.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A Wrong Turn - Arkansas Trooper Retires After Dramatic Mistake</title><link href="/news/2023/09/20/Arkansas-Trooper-Controversy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Wrong Turn - Arkansas Trooper Retires After Dramatic Mistake" /><published>2023-09-20T09:07:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-20T09:07:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/20/Arkansas-Trooper-Controversy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/20/Arkansas-Trooper-Controversy/">&lt;p&gt;While high-speed pursuits often make for thrilling movie scenes, real-life chases can have dire consequences - especially when mistakes are made. Arkansas recently witnessed such an incident when a state trooper mistakenly targeted the wrong vehicle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On a regular Sunday evening on Interstate 40, an Arkansas State Trooper was in hot pursuit of two vehicles reportedly speeding over 100 mph. One of these was a white sedan. In the midst of this chase, Trooper Cpl. Thomas Hubbard, possibly overwhelmed by the speed and intensity, misidentified a completely unrelated white sedan as the suspect’s car.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Without a moment’s hesitation, Hubbard executed a PIT (precision immobilization technique) maneuver on the innocent vehicle. For those unfamiliar, a PIT maneuver is a tactic used by police to force a fleeing car to lose control and stop. This involves a controlled hit by the police vehicle to the side near a rear wheel of the pursued vehicle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The unsuspecting white sedan, taken off guard, was sent spiraling to the shoulder of the interstate. Dashcam footage vividly captured this entire sequence: the rapid chase, the sedan flashing its brakes, and the subsequent collision.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But what about the occupants of the car? Miraculously, both the driver and the passenger emerged from the crash unscathed. They both declined medical treatment, demonstrating the resilience humans sometimes show in the face of sudden adversity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The aftermath of the incident has led to swift action. Hubbard has since submitted his retirement and remains off duty. The Arkansas State Police initiated an immediate internal review.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet, this isn’t the first time the Arkansas State Police have found themselves under scrutiny for PIT maneuvers. Back in 2021, a woman took legal action against another trooper who “negligently performed” a PIT maneuver, causing her car to overturn at 60 mph. Further investigations by local news revealed that between January 2017 and December 2020, the technique was used a staggering 306 times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But with such a powerful tactic comes grave responsibility. The Washington Post reported that since 2016, at least 30 people have lost their lives due to PIT maneuvers. Eighteen of these were for minor traffic violations, such as speeding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the wake of such statistics and recent incidents, it begs the question: Is it time for a thorough review and possible revision of this pursuit technique?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">While high-speed pursuits often make for thrilling movie scenes, real-life chases can have dire consequences - especially when mistakes are made. Arkansas recently witnessed such an incident when a state trooper mistakenly targeted the wrong vehicle. On a regular Sunday evening on Interstate 40, an Arkansas State Trooper was in hot pursuit of two vehicles reportedly speeding over 100 mph. One of these was a white sedan. In the midst of this chase, Trooper Cpl. Thomas Hubbard, possibly overwhelmed by the speed and intensity, misidentified a completely unrelated white sedan as the suspect’s car. Without a moment’s hesitation, Hubbard executed a PIT (precision immobilization technique) maneuver on the innocent vehicle. For those unfamiliar, a PIT maneuver is a tactic used by police to force a fleeing car to lose control and stop. This involves a controlled hit by the police vehicle to the side near a rear wheel of the pursued vehicle. The unsuspecting white sedan, taken off guard, was sent spiraling to the shoulder of the interstate. Dashcam footage vividly captured this entire sequence: the rapid chase, the sedan flashing its brakes, and the subsequent collision. But what about the occupants of the car? Miraculously, both the driver and the passenger emerged from the crash unscathed. They both declined medical treatment, demonstrating the resilience humans sometimes show in the face of sudden adversity. The aftermath of the incident has led to swift action. Hubbard has since submitted his retirement and remains off duty. The Arkansas State Police initiated an immediate internal review. Yet, this isn’t the first time the Arkansas State Police have found themselves under scrutiny for PIT maneuvers. Back in 2021, a woman took legal action against another trooper who “negligently performed” a PIT maneuver, causing her car to overturn at 60 mph. Further investigations by local news revealed that between January 2017 and December 2020, the technique was used a staggering 306 times. But with such a powerful tactic comes grave responsibility. The Washington Post reported that since 2016, at least 30 people have lost their lives due to PIT maneuvers. Eighteen of these were for minor traffic violations, such as speeding. In the wake of such statistics and recent incidents, it begs the question: Is it time for a thorough review and possible revision of this pursuit technique?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">When Freedom of Speech Faces Jail - The Lira Case in Ukraine</title><link href="/news/2023/09/20/Free-Speech-In-Ukraine/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="When Freedom of Speech Faces Jail - The Lira Case in Ukraine" /><published>2023-09-20T08:03:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-20T08:03:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/20/Free-Speech-In-Ukraine</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/20/Free-Speech-In-Ukraine/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Freedom Under Fire&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As Washington D.C.’s lawmakers debate over funneling billions of taxpayer dollars into Ukraine, the nation hailed for its democratic values, a controversial situation unfolds in the shadows. Gonzalo Lira, an American citizen journalist, remains behind bars in Ukraine. His supposed crime? Allegedly spreading Russian propaganda.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Billions on the Table&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;President Joe Biden’s administration is in talks to sanction another $24 billion for Ukraine. This is in addition to the massive $113 billion that Congress has already greenlit for the country since the onset of its conflict with Russia. While supporting Ukraine, Biden emphasized that such investment aids “the future of every country that seeks a world governed by basic rules.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet, one crucial issue remained absent from the president’s discourse, especially at the United Nations. The matter of Gonzalo Lira, the American-Chilean dual citizen jailed in Ukraine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lira’s Contentious Arrest&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gonzalo Lira, living in Ukraine’s Kharkiv city when Russia invaded, faces a potential prison term of five to eight years under Ukraine’s wartime propaganda regulations. He was apprehended in May, with Ukrainian authorities accusing him of producing content favoring Russia on his YouTube channel. Here, he challenged the mainstream narratives about the war, even suggesting provocations from the Ukrainian side and concerns about NATO’s eastward expansion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lira’s attempts to cross the Ukrainian-Hungarian border to claim asylum after a bail release led to his sudden social media silence. His chilling last words in a video hinted at a potential re-arrest and the grim prospect of “dying in prison.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Real Story Behind the Charges?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ukraine’s government alleges that Lira intended to legitimize Russia’s aggression against their nation. However, the charge sheet makes no mention of Lira ever collaborating with the Russian government or committing any tangible crimes beyond his social media statements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lira’s defense is simple: he shared his opinions on the conflict without causing harm to anyone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moreover, during his initial incarceration, Lira claims he faced physical abuse from fellow prisoners, indirectly facilitated by prison guards. He expressed disappointment, feeling the Chilean embassy showed more concern for his well-being than the U.S. State Department.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a response, a State Department spokesperson affirmed their knowledge of Lira’s detention and vowed to assist U.S. citizens abroad. However, the depth of this assistance remains unclear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Greater Implications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ukrainian military spokesperson Sarah Ashton-Cirillo, recently in the limelight for her bold statements against supposed Russian propagandists, testified against Lira, but asserted he was in good health during their encounter. U.S. Senator J.D. Vance has meanwhile raised concerns over Ukraine’s stance on free speech, questioning the measures they might take against it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ironically, while Lira remains detained, the Biden administration negotiated with Iran, leading to the release of five Americans in exchange for a $6 billion deal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As dollars continue flowing into Ukraine, it’s crucial to ask: At what cost to freedom and democratic values?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Freedom Under Fire As Washington D.C.’s lawmakers debate over funneling billions of taxpayer dollars into Ukraine, the nation hailed for its democratic values, a controversial situation unfolds in the shadows. Gonzalo Lira, an American citizen journalist, remains behind bars in Ukraine. His supposed crime? Allegedly spreading Russian propaganda. Billions on the Table President Joe Biden’s administration is in talks to sanction another $24 billion for Ukraine. This is in addition to the massive $113 billion that Congress has already greenlit for the country since the onset of its conflict with Russia. While supporting Ukraine, Biden emphasized that such investment aids “the future of every country that seeks a world governed by basic rules.” Yet, one crucial issue remained absent from the president’s discourse, especially at the United Nations. The matter of Gonzalo Lira, the American-Chilean dual citizen jailed in Ukraine. Lira’s Contentious Arrest Gonzalo Lira, living in Ukraine’s Kharkiv city when Russia invaded, faces a potential prison term of five to eight years under Ukraine’s wartime propaganda regulations. He was apprehended in May, with Ukrainian authorities accusing him of producing content favoring Russia on his YouTube channel. Here, he challenged the mainstream narratives about the war, even suggesting provocations from the Ukrainian side and concerns about NATO’s eastward expansion. Lira’s attempts to cross the Ukrainian-Hungarian border to claim asylum after a bail release led to his sudden social media silence. His chilling last words in a video hinted at a potential re-arrest and the grim prospect of “dying in prison.” The Real Story Behind the Charges? Ukraine’s government alleges that Lira intended to legitimize Russia’s aggression against their nation. However, the charge sheet makes no mention of Lira ever collaborating with the Russian government or committing any tangible crimes beyond his social media statements. Lira’s defense is simple: he shared his opinions on the conflict without causing harm to anyone. Moreover, during his initial incarceration, Lira claims he faced physical abuse from fellow prisoners, indirectly facilitated by prison guards. He expressed disappointment, feeling the Chilean embassy showed more concern for his well-being than the U.S. State Department. In a response, a State Department spokesperson affirmed their knowledge of Lira’s detention and vowed to assist U.S. citizens abroad. However, the depth of this assistance remains unclear. The Greater Implications Ukrainian military spokesperson Sarah Ashton-Cirillo, recently in the limelight for her bold statements against supposed Russian propagandists, testified against Lira, but asserted he was in good health during their encounter. U.S. Senator J.D. Vance has meanwhile raised concerns over Ukraine’s stance on free speech, questioning the measures they might take against it. Ironically, while Lira remains detained, the Biden administration negotiated with Iran, leading to the release of five Americans in exchange for a $6 billion deal. As dollars continue flowing into Ukraine, it’s crucial to ask: At what cost to freedom and democratic values?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">High-Profile Split - Bijou Phillips Seeks Divorce From Convicted Actor Danny Masterson</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/20/Bijou-Divorce/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="High-Profile Split - Bijou Phillips Seeks Divorce From Convicted Actor Danny Masterson" /><published>2023-09-20T07:12:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-20T07:12:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/20/Bijou-Divorce</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/20/Bijou-Divorce/">&lt;p&gt;In a turn of events that’s captured the attention of Hollywood and fans worldwide, Bijou Phillips, model and actress, has filed for divorce from her husband, actor Danny Masterson, best known for his role in the popular sitcom “That ’70s Show.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-marriage-under-the-spotlight&quot;&gt;A Marriage Under the Spotlight&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Phillips, 43, has cited “irreconcilable differences” in her official court documents. The couple, who got married in 2011, shares a daughter. Phillips’ petition notably seeks full legal and physical custody of their child, proposing visitation rights for Masterson.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While many knew them as a vibrant pair, especially after seeing them in matching outfits at various events, the shadows of recent events loomed large over their relationship. Just two weeks ago, Masterson, 47, received a sentence of 30 years to life in prison on two counts of forcible rape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-trials-and-emotional-rollercoaster&quot;&gt;The Trials and Emotional Rollercoaster&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The charges and subsequent conviction shook Hollywood. Masterson was on trial twice, with the first ending in a mistrial last November. He had faced accusations related to events occurring between 2001 and 2003 at his Hollywood Hills residence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Throughout the legal ordeals, Phillips remained a steadfast presence, supporting her husband in court. Sketches from the courtroom even captured a poignant moment where Masterson blew a kiss to his wife after his sentencing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This unwavering support might be why the news of their divorce has come as a surprise to many. Just last week, sources claimed Phillips had “no plans” to leave Masterson, even expressing her heartbreak and urging the court to consider his pivotal role in their family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-look-back-at-their-journey&quot;&gt;A Look Back at Their Journey&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The duo first crossed paths at a celebrity poker game in 2004. Their connection was instantaneous, leading to a 19-year journey together filled with ups and downs. They celebrated their union in 2011 and welcomed their daughter in 2014. Phillips once wrote about their bond, saying, “Danny and I have been together for 19 years… I can say that Danny has literally been a life-saving partner to me.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Masterson’s legal team has already signaled plans to appeal the court’s decision, citing alleged mistakes during the trial. On a related note, when the Church of Scientology was asked for a comment on Masterson’s case, they reaffirmed their policy urging members to adhere to the laws and denied any accusations of harassment towards the accusers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As this chapter ends and new ones begin for both Phillips and Masterson, fans and the entertainment world will be keenly watching and hoping for healing and closure for all involved.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">In a turn of events that’s captured the attention of Hollywood and fans worldwide, Bijou Phillips, model and actress, has filed for divorce from her husband, actor Danny Masterson, best known for his role in the popular sitcom “That ’70s Show.” A Marriage Under the Spotlight Phillips, 43, has cited “irreconcilable differences” in her official court documents. The couple, who got married in 2011, shares a daughter. Phillips’ petition notably seeks full legal and physical custody of their child, proposing visitation rights for Masterson. While many knew them as a vibrant pair, especially after seeing them in matching outfits at various events, the shadows of recent events loomed large over their relationship. Just two weeks ago, Masterson, 47, received a sentence of 30 years to life in prison on two counts of forcible rape. The Trials and Emotional Rollercoaster The charges and subsequent conviction shook Hollywood. Masterson was on trial twice, with the first ending in a mistrial last November. He had faced accusations related to events occurring between 2001 and 2003 at his Hollywood Hills residence. Throughout the legal ordeals, Phillips remained a steadfast presence, supporting her husband in court. Sketches from the courtroom even captured a poignant moment where Masterson blew a kiss to his wife after his sentencing. This unwavering support might be why the news of their divorce has come as a surprise to many. Just last week, sources claimed Phillips had “no plans” to leave Masterson, even expressing her heartbreak and urging the court to consider his pivotal role in their family. A Look Back at Their Journey The duo first crossed paths at a celebrity poker game in 2004. Their connection was instantaneous, leading to a 19-year journey together filled with ups and downs. They celebrated their union in 2011 and welcomed their daughter in 2014. Phillips once wrote about their bond, saying, “Danny and I have been together for 19 years… I can say that Danny has literally been a life-saving partner to me.” Masterson’s legal team has already signaled plans to appeal the court’s decision, citing alleged mistakes during the trial. On a related note, when the Church of Scientology was asked for a comment on Masterson’s case, they reaffirmed their policy urging members to adhere to the laws and denied any accusations of harassment towards the accusers. As this chapter ends and new ones begin for both Phillips and Masterson, fans and the entertainment world will be keenly watching and hoping for healing and closure for all involved.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump Calls Out Empty Seats at Biden’s UN Address</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/20/Trump-UN-Response/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump Calls Out Empty Seats at Biden’s UN Address" /><published>2023-09-20T06:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-20T06:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/20/Trump-UN-Response</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/20/Trump-UN-Response/">&lt;p&gt;In a recent post on Truth Social, former President Donald Trump pulled no punches when he highlighted the noticeably empty seats at President Joe Biden’s address to the United Nations General Assembly in New York. Trump’s assertion was clear: under Biden’s administration, America seems to have lost a measure of international respect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Biden Speaks to Half-Filled Hall&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Biden just finished his surrender (‘speech’) at the United Nations, and nobody, despite all we give them, showed up. No respect for America any longer!” Trump’s message on Truth Social stated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This observation was further underscored by the conspicuous absence of several world leaders. Notably missing were French President Emmanuel Macron, U.K. Prime Minister Rishi Sunak, India’s Prime Minister Narendra Modi, Chinese President Xi Jinping, and Russian President Vladimir Putin. With these key players absent, the U.S. was the only member of the five permanent members of the U.N. Security Council in attendance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Richard Gowan, U.N. director for the International Crisis Group, expressed his views to CBS News, noting the significance of the absence of Sunak and Macron.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Biden’s Appeal Amidst a Hollowed Audience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In his address, President Biden made passionate pleas to those present, emphasizing the importance of supporting Ukraine against Russia’s invasion. “Russia believes that the world will grow weary and allow it to brutalize Ukraine without consequence,” Biden remarked, urging the world to act.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In stark contrast, Trump has offered a decisive approach, stating his intention to resolve the Ukraine crisis within 24 hours should he be re-elected in 2024.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Questionable Choices on Iran&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adding to the list of criticisms, Biden’s recent dealings with Iran have come under severe scrutiny. A prisoner swap agreement, which allowed Iran to tap into $6 billion of previously frozen oil revenue, has been slammed by Republicans, including Trump.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The former President expressed his incredulity on Truth Social, questioning the wisdom of releasing funds while securing a mere trade of detainees. “How much of a kickback does Crooked Joe Biden get? Does anyone realize how much money 6 Billion Dollars is?” Trump asked pointedly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The White House countered by emphasizing that the funds would be strictly monitored and used only for humanitarian purposes. However, this response hasn’t silenced critics, including Trump, who see this move as a reflection of a broader theme of perceived weakness in Biden’s administration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With Biden’s recent actions raising eyebrows both at home and on the international stage, one can’t help but ponder if America’s position on the world stage is truly waning.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a recent post on Truth Social, former President Donald Trump pulled no punches when he highlighted the noticeably empty seats at President Joe Biden’s address to the United Nations General Assembly in New York. Trump’s assertion was clear: under Biden’s administration, America seems to have lost a measure of international respect. Biden Speaks to Half-Filled Hall “Biden just finished his surrender (‘speech’) at the United Nations, and nobody, despite all we give them, showed up. No respect for America any longer!” Trump’s message on Truth Social stated. This observation was further underscored by the conspicuous absence of several world leaders. Notably missing were French President Emmanuel Macron, U.K. Prime Minister Rishi Sunak, India’s Prime Minister Narendra Modi, Chinese President Xi Jinping, and Russian President Vladimir Putin. With these key players absent, the U.S. was the only member of the five permanent members of the U.N. Security Council in attendance. Richard Gowan, U.N. director for the International Crisis Group, expressed his views to CBS News, noting the significance of the absence of Sunak and Macron. Biden’s Appeal Amidst a Hollowed Audience In his address, President Biden made passionate pleas to those present, emphasizing the importance of supporting Ukraine against Russia’s invasion. “Russia believes that the world will grow weary and allow it to brutalize Ukraine without consequence,” Biden remarked, urging the world to act. In stark contrast, Trump has offered a decisive approach, stating his intention to resolve the Ukraine crisis within 24 hours should he be re-elected in 2024. Questionable Choices on Iran Adding to the list of criticisms, Biden’s recent dealings with Iran have come under severe scrutiny. A prisoner swap agreement, which allowed Iran to tap into $6 billion of previously frozen oil revenue, has been slammed by Republicans, including Trump. The former President expressed his incredulity on Truth Social, questioning the wisdom of releasing funds while securing a mere trade of detainees. “How much of a kickback does Crooked Joe Biden get? Does anyone realize how much money 6 Billion Dollars is?” Trump asked pointedly. The White House countered by emphasizing that the funds would be strictly monitored and used only for humanitarian purposes. However, this response hasn’t silenced critics, including Trump, who see this move as a reflection of a broader theme of perceived weakness in Biden’s administration. With Biden’s recent actions raising eyebrows both at home and on the international stage, one can’t help but ponder if America’s position on the world stage is truly waning.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">China’s Land Grabs in US - An Undeniable Threat to National Security</title><link href="/news/2023/09/19/China-National-Security-Concern/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="China’s Land Grabs in US - An Undeniable Threat to National Security" /><published>2023-09-19T17:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-19T17:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/19/China-National-Security-Concern</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/19/China-National-Security-Concern/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;China’s Footprint on American Soil Raises Red Flags&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Chinese companies buying up land on American soil are not just any companies; they have strong ties to the Chinese Communist Party (CCP). Rep. John Moolenaar, a Republican from Michigan, sees this as a ticking time bomb for U.S. national security. His warning? Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen needs to recognize the grave implications of these purchases.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Threat in Michigan&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earlier this year, Gotion Inc., a company deeply linked to the CCP, acquired a sizable plot of 270 acres in Michigan. Their intention is to build a $2.4 billion battery plant. Alarmingly, this location is just a stone’s throw (about 100 miles) from Camp Grayling, America’s most expansive National Guard training facility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s even more startling? Michigan is set to offer Gotion a whopping $175 million in grants and tax exemptions that would save them a staggering $540 million over 30 years. This is taxpayer money potentially aiding a national security risk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Demand for Tighter Scrutiny&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Moolenaar, being a member of the House Select Committee on the Chinese Communist Party, is urging for a thorough review by the Committee on Foreign Investment in the U.S. (CFIUS). This body exists to vet foreign investments in the U.S., particularly when there’s a whisper of national security risk. “National security is at stake,” Moolenaar emphasizes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Together with Rep. Mike Gallagher of Wisconsin, Moolenaar penned a letter to Yellen. Their clear-cut request? Block companies affiliated with the CCP from benefiting from the tax incentives outlined in the Inflation Reduction Act.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gotion, attempting to circumvent full oversight, has requested a CFIUS review—but solely on the land buy, excluding their actual plans for the acquired territory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Pattern of Concerns&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is not an isolated incident. Last year, the Fufeng Group, another firm tied to the CCP, had intentions to acquire 300 acres near the Grand Forks Air Force Base in North Dakota. Though CFIUS claimed a lack of jurisdiction to scrutinize the deal, the U.S. military rightly intervened to halt the transaction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Moolenaar fervently hopes for the Treasury Department’s proactive engagement this time. In his words, “This isn’t mere business. It’s about the very heart of our national security.”&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">China’s Footprint on American Soil Raises Red Flags The Chinese companies buying up land on American soil are not just any companies; they have strong ties to the Chinese Communist Party (CCP). Rep. John Moolenaar, a Republican from Michigan, sees this as a ticking time bomb for U.S. national security. His warning? Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen needs to recognize the grave implications of these purchases. The Threat in Michigan Earlier this year, Gotion Inc., a company deeply linked to the CCP, acquired a sizable plot of 270 acres in Michigan. Their intention is to build a $2.4 billion battery plant. Alarmingly, this location is just a stone’s throw (about 100 miles) from Camp Grayling, America’s most expansive National Guard training facility. What’s even more startling? Michigan is set to offer Gotion a whopping $175 million in grants and tax exemptions that would save them a staggering $540 million over 30 years. This is taxpayer money potentially aiding a national security risk. Demand for Tighter Scrutiny Rep. Moolenaar, being a member of the House Select Committee on the Chinese Communist Party, is urging for a thorough review by the Committee on Foreign Investment in the U.S. (CFIUS). This body exists to vet foreign investments in the U.S., particularly when there’s a whisper of national security risk. “National security is at stake,” Moolenaar emphasizes. Together with Rep. Mike Gallagher of Wisconsin, Moolenaar penned a letter to Yellen. Their clear-cut request? Block companies affiliated with the CCP from benefiting from the tax incentives outlined in the Inflation Reduction Act. Gotion, attempting to circumvent full oversight, has requested a CFIUS review—but solely on the land buy, excluding their actual plans for the acquired territory. A Pattern of Concerns This is not an isolated incident. Last year, the Fufeng Group, another firm tied to the CCP, had intentions to acquire 300 acres near the Grand Forks Air Force Base in North Dakota. Though CFIUS claimed a lack of jurisdiction to scrutinize the deal, the U.S. military rightly intervened to halt the transaction. Rep. Moolenaar fervently hopes for the Treasury Department’s proactive engagement this time. In his words, “This isn’t mere business. It’s about the very heart of our national security.”</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A Cinematic Journey Down “Route 60 - The Biblical Highway”</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/19/Biblical-Highway-Film/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Cinematic Journey Down “Route 60 - The Biblical Highway”" /><published>2023-09-19T16:10:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-19T16:10:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/19/Biblical-Highway-Film</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/19/Biblical-Highway-Film/">&lt;p&gt;Have you ever wondered about the actual places where iconic biblical figures like Jesus and Abraham trod? The upcoming film, “Route 60: The Biblical Highway”, is set to take audiences on a captivating tour of these ancient landmarks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;route-60---bridging-the-past-and-the-present&quot;&gt;“Route 60” - Bridging The Past And The Present&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The film showcases a 150-mile stretch in Israel, from Nazareth in the north to Beersheba in the south, commonly referred to as Route 60. This is the same path that figures such as Abraham and Jesus are believed to have walked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The journey is guided by former U.S. Secretary of State Mike Pompeo and David Friedman, who was the U.S. ambassador to Israel. With Pompeo’s Christian background and Friedman’s Jewish heritage, viewers will get dual perspectives on the rich history embedded in this sacred land.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2023/09/672/378/Highway-4.jpg?ve=1&amp;amp;tl=1&quot; alt=&quot;Image&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Mike Pompeo and David Friedman exploring biblical sites.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;insights-and-reflections&quot;&gt;Insights and Reflections&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Throughout the movie, Friedman emphasizes the significance of Route 60, calling it “the road that Abraham, the father of nations, walked” and highlighting its centrality to Christian beliefs due to its association with Jesus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The film doesn’t just focus on the spiritual; it draws parallels between biblical history and modern American politics. Moreover, with both guides having served under the Trump administration, there’s also a recounting of some key Middle East diplomatic milestones, including the landmark Abraham Accords.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;landmarks-and-discoveries&quot;&gt;Landmarks and Discoveries&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Viewers will be transported to the City of David in Jerusalem, where Jesus is believed to have healed a blind man. The team also visits Rachel’s tomb near Bethlehem, shedding light on its significance in Jewish traditions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A notable mention is the Church of the Holy Sepulchre, venerated as the burial place of Jesus Christ. Pompeo, familiar with Christian history, introduces audiences to the Garden of Gethsemane, the place Jesus visited after the Last Supper and where he was later arrested.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;contemporary-resonance&quot;&gt;Contemporary Resonance&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Besides the historical and spiritual journey, the film touches upon present-day conflicts. Route 60 traverses through Judea and Samaria, areas rich with biblical history but also centers of modern-day disputes between Palestinians and Israelis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The movie is touted by Friedman as “a very uplifting and spiritually invigorating film” and is sure to resonate with those intrigued by biblical history, as well as those keen on understanding its impact on today’s geopolitics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As “Route 60: The Biblical Highway” gets set to premiere in 1,500 U.S. theaters, audiences across the country await a cinematic experience that promises to bridge ancient tales with contemporary insights.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Have you ever wondered about the actual places where iconic biblical figures like Jesus and Abraham trod? The upcoming film, “Route 60: The Biblical Highway”, is set to take audiences on a captivating tour of these ancient landmarks. “Route 60” - Bridging The Past And The Present The film showcases a 150-mile stretch in Israel, from Nazareth in the north to Beersheba in the south, commonly referred to as Route 60. This is the same path that figures such as Abraham and Jesus are believed to have walked. The journey is guided by former U.S. Secretary of State Mike Pompeo and David Friedman, who was the U.S. ambassador to Israel. With Pompeo’s Christian background and Friedman’s Jewish heritage, viewers will get dual perspectives on the rich history embedded in this sacred land. Mike Pompeo and David Friedman exploring biblical sites. Insights and Reflections Throughout the movie, Friedman emphasizes the significance of Route 60, calling it “the road that Abraham, the father of nations, walked” and highlighting its centrality to Christian beliefs due to its association with Jesus. The film doesn’t just focus on the spiritual; it draws parallels between biblical history and modern American politics. Moreover, with both guides having served under the Trump administration, there’s also a recounting of some key Middle East diplomatic milestones, including the landmark Abraham Accords. Landmarks and Discoveries Viewers will be transported to the City of David in Jerusalem, where Jesus is believed to have healed a blind man. The team also visits Rachel’s tomb near Bethlehem, shedding light on its significance in Jewish traditions. A notable mention is the Church of the Holy Sepulchre, venerated as the burial place of Jesus Christ. Pompeo, familiar with Christian history, introduces audiences to the Garden of Gethsemane, the place Jesus visited after the Last Supper and where he was later arrested. Contemporary Resonance Besides the historical and spiritual journey, the film touches upon present-day conflicts. Route 60 traverses through Judea and Samaria, areas rich with biblical history but also centers of modern-day disputes between Palestinians and Israelis. The movie is touted by Friedman as “a very uplifting and spiritually invigorating film” and is sure to resonate with those intrigued by biblical history, as well as those keen on understanding its impact on today’s geopolitics. As “Route 60: The Biblical Highway” gets set to premiere in 1,500 U.S. theaters, audiences across the country await a cinematic experience that promises to bridge ancient tales with contemporary insights.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Surge in Public Sector Jobs - 2023 Sees Massive Hiring Wave</title><link href="/news/2023/09/19/Public-Sector-Jobs-Boom/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Surge in Public Sector Jobs - 2023 Sees Massive Hiring Wave" /><published>2023-09-19T15:04:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-19T15:04:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/19/Public-Sector-Jobs-Boom</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/19/Public-Sector-Jobs-Boom/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A New Dawn for Public Sector Employment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the first eight months of 2023, there’s been a notable rise in public-sector job offerings. As reported by &lt;em&gt;The Wall Street Journal&lt;/em&gt;, the Bureau of Labor Statistics indicates an addition of 327,000 positions in the public sector. This impressive number represents almost 20% of all new jobs created this year, a significant leap from the mere 5% of total employment growth witnessed in the previous year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why the Sudden Jump?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are a few factors that contributed to this growth. For one, the aftermath of the 9/11 terrorist attacks in 2001 witnessed a similar hiring spree, when the U.S. government was on a hiring spree to address public safety concerns. Julia Pollak, an economist at the popular online job platform ZipRecruiter, made this insightful comparison.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Additionally, the onset of the coronavirus pandemic saw a vast number of teachers, police officers, and other essential public workers stepping away from their roles. This left a massive void in the public sector, which is now being filled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Border Patrol Ups Its Game&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A clear illustration of the public sector’s aggressive hiring approach can be seen in the U.S. Customs and Border Protection’s recent activities. They’ve strengthened their presence along the Mexico border. As part of their recruitment strategy, they’re offering attractive bonuses and other enticing incentives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the topic of incentives, job postings on ZipRecruiter for government roles this year are showcasing salaries that are roughly 20% higher than what they were in 2022. This substantial bump in salary offerings is bound to make these roles more appealing to job seekers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Word of Caution&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While this growth in the public sector is commendable, economists and HR leaders sound a word of caution. If the economy were to falter, resulting in budget deficits, the current momentum in public sector hiring could face significant challenges. Economic shortfalls could hinder governments’ ability to recruit for new positions in the future, making it imperative to monitor the situation closely.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">A New Dawn for Public Sector Employment In the first eight months of 2023, there’s been a notable rise in public-sector job offerings. As reported by The Wall Street Journal, the Bureau of Labor Statistics indicates an addition of 327,000 positions in the public sector. This impressive number represents almost 20% of all new jobs created this year, a significant leap from the mere 5% of total employment growth witnessed in the previous year. Why the Sudden Jump? There are a few factors that contributed to this growth. For one, the aftermath of the 9/11 terrorist attacks in 2001 witnessed a similar hiring spree, when the U.S. government was on a hiring spree to address public safety concerns. Julia Pollak, an economist at the popular online job platform ZipRecruiter, made this insightful comparison. Additionally, the onset of the coronavirus pandemic saw a vast number of teachers, police officers, and other essential public workers stepping away from their roles. This left a massive void in the public sector, which is now being filled. Border Patrol Ups Its Game A clear illustration of the public sector’s aggressive hiring approach can be seen in the U.S. Customs and Border Protection’s recent activities. They’ve strengthened their presence along the Mexico border. As part of their recruitment strategy, they’re offering attractive bonuses and other enticing incentives. On the topic of incentives, job postings on ZipRecruiter for government roles this year are showcasing salaries that are roughly 20% higher than what they were in 2022. This substantial bump in salary offerings is bound to make these roles more appealing to job seekers. A Word of Caution While this growth in the public sector is commendable, economists and HR leaders sound a word of caution. If the economy were to falter, resulting in budget deficits, the current momentum in public sector hiring could face significant challenges. Economic shortfalls could hinder governments’ ability to recruit for new positions in the future, making it imperative to monitor the situation closely.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump Champions Auto Workers in Detroit Amidst GOP Debate</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/19/Trump-Detroit/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump Champions Auto Workers in Detroit Amidst GOP Debate" /><published>2023-09-19T14:05:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-19T14:05:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/19/Trump-Detroit</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/19/Trump-Detroit/">&lt;p&gt;As the GOP candidates gear up for the second debate, Former President Donald Trump is once again pivoting away from the spotlight of party politics. Instead, he’s heading to Detroit, showing his support for the striking members of the United Auto Workers (UAW).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trump’s Unwavering Support for the Working Class&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Multiple sources, including Breitbart News and The New York Times, have confirmed Trump’s forthcoming appearance with UAW members, as they strike against automotive giants — General Motors, Ford, and Stellantis. This bold move is seen as a counter to the GOP debate scheduled at the Ronald Reagan Presidential Library in California.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main focus of the union’s strike centers around higher wages amidst rising inflation and ensuring job security in President Joe Biden’s shifting vehicle agenda. Trump is slated to deliver a prime-time speech to current and former union members, highlighting these concerns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Strategic Move With A Broader Goal?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This isn’t the first time Trump has opted for such a strategy. Instead of attending the first GOP debate, he chose a one-on-one with Tucker Carlson, the host of the “Tucker on Twitter” show. This move generated significant attention, underscoring Trump’s distinctive style.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many believe Trump’s approach is centered less on the GOP primaries and more on a potential general election rematch against President Biden. Historically, union workers, traditionally aligned with Democrats, played a crucial role in electing Trump in 2016.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Clear Message for the UAW and Biden’s Policies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a recent post on Truth Social, Trump made his feelings clear about Biden’s electric vehicle strategy, suggesting it adversely affects UAW members. “AUTOWORKERS, VOTE FOR TRUMP – I’LL MAKE YOU VICTORIOUS &amp;amp; RICH,” Trump emphasized, urging workers to reconsider any allegiance to leaders who do not prioritize their interests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump’s message is clear: he stands firmly with the American working class. As the former President champions the cause of auto workers in Detroit, it becomes evident that his commitment to the everyday American remains undiminished.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">As the GOP candidates gear up for the second debate, Former President Donald Trump is once again pivoting away from the spotlight of party politics. Instead, he’s heading to Detroit, showing his support for the striking members of the United Auto Workers (UAW). Trump’s Unwavering Support for the Working Class Multiple sources, including Breitbart News and The New York Times, have confirmed Trump’s forthcoming appearance with UAW members, as they strike against automotive giants — General Motors, Ford, and Stellantis. This bold move is seen as a counter to the GOP debate scheduled at the Ronald Reagan Presidential Library in California. The main focus of the union’s strike centers around higher wages amidst rising inflation and ensuring job security in President Joe Biden’s shifting vehicle agenda. Trump is slated to deliver a prime-time speech to current and former union members, highlighting these concerns. A Strategic Move With A Broader Goal? This isn’t the first time Trump has opted for such a strategy. Instead of attending the first GOP debate, he chose a one-on-one with Tucker Carlson, the host of the “Tucker on Twitter” show. This move generated significant attention, underscoring Trump’s distinctive style. Many believe Trump’s approach is centered less on the GOP primaries and more on a potential general election rematch against President Biden. Historically, union workers, traditionally aligned with Democrats, played a crucial role in electing Trump in 2016. A Clear Message for the UAW and Biden’s Policies In a recent post on Truth Social, Trump made his feelings clear about Biden’s electric vehicle strategy, suggesting it adversely affects UAW members. “AUTOWORKERS, VOTE FOR TRUMP – I’LL MAKE YOU VICTORIOUS &amp;amp; RICH,” Trump emphasized, urging workers to reconsider any allegiance to leaders who do not prioritize their interests. Trump’s message is clear: he stands firmly with the American working class. As the former President champions the cause of auto workers in Detroit, it becomes evident that his commitment to the everyday American remains undiminished.</summary></entry></feed>