<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-09-18T13:13:58-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/09/18/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-09-18T13:13:58-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-18T13:13:58-04:00</updated><id>/2023/09/18/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/18/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Ambush Attack on LA Sheriff’s Deputy Ends in Arrest</title><link href="/news/2023/09/18/Arrest-in-LA-Deputy-Ambush/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ambush Attack on LA Sheriff’s Deputy Ends in Arrest" /><published>2023-09-18T13:04:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-18T13:04:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/18/Arrest-in-LA-Deputy-Ambush</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/18/Arrest-in-LA-Deputy-Ambush/">&lt;p&gt;Los Angeles Sheriff’s Deputy Ryan Clinkunbroomer was tragically shot and killed while on duty in Palmdale, California. Now, sources have confirmed to Fox News that an arrest has been made in connection with this horrific incident.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Swift Break in the Case&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Investigators received a pivotal tip which led them to a residence in Palmdale - the same location where Clinkunbroomer was ambushed in his patrol vehicle on Saturday, Sept. 16. A relative of the suspect offered crucial information about the case. As a result, the male suspect was detained without any disruptions, with officers using gas to ensure a peaceful arrest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Reward for Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the wake of the shooting, a significant $250,000 reward was publicized for any leads that would result in an arrest. Surveillance footage showing the moments leading up to the unfortunate event was released. The clip showcased a suspicious black car positioning itself next to Clinkunbroomer’s cruiser, right before the fatal shooting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even though the surveillance video doesn’t reveal the shooting itself, it captures the black vehicle speeding away while the deputy’s cruiser rolls forward slowly, eventually stopping. An observant citizen noticed Clinkunbroomer unresponsive in his car and promptly alerted fellow deputies at the Palmdale Sheriff’s Station.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heading to the Hospital&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With no time to lose, Clinkunbroomer was rushed to the hospital in his cruiser. Midway, an ambulance reached the cruiser, took over the transportation, and another deputy drove his vehicle to a medical center in Lancaster.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While authorities have made progress in the case, the motive behind the shooting remains uncertain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Life of Service&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remembered fondly by his peers and superiors, Clinkunbroomer had served the Palmdale and Antelope Valley communities for eight years. Sheriff Robert Luna remarked about the deputy’s dedication and service, noting that both Clinkunbroomer’s father and grandfather had served in the sheriff’s department as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sheriff Luna voiced his grief on X (formerly known as Twitter), highlighting the sacrifice Ryan Clinkunbroomer made for his community. “He laid everything on the line to serve us,” Luna expressed, underscoring the deputy’s commitment&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Los Angeles Sheriff’s Deputy Ryan Clinkunbroomer was tragically shot and killed while on duty in Palmdale, California. Now, sources have confirmed to Fox News that an arrest has been made in connection with this horrific incident. A Swift Break in the Case Investigators received a pivotal tip which led them to a residence in Palmdale - the same location where Clinkunbroomer was ambushed in his patrol vehicle on Saturday, Sept. 16. A relative of the suspect offered crucial information about the case. As a result, the male suspect was detained without any disruptions, with officers using gas to ensure a peaceful arrest. A Reward for Information In the wake of the shooting, a significant $250,000 reward was publicized for any leads that would result in an arrest. Surveillance footage showing the moments leading up to the unfortunate event was released. The clip showcased a suspicious black car positioning itself next to Clinkunbroomer’s cruiser, right before the fatal shooting. Even though the surveillance video doesn’t reveal the shooting itself, it captures the black vehicle speeding away while the deputy’s cruiser rolls forward slowly, eventually stopping. An observant citizen noticed Clinkunbroomer unresponsive in his car and promptly alerted fellow deputies at the Palmdale Sheriff’s Station. Heading to the Hospital With no time to lose, Clinkunbroomer was rushed to the hospital in his cruiser. Midway, an ambulance reached the cruiser, took over the transportation, and another deputy drove his vehicle to a medical center in Lancaster. While authorities have made progress in the case, the motive behind the shooting remains uncertain. A Life of Service Remembered fondly by his peers and superiors, Clinkunbroomer had served the Palmdale and Antelope Valley communities for eight years. Sheriff Robert Luna remarked about the deputy’s dedication and service, noting that both Clinkunbroomer’s father and grandfather had served in the sheriff’s department as well. Sheriff Luna voiced his grief on X (formerly known as Twitter), highlighting the sacrifice Ryan Clinkunbroomer made for his community. “He laid everything on the line to serve us,” Luna expressed, underscoring the deputy’s commitment</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Impersonator with Guns Crashes RFK Jr Event - A Startling Encounter</title><link href="/news/2023/09/18/Imposing-Impersonator/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Impersonator with Guns Crashes RFK Jr Event - A Startling Encounter" /><published>2023-09-18T11:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-18T11:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/18/Imposing-Impersonator</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/18/Imposing-Impersonator/">&lt;p&gt;In a startling incident, a man was detained at a campaign event for Democratic presidential candidate Robert F. Kennedy Jr. in Los Angeles. Why? He was impersonating a U.S. Marshal, complete with shoulder holsters holding loaded pistols and spare ammo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Los Angeles Police Department identified this man as 44-year-old Adrian Paul Aispuro. Shortly after the incident, Kennedy expressed his gratitude on X, which was once known as Twitter. He thanked the security guards for their fast action.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kennedy wrote, “I’m very grateful that alert and fast-acting protectors from Gavin de Becker and Associates (GDBA) spotted and detained an armed man who attempted to approach me at my Hispanic Heritage speech at the Wilshire Ebell Theatre in Los Angeles tonight.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, the impersonator had not just any badge, but a U.S. Marshal badge. He introduced himself as part of Kennedy’s security detail. Thankfully, the GDBA team was on their toes. They detained him till the LAPD could arrive and make an arrest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kennedy, who is challenging President Biden, also mentioned he has yet to get protection from the Secret Service. He said, “I’m still hoping President Biden will grant me Secret Service protection. I am the first presidential candidate in history to whom the White House has denied a request for protection.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This denial comes even though, back in 1968, Robert F. Kennedy was tragically shot and killed in LA, not far from where this recent event took place. Kennedy Jr.’s uncle, former President John F. Kennedy, was also assassinated in 1963.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Photos of Aispuro from the event have been circulating online. He was caught wearing a black shirt stamped with “Emergency Medical Services.” As of now, he remains in custody with a bail set at $35,000.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This incident is a sobering reminder of the potential threats political figures face, even in modern-day campaigns. It underscores the importance of security and protection for those in the public eye.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a startling incident, a man was detained at a campaign event for Democratic presidential candidate Robert F. Kennedy Jr. in Los Angeles. Why? He was impersonating a U.S. Marshal, complete with shoulder holsters holding loaded pistols and spare ammo. The Los Angeles Police Department identified this man as 44-year-old Adrian Paul Aispuro. Shortly after the incident, Kennedy expressed his gratitude on X, which was once known as Twitter. He thanked the security guards for their fast action. Kennedy wrote, “I’m very grateful that alert and fast-acting protectors from Gavin de Becker and Associates (GDBA) spotted and detained an armed man who attempted to approach me at my Hispanic Heritage speech at the Wilshire Ebell Theatre in Los Angeles tonight.” Interestingly, the impersonator had not just any badge, but a U.S. Marshal badge. He introduced himself as part of Kennedy’s security detail. Thankfully, the GDBA team was on their toes. They detained him till the LAPD could arrive and make an arrest. Kennedy, who is challenging President Biden, also mentioned he has yet to get protection from the Secret Service. He said, “I’m still hoping President Biden will grant me Secret Service protection. I am the first presidential candidate in history to whom the White House has denied a request for protection.” This denial comes even though, back in 1968, Robert F. Kennedy was tragically shot and killed in LA, not far from where this recent event took place. Kennedy Jr.’s uncle, former President John F. Kennedy, was also assassinated in 1963. Photos of Aispuro from the event have been circulating online. He was caught wearing a black shirt stamped with “Emergency Medical Services.” As of now, he remains in custody with a bail set at $35,000. This incident is a sobering reminder of the potential threats political figures face, even in modern-day campaigns. It underscores the importance of security and protection for those in the public eye.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">NKorea’s Kim Strengthens Ties - Returns with Russian Drones and More</title><link href="/news/2023/09/18/NKorea-Russia-Ties/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="NKorea’s Kim Strengthens Ties - Returns with Russian Drones and More" /><published>2023-09-18T10:09:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-18T10:09:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/18/NKorea-Russia-Ties</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/18/NKorea-Russia-Ties/">&lt;p&gt;In a move that’s garnered international attention, North Korean leader Kim Jong Un recently wrapped up a noteworthy six-day visit to Russia. This trip, Kim’s first outside North Korea since the onset of the coronavirus pandemic, had a significant focus on military cooperation between the two nations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;strengthened-relations-amidst-western-concerns&quot;&gt;Strengthened Relations Amidst Western Concerns&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kim’s visit signals a deepening bond between Russia and North Korea, much to the West’s alarm. Observers are anxious about the implications of strengthened ties, especially given Russia’s ongoing conflict in Ukraine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Throughout his visit, Kim engaged in various activities signifying the military unity between the two nations, including a symbolic rifle exchange with Russian President Vladimir Putin and close inspections of advanced Russian weaponry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;defying-international-sanctions&quot;&gt;Defying International Sanctions?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Russia’s Foreign Minister, Sergei Lavrov, during a national television broadcast, underscored Russia’s intention to bolster its alliance with North Korea, irrespective of UN sanctions. “We will be developing equal, fair interaction with the DPRK,” Lavrov noted, referring to North Korea by its official name.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of the many gestures that highlighted the trip, Kim’s reception of drones and a bulletproof vest from the governor of Russia’s Primorye region, which neighbors North Korea, was particularly significant. This gift, comprising five explosive drones and a reconnaissance drone, marked a symbolic end to Kim’s stay in Vladivostok, the Pacific port city just beyond the North Korean border.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond military discussions, the two nations have also deliberated on reviving certain infrastructure projects, escalating grain supplies, and resuming routine air travel. An upcoming official meeting between the two countries is slated for November in Pyongyang.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;an-era-of-renewed-cooperation&quot;&gt;An Era of Renewed Cooperation?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Historical allies, Russia and North Korea, both subjected to global sanctions, have shown signs of renewed camaraderie. Their respective sanctions are due to Moscow’s Ukraine interventions and Pyongyang’s nuclear weapon trials.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During their meeting, Putin and Kim deliberated on the potential for enhanced cooperation and military ties. While Moscow might be eyeing North Korean ammunition for its Ukraine operations, Pyongyang seeks Russia’s expertise in propelling its missile program. Notably, no official agreement has been confirmed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The North Korean state news agency, KCNA, portrayed Kim’s trip as the beginning of a “new era of friendship, solidarity, and cooperation” between the two nations. As a testament to their deepening ties, Putin has accepted an invitation to visit North Korea and even proposed sending a North Korean astronaut to space, a historical first.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the world watches, the evolving alliance between Russia and North Korea will undoubtedly influence the geopolitical landscape in the days to come.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a move that’s garnered international attention, North Korean leader Kim Jong Un recently wrapped up a noteworthy six-day visit to Russia. This trip, Kim’s first outside North Korea since the onset of the coronavirus pandemic, had a significant focus on military cooperation between the two nations. Strengthened Relations Amidst Western Concerns Kim’s visit signals a deepening bond between Russia and North Korea, much to the West’s alarm. Observers are anxious about the implications of strengthened ties, especially given Russia’s ongoing conflict in Ukraine. Throughout his visit, Kim engaged in various activities signifying the military unity between the two nations, including a symbolic rifle exchange with Russian President Vladimir Putin and close inspections of advanced Russian weaponry. Defying International Sanctions? Russia’s Foreign Minister, Sergei Lavrov, during a national television broadcast, underscored Russia’s intention to bolster its alliance with North Korea, irrespective of UN sanctions. “We will be developing equal, fair interaction with the DPRK,” Lavrov noted, referring to North Korea by its official name. Of the many gestures that highlighted the trip, Kim’s reception of drones and a bulletproof vest from the governor of Russia’s Primorye region, which neighbors North Korea, was particularly significant. This gift, comprising five explosive drones and a reconnaissance drone, marked a symbolic end to Kim’s stay in Vladivostok, the Pacific port city just beyond the North Korean border. Beyond military discussions, the two nations have also deliberated on reviving certain infrastructure projects, escalating grain supplies, and resuming routine air travel. An upcoming official meeting between the two countries is slated for November in Pyongyang. An Era of Renewed Cooperation? Historical allies, Russia and North Korea, both subjected to global sanctions, have shown signs of renewed camaraderie. Their respective sanctions are due to Moscow’s Ukraine interventions and Pyongyang’s nuclear weapon trials. During their meeting, Putin and Kim deliberated on the potential for enhanced cooperation and military ties. While Moscow might be eyeing North Korean ammunition for its Ukraine operations, Pyongyang seeks Russia’s expertise in propelling its missile program. Notably, no official agreement has been confirmed. The North Korean state news agency, KCNA, portrayed Kim’s trip as the beginning of a “new era of friendship, solidarity, and cooperation” between the two nations. As a testament to their deepening ties, Putin has accepted an invitation to visit North Korea and even proposed sending a North Korean astronaut to space, a historical first. As the world watches, the evolving alliance between Russia and North Korea will undoubtedly influence the geopolitical landscape in the days to come.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump vs. Biden - A Michigan Showdown on the Horizon?</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/18/Trump-Biden-Michigan-Showdown/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump vs. Biden - A Michigan Showdown on the Horizon?" /><published>2023-09-18T09:15:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-18T09:15:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/18/Trump-Biden-Michigan-Showdown</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/18/Trump-Biden-Michigan-Showdown/">&lt;p&gt;Michigan, often regarded as the heartbeat of America’s political battlegrounds, has once again captured national attention. A recent poll by Susquehanna Polling and Research suggests that if a presidential election were to take place today between Former President Donald Trump and President Joe Biden, the outcome would be too close to call.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;trump-and-biden-the-michigan-standoff&quot;&gt;Trump and Biden: The Michigan Standoff&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The poll, initially shared with the Hill, indicates that 46% of probable Michigander voters would rally behind Biden, with Trump trailing close at 43%. Surprisingly, a considerable 11% remain undecided. With a margin of error standing at 3.7%, it’s clear: these political heavyweights are virtually tied in the Wolverine State.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump’s strong grip on the GOP is evident, with a commendable 90% support from his party base. Comparatively, Biden garners support from 87% of Democrat respondents. Jim Lee, the president of Susquehanna Polling and Research, pointed out a significant tidbit: Biden’s support among Democrats in Michigan has seen a slight dip from 97% in 2020. On the other hand, Trump’s GOP support remains consistent, witnessing only a minor dip from 94% in the previous election.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;independents--the-national-trend&quot;&gt;Independents &amp;amp; the National Trend&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although Biden seems to have a modest lead with independent voters in Michigan (44% vs. Trump’s 37%), national trends are slightly leaning in Trump’s favor. Both Harvard-Harris and CBS News/YouGov polls depict Trump holding an edge among the independent voters at the national level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;michigan-a-legacy-of-close-calls&quot;&gt;Michigan: A Legacy of Close Calls&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Historically, Michigan has been a decisive battleground. Trump’s 2016 victory over Hillary Clinton by a mere one-third of a percentage point is a testament to that. Comparatively, Biden’s win over Trump in 2020 was by a little less than three percentage points. A shift of a few votes can change the course of history in Michigan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;trump-leads-the-gop-desantis-trails&quot;&gt;Trump Leads the GOP, DeSantis Trails&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the Trump vs. Biden matchup is drawing significant attention, there’s also a buzz around other potential contenders. If Governor Ron DeSantis of Florida were to be pitted against Biden, he’d fare slightly worse than Trump, lagging behind by three more points. However, within the GOP, Trump remains the alpha, garnering a massive 65% support, leaving DeSantis trailing significantly at 18%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;wrapping-up&quot;&gt;Wrapping Up&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While these polls provide a sneak peek into the current political sentiment, they’re merely snapshots in time. Michigan’s political landscape has always been dynamic, and only time will reveal the true sentiments of its voters. One thing remains certain: Michigan will be a state to watch in any upcoming elections.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Michigan, often regarded as the heartbeat of America’s political battlegrounds, has once again captured national attention. A recent poll by Susquehanna Polling and Research suggests that if a presidential election were to take place today between Former President Donald Trump and President Joe Biden, the outcome would be too close to call. Trump and Biden: The Michigan Standoff The poll, initially shared with the Hill, indicates that 46% of probable Michigander voters would rally behind Biden, with Trump trailing close at 43%. Surprisingly, a considerable 11% remain undecided. With a margin of error standing at 3.7%, it’s clear: these political heavyweights are virtually tied in the Wolverine State. Trump’s strong grip on the GOP is evident, with a commendable 90% support from his party base. Comparatively, Biden garners support from 87% of Democrat respondents. Jim Lee, the president of Susquehanna Polling and Research, pointed out a significant tidbit: Biden’s support among Democrats in Michigan has seen a slight dip from 97% in 2020. On the other hand, Trump’s GOP support remains consistent, witnessing only a minor dip from 94% in the previous election. Independents &amp;amp; the National Trend Although Biden seems to have a modest lead with independent voters in Michigan (44% vs. Trump’s 37%), national trends are slightly leaning in Trump’s favor. Both Harvard-Harris and CBS News/YouGov polls depict Trump holding an edge among the independent voters at the national level. Michigan: A Legacy of Close Calls Historically, Michigan has been a decisive battleground. Trump’s 2016 victory over Hillary Clinton by a mere one-third of a percentage point is a testament to that. Comparatively, Biden’s win over Trump in 2020 was by a little less than three percentage points. A shift of a few votes can change the course of history in Michigan. Trump Leads the GOP, DeSantis Trails While the Trump vs. Biden matchup is drawing significant attention, there’s also a buzz around other potential contenders. If Governor Ron DeSantis of Florida were to be pitted against Biden, he’d fare slightly worse than Trump, lagging behind by three more points. However, within the GOP, Trump remains the alpha, garnering a massive 65% support, leaving DeSantis trailing significantly at 18%. Wrapping Up While these polls provide a sneak peek into the current political sentiment, they’re merely snapshots in time. Michigan’s political landscape has always been dynamic, and only time will reveal the true sentiments of its voters. One thing remains certain: Michigan will be a state to watch in any upcoming elections.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Farmer Exemplifies Second Amendment Rights - Halts Burglars in Their Tracks</title><link href="/news/2023/09/18/Farmer-Stands-Ground/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Farmer Exemplifies Second Amendment Rights - Halts Burglars in Their Tracks" /><published>2023-09-18T08:02:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-18T08:02:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/18/Farmer-Stands-Ground</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/18/Farmer-Stands-Ground/">&lt;p&gt;Amidst rising concerns about property crimes, a Washington state farmer recently demonstrated the importance and effectiveness of the Second Amendment. The farmer exercised his constitutional right by holding two suspected burglars at gunpoint on his land until the police arrived.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;crime-halted-by-vigilance&quot;&gt;Crime Halted by Vigilance&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last Saturday, around 7 p.m., Grant County deputies received a report of two individuals suspected of burglary on a farm in Quincy. The farmer discovered these intruders on his property, allegedly attempting to target two of his farm shops. Acting responsibly and quickly, the farmer drew his firearm, holding the suspects in place until law enforcement could take over.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Upon investigation, the deputies, with the aid of footprints found inside the shops, identified the two men as 45-year-old Glenn Richard of Quincy and 28-year-old Jesus Rangel of Mattawa. Both were subsequently arrested on burglary charges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2023/09/720/405/grantcount2.png?ve=1&amp;amp;tl=1&quot; alt=&quot;View of the farm&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;A scenic view of farmland in Quincy, Washington, a testament to the hard work and vigilance of its residents.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-broader-picture&quot;&gt;The Broader Picture&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Grant County Sheriff’s Office spokesman, Kyle Foreman, commended the responsible gun owners in the county. Speaking to local media, he stated, “We have many responsible gun owners here in Grant County and if they are outside protecting their property, they can certainly hold someone at gunpoint and then call 911 to have us come and investigate.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Foreman further elaborated on the legal grounds supporting the farmer’s actions. The law in Washington allows residents to reasonably detain someone who unlawfully enters their property, as long as the detention is reasonable in both duration and manner. This legal provision ensures property owners can safeguard their belongings and lands from potential intruders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;supporting-the-second-amendment&quot;&gt;Supporting the Second Amendment&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The story of the vigilant farmer stands as a testament to the critical role the Second Amendment plays in safeguarding individual rights and properties. It offers a compelling narrative in favor of responsible gun ownership, particularly in areas where properties might be vulnerable to such criminal activities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a society where property crimes are increasingly prevalent, it’s vital that citizens feel empowered and have the means to protect themselves and their belongings. This incident, and others like it, exemplify the importance of upholding the Second Amendment in ensuring that right.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Amidst rising concerns about property crimes, a Washington state farmer recently demonstrated the importance and effectiveness of the Second Amendment. The farmer exercised his constitutional right by holding two suspected burglars at gunpoint on his land until the police arrived. Crime Halted by Vigilance Last Saturday, around 7 p.m., Grant County deputies received a report of two individuals suspected of burglary on a farm in Quincy. The farmer discovered these intruders on his property, allegedly attempting to target two of his farm shops. Acting responsibly and quickly, the farmer drew his firearm, holding the suspects in place until law enforcement could take over. Upon investigation, the deputies, with the aid of footprints found inside the shops, identified the two men as 45-year-old Glenn Richard of Quincy and 28-year-old Jesus Rangel of Mattawa. Both were subsequently arrested on burglary charges. A scenic view of farmland in Quincy, Washington, a testament to the hard work and vigilance of its residents. The Broader Picture Grant County Sheriff’s Office spokesman, Kyle Foreman, commended the responsible gun owners in the county. Speaking to local media, he stated, “We have many responsible gun owners here in Grant County and if they are outside protecting their property, they can certainly hold someone at gunpoint and then call 911 to have us come and investigate.” Foreman further elaborated on the legal grounds supporting the farmer’s actions. The law in Washington allows residents to reasonably detain someone who unlawfully enters their property, as long as the detention is reasonable in both duration and manner. This legal provision ensures property owners can safeguard their belongings and lands from potential intruders. Supporting the Second Amendment The story of the vigilant farmer stands as a testament to the critical role the Second Amendment plays in safeguarding individual rights and properties. It offers a compelling narrative in favor of responsible gun ownership, particularly in areas where properties might be vulnerable to such criminal activities. In a society where property crimes are increasingly prevalent, it’s vital that citizens feel empowered and have the means to protect themselves and their belongings. This incident, and others like it, exemplify the importance of upholding the Second Amendment in ensuring that right.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Drew Barrymore Hits Pause - Daytime Show on Hold Amid WGA Strike</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/18/Barrymore-Show-Pause/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Drew Barrymore Hits Pause - Daytime Show on Hold Amid WGA Strike" /><published>2023-09-18T07:05:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-18T07:05:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/18/Barrymore-Show-Pause</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/18/Barrymore-Show-Pause/">&lt;p&gt;In a turn of events that’s grabbed the attention of the entertainment industry, Drew Barrymore has chosen to halt the production of her popular daytime talk show until the ongoing Writers Guild of America (WGA) strike is resolved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;listening-and-learning&quot;&gt;Listening and Learning&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Barrymore, known for her roles in various hit movies and her recent venture into daytime television, shared her decision on social media. “I have listened to everyone, and I am making the decision to pause the show’s premiere until the strike is over,” she stated on her Instagram.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This surprising announcement comes a week after she declared her support for the strike, yet revealed plans to continue recording her show. Her reasoning? To ensure the rest of her show’s crew, whose livelihoods depend on the show, could get back to their jobs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tug-of-war-in-tinseltown&quot;&gt;Tug of War in Tinseltown&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The WGA did not take Barrymore’s original decision lightly. Following her initial announcement, other notable celebrities, including Bill Maher, Jennifer Hudson, and Sherri Shepherd, decided they too would continue with their respective shows despite the strike.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This ongoing writers’ strike, combined with a work stoppage from the Screen Actors Guild, has effectively brought most of North America’s TV and film productions to a standstill.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;an-emotional-apology&quot;&gt;An Emotional Apology&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earlier, Barrymore took to Instagram, sharing a heartfelt video. Tearfully, she apologized to the striking writers, emphasizing the importance of the issues at stake. “This is bigger than me, and there are other people’s jobs on the line,” she emphasized.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, within a day, this emotional video was no longer available on her profile, raising more questions about the internal and external pressures faced by celebrities during such industry disputes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It remains to be seen how long the WGA strike will continue, but Barrymore’s decision to pause is a significant move in the ever-evolving landscape of entertainment industry politics.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">In a turn of events that’s grabbed the attention of the entertainment industry, Drew Barrymore has chosen to halt the production of her popular daytime talk show until the ongoing Writers Guild of America (WGA) strike is resolved. Listening and Learning Barrymore, known for her roles in various hit movies and her recent venture into daytime television, shared her decision on social media. “I have listened to everyone, and I am making the decision to pause the show’s premiere until the strike is over,” she stated on her Instagram. This surprising announcement comes a week after she declared her support for the strike, yet revealed plans to continue recording her show. Her reasoning? To ensure the rest of her show’s crew, whose livelihoods depend on the show, could get back to their jobs. Tug of War in Tinseltown The WGA did not take Barrymore’s original decision lightly. Following her initial announcement, other notable celebrities, including Bill Maher, Jennifer Hudson, and Sherri Shepherd, decided they too would continue with their respective shows despite the strike. This ongoing writers’ strike, combined with a work stoppage from the Screen Actors Guild, has effectively brought most of North America’s TV and film productions to a standstill. An Emotional Apology Earlier, Barrymore took to Instagram, sharing a heartfelt video. Tearfully, she apologized to the striking writers, emphasizing the importance of the issues at stake. “This is bigger than me, and there are other people’s jobs on the line,” she emphasized. However, within a day, this emotional video was no longer available on her profile, raising more questions about the internal and external pressures faced by celebrities during such industry disputes. It remains to be seen how long the WGA strike will continue, but Barrymore’s decision to pause is a significant move in the ever-evolving landscape of entertainment industry politics.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump Calls Out Pelosi’s Security Decision Ahead of Capitol Riot</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/18/Trump-Security-Decision/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump Calls Out Pelosi’s Security Decision Ahead of Capitol Riot" /><published>2023-09-18T06:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-18T06:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/18/Trump-Security-Decision</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/18/Trump-Security-Decision/">&lt;p&gt;In an enlightening interview, former President Donald Trump recently argued against former House Speaker Nancy Pelosi, claiming her decisions played a significant role in the events that transpired on January 6th.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-decision-not-taken&quot;&gt;The Decision Not Taken&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking with NBC’s “Meet the Press” host, Kristen Welker, Trump didn’t hold back. He stated, “Nancy Pelosi was in charge of security. She turned down 10,000 soldiers. If she didn’t turn down the soldiers, you wouldn’t have had Jan. 6.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welker challenged Trump’s stance, mentioning that Pelosi lacked the same security authority he possessed as the commander in chief. But Trump countered by highlighting how the Capitol police, who he described as “great people,” had testified against Pelosi.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2023/09/720/405/GettyImages-1683740340.jpg?ve=1&amp;amp;tl=1&quot; alt=&quot;Trump speaking at the Pray Vote Stand Summit&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Former President Donald Trump holds firm to his belief that former Speaker of the House, Nancy Pelosi, played a significant role in the Jan. 6 events.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump reiterated that Pelosi held authority over the Capitol and that her alleged refusal to bolster security with the National Guard, even after his request, was a major oversight. In his eyes, Pelosi’s decision is a clear indicator of her responsibility for the events of January 6th.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;different-versions-of-the-story&quot;&gt;Different Versions of the Story&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naturally, there have been conflicting accounts on who was responsible for the security decisions that day. Some point out that the choice to summon National Guard troops to the Capitol rests with the Capitol Police Board, which includes members like the House and Senate sergeants at arms. These officials reportedly decided against deploying the Guard before the riots but called for backup when the situation intensified.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The former Capitol Police Chief, Steven Sund, previously stated to &lt;em&gt;The Washington Post&lt;/em&gt; that he had requested backup several times both before and during the riot. According to him, these pleas were either delayed or denied outright.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2023/09/720/405/GettyImages-1681663999.jpg?ve=1&amp;amp;tl=1&quot; alt=&quot;Pelosi attends event&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Nancy Pelosi attends an event recently, where she praised the efforts of the Jan. 6 committee.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;leadership-on-display&quot;&gt;Leadership on Display&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When asked about his leadership during those tumultuous events, Trump confidently stated, “Yes, absolutely, I did.” He also touched upon the allegations made against him, refuting claims by a former aide and making it clear that he felt the charges against him were politically motivated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Regardless of where one stands on this issue, it’s evident that the January 6th event will remain a significant topic of debate and discussion in political circles. As investigations and inquiries continue, the hope is that a clearer picture of responsibility and accountability will emerge.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In an enlightening interview, former President Donald Trump recently argued against former House Speaker Nancy Pelosi, claiming her decisions played a significant role in the events that transpired on January 6th. The Decision Not Taken Speaking with NBC’s “Meet the Press” host, Kristen Welker, Trump didn’t hold back. He stated, “Nancy Pelosi was in charge of security. She turned down 10,000 soldiers. If she didn’t turn down the soldiers, you wouldn’t have had Jan. 6.” Welker challenged Trump’s stance, mentioning that Pelosi lacked the same security authority he possessed as the commander in chief. But Trump countered by highlighting how the Capitol police, who he described as “great people,” had testified against Pelosi. Former President Donald Trump holds firm to his belief that former Speaker of the House, Nancy Pelosi, played a significant role in the Jan. 6 events. Trump reiterated that Pelosi held authority over the Capitol and that her alleged refusal to bolster security with the National Guard, even after his request, was a major oversight. In his eyes, Pelosi’s decision is a clear indicator of her responsibility for the events of January 6th. Different Versions of the Story Naturally, there have been conflicting accounts on who was responsible for the security decisions that day. Some point out that the choice to summon National Guard troops to the Capitol rests with the Capitol Police Board, which includes members like the House and Senate sergeants at arms. These officials reportedly decided against deploying the Guard before the riots but called for backup when the situation intensified. The former Capitol Police Chief, Steven Sund, previously stated to The Washington Post that he had requested backup several times both before and during the riot. According to him, these pleas were either delayed or denied outright. Nancy Pelosi attends an event recently, where she praised the efforts of the Jan. 6 committee. Leadership on Display When asked about his leadership during those tumultuous events, Trump confidently stated, “Yes, absolutely, I did.” He also touched upon the allegations made against him, refuting claims by a former aide and making it clear that he felt the charges against him were politically motivated. Regardless of where one stands on this issue, it’s evident that the January 6th event will remain a significant topic of debate and discussion in political circles. As investigations and inquiries continue, the hope is that a clearer picture of responsibility and accountability will emerge.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump Talks Competency - Age Limits ‘Not Necessary’</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/17/Trump-Competency-Tests/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump Talks Competency - Age Limits ‘Not Necessary’" /><published>2023-09-17T16:45:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-17T16:45:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/17/Trump-Competency-Tests</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/17/Trump-Competency-Tests/">&lt;p&gt;While age limits for politicians are gaining traction in public discourse, former President Donald Trump has a different take. Instead of focusing on age, he believes competency tests would be more beneficial.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a recent interview on NBC’s “Meet the Press,” Trump, at age 77, shared his views. He responded to host Kristen Welker’s questions about age limits, especially since Trump and current President Joe Biden, who’s 80, are potential opponents in the 2024 elections.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recalling a test he took a few years ago at Walter Reed, Trump said, “I aced it. I get everything right. I’m all for testing. I frankly think testing would be a good thing.” But is it constitutional? The former president believes some might see it that way, though he isn’t certain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump added, “[You] know, some of the greatest world leaders have been in their 80s. I’m not anywhere very near 80, by the way.” He emphasized that it’s not about Biden’s age but his competence, which he sees as a bigger concern.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But what about Trump’s age? If he wins the 2024 elections, he’ll be nearing 80 in his term. Biden, if re-elected, would be 82 at the beginning of his next term. Biden’s age has been a frequent topic of discussion due to occasional lapses in memory and stuttered speeches.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another vocal advocate for competency testing is former South Carolina Governor Nikki Haley. She’s been proactive in pushing for cognitive tests for politicians, particularly for those over 75. Notably, she hasn’t supported age limits. Mockingly referring to the U.S. Senate as “the most privileged nursing home in the country,” she called for legislation that would require competency tests for both presidential candidates and Congress members.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Haley’s comments came in the wake of health concerns involving Senate minority leader Mitch McConnell and Sen. Dianne Feinstein, D-Calif. Discussing their health episodes, she remarked, “It’s sad. No one should feel good about seeing that.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the upcoming 2024 Republican Presidential Primary, Haley is set to challenge Trump. However, current polls indicate Trump’s lead over other candidates remains significant. Despite this, Trump voiced his appreciation for the idea of a female vice president, assuring that he would “pick the best person.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The debate around age and competence is unlikely to subside, especially as the 2024 elections approach. But one thing is clear: the need for efficient and competent leadership is paramount, no matter the age.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">While age limits for politicians are gaining traction in public discourse, former President Donald Trump has a different take. Instead of focusing on age, he believes competency tests would be more beneficial. In a recent interview on NBC’s “Meet the Press,” Trump, at age 77, shared his views. He responded to host Kristen Welker’s questions about age limits, especially since Trump and current President Joe Biden, who’s 80, are potential opponents in the 2024 elections. Recalling a test he took a few years ago at Walter Reed, Trump said, “I aced it. I get everything right. I’m all for testing. I frankly think testing would be a good thing.” But is it constitutional? The former president believes some might see it that way, though he isn’t certain. Trump added, “[You] know, some of the greatest world leaders have been in their 80s. I’m not anywhere very near 80, by the way.” He emphasized that it’s not about Biden’s age but his competence, which he sees as a bigger concern. But what about Trump’s age? If he wins the 2024 elections, he’ll be nearing 80 in his term. Biden, if re-elected, would be 82 at the beginning of his next term. Biden’s age has been a frequent topic of discussion due to occasional lapses in memory and stuttered speeches. Another vocal advocate for competency testing is former South Carolina Governor Nikki Haley. She’s been proactive in pushing for cognitive tests for politicians, particularly for those over 75. Notably, she hasn’t supported age limits. Mockingly referring to the U.S. Senate as “the most privileged nursing home in the country,” she called for legislation that would require competency tests for both presidential candidates and Congress members. Haley’s comments came in the wake of health concerns involving Senate minority leader Mitch McConnell and Sen. Dianne Feinstein, D-Calif. Discussing their health episodes, she remarked, “It’s sad. No one should feel good about seeing that.” In the upcoming 2024 Republican Presidential Primary, Haley is set to challenge Trump. However, current polls indicate Trump’s lead over other candidates remains significant. Despite this, Trump voiced his appreciation for the idea of a female vice president, assuring that he would “pick the best person.” The debate around age and competence is unlikely to subside, especially as the 2024 elections approach. But one thing is clear: the need for efficient and competent leadership is paramount, no matter the age.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Biden’s Oversight - Texas Border Town Overrun by Unprecedented Migrant Numbers</title><link href="/news/2023/09/17/Biden-Texas-Migrant-Surge/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Biden’s Oversight - Texas Border Town Overrun by Unprecedented Migrant Numbers" /><published>2023-09-17T15:52:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-17T15:52:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/17/Biden-Texas-Migrant-Surge</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/17/Biden-Texas-Migrant-Surge/">&lt;p&gt;The Texas border town of Eagle Pass experienced an extraordinary and concerning day when, in just 24 hours, over 1,300 migrants were apprehended. This number surpassed the combined total from all eleven El Paso Border Patrol Sector stations, highlighting a serious surge in this small town.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-strained-system&quot;&gt;A Strained System&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eagle Pass, with a population of only around 30,000 residents, is feeling the pressure. The apprehensions in a single day have overwhelmed the town’s Border Patrol processing facility and the ability of non-government (NGO) shelters to accommodate such a surge. This immense inflow has left the local system stretched thin, with one source noting, “In just one eight-hour shift, more than 700 migrants were taken into custody. We lack the capacity to deal with it. This system is broken.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;overburdened-facilities&quot;&gt;Overburdened Facilities&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With only one soft-sided processing facility operating in the area, the number of detained migrants skyrocketed to over 3,000. This volume is three times its designated capacity. Unfortunately, this overload prompted the Border Patrol to conduct mass releases into the town. Migrants, without sufficient funds for travel, were observed attempting the daunting walk from Eagle Pass to San Antonio, Texas, a journey spanning over 150 miles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-failing-response&quot;&gt;A Failing Response&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The strategy from the top seems disconnected from the ground reality. Instead of effectively addressing the growing crisis, the response appears to be one of surrender. “Our facilities are full, the NGO shelters have exceeded their capacity as well, and we are releasing every migrant we can just to stay afloat,” an inside source shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Local residents are feeling the brunt of this surge firsthand. Migrants wander the city streets, lacking funds for bus tickets or meals. The only NGO shelter, Mission Border Hope, has had to turn away migrants who can’t afford the $50 bus ticket to San Antonio. This situation puts these migrants in an even more vulnerable position, expecting them to travel hundreds of miles without adequate resources.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the town’s Border Patrol aims to release migrants to the shelter, intending to prevent adding to the homeless population, the lack of proper planning and infrastructure has made this a losing strategy. “We had no knowledge that the poorest of migrants would be thrown out on the streets and expected to walk more than 150 miles to the next largest city, but that is where we are,” the source added.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s evident that Eagle Pass, and Texas at large, needs an effective solution that addresses the immediate concerns of overwhelmed facilities and the long-term implications of mass releases into small towns. At the core of this crisis is the Biden administration, which must acknowledge its role and take definitive action to mend this worsening situation.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">The Texas border town of Eagle Pass experienced an extraordinary and concerning day when, in just 24 hours, over 1,300 migrants were apprehended. This number surpassed the combined total from all eleven El Paso Border Patrol Sector stations, highlighting a serious surge in this small town. A Strained System Eagle Pass, with a population of only around 30,000 residents, is feeling the pressure. The apprehensions in a single day have overwhelmed the town’s Border Patrol processing facility and the ability of non-government (NGO) shelters to accommodate such a surge. This immense inflow has left the local system stretched thin, with one source noting, “In just one eight-hour shift, more than 700 migrants were taken into custody. We lack the capacity to deal with it. This system is broken.” Overburdened Facilities With only one soft-sided processing facility operating in the area, the number of detained migrants skyrocketed to over 3,000. This volume is three times its designated capacity. Unfortunately, this overload prompted the Border Patrol to conduct mass releases into the town. Migrants, without sufficient funds for travel, were observed attempting the daunting walk from Eagle Pass to San Antonio, Texas, a journey spanning over 150 miles. A Failing Response The strategy from the top seems disconnected from the ground reality. Instead of effectively addressing the growing crisis, the response appears to be one of surrender. “Our facilities are full, the NGO shelters have exceeded their capacity as well, and we are releasing every migrant we can just to stay afloat,” an inside source shared. Local residents are feeling the brunt of this surge firsthand. Migrants wander the city streets, lacking funds for bus tickets or meals. The only NGO shelter, Mission Border Hope, has had to turn away migrants who can’t afford the $50 bus ticket to San Antonio. This situation puts these migrants in an even more vulnerable position, expecting them to travel hundreds of miles without adequate resources. While the town’s Border Patrol aims to release migrants to the shelter, intending to prevent adding to the homeless population, the lack of proper planning and infrastructure has made this a losing strategy. “We had no knowledge that the poorest of migrants would be thrown out on the streets and expected to walk more than 150 miles to the next largest city, but that is where we are,” the source added. It’s evident that Eagle Pass, and Texas at large, needs an effective solution that addresses the immediate concerns of overwhelmed facilities and the long-term implications of mass releases into small towns. At the core of this crisis is the Biden administration, which must acknowledge its role and take definitive action to mend this worsening situation.</summary></entry></feed>