<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-10-14T16:14:52-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/14/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-14T16:14:52-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-14T16:14:52-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/14/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/14/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/14/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-14T16:14:52-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-14T16:14:52-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/14/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/14/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/">&lt;p&gt;Recent surprise attacks by Hamas on Israel has fueled ongoing tensions between staunchly conservative commentators and the progressive “Squad” Democrats known for criticizing Israel. The intensity of the backlash highlights the deep political divide over foreign policy in the Middle East.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Hamas’ shocking attack, several members of the “Squad,” including Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.), called for a “ceasefire and de-escalation,” condemning the violence. The absence of a statement from Rep. Rashida Tlaib (D-Mich.) was notably called out by conservative media outlets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;South Carolina GOP Rep. Nancy Mace quickly labeled Ocasio-Cortez a “Hamas apologist” in response to her call for peace and de-escalation. Rep. Ilhan Omar (D-Minn.), no stranger to controversy surrounding her views on Israel, echoed the call for de-escalation and ceasefire. Omar’s prior statements comparing the US and Israel to terrorist groups like Hamas and the Taliban resurfaced in the debate, fueling more criticisms. Omar’s 2019 tweet, where she opined that “Israel has hypnotized the world,” also continues to haunt her political career, often cited by critics to challenge her stance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conservative commentators have been especially vocal. “FOX &amp;amp; Friends Weekend” co-host Rachel Campos-Duffy took aim at Omar, saying she fails to recognize the peace in the Middle East under Trump’s administration. Conservative pundit John Hasson also called out Omar, claiming she insinuated that attacks on IDF forces were acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Massachusetts Democrat Rep. Ayanna Pressley’s concerns over the “devastating attacks on Israelis” were met with skepticism. A prominent conservative online personality, Comfortably Smug, accused the “Squad” of advising Israel to back down after the nation suffered massive attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Jamaal Bowman’s call for an end to the Gaza blockade, in addition to condemning the Hamas attacks, was met with criticism from conservative radio host Jason Rantz. He accused Bowman of pairing his condemnation of terrorism with unwarranted criticisms of Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Cori Bush emphasized the urgent need for a ceasefire, while pushing for an end to “U.S. support for Israeli military occupation and apartheid.” Defense attorney Marina Medvin criticized Bush, suggesting that she equates the death of Palestinian terrorists to the horrific acts committed against Jewish civilians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amidst the political turmoil and intense debate, the attacks have taken a heavy toll. Israeli media report over 300 dead due to the wide-ranging assault. Gaza health officials note that at least 200 Palestinians have perished in the retaliatory Israeli air strikes following the initial Hamas attack. As the situation remains volatile, both sides continue to count their casualties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This divisive issue showcases the challenge America faces in crafting a unified approach to foreign policy, with deeply entrenched political divides at play. As the situation develops, the debate is bound to intensify, shedding light on the complexities of U.S. politics in the global arena.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Majority Believe Biden Was Improperly Involved in Son’s Business Controversies: AP-NORC Poll</title><link href="/news/2023/10/14/Biden-Hunter-Business-Poll/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Majority Believe Biden Was Improperly Involved in Son’s Business Controversies: AP-NORC Poll" /><published>2023-10-14T15:05:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-14T15:05:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/14/Biden-Hunter-Business-Poll</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/14/Biden-Hunter-Business-Poll/">&lt;p&gt;Recent poll results have ignited fresh debate around President Joe Biden’s involvement with his son Hunter Biden’s controversial business affairs. The AP-NORC poll, released this week, shows a significant portion of Americans questioning the President’s actions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of the participants, a substantial 68% felt that Biden might have engaged in either unethical or downright illegal actions regarding his son’s business operations. Only a mere 30% of the respondents believed that the President was entirely innocent in this matter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A closer look at these figures shows party affiliations driving some of the perceptions. While 40% of Democratic participants expressed concerns about Biden’s possible misdeeds (with 8% thinking he acted illegally and 32% sensing unethical behavior), a whopping 96% of Republicans held reservations. Of this percentage, 65% believed that President Biden engaged in illegal activities and 35% felt he acted unethically.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, despite these alarming figures, public sentiment appears less supportive of the impeachment inquiry the GOP has initiated against Biden concerning Hunter’s business engagements. Of the polled individuals, only 33% seemed to endorse this inquiry, while 39% expressed their disapproval. Surprisingly, a significant 26% didn’t voice any opinion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Predictably, party lines play a noticeable role here too. A significant 67% of Republican respondents backed the impeachment inquiry, whereas only a tiny 7% of Democrats did the same. However, what’s noteworthy is the knowledge gap: barely 54% of respondents claimed familiarity with the ongoing impeachment process. Among these, almost half (49%) disapproved of the inquiry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amidst this backdrop of political intrigue and skepticism, the poll also touched upon public trust in parties to counteract government corruption. Responses were split, with 19% leaning towards the Republicans and 28% favoring the Democrats. Yet, the most telling figure might be the combined 52% who either found both parties equally reliable or didn’t trust either at all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conducted between October 5-9 and surveying 1,163 adults across the country, the AP-NORC poll gives an insightful glimpse into the current political climate. While the President and his son, Hunter, remain central figures in this whirlwind, the poll’s margin of error stands at +/- 3.9 percentage points.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These results underscore a politically charged atmosphere and highlight the pressing need for clarity, transparency, and robust democratic dialogue.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Recent poll results have ignited fresh debate around President Joe Biden’s involvement with his son Hunter Biden’s controversial business affairs. The AP-NORC poll, released this week, shows a significant portion of Americans questioning the President’s actions. Of the participants, a substantial 68% felt that Biden might have engaged in either unethical or downright illegal actions regarding his son’s business operations. Only a mere 30% of the respondents believed that the President was entirely innocent in this matter. A closer look at these figures shows party affiliations driving some of the perceptions. While 40% of Democratic participants expressed concerns about Biden’s possible misdeeds (with 8% thinking he acted illegally and 32% sensing unethical behavior), a whopping 96% of Republicans held reservations. Of this percentage, 65% believed that President Biden engaged in illegal activities and 35% felt he acted unethically. However, despite these alarming figures, public sentiment appears less supportive of the impeachment inquiry the GOP has initiated against Biden concerning Hunter’s business engagements. Of the polled individuals, only 33% seemed to endorse this inquiry, while 39% expressed their disapproval. Surprisingly, a significant 26% didn’t voice any opinion. Predictably, party lines play a noticeable role here too. A significant 67% of Republican respondents backed the impeachment inquiry, whereas only a tiny 7% of Democrats did the same. However, what’s noteworthy is the knowledge gap: barely 54% of respondents claimed familiarity with the ongoing impeachment process. Among these, almost half (49%) disapproved of the inquiry. Amidst this backdrop of political intrigue and skepticism, the poll also touched upon public trust in parties to counteract government corruption. Responses were split, with 19% leaning towards the Republicans and 28% favoring the Democrats. Yet, the most telling figure might be the combined 52% who either found both parties equally reliable or didn’t trust either at all. Conducted between October 5-9 and surveying 1,163 adults across the country, the AP-NORC poll gives an insightful glimpse into the current political climate. While the President and his son, Hunter, remain central figures in this whirlwind, the poll’s margin of error stands at +/- 3.9 percentage points. These results underscore a politically charged atmosphere and highlight the pressing need for clarity, transparency, and robust democratic dialogue.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">CIA Predicted Imminent Hamas Assault, But Was Anyone Listening?</title><link href="/news/2023/10/14/CIA-Warnings-Hamas-Attack/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="CIA Predicted Imminent Hamas Assault, But Was Anyone Listening?" /><published>2023-10-14T11:45:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-14T11:45:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/14/CIA-Warnings-Hamas-Attack</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/14/CIA-Warnings-Hamas-Attack/">&lt;p&gt;Amidst the aftermath of last week’s catastrophic attack on Israel, revelations have emerged that the Central Intelligence Agency (CIA) had issued multiple warnings signaling a forthcoming Hamas assault. Notably, leading news outlets, The New York Times and CNN, shed light on this matter on Friday, raising pressing questions about potential intelligence oversights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With sources confirming that the CIA had delivered at least two distinct warnings in the weeks preceding the onslaught on Israel, the gravest of which came merely days prior to the event, there’s increasing scrutiny on whether these alarms were heeded. The New York Times disclosed that neither President Joe Biden nor key White House officials had been briefed on these reports, further amplifying concerns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These CIA assessments, particularly those dated Sept. 28 and then Oct. 5 and 6, primarily stemmed from intelligence insights provided by Israel. Whether Israel was duly informed remains uncertain. However, as the dust settles from last Saturday’s attack, launched on Oct. 7, the catastrophic results of these alerts going unheeded are starkly apparent. A staggering death toll of over 1,300 in Israel includes 27 American citizens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a statement, the Sept. 28 report had cautioned about Hamas gearing up for a series of rocket attacks on Israel, an unfortunately common event in the region’s volatile history. The subsequent reports, on Oct. 5 and 6, progressively elevated the urgency, with the latter alerting about an impending attack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet, the gravity of the situation extends beyond these recent revelations. It emerges that Rep. Mike McCaul, R-Texas, and chairman of the House Foreign Affairs Committee, disclosed that Israel had also been warned by Egypt just three days ahead of the Hamas strike. The depth and specificity of that warning remain undisclosed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Highlighting the recurring nature of these alerts, an intelligence source mentioned to CNN, “This is something that has historically been the norm between Hamas and Israel.” Consequently, both the U.S. and Israel now find themselves facing fierce criticism for the perceived lapse in intelligence. Despite the warnings not fully encompassing the magnitude of Hamas’ eventual brutality, they follow a concerning trend of intelligence alerts over the past year being frequently sidelined.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A senior Arab official, voicing the frustration echoed by many, stated, “They never listened every time we warned them.” The aftermath of the attack has been nothing short of horrific, with the scale of devastation far surpassing the expectations of even the attackers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the backdrop of this tragedy and the emerging reports on missed warnings, the question lingers: Will this be a turning point in heeding intelligence assessments in the future?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Amidst the aftermath of last week’s catastrophic attack on Israel, revelations have emerged that the Central Intelligence Agency (CIA) had issued multiple warnings signaling a forthcoming Hamas assault. Notably, leading news outlets, The New York Times and CNN, shed light on this matter on Friday, raising pressing questions about potential intelligence oversights. With sources confirming that the CIA had delivered at least two distinct warnings in the weeks preceding the onslaught on Israel, the gravest of which came merely days prior to the event, there’s increasing scrutiny on whether these alarms were heeded. The New York Times disclosed that neither President Joe Biden nor key White House officials had been briefed on these reports, further amplifying concerns. These CIA assessments, particularly those dated Sept. 28 and then Oct. 5 and 6, primarily stemmed from intelligence insights provided by Israel. Whether Israel was duly informed remains uncertain. However, as the dust settles from last Saturday’s attack, launched on Oct. 7, the catastrophic results of these alerts going unheeded are starkly apparent. A staggering death toll of over 1,300 in Israel includes 27 American citizens. In a statement, the Sept. 28 report had cautioned about Hamas gearing up for a series of rocket attacks on Israel, an unfortunately common event in the region’s volatile history. The subsequent reports, on Oct. 5 and 6, progressively elevated the urgency, with the latter alerting about an impending attack. Yet, the gravity of the situation extends beyond these recent revelations. It emerges that Rep. Mike McCaul, R-Texas, and chairman of the House Foreign Affairs Committee, disclosed that Israel had also been warned by Egypt just three days ahead of the Hamas strike. The depth and specificity of that warning remain undisclosed. Highlighting the recurring nature of these alerts, an intelligence source mentioned to CNN, “This is something that has historically been the norm between Hamas and Israel.” Consequently, both the U.S. and Israel now find themselves facing fierce criticism for the perceived lapse in intelligence. Despite the warnings not fully encompassing the magnitude of Hamas’ eventual brutality, they follow a concerning trend of intelligence alerts over the past year being frequently sidelined. A senior Arab official, voicing the frustration echoed by many, stated, “They never listened every time we warned them.” The aftermath of the attack has been nothing short of horrific, with the scale of devastation far surpassing the expectations of even the attackers. In the backdrop of this tragedy and the emerging reports on missed warnings, the question lingers: Will this be a turning point in heeding intelligence assessments in the future?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">NYC Councilwoman Arrested Over Firearm at Brooklyn Rally</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/14/NYC-Lawmaker-Arrest/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="NYC Councilwoman Arrested Over Firearm at Brooklyn Rally" /><published>2023-10-14T10:20:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-14T10:20:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/14/NYC-Lawmaker-Arrest</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/14/NYC-Lawmaker-Arrest/">&lt;p&gt;In a surprising turn of events, New York City’s Republican Councilwoman, Inna Vernikov, has been arrested after being seen with a handgun during a pro-Palestinian rally at Brooklyn College. This incident, which has caused quite a stir, once again brings the nation’s attention to the polarizing debates surrounding gun rights, public safety, and political discourse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The New York City Police Department (NYPD) confirmed Vernikov’s arrest after images circulating on social media showed the butt-end of a firearm sticking out from her pants during the demonstration. The photographs, captured by attendees at the scene, rapidly spread, drawing swift reactions from both supporters and critics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Authorities apprehended Vernikov, the representative for southern Brooklyn, around 3 a.m., charging her with criminal possession of a firearm. While Vernikov is licensed to possess the firearm, New York state law dictates that firearms are prohibited in “sensitive locations,” which includes educational institutions like Brooklyn College and places where individuals gather to express their constitutional rights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the negative optics, the NYPD clarified that “At no point in time was anyone menaced or injured as a result of her possessing the firearm at the earlier protest.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, Vernikov didn’t stay silent during the event. She uploaded a video of herself amidst the rally attendees, sharing her strong views against those supporting Hamas, going as far as to label them as “terrorists without the bombs.” This stance, coupled with the firearm controversy, has fueled heated debates across various online platforms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The repercussions of this incident extend beyond Vernikov. High-profile figures, like New York State Sen. Julia Salazar, a prominent Democratic socialist from Brooklyn, have condemned Vernikov’s alleged actions. Salazar emphasized the gravity of an elected official carrying a firearm to an educational institution, particularly during such a charged event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The incident brings to light the complexities of the current political and social environment, not only in New York City but across the nation. As public figures become more embroiled in controversies, the pressing question remains: How do we ensure safety and uphold the law while preserving the rights and freedoms that are intrinsic to our democracy?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Councilwoman Vernikov has yet to comment on the incident.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a surprising turn of events, New York City’s Republican Councilwoman, Inna Vernikov, has been arrested after being seen with a handgun during a pro-Palestinian rally at Brooklyn College. This incident, which has caused quite a stir, once again brings the nation’s attention to the polarizing debates surrounding gun rights, public safety, and political discourse. The New York City Police Department (NYPD) confirmed Vernikov’s arrest after images circulating on social media showed the butt-end of a firearm sticking out from her pants during the demonstration. The photographs, captured by attendees at the scene, rapidly spread, drawing swift reactions from both supporters and critics. Authorities apprehended Vernikov, the representative for southern Brooklyn, around 3 a.m., charging her with criminal possession of a firearm. While Vernikov is licensed to possess the firearm, New York state law dictates that firearms are prohibited in “sensitive locations,” which includes educational institutions like Brooklyn College and places where individuals gather to express their constitutional rights. Despite the negative optics, the NYPD clarified that “At no point in time was anyone menaced or injured as a result of her possessing the firearm at the earlier protest.” Interestingly, Vernikov didn’t stay silent during the event. She uploaded a video of herself amidst the rally attendees, sharing her strong views against those supporting Hamas, going as far as to label them as “terrorists without the bombs.” This stance, coupled with the firearm controversy, has fueled heated debates across various online platforms. The repercussions of this incident extend beyond Vernikov. High-profile figures, like New York State Sen. Julia Salazar, a prominent Democratic socialist from Brooklyn, have condemned Vernikov’s alleged actions. Salazar emphasized the gravity of an elected official carrying a firearm to an educational institution, particularly during such a charged event. The incident brings to light the complexities of the current political and social environment, not only in New York City but across the nation. As public figures become more embroiled in controversies, the pressing question remains: How do we ensure safety and uphold the law while preserving the rights and freedoms that are intrinsic to our democracy? Councilwoman Vernikov has yet to comment on the incident.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Public Trust in Congress Hits a New Low, Says Gallup Poll</title><link href="/news/2023/10/14/Congress-Trust-Issue/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Public Trust in Congress Hits a New Low, Says Gallup Poll" /><published>2023-10-14T09:15:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-14T09:15:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/14/Congress-Trust-Issue</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/14/Congress-Trust-Issue/">&lt;p&gt;It’s official: The latest Gallup survey reveals that trust in Congress is at its lowest ebb among American institutions. While local governments seem to have the confidence of the majority, Congress lags far behind, with only a fraction showing trust in its ability to handle domestic issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to the recent Gallup poll, a whopping 67% of Americans place their trust in local governments to tackle local issues. However, when it comes to Congress, only 32% believe they can effectively address national concerns. The disparity is clear: Americans tend to lean towards their local representatives when it comes to faith in problem-solving.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But how do other government sectors fare? State governments receive a trust score of 60% from the public, while 55% trust the American populace “as a whole” to manage the challenges facing the nation. Interestingly, the judicial branch secures a 49% trust score, closely trailed by the federal government at 44%, the executive branch at 41%, and political candidates at 40%. Congress stands at the rear, witnessing a decline of 6 points from last year’s Gallup results.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One key takeaway from the poll is that trust in governmental bodies has seen an overall decline since 1972. For instance, while the current 67% trust level in local governments is impressive, it’s still 3 points down from historical averages. Moreover, the judicial branch, headed by the Supreme Court, has observed the steepest decline with a drop of 17 points since 1972.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This erosion of trust in the Supreme Court may be attributed to a series of conservative-leaning decisions, notably the controversial verdict on abortion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gallup’s findings highlight a prevailing sentiment: Americans believe local and state governments are more attuned to their needs and concerns. In a nation grappling with political divides and legislative stagnation, local bodies are perceived as more adaptable and efficient.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The survey’s timing also offers a significant context. Conducted between September 1-23, the findings came just a week before Congress narrowly averted a governmental shutdown. Additionally, the GOP-led House is currently functioning without a speaker, intensifying uncertainties around another potential shutdown.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, while local governments remain pillars of trust for most Americans, there’s an evident need for federal institutions, especially Congress, to bridge the widening trust gap. As Gallup points out, the continuous decline in confidence spells a concerning trajectory for the nation’s democratic institutions.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">It’s official: The latest Gallup survey reveals that trust in Congress is at its lowest ebb among American institutions. While local governments seem to have the confidence of the majority, Congress lags far behind, with only a fraction showing trust in its ability to handle domestic issues. According to the recent Gallup poll, a whopping 67% of Americans place their trust in local governments to tackle local issues. However, when it comes to Congress, only 32% believe they can effectively address national concerns. The disparity is clear: Americans tend to lean towards their local representatives when it comes to faith in problem-solving. But how do other government sectors fare? State governments receive a trust score of 60% from the public, while 55% trust the American populace “as a whole” to manage the challenges facing the nation. Interestingly, the judicial branch secures a 49% trust score, closely trailed by the federal government at 44%, the executive branch at 41%, and political candidates at 40%. Congress stands at the rear, witnessing a decline of 6 points from last year’s Gallup results. One key takeaway from the poll is that trust in governmental bodies has seen an overall decline since 1972. For instance, while the current 67% trust level in local governments is impressive, it’s still 3 points down from historical averages. Moreover, the judicial branch, headed by the Supreme Court, has observed the steepest decline with a drop of 17 points since 1972. This erosion of trust in the Supreme Court may be attributed to a series of conservative-leaning decisions, notably the controversial verdict on abortion. Gallup’s findings highlight a prevailing sentiment: Americans believe local and state governments are more attuned to their needs and concerns. In a nation grappling with political divides and legislative stagnation, local bodies are perceived as more adaptable and efficient. The survey’s timing also offers a significant context. Conducted between September 1-23, the findings came just a week before Congress narrowly averted a governmental shutdown. Additionally, the GOP-led House is currently functioning without a speaker, intensifying uncertainties around another potential shutdown. In conclusion, while local governments remain pillars of trust for most Americans, there’s an evident need for federal institutions, especially Congress, to bridge the widening trust gap. As Gallup points out, the continuous decline in confidence spells a concerning trajectory for the nation’s democratic institutions.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hollywood Actors’ Strike Halts Amid Global ‘Day of Jihad’ Concerns</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/14/Hollywood-Actors-Strike-Safety/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hollywood Actors’ Strike Halts Amid Global ‘Day of Jihad’ Concerns" /><published>2023-10-14T08:01:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-14T08:01:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/14/Hollywood-Actors-Strike-Safety</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/14/Hollywood-Actors-Strike-Safety/">&lt;p&gt;Hollywood has always been a place of spectacle, but it’s not always about the latest blockbuster or red-carpet event. This year, the spotlight is on a strike by the members of SAG-AFTRA, Hollywood’s largest union representing actors and other media professionals. But what was supposed to be a demonstration of unity took a sudden turn when the union decided to halt picketing on Friday due to significant global security concerns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The decision came after Hamas, a Palestinian organization, declared a worldwide “Day of Jihad,” urging Muslims globally to take to the streets. While SAG-AFTRA’s leadership advised members to prioritize safety, they refrained from specifically mentioning the “Day of Jihad.” Instead, their statement simply urged members to “stay safe.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Major media outlets have presented varying interpretations of the Hamas declaration. While some labeled it a “day of rage” or “demonstrations,” others reported that Hamas described it as “The Friday of the Al-Aqsa Flood,” referencing a recent operation where the group initiated an attack that resulted in a tragic loss of over 1,200 Israeli lives. Regardless of the terminology, the message was clear: security forces worldwide braced themselves for potential unrest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In response to the impending event, the New York City Police Department (NYPD) took immediate action, directing all officers to be on duty in uniform on Friday, highlighting the gravity of the situation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s worth noting that SAG-AFTRA members initially began their strike on July 14, 2023, and have been in negotiations with studios since. This recent interruption in their protests comes after a surprising setback in their discussions. While the writers’ union successfully negotiated a new contract just days before, SAG-AFTRA’s recent proposals seemingly fell on deaf ears, leaving the entertainment industry in a state of uncertainty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This situation underscores the sometimes-unexpected interplay between global politics and the world of entertainment. With Hollywood actors pausing their strike due to concerns of potential global unrest, it’s a stark reminder that even the glittering world of showbiz is not immune to the larger events shaping our world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For now, as SAG-AFTRA members await further directives from their union leaders, the world watches, hoping for peaceful resolutions on both the entertainment and global fronts.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Hollywood has always been a place of spectacle, but it’s not always about the latest blockbuster or red-carpet event. This year, the spotlight is on a strike by the members of SAG-AFTRA, Hollywood’s largest union representing actors and other media professionals. But what was supposed to be a demonstration of unity took a sudden turn when the union decided to halt picketing on Friday due to significant global security concerns. The decision came after Hamas, a Palestinian organization, declared a worldwide “Day of Jihad,” urging Muslims globally to take to the streets. While SAG-AFTRA’s leadership advised members to prioritize safety, they refrained from specifically mentioning the “Day of Jihad.” Instead, their statement simply urged members to “stay safe.” Major media outlets have presented varying interpretations of the Hamas declaration. While some labeled it a “day of rage” or “demonstrations,” others reported that Hamas described it as “The Friday of the Al-Aqsa Flood,” referencing a recent operation where the group initiated an attack that resulted in a tragic loss of over 1,200 Israeli lives. Regardless of the terminology, the message was clear: security forces worldwide braced themselves for potential unrest. In response to the impending event, the New York City Police Department (NYPD) took immediate action, directing all officers to be on duty in uniform on Friday, highlighting the gravity of the situation. It’s worth noting that SAG-AFTRA members initially began their strike on July 14, 2023, and have been in negotiations with studios since. This recent interruption in their protests comes after a surprising setback in their discussions. While the writers’ union successfully negotiated a new contract just days before, SAG-AFTRA’s recent proposals seemingly fell on deaf ears, leaving the entertainment industry in a state of uncertainty. This situation underscores the sometimes-unexpected interplay between global politics and the world of entertainment. With Hollywood actors pausing their strike due to concerns of potential global unrest, it’s a stark reminder that even the glittering world of showbiz is not immune to the larger events shaping our world. For now, as SAG-AFTRA members await further directives from their union leaders, the world watches, hoping for peaceful resolutions on both the entertainment and global fronts.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">GOP’s Tug of War: Jim Jordan Secures Nomination, Yet House Speaker Seat Remains Vacant</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/14/GOP-Jim-Jordan-Nomination/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="GOP’s Tug of War: Jim Jordan Secures Nomination, Yet House Speaker Seat Remains Vacant" /><published>2023-10-14T07:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-14T07:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/14/GOP-Jim-Jordan-Nomination</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/14/GOP-Jim-Jordan-Nomination/">&lt;p&gt;The GOP’s search for the next House Speaker, one of the most powerful roles in U.S. politics, continues as Rep. Jim Jordan clinches the nomination but fails to secure enough votes to officially take on the role.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Friday, Jordan, a staunch conservative known for his vocal advocacy for the party’s right wing, earned the nomination to lead the U.S. House of Representatives. Notably, he has the backing of political heavyweights like former House Minority Leader Kevin McCarthy and former President Donald Trump, who’s currently leading the charge for the GOP’s 2024 presidential nomination.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the road to the speaker’s gavel is proving to be arduous for Jordan. In two consecutive voting rounds, he failed to achieve the 217 votes required, despite having the majority of House Republicans’ support. The initial vote saw Jordan triumph over Georgia lawmaker Austin Scott with a 124-81 vote. Subsequently, Jordan acquired a 152-55 victory in the second round but remained short of the necessary votes to assume the prestigious role.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This leadership crisis underscores the GOP’s internal struggles. Kevin McCarthy’s surprising ousting by a faction of Republican rebels on October 3rd left a void, making the party’s quest for a successor a central focus. Compounding these challenges are significant global events like the escalating Middle East war and Russia’s offensive on Ukraine. Moreover, with a looming government shutdown set for November 17, there’s an added urgency for the House to resolve its leadership quagmire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many within the GOP express concerns that go beyond finding the right leader. “There’s a lack of trust. There’s a lack of transparency,” noted Representative Kat Cammack, emphasizing the need to rebuild the party’s foundations before deciding on the House Speaker.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, Jordan’s nomination journey had an earlier setback when he lost to Steve Scalise, a frontrunner for the role. But Scalise’s aspirations were short-lived, as he soon abandoned his bid when uniting the Republicans behind him proved challenging.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amid these challenges, Jordan remains optimistic. “I think I can unite the conference, I think I can tell the country what we’re doing and why it matters,” he confidently shared with reporters pre-vote. Advocates for Jordan, like Representative Nicole Malliotakis, emphasize his resilience and negotiating prowess, especially when dealing with Democratic adversaries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the path forward remains murky. The last two Republican Speakers, John Boehner and Paul Ryan, faced intense pressure from the party’s right-wing factions. The GOP hopes to avoid past embarrassments and unite behind a strong leader who can navigate the tumultuous political landscape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For now, the wait continues, with the decisive vote for the next House Speaker slated for Monday at 6 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">The GOP’s search for the next House Speaker, one of the most powerful roles in U.S. politics, continues as Rep. Jim Jordan clinches the nomination but fails to secure enough votes to officially take on the role. On Friday, Jordan, a staunch conservative known for his vocal advocacy for the party’s right wing, earned the nomination to lead the U.S. House of Representatives. Notably, he has the backing of political heavyweights like former House Minority Leader Kevin McCarthy and former President Donald Trump, who’s currently leading the charge for the GOP’s 2024 presidential nomination. However, the road to the speaker’s gavel is proving to be arduous for Jordan. In two consecutive voting rounds, he failed to achieve the 217 votes required, despite having the majority of House Republicans’ support. The initial vote saw Jordan triumph over Georgia lawmaker Austin Scott with a 124-81 vote. Subsequently, Jordan acquired a 152-55 victory in the second round but remained short of the necessary votes to assume the prestigious role. This leadership crisis underscores the GOP’s internal struggles. Kevin McCarthy’s surprising ousting by a faction of Republican rebels on October 3rd left a void, making the party’s quest for a successor a central focus. Compounding these challenges are significant global events like the escalating Middle East war and Russia’s offensive on Ukraine. Moreover, with a looming government shutdown set for November 17, there’s an added urgency for the House to resolve its leadership quagmire. Many within the GOP express concerns that go beyond finding the right leader. “There’s a lack of trust. There’s a lack of transparency,” noted Representative Kat Cammack, emphasizing the need to rebuild the party’s foundations before deciding on the House Speaker. Interestingly, Jordan’s nomination journey had an earlier setback when he lost to Steve Scalise, a frontrunner for the role. But Scalise’s aspirations were short-lived, as he soon abandoned his bid when uniting the Republicans behind him proved challenging. Amid these challenges, Jordan remains optimistic. “I think I can unite the conference, I think I can tell the country what we’re doing and why it matters,” he confidently shared with reporters pre-vote. Advocates for Jordan, like Representative Nicole Malliotakis, emphasize his resilience and negotiating prowess, especially when dealing with Democratic adversaries. However, the path forward remains murky. The last two Republican Speakers, John Boehner and Paul Ryan, faced intense pressure from the party’s right-wing factions. The GOP hopes to avoid past embarrassments and unite behind a strong leader who can navigate the tumultuous political landscape. For now, the wait continues, with the decisive vote for the next House Speaker slated for Monday at 6 p.m.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Pro-Palestinian Protesters Arrested Outside Schumer’s NYC Residence</title><link href="/news/2023/10/14/Protest-NYC-Schumer/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Pro-Palestinian Protesters Arrested Outside Schumer’s NYC Residence" /><published>2023-10-14T06:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-14T06:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/14/Protest-NYC-Schumer</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/14/Protest-NYC-Schumer/">&lt;p&gt;Amid the heightened tensions and ongoing demonstrations surrounding the Israel-Hamas conflict, Senator Chuck Schumer’s New York City apartment became the center of attention on Friday night. Schumer, the Senate Majority Leader from New York, witnessed a pro-Palestinian protest right outside his residence, leading to several arrests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The protest, as confirmed by Fox News Digital, unfolded during the senator’s intimate Shabbat dinner with family. The gathering was particularly timely, as Schumer is on the cusp of a pivotal journey to Israel as part of a bipartisan CODEL (Congressional Delegation) trip set for the weekend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although the exact number of arrests remains undisclosed, a police spokesperson confirmed that multiple protesters were taken into custody. The incident in front of Schumer’s apartment is just one of several pro-Palestinian protests that have been staged across New York City in recent times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sen. Schumer has been a focal point of discussions lately, not only due to his prominent position in the Senate but also due to his imminent Israel trip. The visit is drawing attention as it’s expected to bring together a delegation of bipartisan lawmakers, aiming for constructive dialogues and strengthening ties amidst volatile times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earlier on the same day, another separate protest saw confrontations escalate between participants, resulting in the arrest of at least two individuals. Footage emerging from this demonstration showcased a sizable group of passionate protesters vocally demanding the release of the detained, chanting “Set him free!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The backdrop to these events is the devastating Israel-Hamas war, a conflict that has tragically claimed numerous lives. Current figures indicate that at least 2,800 people have lost their lives in this war, including a minimum of 1,200 innocent Israeli civilians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In an era of social and political upheaval, the role of the U.S. and its leaders in navigating these tumultuous waters is crucial. As Senator Schumer prepares for his visit to Israel, these protests in his home city underscore the complexities and emotional intensity surrounding the conflict.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the world watches, there’s hope that such bipartisan trips might pave the way for constructive dialogues, mutual understanding, and, ultimately, lasting peace in the region.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Amid the heightened tensions and ongoing demonstrations surrounding the Israel-Hamas conflict, Senator Chuck Schumer’s New York City apartment became the center of attention on Friday night. Schumer, the Senate Majority Leader from New York, witnessed a pro-Palestinian protest right outside his residence, leading to several arrests. The protest, as confirmed by Fox News Digital, unfolded during the senator’s intimate Shabbat dinner with family. The gathering was particularly timely, as Schumer is on the cusp of a pivotal journey to Israel as part of a bipartisan CODEL (Congressional Delegation) trip set for the weekend. Although the exact number of arrests remains undisclosed, a police spokesperson confirmed that multiple protesters were taken into custody. The incident in front of Schumer’s apartment is just one of several pro-Palestinian protests that have been staged across New York City in recent times. Sen. Schumer has been a focal point of discussions lately, not only due to his prominent position in the Senate but also due to his imminent Israel trip. The visit is drawing attention as it’s expected to bring together a delegation of bipartisan lawmakers, aiming for constructive dialogues and strengthening ties amidst volatile times. Earlier on the same day, another separate protest saw confrontations escalate between participants, resulting in the arrest of at least two individuals. Footage emerging from this demonstration showcased a sizable group of passionate protesters vocally demanding the release of the detained, chanting “Set him free!” The backdrop to these events is the devastating Israel-Hamas war, a conflict that has tragically claimed numerous lives. Current figures indicate that at least 2,800 people have lost their lives in this war, including a minimum of 1,200 innocent Israeli civilians. In an era of social and political upheaval, the role of the U.S. and its leaders in navigating these tumultuous waters is crucial. As Senator Schumer prepares for his visit to Israel, these protests in his home city underscore the complexities and emotional intensity surrounding the conflict. As the world watches, there’s hope that such bipartisan trips might pave the way for constructive dialogues, mutual understanding, and, ultimately, lasting peace in the region.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Drunken Intruder’s Midnight Romp in Kid’s Room Interrupted by Armed Dad</title><link href="/news/2023/10/13/North-Dakota-Intrusion/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Drunken Intruder’s Midnight Romp in Kid’s Room Interrupted by Armed Dad" /><published>2023-10-13T15:07:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-13T15:07:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/13/North-Dakota-Intrusion</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/13/North-Dakota-Intrusion/">&lt;p&gt;In a bizarre incident that recently unfolded in North Dakota, a homeowner was confronted with the alarming sight of a naked and heavily inebriated man wreaking havoc in his daughter’s bedroom. The shocking event, taking place in the early hours, is a stark reminder of the unpredictability and potential dangers lurking even in familiar surroundings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the silent hours of a Friday morning, the family’s peace was shattered by loud banging noises resonating from within their residence. On investigating the disturbance, the father discovered the intruder, later identified as Alvin Ducheneaux, causing a ruckus in his daughter’s unoccupied room, tossing toys and clothes around in wild abandon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a swift response to the unexpected intrusion, the father grabbed his firearm and held Ducheneaux at gunpoint, while instructing his wife to immediately alert the police. Bismarck Police Department promptly arrived at the West Bowen Avenue residence, finding the scene as reported.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The turn of events raises questions on home security and the importance of remaining vigilant. The intruder, Ducheneaux, reportedly made his way into the home through an unlocked back door after the family had turned in for the night. On top of the sheer audacity of his naked intrusion, Ducheneaux compounded his criminal act by inflicting damage on the property, destroying a shoe rack and causing an estimated $200 worth of damage in the child’s room.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the exact motivations behind Ducheneaux’s actions remain unclear, the homeowners speculate that the inebriated man might have confused their home with a neighbor’s. This possibility, however faint, highlights the complexities and dangers of intoxication, with the potential for unexpected and severe consequences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The aftermath of the incident saw Ducheneaux charged with several offenses, including Burglary, Night (Class B Felony), Criminal Mischief, Willful Damage (Class B Misdemeanor), and Disorderly Conduct, Offensive Condition (Class B Misdemeanor). The seriousness of his actions has landed him in the local jail with a $5,000 cash bond. With his court appearance slated for November, Ducheneaux may confront up to a decade in prison for the felony charge alone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The shocking incident serves as a wakeup call for residents everywhere about the significance of home security and the unpredictable nature of such occurrences. As the family grapples with the aftermath of this startling episode, communities are reminded to remain vigilant and prioritize the safety of their homes and loved ones.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a bizarre incident that recently unfolded in North Dakota, a homeowner was confronted with the alarming sight of a naked and heavily inebriated man wreaking havoc in his daughter’s bedroom. The shocking event, taking place in the early hours, is a stark reminder of the unpredictability and potential dangers lurking even in familiar surroundings. In the silent hours of a Friday morning, the family’s peace was shattered by loud banging noises resonating from within their residence. On investigating the disturbance, the father discovered the intruder, later identified as Alvin Ducheneaux, causing a ruckus in his daughter’s unoccupied room, tossing toys and clothes around in wild abandon. In a swift response to the unexpected intrusion, the father grabbed his firearm and held Ducheneaux at gunpoint, while instructing his wife to immediately alert the police. Bismarck Police Department promptly arrived at the West Bowen Avenue residence, finding the scene as reported. The turn of events raises questions on home security and the importance of remaining vigilant. The intruder, Ducheneaux, reportedly made his way into the home through an unlocked back door after the family had turned in for the night. On top of the sheer audacity of his naked intrusion, Ducheneaux compounded his criminal act by inflicting damage on the property, destroying a shoe rack and causing an estimated $200 worth of damage in the child’s room. While the exact motivations behind Ducheneaux’s actions remain unclear, the homeowners speculate that the inebriated man might have confused their home with a neighbor’s. This possibility, however faint, highlights the complexities and dangers of intoxication, with the potential for unexpected and severe consequences. The aftermath of the incident saw Ducheneaux charged with several offenses, including Burglary, Night (Class B Felony), Criminal Mischief, Willful Damage (Class B Misdemeanor), and Disorderly Conduct, Offensive Condition (Class B Misdemeanor). The seriousness of his actions has landed him in the local jail with a $5,000 cash bond. With his court appearance slated for November, Ducheneaux may confront up to a decade in prison for the felony charge alone. The shocking incident serves as a wakeup call for residents everywhere about the significance of home security and the unpredictable nature of such occurrences. As the family grapples with the aftermath of this startling episode, communities are reminded to remain vigilant and prioritize the safety of their homes and loved ones.</summary></entry></feed>