<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-10-05T08:32:46-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/05/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-05T08:32:46-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-05T08:32:46-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/05/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/05/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">California Teacher Arrested for Teaching While Intoxicated</title><link href="/news/2023/10/05/Drunk-Teacher-Arrested/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="California Teacher Arrested for Teaching While Intoxicated" /><published>2023-10-05T08:24:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-05T08:24:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/05/Drunk-Teacher-Arrested</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/05/Drunk-Teacher-Arrested/">&lt;p&gt;A shocking incident at Nuestro Elementary School in Live Oak, California, has drawn considerable attention and concern. Wendy Munson, 57, a second-grade teacher at the school, was arrested on charges of teaching while under the influence of alcohol.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Responding to a report on Monday morning, sheriff’s deputies found Munson visibly impaired during her teaching hours. Following this discovery, she was subjected to a sobriety test which she subsequently failed. Munson was then arrested at approximately 8:20 a.m. and charged with driving with a blood alcohol content exceeding .08 percent, drunk driving, and child abuse with potential for severe bodily injury, as outlined in a Sutter County Sheriff’s Department press release.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The alarming incident came to light when a co-worker at the school contacted local law enforcement. The arresting officers stated that when they arrived at the scene, Munson was actively teaching her class. It was later revealed that her blood alcohol level was nearly double the legal limit, even two hours after the initial interaction with the deputies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Baljinder Dhillon, Nuestro Elementary School District Superintendent, promptly addressed the matter by sending a letter to parents, assuring them of their children’s safety. He mentioned that Munson was taken into custody without any disturbances, ensuring that the students did not witness the unsettling arrest. The letter also highlighted the school’s proactive approach by stating, “Your 2nd graders will have a long-term substitute. Our students’ safety and well-being remain our highest priority.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kaitlynn Conley, a concerned parent, expressed her disbelief in an interview with CBS News. “I thought it was crazy,” she stated. Adding her perspective on Munson’s actions, she said, “I think she should’ve called out of work. I know people have fun weekends, but that was definitely not okay as an educator.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to these reports, the sheriff’s office confirmed the existence of footage capturing Munson driving to school in her inebriated state.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wendy Munson’s arraignment is set for 3 p.m. Wednesday. As of now, there is no confirmation regarding her legal representation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The incident at Nuestro Elementary underscores the need for schools to maintain strict safety and professional standards, ensuring an optimal environment for both students and staff.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">A shocking incident at Nuestro Elementary School in Live Oak, California, has drawn considerable attention and concern. Wendy Munson, 57, a second-grade teacher at the school, was arrested on charges of teaching while under the influence of alcohol. Responding to a report on Monday morning, sheriff’s deputies found Munson visibly impaired during her teaching hours. Following this discovery, she was subjected to a sobriety test which she subsequently failed. Munson was then arrested at approximately 8:20 a.m. and charged with driving with a blood alcohol content exceeding .08 percent, drunk driving, and child abuse with potential for severe bodily injury, as outlined in a Sutter County Sheriff’s Department press release. The alarming incident came to light when a co-worker at the school contacted local law enforcement. The arresting officers stated that when they arrived at the scene, Munson was actively teaching her class. It was later revealed that her blood alcohol level was nearly double the legal limit, even two hours after the initial interaction with the deputies. Baljinder Dhillon, Nuestro Elementary School District Superintendent, promptly addressed the matter by sending a letter to parents, assuring them of their children’s safety. He mentioned that Munson was taken into custody without any disturbances, ensuring that the students did not witness the unsettling arrest. The letter also highlighted the school’s proactive approach by stating, “Your 2nd graders will have a long-term substitute. Our students’ safety and well-being remain our highest priority.” Kaitlynn Conley, a concerned parent, expressed her disbelief in an interview with CBS News. “I thought it was crazy,” she stated. Adding her perspective on Munson’s actions, she said, “I think she should’ve called out of work. I know people have fun weekends, but that was definitely not okay as an educator.” In addition to these reports, the sheriff’s office confirmed the existence of footage capturing Munson driving to school in her inebriated state. Wendy Munson’s arraignment is set for 3 p.m. Wednesday. As of now, there is no confirmation regarding her legal representation. The incident at Nuestro Elementary underscores the need for schools to maintain strict safety and professional standards, ensuring an optimal environment for both students and staff.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Rep. Steve Scalise Jumps into the Race for House Speaker</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/05/Scalise-Speaker-Bid/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rep. Steve Scalise Jumps into the Race for House Speaker" /><published>2023-10-05T07:19:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-05T07:19:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/05/Scalise-Speaker-Bid</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/05/Scalise-Speaker-Bid/">&lt;p&gt;In a significant development in the political arena, Rep. Steve Scalise (R-LA) has declared his intent to run for the Speaker of the House. The House Majority Leader made the announcement on Wednesday, expressing that he seeks the nomination with “a strong sense of responsibility and purpose.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Scalise, a prominent figure from Louisiana, enjoys considerable support and affection from his fellow lawmakers. His announcement places him as a leading contender for the esteemed position. Many in the political circles remember Scalise for his tragic injury in 2017 when he was shot during a practice for a Republican baseball team. His resilience post the injury, including an extended recovery period and ongoing health challenges, is often viewed as a testament to his commitment to public service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Congressman’s credentials are impressive, having served as the Republican Whip for nearly ten years. He was also the Chairman of the Republican Conservative Committee (RSC), recognized as the most extensive conservative group within the House. The current chair of the RSC, Rep. Kevin Hern (R-OK), is speculated to join the race too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The dynamics of Scalise’s bid are fascinating, especially considering the recent events within the House Republican Conference. Rep. Kevin McCarthy’s (R-CA) recent ousting from the top House position has set the stage for new leadership. Despite Scalise and McCarthy showcasing a publicly amicable relationship, they weren’t particularly close allies. In crucial situations, McCarthy often leaned on Rep. Garrett Graves (R-LA) and Speaker Pro Tem Patrick McHenry (R-NC) instead of top deputies like Scalise and Majority Whip Tom Emmer (R-MN). This distance from McCarthy might turn out to be a strategic advantage for Scalise in the upcoming Speaker race.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, Scalise’s health might be a point of consideration for some colleagues. The Congressman recently shared the distressing news of a cancer diagnosis. While this could raise concerns about his ability to shoulder the demanding role, many peers have lauded his decision to run for the position.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Jim Jordan (R-OH) has also expressed his intent to vie for the Speaker post, adding more intrigue to the unfolding political drama.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the coming days, as the race for the Speaker of the House intensifies, Scalise’s leadership qualities, experience, and resilience will undoubtedly be at the forefront of discussions. His entry has certainly set the stage for a captivating contest.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a significant development in the political arena, Rep. Steve Scalise (R-LA) has declared his intent to run for the Speaker of the House. The House Majority Leader made the announcement on Wednesday, expressing that he seeks the nomination with “a strong sense of responsibility and purpose.” Scalise, a prominent figure from Louisiana, enjoys considerable support and affection from his fellow lawmakers. His announcement places him as a leading contender for the esteemed position. Many in the political circles remember Scalise for his tragic injury in 2017 when he was shot during a practice for a Republican baseball team. His resilience post the injury, including an extended recovery period and ongoing health challenges, is often viewed as a testament to his commitment to public service. The Congressman’s credentials are impressive, having served as the Republican Whip for nearly ten years. He was also the Chairman of the Republican Conservative Committee (RSC), recognized as the most extensive conservative group within the House. The current chair of the RSC, Rep. Kevin Hern (R-OK), is speculated to join the race too. The dynamics of Scalise’s bid are fascinating, especially considering the recent events within the House Republican Conference. Rep. Kevin McCarthy’s (R-CA) recent ousting from the top House position has set the stage for new leadership. Despite Scalise and McCarthy showcasing a publicly amicable relationship, they weren’t particularly close allies. In crucial situations, McCarthy often leaned on Rep. Garrett Graves (R-LA) and Speaker Pro Tem Patrick McHenry (R-NC) instead of top deputies like Scalise and Majority Whip Tom Emmer (R-MN). This distance from McCarthy might turn out to be a strategic advantage for Scalise in the upcoming Speaker race. However, Scalise’s health might be a point of consideration for some colleagues. The Congressman recently shared the distressing news of a cancer diagnosis. While this could raise concerns about his ability to shoulder the demanding role, many peers have lauded his decision to run for the position. Rep. Jim Jordan (R-OH) has also expressed his intent to vie for the Speaker post, adding more intrigue to the unfolding political drama. In the coming days, as the race for the Speaker of the House intensifies, Scalise’s leadership qualities, experience, and resilience will undoubtedly be at the forefront of discussions. His entry has certainly set the stage for a captivating contest.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Protecting the Philly Cheesesteak: Iconic Joint Ups Security Amid Crime Surge</title><link href="/news/2023/10/05/Philly-Cheesesteak-Security/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Protecting the Philly Cheesesteak: Iconic Joint Ups Security Amid Crime Surge" /><published>2023-10-05T06:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-05T06:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/05/Philly-Cheesesteak-Security</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/05/Philly-Cheesesteak-Security/">&lt;p&gt;In a robust response to the escalating crime rate, Jim’s West Steaks &amp;amp; Hoagies, a cherished Philly cheesesteak institution, has enlisted armed security personnel to shield its patrons and workforce. This measure underscores a broader trend in Philadelphia, where businesses increasingly prioritize security in the face of mounting threats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Victoria Wylie, the co-owner of the famed eatery, emphasized the importance of proactive safety measures. “We’re no longer waiting for tragedies to strike. Prevention is our mantra,” Wylie shared with Fox News. In September, after the restaurant’s re-launch, security became paramount, especially considering a past armed robbery incident at the establishment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In recent years, Philadelphia has joined the ranks of various U.S. cities witnessing a crime surge. The city recorded a disturbing increase in homicides, surpassing 500 in consecutive years. Additionally, Philadelphia Police Department data reveals an alarming 16% rise in overall crime year-to-date.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given these challenges, Wylie’s concerns are far from misplaced. “West Philadelphia, where we serve our delectable cheesesteaks, is not immune to this crime wave,” Wylie remarked. As someone reintroducing a beloved restaurant to its eager fans, she explained, “It’s unpredictable. We don’t truly know who might walk in.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To give a clearer picture, a video circulated on Jim’s West Steaks &amp;amp; Hoagies’ Instagram showcased an armed security guard, toting an assault-style rifle, standing guard. Wylie confirmed these guards’ presence during operational hours, underlining their unwavering commitment to ensuring safety.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Historical data sheds light on the stakes at play. In 2015, armed robbers made away with $215 from the cash register and the pockets of unsuspecting patrons at Jim’s Steaks. Such unsettling memories bolstered the current ownership’s resolve to strengthen security measures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While certain crime categories like armed robberies have witnessed a decrease, they remain elevated compared to pre-pandemic levels. September was particularly tumultuous. Swarms of thieves descended on various Philadelphia businesses, leading to widescale lootings. Such rampant theft compelled the Pennsylvania Liquor Control Board to momentarily shutter all 48 city-based retail outlets, prioritizing safety.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Benjamin Nochum, the store manager of Patriot Pharmacy, which was looted in September, expressed his anguish, “Looters aren’t just stealing from businesses; they’re stealing from our communities.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amid this backdrop, Wylie remains steadfast. Her primary aim is not just to serve the city’s favorite cheesesteaks but to provide a safe dining experience. “Our priority is people’s safety,” she stated firmly. In her view, the best way to deter potential criminals is by showing that safety precautions are already in place. Her hope is for patrons to continue relishing their cheesesteaks, knowing they’re in a secure environment.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a robust response to the escalating crime rate, Jim’s West Steaks &amp;amp; Hoagies, a cherished Philly cheesesteak institution, has enlisted armed security personnel to shield its patrons and workforce. This measure underscores a broader trend in Philadelphia, where businesses increasingly prioritize security in the face of mounting threats. Victoria Wylie, the co-owner of the famed eatery, emphasized the importance of proactive safety measures. “We’re no longer waiting for tragedies to strike. Prevention is our mantra,” Wylie shared with Fox News. In September, after the restaurant’s re-launch, security became paramount, especially considering a past armed robbery incident at the establishment. In recent years, Philadelphia has joined the ranks of various U.S. cities witnessing a crime surge. The city recorded a disturbing increase in homicides, surpassing 500 in consecutive years. Additionally, Philadelphia Police Department data reveals an alarming 16% rise in overall crime year-to-date. Given these challenges, Wylie’s concerns are far from misplaced. “West Philadelphia, where we serve our delectable cheesesteaks, is not immune to this crime wave,” Wylie remarked. As someone reintroducing a beloved restaurant to its eager fans, she explained, “It’s unpredictable. We don’t truly know who might walk in.” To give a clearer picture, a video circulated on Jim’s West Steaks &amp;amp; Hoagies’ Instagram showcased an armed security guard, toting an assault-style rifle, standing guard. Wylie confirmed these guards’ presence during operational hours, underlining their unwavering commitment to ensuring safety. Historical data sheds light on the stakes at play. In 2015, armed robbers made away with $215 from the cash register and the pockets of unsuspecting patrons at Jim’s Steaks. Such unsettling memories bolstered the current ownership’s resolve to strengthen security measures. While certain crime categories like armed robberies have witnessed a decrease, they remain elevated compared to pre-pandemic levels. September was particularly tumultuous. Swarms of thieves descended on various Philadelphia businesses, leading to widescale lootings. Such rampant theft compelled the Pennsylvania Liquor Control Board to momentarily shutter all 48 city-based retail outlets, prioritizing safety. Benjamin Nochum, the store manager of Patriot Pharmacy, which was looted in September, expressed his anguish, “Looters aren’t just stealing from businesses; they’re stealing from our communities.” Amid this backdrop, Wylie remains steadfast. Her primary aim is not just to serve the city’s favorite cheesesteaks but to provide a safe dining experience. “Our priority is people’s safety,” she stated firmly. In her view, the best way to deter potential criminals is by showing that safety precautions are already in place. Her hope is for patrons to continue relishing their cheesesteaks, knowing they’re in a secure environment.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Rep. Luna’s Principled Stance: A Beacon of Hope in House Leadership?</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/04/Luna-Leadership-Stand/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rep. Luna’s Principled Stance: A Beacon of Hope in House Leadership?" /><published>2023-10-04T16:34:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-04T16:34:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/04/Luna-Leadership-Stand</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/04/Luna-Leadership-Stand/">&lt;p&gt;In times where true leadership and principles seem to be waning in Washington, Rep. Anna Paulina Luna (R-Fla.) has emerged as a refreshing voice of clarity and conviction. Drawing a line in the sand, Luna has decisively declared her support for a House speaker only if they are unwavering in their commitment to bring President Joe Biden’s impeachment to the House floor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Following the surprising exit of Rep. Kevin McCarthy (R-Calif.) from the distinguished speaker’s position, Luna didn’t shy away. She succinctly laid out the path for integrity in leadership: “A speaker who stands up against Jack Smith’s questionable election interference probes, ensures accountability by subpoenaing Hunter Biden, and remains resolute in ushering an impeachment vote for Joe Biden.” Luna’s principled stance was shared with the nation on X, the successor to Twitter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With a heartfelt emphasis on safeguarding transparent elections and eliminating governmental shadows, Luna rightfully pointed out, “The very essence of America depends on actions reflecting these values. My support is conditional on these uncompromising terms.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Presently, the House is in a precarious position. The absence of a speaker has left the legislative body in limbo, requiring the swift election of a dedicated leader to move forward. It’s noteworthy that Luna, in her continued pursuit of genuine representation, opted not to participate in the contentious vote which led to McCarthy’s ousting. McCarthy’s departure was marked by eight of his party members aligning with Democrats, resulting in a narrow 216-210 vote against him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking back, although McCarthy had ignited the spark of an impeachment inquiry against Biden, he abstained from seeing it through to a vote, betraying the anticipation of many. Luna’s initial reluctance to back McCarthy earlier this year is now seen in a new light. After days of voting and uncertainty, McCarthy clinched the speaker position on the 15th ballot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, with Luna’s commendable and straightforward stance, the nation watches keenly. Who among the House leadership will step up, aligning with Luna’s vision for a transparent and accountable America? As the winds of change blow through Washington, it’s evident that the discussion surrounding Biden’s potential impeachment could very well shape the House’s leadership narrative in the coming phase.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In times where true leadership and principles seem to be waning in Washington, Rep. Anna Paulina Luna (R-Fla.) has emerged as a refreshing voice of clarity and conviction. Drawing a line in the sand, Luna has decisively declared her support for a House speaker only if they are unwavering in their commitment to bring President Joe Biden’s impeachment to the House floor. Following the surprising exit of Rep. Kevin McCarthy (R-Calif.) from the distinguished speaker’s position, Luna didn’t shy away. She succinctly laid out the path for integrity in leadership: “A speaker who stands up against Jack Smith’s questionable election interference probes, ensures accountability by subpoenaing Hunter Biden, and remains resolute in ushering an impeachment vote for Joe Biden.” Luna’s principled stance was shared with the nation on X, the successor to Twitter. With a heartfelt emphasis on safeguarding transparent elections and eliminating governmental shadows, Luna rightfully pointed out, “The very essence of America depends on actions reflecting these values. My support is conditional on these uncompromising terms.” Presently, the House is in a precarious position. The absence of a speaker has left the legislative body in limbo, requiring the swift election of a dedicated leader to move forward. It’s noteworthy that Luna, in her continued pursuit of genuine representation, opted not to participate in the contentious vote which led to McCarthy’s ousting. McCarthy’s departure was marked by eight of his party members aligning with Democrats, resulting in a narrow 216-210 vote against him. Looking back, although McCarthy had ignited the spark of an impeachment inquiry against Biden, he abstained from seeing it through to a vote, betraying the anticipation of many. Luna’s initial reluctance to back McCarthy earlier this year is now seen in a new light. After days of voting and uncertainty, McCarthy clinched the speaker position on the 15th ballot. Now, with Luna’s commendable and straightforward stance, the nation watches keenly. Who among the House leadership will step up, aligning with Luna’s vision for a transparent and accountable America? As the winds of change blow through Washington, it’s evident that the discussion surrounding Biden’s potential impeachment could very well shape the House’s leadership narrative in the coming phase.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Grimes Takes Legal Action Against Elon Musk: Parental Rights at Stake</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/04/Grimes-Elon-Musk-Parental-Rights/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Grimes Takes Legal Action Against Elon Musk: Parental Rights at Stake" /><published>2023-10-04T14:31:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-04T14:31:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/04/Grimes-Elon-Musk-Parental-Rights</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/04/Grimes-Elon-Musk-Parental-Rights/">&lt;p&gt;In the world of entertainment and tech billionaires, few partnerships have garnered as much attention as that of singer Grimes and entrepreneur Elon Musk. However, their relationship is once again in the limelight, not for a new track or tech innovation, but for a legal tussle involving the parental rights of their three uniquely-named children: X Æ A-Xii, Exa Dark Sideræl, and Techno Mechanicus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Grimes, known offstage as Claire Boucher, recently lodged a “petition to establish parental relationship” in a California court, as reported by the Daily Mail. Such petitions serve to legally identify a child’s parents, especially when the parents have never tied the knot. Beyond mere identification, these petitions can be a stepping stone to child custody and support order proceedings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite this move, the 35-year-old artist hasn’t publicly expressed desires regarding child support or custody rights. As for Musk, the visionary behind ventures such as Tesla and SpaceX, there hasn’t been any public acknowledgment or response to the petition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Grimes’ concerns run deeper than formalities. A now-removed post on the platform, X, conveys her anguish: “Tell Shivon to unblock me and tell Elon to let me see my son or plz respond to my lawyer,” she said, alluding to Shivon Zilis. Zilis, an executive at Musk’s neurotech firm, Neuralink, bore Musk’s twins via IVF, though she maintains a strictly professional relationship with him. Grimes’ pain is palpable as she continues, “I have never even been allowed to see a photo of these children until this moment, despite the situation utterly ripping my family apart.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Elon Musk, whose family tree boasts 11 branches in the form of his children, seems to have complex dynamics when it comes to parenthood. Besides the trio with Grimes, he has 17-month-old twins, Azure and Strider, with Zilis, and six more children with his first wife, Justine Wilson. Tragically, one of them, Nevada, succumbed to Sudden Infant Death Syndrome as an infant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given the Tesla CEO’s vocal concerns about potential population declines, his stance on having children seems clear. As he expressed on X, “Having children is saving the world.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As this legal drama unfolds, fans and onlookers can only hope for a resolution that prioritizes the well-being of the children involved.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">In the world of entertainment and tech billionaires, few partnerships have garnered as much attention as that of singer Grimes and entrepreneur Elon Musk. However, their relationship is once again in the limelight, not for a new track or tech innovation, but for a legal tussle involving the parental rights of their three uniquely-named children: X Æ A-Xii, Exa Dark Sideræl, and Techno Mechanicus. Grimes, known offstage as Claire Boucher, recently lodged a “petition to establish parental relationship” in a California court, as reported by the Daily Mail. Such petitions serve to legally identify a child’s parents, especially when the parents have never tied the knot. Beyond mere identification, these petitions can be a stepping stone to child custody and support order proceedings. Despite this move, the 35-year-old artist hasn’t publicly expressed desires regarding child support or custody rights. As for Musk, the visionary behind ventures such as Tesla and SpaceX, there hasn’t been any public acknowledgment or response to the petition. Grimes’ concerns run deeper than formalities. A now-removed post on the platform, X, conveys her anguish: “Tell Shivon to unblock me and tell Elon to let me see my son or plz respond to my lawyer,” she said, alluding to Shivon Zilis. Zilis, an executive at Musk’s neurotech firm, Neuralink, bore Musk’s twins via IVF, though she maintains a strictly professional relationship with him. Grimes’ pain is palpable as she continues, “I have never even been allowed to see a photo of these children until this moment, despite the situation utterly ripping my family apart.” Elon Musk, whose family tree boasts 11 branches in the form of his children, seems to have complex dynamics when it comes to parenthood. Besides the trio with Grimes, he has 17-month-old twins, Azure and Strider, with Zilis, and six more children with his first wife, Justine Wilson. Tragically, one of them, Nevada, succumbed to Sudden Infant Death Syndrome as an infant. Given the Tesla CEO’s vocal concerns about potential population declines, his stance on having children seems clear. As he expressed on X, “Having children is saving the world.” As this legal drama unfolds, fans and onlookers can only hope for a resolution that prioritizes the well-being of the children involved.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Shocking Revelation: Son of Charlotte Sena’s Kidnapping Suspect Hopes His Father Faces Maximum Penalty</title><link href="/news/2023/10/04/Kidnapping-Suspect-Son/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Shocking Revelation: Son of Charlotte Sena’s Kidnapping Suspect Hopes His Father Faces Maximum Penalty" /><published>2023-10-04T12:26:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-04T12:26:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/04/Kidnapping-Suspect-Son</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/04/Kidnapping-Suspect-Son/">&lt;p&gt;In a startling turn of events surrounding the kidnapping case of Charlotte Sena, the man claiming to be the son of the prime suspect, Craig Ross Jr., broke his silence. As the media spotlight zooms in on this harrowing case, the supposed offspring hopes that his father “dies in prison.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Charlotte Sena’s disappearance made headlines when she vanished after a simple bike ride in Lake Moreau State Park. Fortunately, the child was later found, having been hidden in a cabinet within Ross’s unkempt camper, parked behind another property in the vicinity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This tumultuous case has captured the nation’s attention, as desperate searches led to an unexpected outcome. After the young girl’s ordeal, her family expressed their heartfelt gratitude to the various agencies, volunteers, and community members who rallied together to ensure Charlotte’s safe return. The Sena family is now channeling their efforts to help Charlotte recover, dedicating a GoFundMe campaign to support the 9-year-old’s journey.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ross Jr., now in custody on charges of first-degree kidnapping, had previously left a ransom note in the Sena family’s mailbox, leading to his arrest. The swift action of state police was pivotal in capturing Ross Jr., with their investigation further bolstered by evidence from a past DUI arrest in 1999.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As investigators don their Tyvek suits, poring over Ross Jr.’s Porter Corners residence and removing key evidence, the unexpected appearance of a man claiming to be the accused’s son added another layer to this unfolding drama. Frustrated and overwhelmed, he vented his dismay, stating, “Yeah, he’s my father, but why do I have to deal with this? Everyone is asking me all this. I don’t know anything. I hate him and hope he dies in prison.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This case serves as a sobering reminder of the impact of crime not only on the victims but also on the families of those accused. The community’s support has been unwavering, with the New York State Police and the FBI receiving particular praise for their role in ensuring Charlotte’s safe return.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the case continues to unravel, the focus remains on supporting young Charlotte, highlighting the importance of community vigilance, and hoping for justice to prevail.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a startling turn of events surrounding the kidnapping case of Charlotte Sena, the man claiming to be the son of the prime suspect, Craig Ross Jr., broke his silence. As the media spotlight zooms in on this harrowing case, the supposed offspring hopes that his father “dies in prison.” Charlotte Sena’s disappearance made headlines when she vanished after a simple bike ride in Lake Moreau State Park. Fortunately, the child was later found, having been hidden in a cabinet within Ross’s unkempt camper, parked behind another property in the vicinity. This tumultuous case has captured the nation’s attention, as desperate searches led to an unexpected outcome. After the young girl’s ordeal, her family expressed their heartfelt gratitude to the various agencies, volunteers, and community members who rallied together to ensure Charlotte’s safe return. The Sena family is now channeling their efforts to help Charlotte recover, dedicating a GoFundMe campaign to support the 9-year-old’s journey. Ross Jr., now in custody on charges of first-degree kidnapping, had previously left a ransom note in the Sena family’s mailbox, leading to his arrest. The swift action of state police was pivotal in capturing Ross Jr., with their investigation further bolstered by evidence from a past DUI arrest in 1999. As investigators don their Tyvek suits, poring over Ross Jr.’s Porter Corners residence and removing key evidence, the unexpected appearance of a man claiming to be the accused’s son added another layer to this unfolding drama. Frustrated and overwhelmed, he vented his dismay, stating, “Yeah, he’s my father, but why do I have to deal with this? Everyone is asking me all this. I don’t know anything. I hate him and hope he dies in prison.” This case serves as a sobering reminder of the impact of crime not only on the victims but also on the families of those accused. The community’s support has been unwavering, with the New York State Police and the FBI receiving particular praise for their role in ensuring Charlotte’s safe return. As the case continues to unravel, the focus remains on supporting young Charlotte, highlighting the importance of community vigilance, and hoping for justice to prevail.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">American Student’s Dubai Layover Spirals into Four-Month Ordeal</title><link href="/news/2023/10/04/Dubai-Layover-Nightmare/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="American Student’s Dubai Layover Spirals into Four-Month Ordeal" /><published>2023-10-04T10:17:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-04T10:17:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/04/Dubai-Layover-Nightmare</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/04/Dubai-Layover-Nightmare/">&lt;p&gt;Elizabeth Polanco De Los Santos, a 21-year-old American college student, faced an unexpected twist during her travels. What was supposed to be a 10-hour layover in Dubai turned into a four-month-long legal challenge, landing her on the United Arab Emirates’ (UAE) no-fly list and resulting in a year-long jail sentence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;De Los Santos, after vacationing in Turkey, was returning home via Dubai International Airport. However, things took a turn on July 14 when she encountered issues with customs officials. The New York student’s “waist trainer” corset, which she wore due to recent surgery, set off detectors, leading to further screening. In a private room, when asked to remove her garment, she tried explaining her medical condition, which required the corset. Feeling “violated” during this process, De Los Santos reportedly touched an airport official’s arm, a gesture that escalated into accusations of “assault and insult.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The altercation’s aftermath was swift and severe. Despite paying a fine of AED 10,000 ($2,722 USD), De Los Santos received a year-long jail sentence. Her original flight on July 15 came and went without her. Furthermore, the UAE’s automatic appeal process implies she could be in the country for an indefinite period.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Radha Stirling, chief executive of “Detained in Dubai,” emphasized the consequences of transiting through Dubai. The organization, which advocates for travelers stuck in such challenging situations in the UAE, is currently supporting De Los Santos. Stirling points out that government employees in Dubai could potentially exploit situations like these, seeking out-of-court settlements. She strongly believes that the reputation of UAE as a reliable transport and tourism hub is at stake due to incidents of this nature.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;De Los Santos’ next court appearance is slated for October 24. In the meantime, “Detained in Dubai” is tirelessly working to assist her. The organization, established in 2008, has previously aided US national Tierra Young Allen, known as “Sassy Trucker” on TikTok, who found herself in a similar predicament in the UAE.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For travelers, De Los Santos’ experience serves as a cautionary tale about the unforeseen complications that might arise during international transit. As her ordeal continues, it also highlights the pressing need for transparency and fair treatment in international legal systems.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Elizabeth Polanco De Los Santos, a 21-year-old American college student, faced an unexpected twist during her travels. What was supposed to be a 10-hour layover in Dubai turned into a four-month-long legal challenge, landing her on the United Arab Emirates’ (UAE) no-fly list and resulting in a year-long jail sentence. De Los Santos, after vacationing in Turkey, was returning home via Dubai International Airport. However, things took a turn on July 14 when she encountered issues with customs officials. The New York student’s “waist trainer” corset, which she wore due to recent surgery, set off detectors, leading to further screening. In a private room, when asked to remove her garment, she tried explaining her medical condition, which required the corset. Feeling “violated” during this process, De Los Santos reportedly touched an airport official’s arm, a gesture that escalated into accusations of “assault and insult.” The altercation’s aftermath was swift and severe. Despite paying a fine of AED 10,000 ($2,722 USD), De Los Santos received a year-long jail sentence. Her original flight on July 15 came and went without her. Furthermore, the UAE’s automatic appeal process implies she could be in the country for an indefinite period. Radha Stirling, chief executive of “Detained in Dubai,” emphasized the consequences of transiting through Dubai. The organization, which advocates for travelers stuck in such challenging situations in the UAE, is currently supporting De Los Santos. Stirling points out that government employees in Dubai could potentially exploit situations like these, seeking out-of-court settlements. She strongly believes that the reputation of UAE as a reliable transport and tourism hub is at stake due to incidents of this nature. De Los Santos’ next court appearance is slated for October 24. In the meantime, “Detained in Dubai” is tirelessly working to assist her. The organization, established in 2008, has previously aided US national Tierra Young Allen, known as “Sassy Trucker” on TikTok, who found herself in a similar predicament in the UAE. For travelers, De Los Santos’ experience serves as a cautionary tale about the unforeseen complications that might arise during international transit. As her ordeal continues, it also highlights the pressing need for transparency and fair treatment in international legal systems.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hunter Biden Faces Court - Gun Charges Amidst Weiss’ Investigation</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/04/Hunter-Biden-Gun-Charges/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hunter Biden Faces Court - Gun Charges Amidst Weiss’ Investigation" /><published>2023-10-04T09:04:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-04T09:04:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/04/Hunter-Biden-Gun-Charges</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/04/Hunter-Biden-Gun-Charges/">&lt;p&gt;WILMINGTON, DE - A legal cloud continues to hang over the first family as Hunter Biden, President Joe Biden’s son, firmly declared his innocence in a Delaware court on Tuesday. Facing federal gun charges resulting from Special Counsel David Weiss’ prolonged investigation, Biden entered a not guilty plea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The charges brought against him are weighty:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Making a false statement during a firearm purchase.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Providing inaccurate information mandatory for a federal firearms licensed dealer.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Possession of a firearm as someone unlawfully using or addicted to controlled substances.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A collective total of potential 25 years in prison looms over Biden if convicted on all counts, alongside a hefty fine of $250,000 for each charge and the possibility of three years under supervised release.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the severity of the charges, Biden maintains his innocence. Magistrate Judge Christopher Burke, who oversaw the arraignment, has set specific conditions for Biden’s release. These include seeking employment, transparency about international travel plans, abstinence from firearms, drugs, and alcohol, and mandatory participation in a drug counseling program. Notably, Biden passed a drug test during the hearing, addressing concerns about potential substance misuse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Abbe Lowell, Hunter Biden’s defense attorney, disclosed plans to file a motion to dismiss based on a diversion agreement related to the gun charges, asserting its continued validity. This agreement was initially part of a plea deal to address misdemeanor tax counts, which disintegrated in July. As a result, Biden had no choice but to plead not guilty to two misdemeanor tax charges and a felony gun charge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This recent appearance in court revolves around allegations from 2018. The indictment claims that Biden, while acquiring a Colt Cobra 38SPL Revolver, dishonestly asserted on Form 4473 that he wasn’t unlawfully using or addicted to any narcotic or controlled substance, a statement the authorities contend was false.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Federal prosecutors Leo Wise and Derek Hines represented the government at the hearing, while Weiss was absent. Previous reports suggest that Hunter Biden’s firearm became a matter of public concern when it was discarded in a trash can near a Delaware school in 2018.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although the defense appears ready to challenge the charges on several fronts, including the validity and constitutionality of the implicated statutes, it’s evident that this legal battle is just heating up. As the story develops, its impact on the Biden family and the wider political landscape remains to be seen.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">WILMINGTON, DE - A legal cloud continues to hang over the first family as Hunter Biden, President Joe Biden’s son, firmly declared his innocence in a Delaware court on Tuesday. Facing federal gun charges resulting from Special Counsel David Weiss’ prolonged investigation, Biden entered a not guilty plea. The charges brought against him are weighty: Making a false statement during a firearm purchase. Providing inaccurate information mandatory for a federal firearms licensed dealer. Possession of a firearm as someone unlawfully using or addicted to controlled substances. A collective total of potential 25 years in prison looms over Biden if convicted on all counts, alongside a hefty fine of $250,000 for each charge and the possibility of three years under supervised release. Despite the severity of the charges, Biden maintains his innocence. Magistrate Judge Christopher Burke, who oversaw the arraignment, has set specific conditions for Biden’s release. These include seeking employment, transparency about international travel plans, abstinence from firearms, drugs, and alcohol, and mandatory participation in a drug counseling program. Notably, Biden passed a drug test during the hearing, addressing concerns about potential substance misuse. Abbe Lowell, Hunter Biden’s defense attorney, disclosed plans to file a motion to dismiss based on a diversion agreement related to the gun charges, asserting its continued validity. This agreement was initially part of a plea deal to address misdemeanor tax counts, which disintegrated in July. As a result, Biden had no choice but to plead not guilty to two misdemeanor tax charges and a felony gun charge. This recent appearance in court revolves around allegations from 2018. The indictment claims that Biden, while acquiring a Colt Cobra 38SPL Revolver, dishonestly asserted on Form 4473 that he wasn’t unlawfully using or addicted to any narcotic or controlled substance, a statement the authorities contend was false. Federal prosecutors Leo Wise and Derek Hines represented the government at the hearing, while Weiss was absent. Previous reports suggest that Hunter Biden’s firearm became a matter of public concern when it was discarded in a trash can near a Delaware school in 2018. Although the defense appears ready to challenge the charges on several fronts, including the validity and constitutionality of the implicated statutes, it’s evident that this legal battle is just heating up. As the story develops, its impact on the Biden family and the wider political landscape remains to be seen.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Robin Williams’ AI Voice Controversy - Daughter Speaks Out</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/04/Robin-Williams-AI-Controversy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Robin Williams’ AI Voice Controversy - Daughter Speaks Out" /><published>2023-10-04T08:12:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-04T08:12:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/04/Robin-Williams-AI-Controversy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/04/Robin-Williams-AI-Controversy/">&lt;p&gt;Zelda Williams, daughter of the beloved late actor Robin Williams, has publicly criticized the utilization of artificial intelligence (AI) to emulate her father’s distinctive voice. She described the technology-driven imitation as a “horrendous Frankensteinian monster.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Hollywood community, ever adapting to technological progress, recently encountered a controversial application of AI — recreating voices of actors, especially those who’ve passed away. The trend touched a nerve with Zelda, who articulated her disapproval in an impassioned Instagram Story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She highlighted her unique standpoint, writing, “I am not an impartial voice in SAG’s fight against AI,” referencing the screen actors union. Zelda emphasized the ethical concerns, stating, “I’ve witnessed for YEARS how many people want to train these models to create/recreate actors who cannot consent, like Dad. This isn’t theoretical, it is very very real.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the impersonation of Robin’s voice might unsettle fans, the broader issue at hand extends beyond personal sentiments. “I’ve already heard AI used to get his ‘voice’ to say whatever people want,” Zelda remarked, pointing out the deeper implications of the technology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zelda’s main contention is with the principle behind the act. She believes that living actors “deserve a chance to create characters with their choices, to voice cartoons, to put their HUMAN effort and time into the pursuit of performance.” Using AI, she argues, can lead to shallow reproductions that lack the depth, emotion, and nuance that human actors bring to their roles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In her pointed critique, she described AI simulations of actors as being, “at their very best, a poor facsimile of greater people, but at their worst, a horrendous Frankensteinian monster, cobbled together from the worst bits of everything this industry is, instead of what it should stand for.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This isn’t a lone outcry. Other prominent figures in Hollywood, like James Cameron, Christopher Nolan, and Tim Burton, have previously expressed reservations about such technology. Their combined voices raise a significant question about the industry’s future direction and the ethical considerations of AI.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As technology continues to push boundaries, Hollywood, and the world at large, will need to grapple with the moral quandaries it presents. Zelda’s candid remarks shed light on an issue that’s bound to grow more prominent in the coming years.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Zelda Williams, daughter of the beloved late actor Robin Williams, has publicly criticized the utilization of artificial intelligence (AI) to emulate her father’s distinctive voice. She described the technology-driven imitation as a “horrendous Frankensteinian monster.” The Hollywood community, ever adapting to technological progress, recently encountered a controversial application of AI — recreating voices of actors, especially those who’ve passed away. The trend touched a nerve with Zelda, who articulated her disapproval in an impassioned Instagram Story. She highlighted her unique standpoint, writing, “I am not an impartial voice in SAG’s fight against AI,” referencing the screen actors union. Zelda emphasized the ethical concerns, stating, “I’ve witnessed for YEARS how many people want to train these models to create/recreate actors who cannot consent, like Dad. This isn’t theoretical, it is very very real.” While the impersonation of Robin’s voice might unsettle fans, the broader issue at hand extends beyond personal sentiments. “I’ve already heard AI used to get his ‘voice’ to say whatever people want,” Zelda remarked, pointing out the deeper implications of the technology. Zelda’s main contention is with the principle behind the act. She believes that living actors “deserve a chance to create characters with their choices, to voice cartoons, to put their HUMAN effort and time into the pursuit of performance.” Using AI, she argues, can lead to shallow reproductions that lack the depth, emotion, and nuance that human actors bring to their roles. In her pointed critique, she described AI simulations of actors as being, “at their very best, a poor facsimile of greater people, but at their worst, a horrendous Frankensteinian monster, cobbled together from the worst bits of everything this industry is, instead of what it should stand for.” This isn’t a lone outcry. Other prominent figures in Hollywood, like James Cameron, Christopher Nolan, and Tim Burton, have previously expressed reservations about such technology. Their combined voices raise a significant question about the industry’s future direction and the ethical considerations of AI. As technology continues to push boundaries, Hollywood, and the world at large, will need to grapple with the moral quandaries it presents. Zelda’s candid remarks shed light on an issue that’s bound to grow more prominent in the coming years.</summary></entry></feed>