<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-10-24T02:20:49-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/24/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-24T02:20:49-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-24T02:20:49-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/24/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/24/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/24/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-24T02:20:49-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-24T02:20:49-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/24/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/24/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/">&lt;p&gt;Recent surprise attacks by Hamas on Israel has fueled ongoing tensions between staunchly conservative commentators and the progressive “Squad” Democrats known for criticizing Israel. The intensity of the backlash highlights the deep political divide over foreign policy in the Middle East.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Hamas’ shocking attack, several members of the “Squad,” including Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.), called for a “ceasefire and de-escalation,” condemning the violence. The absence of a statement from Rep. Rashida Tlaib (D-Mich.) was notably called out by conservative media outlets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;South Carolina GOP Rep. Nancy Mace quickly labeled Ocasio-Cortez a “Hamas apologist” in response to her call for peace and de-escalation. Rep. Ilhan Omar (D-Minn.), no stranger to controversy surrounding her views on Israel, echoed the call for de-escalation and ceasefire. Omar’s prior statements comparing the US and Israel to terrorist groups like Hamas and the Taliban resurfaced in the debate, fueling more criticisms. Omar’s 2019 tweet, where she opined that “Israel has hypnotized the world,” also continues to haunt her political career, often cited by critics to challenge her stance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conservative commentators have been especially vocal. “FOX &amp;amp; Friends Weekend” co-host Rachel Campos-Duffy took aim at Omar, saying she fails to recognize the peace in the Middle East under Trump’s administration. Conservative pundit John Hasson also called out Omar, claiming she insinuated that attacks on IDF forces were acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Massachusetts Democrat Rep. Ayanna Pressley’s concerns over the “devastating attacks on Israelis” were met with skepticism. A prominent conservative online personality, Comfortably Smug, accused the “Squad” of advising Israel to back down after the nation suffered massive attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Jamaal Bowman’s call for an end to the Gaza blockade, in addition to condemning the Hamas attacks, was met with criticism from conservative radio host Jason Rantz. He accused Bowman of pairing his condemnation of terrorism with unwarranted criticisms of Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Cori Bush emphasized the urgent need for a ceasefire, while pushing for an end to “U.S. support for Israeli military occupation and apartheid.” Defense attorney Marina Medvin criticized Bush, suggesting that she equates the death of Palestinian terrorists to the horrific acts committed against Jewish civilians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amidst the political turmoil and intense debate, the attacks have taken a heavy toll. Israeli media report over 300 dead due to the wide-ranging assault. Gaza health officials note that at least 200 Palestinians have perished in the retaliatory Israeli air strikes following the initial Hamas attack. As the situation remains volatile, both sides continue to count their casualties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This divisive issue showcases the challenge America faces in crafting a unified approach to foreign policy, with deeply entrenched political divides at play. As the situation develops, the debate is bound to intensify, shedding light on the complexities of U.S. politics in the global arena.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">‘Get the F**k Up’: 50 Cent Slams Biden for Beach Vacation Amid Israel Turmoil</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/23/50-Cent-Biden-Critique/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="‘Get the F**k Up’: 50 Cent Slams Biden for Beach Vacation Amid Israel Turmoil" /><published>2023-10-23T17:16:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-23T17:16:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/23/50-Cent-Biden-Critique</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/23/50-Cent-Biden-Critique/">&lt;p&gt;Amid escalating tensions and violence in the Middle East, rapper 50 Cent has taken to Instagram to deliver a bold and explicit message to President Joe Biden: “Get the f**k up” from your beach vacation and address the crisis. The celebrity’s public call to action highlights the mounting frustration and urgency felt by many as the situation overseas continues to deteriorate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sharing a news report that shows Biden relaxing at his Rehoboth Beach home while Israel faces a severe crisis and Congress is embroiled in chaos, 50 Cent made his feelings clear: “Hey Joe get the fvck up, we in trouble man!” This stark message has resonated with thousands, as it echoes the growing concern over the President’s apparent detachment during a time of international turmoil.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The post brings attention to the dire circumstances in the Middle East, where Israel is grappling with an onslaught of terrorist attacks from Hamas, resulting in the tragic loss of over 1,400 lives, mostly civilians. The rapper’s call to action underscores the need for decisive leadership and immediate engagement, especially when the stability of a region and the lives of innocent people are at stake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;President Biden, 80, had just returned from a brief yet intense trip to Israel, where he spent seven hours on the ground, meeting with Israeli President Benjamin Netanyahu and those directly affected by Hamas’ brutal October 7 terror attack. However, instead of capitalizing on the momentum from this diplomatic endeavor, the President chose to retreat to his Delaware beach home, a decision that has since become a focal point of criticism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Addressing the nation on Friday, Biden attempted to link the aid and support needed by Israel to that of Ukraine, drawing parallels between their respective struggles against aggressors seeking to obliterate their democracies. He likened Hamas’ actions to those of Russian President Vladimir Putin, emphasizing their shared objective of annihilating neighboring democracies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the strong rhetoric, 50 Cent’s Instagram post captures a sentiment shared by many Americans—that in times of international crisis, the nation’s leader must be fully engaged, visible, and ready to take decisive action. The rapper’s explicit call for President Biden to ‘get up’ and tackle the crisis head-on serves as a powerful reminder of the urgency and gravity of the situation, urging the President to rise to the occasion and lead with conviction and urgency.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Amid escalating tensions and violence in the Middle East, rapper 50 Cent has taken to Instagram to deliver a bold and explicit message to President Joe Biden: “Get the f**k up” from your beach vacation and address the crisis. The celebrity’s public call to action highlights the mounting frustration and urgency felt by many as the situation overseas continues to deteriorate. Sharing a news report that shows Biden relaxing at his Rehoboth Beach home while Israel faces a severe crisis and Congress is embroiled in chaos, 50 Cent made his feelings clear: “Hey Joe get the fvck up, we in trouble man!” This stark message has resonated with thousands, as it echoes the growing concern over the President’s apparent detachment during a time of international turmoil. The post brings attention to the dire circumstances in the Middle East, where Israel is grappling with an onslaught of terrorist attacks from Hamas, resulting in the tragic loss of over 1,400 lives, mostly civilians. The rapper’s call to action underscores the need for decisive leadership and immediate engagement, especially when the stability of a region and the lives of innocent people are at stake. President Biden, 80, had just returned from a brief yet intense trip to Israel, where he spent seven hours on the ground, meeting with Israeli President Benjamin Netanyahu and those directly affected by Hamas’ brutal October 7 terror attack. However, instead of capitalizing on the momentum from this diplomatic endeavor, the President chose to retreat to his Delaware beach home, a decision that has since become a focal point of criticism. Addressing the nation on Friday, Biden attempted to link the aid and support needed by Israel to that of Ukraine, drawing parallels between their respective struggles against aggressors seeking to obliterate their democracies. He likened Hamas’ actions to those of Russian President Vladimir Putin, emphasizing their shared objective of annihilating neighboring democracies. Despite the strong rhetoric, 50 Cent’s Instagram post captures a sentiment shared by many Americans—that in times of international crisis, the nation’s leader must be fully engaged, visible, and ready to take decisive action. The rapper’s explicit call for President Biden to ‘get up’ and tackle the crisis head-on serves as a powerful reminder of the urgency and gravity of the situation, urging the President to rise to the occasion and lead with conviction and urgency.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Intense Manhunt Underway: Nashville Police Chief’s Son Wanted for Attempted Murder of Two Officers</title><link href="/news/2023/10/23/Manhunt-Nashville/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Intense Manhunt Underway: Nashville Police Chief’s Son Wanted for Attempted Murder of Two Officers" /><published>2023-10-23T16:08:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-23T16:08:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/23/Manhunt-Nashville</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/23/Manhunt-Nashville/">&lt;p&gt;Tennessee law enforcement is in a race against time, searching for John C. Drake Jr., the 38-year-old estranged son of Metropolitan Nashville Police Chief John Drake. Drake Jr., with a lengthy criminal history and registered as a sex offender, is now the prime suspect in the shooting of two suburban police officers. The incident has spurred an intensive manhunt, putting local communities on high alert.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The officers, Ashely Boleyjack and Gregory Kern of La Vergne Police Department, are currently in stable condition after the brutal encounter on Saturday. Authorities are urging residents to remain vigilant as the search for Drake Jr. intensifies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The incident unfolded around 2:30 p.m. outside a Dollar General store in La Vergne, roughly 20 miles southeast of Nashville. During a “struggle” with the officers, who were investigating a stolen car, Drake Jr. is accused of pulling out a gun and shooting both officers — one in the back and the other multiple times. The Tennessee Bureau of Investigation has since issued warrants for his arrest on two counts of attempted first-degree murder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Drake Jr. is no stranger to law enforcement, with a criminal record spanning back to 2005, including dozens of prior arrests. His rap sheet reveals convictions for rape in 2009 and additional sex offenses over the past decade. Other charges include domestic violence, assault, unlawful possession of a weapon, evading arrest, and multiple violations of the state’s sex offender registry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite his estranged relationship and troubled past, Police Chief John Drake issued a statement urging his son to be held accountable. “He has not been a part of my life for quite some time. He now needs to be found and held accountable for his actions today,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The La Vergne Police Department has described Drake Jr. as a 5 feet, 11 inches tall male, with a muscular build, facial hair, and dreadlocks, last seen wearing a black T-shirt with a white hockey mask emblem and gray pants. He is considered armed and dangerous.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Authorities have lifted the shelter-in-place order in La Vergne but continue to ask the public to remain cautious and report any suspicious activity. Nashville Mayor Freddie O’Connell expressed his support for Chief Drake and the wounded officers, acknowledging the complex emotions involved when a family member is implicated in such a heinous act.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the manhunt enters its second day, the community and law enforcement alike hope for a swift resolution, ensuring justice for the injured officers and safety for the residents of Tennessee.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Tennessee law enforcement is in a race against time, searching for John C. Drake Jr., the 38-year-old estranged son of Metropolitan Nashville Police Chief John Drake. Drake Jr., with a lengthy criminal history and registered as a sex offender, is now the prime suspect in the shooting of two suburban police officers. The incident has spurred an intensive manhunt, putting local communities on high alert. The officers, Ashely Boleyjack and Gregory Kern of La Vergne Police Department, are currently in stable condition after the brutal encounter on Saturday. Authorities are urging residents to remain vigilant as the search for Drake Jr. intensifies. The incident unfolded around 2:30 p.m. outside a Dollar General store in La Vergne, roughly 20 miles southeast of Nashville. During a “struggle” with the officers, who were investigating a stolen car, Drake Jr. is accused of pulling out a gun and shooting both officers — one in the back and the other multiple times. The Tennessee Bureau of Investigation has since issued warrants for his arrest on two counts of attempted first-degree murder. Drake Jr. is no stranger to law enforcement, with a criminal record spanning back to 2005, including dozens of prior arrests. His rap sheet reveals convictions for rape in 2009 and additional sex offenses over the past decade. Other charges include domestic violence, assault, unlawful possession of a weapon, evading arrest, and multiple violations of the state’s sex offender registry. Despite his estranged relationship and troubled past, Police Chief John Drake issued a statement urging his son to be held accountable. “He has not been a part of my life for quite some time. He now needs to be found and held accountable for his actions today,” he said. The La Vergne Police Department has described Drake Jr. as a 5 feet, 11 inches tall male, with a muscular build, facial hair, and dreadlocks, last seen wearing a black T-shirt with a white hockey mask emblem and gray pants. He is considered armed and dangerous. Authorities have lifted the shelter-in-place order in La Vergne but continue to ask the public to remain cautious and report any suspicious activity. Nashville Mayor Freddie O’Connell expressed his support for Chief Drake and the wounded officers, acknowledging the complex emotions involved when a family member is implicated in such a heinous act. As the manhunt enters its second day, the community and law enforcement alike hope for a swift resolution, ensuring justice for the injured officers and safety for the residents of Tennessee.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump Dominates GOP Primary Race, Leaving DeSantis in the Dust</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/23/Trump-Primary-Lead/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump Dominates GOP Primary Race, Leaving DeSantis in the Dust" /><published>2023-10-23T15:04:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-23T15:04:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/23/Trump-Primary-Lead</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/23/Trump-Primary-Lead/">&lt;p&gt;Former President Donald Trump has not just maintained but significantly bolstered his leading position, boasting a double-digit increase in support since June. This comes amidst a series of legal challenges and his conspicuous absence from the initial two GOP primary debates. In contrast, his primary rival, Florida Governor Ron DeSantis, is facing a downward spiral, losing support rapidly, according to the latest data from a USA TODAY/Suffolk University Poll.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The survey paints a clear picture: Trump has successfully captivated the majority of Republican voters, with 58 percent throwing their weight behind him, marking a robust ten-point climb since June. DeSantis, on the other hand, finds himself lagging substantially, trailing by a staggering 46 points at 12 percent support — a sharp 11-point decrease from his 23 percent standing in June.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Former South Carolina Governor Nikki Haley is closely tailing DeSantis, holding 11 percent of the support, and displaying a positive trajectory with a seven-point leap since June.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The poll, conducted between October 17-20 with a sample of 1,000 registered voters, comes with a margin of error of +/- 3.1 percent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DeSantis, undeterred, is pressing on with his comprehensive tour of Iowa’s counties, aiming to bolster his presence in this crucial early voting state set to cast its votes on January 15. However, the RealClearPolitics average of polls indicates that DeSantis is up against a tough challenge, trailing Trump in Iowa by an average of 33 percent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This development adds to the pressure on DeSantis, who has been on the receiving end of Trump’s sharp critique. Trump recently remarked on DeSantis’s dwindling poll numbers, labeling them as that of a “wounded bird falling from the sky” and prognosticating DeSantis’s imminent exit from the race due to financial constraints.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump’s statement, “After having single handily gotten him elected Governor, with no thanks or glory, it has been a beautiful thing to watch,” adds a layer of personal animosity to the political rivalry, setting the stage for an intense and unpredictable GOP primary race. As the political landscape continues to evolve, all eyes remain on these two dominant figures, eagerly awaiting the next development in this high-stakes political drama.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Former President Donald Trump has not just maintained but significantly bolstered his leading position, boasting a double-digit increase in support since June. This comes amidst a series of legal challenges and his conspicuous absence from the initial two GOP primary debates. In contrast, his primary rival, Florida Governor Ron DeSantis, is facing a downward spiral, losing support rapidly, according to the latest data from a USA TODAY/Suffolk University Poll. The survey paints a clear picture: Trump has successfully captivated the majority of Republican voters, with 58 percent throwing their weight behind him, marking a robust ten-point climb since June. DeSantis, on the other hand, finds himself lagging substantially, trailing by a staggering 46 points at 12 percent support — a sharp 11-point decrease from his 23 percent standing in June. Former South Carolina Governor Nikki Haley is closely tailing DeSantis, holding 11 percent of the support, and displaying a positive trajectory with a seven-point leap since June. The poll, conducted between October 17-20 with a sample of 1,000 registered voters, comes with a margin of error of +/- 3.1 percent. DeSantis, undeterred, is pressing on with his comprehensive tour of Iowa’s counties, aiming to bolster his presence in this crucial early voting state set to cast its votes on January 15. However, the RealClearPolitics average of polls indicates that DeSantis is up against a tough challenge, trailing Trump in Iowa by an average of 33 percent. This development adds to the pressure on DeSantis, who has been on the receiving end of Trump’s sharp critique. Trump recently remarked on DeSantis’s dwindling poll numbers, labeling them as that of a “wounded bird falling from the sky” and prognosticating DeSantis’s imminent exit from the race due to financial constraints. Trump’s statement, “After having single handily gotten him elected Governor, with no thanks or glory, it has been a beautiful thing to watch,” adds a layer of personal animosity to the political rivalry, setting the stage for an intense and unpredictable GOP primary race. As the political landscape continues to evolve, all eyes remain on these two dominant figures, eagerly awaiting the next development in this high-stakes political drama.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Canada on the Brink: The Controversial Push to Offer Medically Assisted Dying for Drug Addicts</title><link href="/news/2023/10/23/Canada-Medical-Assistance-Dying-Drug-Addiction/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Canada on the Brink: The Controversial Push to Offer Medically Assisted Dying for Drug Addicts" /><published>2023-10-23T13:49:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-23T13:49:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/23/Canada-Medical-Assistance-Dying-Drug-Addiction</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/23/Canada-Medical-Assistance-Dying-Drug-Addiction/">&lt;p&gt;As spring draws near, Canada finds itself at a crossroads, with a controversial decision on the horizon that could legalize medically assisted dying for individuals grappling with drug addiction. The country’s Medical Assistance in Dying (MAID) law is set for an expansion, sparking widespread debate and concern over the potential repercussions of such a groundbreaking shift in policy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Toronto Star reports that this legal amendment would include those whose sole medical condition is mental illness, enveloping substance use disorders under its umbrella. This change, set to take effect this March, has prompted the formation of a special parliamentary committee on MAID to meticulously examine the impending law.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Presently, eligibility for MAID is confined to those suffering from a severe disability or illness, resulting in an advanced state of irreversible decline and enduring pain, either physically or psychologically. However, mental illness has remained an exception, until now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With this change, a particular group of Canadians stands on the precipice of accessing MAID in just a few months. This has given rise to urgent discussions and deliberations, with conservative MP Ed Fast expressing deep concerns. He highlights the lack of medical consensus on whether those with mental illnesses should be granted access to MAID, cautioning against normalizing “assisted death as an alternative treatment option.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fast prompts the nation to reflect: “Have we gone too far and too fast with Canada’s assisted suicide program? Will we evolve into a culture of death as the preferred option for those who suffer from mental illness, or will we choose life?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These sentiments are echoed by others who bring attention to instances where individuals have sought MAID due to dire circumstances like low income and insufficient housing, further complicating the debate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Supporters of extending MAID to those with mental illnesses argue that the law will incorporate strict safeguards to prevent misuse. Addressing concerns, former justice minister David Lametti assured Canadians last year that the process won’t be as simple as “walking off the street” to seek medically assisted suicide during times of depression.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Following the committee’s extensive review, its final report in February upheld the decision to expand MAID to cases involving mental illness. However, it emphasized the need for stringent oversight to ensure a safe and proper implementation, highlighting the delicate balance Canada must strike as it navigates this ethical minefield.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the nation awaits the committee’s final decision, the discourse surrounding medically assisted dying and drug addiction continues to intensify, underscoring the need for a thoughtful and compassionate approach to this complex issue.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">As spring draws near, Canada finds itself at a crossroads, with a controversial decision on the horizon that could legalize medically assisted dying for individuals grappling with drug addiction. The country’s Medical Assistance in Dying (MAID) law is set for an expansion, sparking widespread debate and concern over the potential repercussions of such a groundbreaking shift in policy. The Toronto Star reports that this legal amendment would include those whose sole medical condition is mental illness, enveloping substance use disorders under its umbrella. This change, set to take effect this March, has prompted the formation of a special parliamentary committee on MAID to meticulously examine the impending law. Presently, eligibility for MAID is confined to those suffering from a severe disability or illness, resulting in an advanced state of irreversible decline and enduring pain, either physically or psychologically. However, mental illness has remained an exception, until now. With this change, a particular group of Canadians stands on the precipice of accessing MAID in just a few months. This has given rise to urgent discussions and deliberations, with conservative MP Ed Fast expressing deep concerns. He highlights the lack of medical consensus on whether those with mental illnesses should be granted access to MAID, cautioning against normalizing “assisted death as an alternative treatment option.” Fast prompts the nation to reflect: “Have we gone too far and too fast with Canada’s assisted suicide program? Will we evolve into a culture of death as the preferred option for those who suffer from mental illness, or will we choose life?” These sentiments are echoed by others who bring attention to instances where individuals have sought MAID due to dire circumstances like low income and insufficient housing, further complicating the debate. Supporters of extending MAID to those with mental illnesses argue that the law will incorporate strict safeguards to prevent misuse. Addressing concerns, former justice minister David Lametti assured Canadians last year that the process won’t be as simple as “walking off the street” to seek medically assisted suicide during times of depression. Following the committee’s extensive review, its final report in February upheld the decision to expand MAID to cases involving mental illness. However, it emphasized the need for stringent oversight to ensure a safe and proper implementation, highlighting the delicate balance Canada must strike as it navigates this ethical minefield. As the nation awaits the committee’s final decision, the discourse surrounding medically assisted dying and drug addiction continues to intensify, underscoring the need for a thoughtful and compassionate approach to this complex issue.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Defending Democracy: Democrats’ Fear-Driven Attempt to Bar Trump from Colorado’s Ballot</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/23/Trumps-Battle-in-Colorado/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Defending Democracy: Democrats’ Fear-Driven Attempt to Bar Trump from Colorado’s Ballot" /><published>2023-10-23T12:30:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-23T12:30:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/23/Trumps-Battle-in-Colorado</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/23/Trumps-Battle-in-Colorado/">&lt;p&gt;In a significant development that has captured the nation’s attention, a Colorado judge has opted not to dismiss a lawsuit that aims to prevent Donald Trump from securing a spot on the Colorado ballot for the 2024 presidential election. This pivotal ruling by Judge Sarah Wallace, appointed by a Democrat governor, has sparked an intense debate about the state of our democracy and what appears to be a concerted effort to silence one of the most influential political figures in recent history.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump, who currently tops the polls for the Republican presidential nomination, is now contending with legal challenges in numerous states regarding his alleged role in the events of January 6, 2021. These lawsuits, invoking the Fourteenth Amendment, seek to bar individuals who have “engaged in insurrection” from holding public office. Importantly, it must be noted that Trump has not been convicted of insurrection and was acquitted by the U.S. Senate of charges related to insurrection, a fact that his supporters emphasize in defense of his candidacy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Colorado court’s decision, while not a definitive judgment on the matter, sends a troubling message about the current state of democratic values in America. Advocates for Trump, as well as supporters of free speech and fair elections, are expressing grave concerns that this is a calculated attempt by Democrats to manipulate the election process and stifle a strong adversary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Allowing this lawsuit to move forward, Wallace is eroding the foundations of our democratic system, casting doubts on the impartiality of the judiciary, and establishing a precedent that endangers the rights of all Americans to freely participate in the electoral process. The Trump campaign has presented a strong case that his actions on January 6 were tied to “public issues,” warranting protection under the First Amendment. However, Wallace’s decision seems to dismiss this critical aspect of the case, raising questions about her impartiality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Critics contend that this lawsuit, supported by Citizens for Responsibility and Ethics in Washington (CREW), a nonprofit organization with connections to Democratic strategist David Brock, represents nothing short of a partisan assault. Despite claiming to be bipartisan, CREW has faced criticism for its apparent bias against conservatives and Republicans. The involvement of Brock’s network of organizations, which have a history of aligning with Democratic causes, further undermines the credibility of the lawsuit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump’s legal team is expressing confidence that justice will ultimately prevail, stating their belief that the decision will be overturned, whether at the Colorado Supreme Court or the U.S. Supreme Court. The Trump campaign spokesperson underscored that preventing the leading candidate for President of the United States from appearing on the ballot is “simply wrong and un-American.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the legal battle unfolds, it is imperative for Americans of all political stripes to unite in defense of democracy, free speech, and the integrity of our electoral process. The effort to silence Trump represents a direct challenge to these fundamental principles, and it is a fight that demands our attention and action. The future of our nation hangs in the balance, and the outcome of this battle will define the state of American democracy for years to come.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a significant development that has captured the nation’s attention, a Colorado judge has opted not to dismiss a lawsuit that aims to prevent Donald Trump from securing a spot on the Colorado ballot for the 2024 presidential election. This pivotal ruling by Judge Sarah Wallace, appointed by a Democrat governor, has sparked an intense debate about the state of our democracy and what appears to be a concerted effort to silence one of the most influential political figures in recent history. Trump, who currently tops the polls for the Republican presidential nomination, is now contending with legal challenges in numerous states regarding his alleged role in the events of January 6, 2021. These lawsuits, invoking the Fourteenth Amendment, seek to bar individuals who have “engaged in insurrection” from holding public office. Importantly, it must be noted that Trump has not been convicted of insurrection and was acquitted by the U.S. Senate of charges related to insurrection, a fact that his supporters emphasize in defense of his candidacy. The Colorado court’s decision, while not a definitive judgment on the matter, sends a troubling message about the current state of democratic values in America. Advocates for Trump, as well as supporters of free speech and fair elections, are expressing grave concerns that this is a calculated attempt by Democrats to manipulate the election process and stifle a strong adversary. Allowing this lawsuit to move forward, Wallace is eroding the foundations of our democratic system, casting doubts on the impartiality of the judiciary, and establishing a precedent that endangers the rights of all Americans to freely participate in the electoral process. The Trump campaign has presented a strong case that his actions on January 6 were tied to “public issues,” warranting protection under the First Amendment. However, Wallace’s decision seems to dismiss this critical aspect of the case, raising questions about her impartiality. Critics contend that this lawsuit, supported by Citizens for Responsibility and Ethics in Washington (CREW), a nonprofit organization with connections to Democratic strategist David Brock, represents nothing short of a partisan assault. Despite claiming to be bipartisan, CREW has faced criticism for its apparent bias against conservatives and Republicans. The involvement of Brock’s network of organizations, which have a history of aligning with Democratic causes, further undermines the credibility of the lawsuit. Trump’s legal team is expressing confidence that justice will ultimately prevail, stating their belief that the decision will be overturned, whether at the Colorado Supreme Court or the U.S. Supreme Court. The Trump campaign spokesperson underscored that preventing the leading candidate for President of the United States from appearing on the ballot is “simply wrong and un-American.” As the legal battle unfolds, it is imperative for Americans of all political stripes to unite in defense of democracy, free speech, and the integrity of our electoral process. The effort to silence Trump represents a direct challenge to these fundamental principles, and it is a fight that demands our attention and action. The future of our nation hangs in the balance, and the outcome of this battle will define the state of American democracy for years to come.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Upholding Parental Rights: The Necessity of Notification in Schools</title><link href="/news/2023/10/23/Parental-Rights-and-Transgender-Notification/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Upholding Parental Rights: The Necessity of Notification in Schools" /><published>2023-10-23T11:15:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-23T11:15:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/23/Parental-Rights-and-Transgender-Notification</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/23/Parental-Rights-and-Transgender-Notification/">&lt;p&gt;In the realm of education and parental rights, a storm is brewing in the Chino Valley Unified School District (CVUSD) in Southern California. A recent policy requiring schools to notify parents if their child identifies as transgender has come under legal fire, leading to a temporary blockage of parts of the policy by a Superior Court Judge. This situation has triggered an important conversation about the balance between protecting students’ privacy and upholding the fundamental rights of parents in the United States, a topic of paramount concern for many conservative Republicans.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Implemented in July, the CVUSD policy is built on the premise that parents have an inherent right to know about and be involved in all significant aspects of their children’s lives, including their gender identity. California Attorney General Rob Bonta, however, swiftly took legal action against the district, alleging that the policy discriminates against LGBTQ students and infringes on their privacy rights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Judge Michael A. Sachs of the San Bernardino County Superior Court granted a preliminary injunction to halt parts of the policy, conservatives argue that this decision overlooks the essential role of parents in a child’s life, especially during pivotal moments such as grappling with gender identity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For many parents and advocates of the policy, the issue at hand is not about discriminating against LGBTQ students; it’s about preserving the sanctity of the parent-child relationship and ensuring that parents are not kept in the dark about significant developments in their children’s lives. Parents are, after all, the primary caregivers and have a legal and moral obligation to look out for the welfare of their children. Being informed is a prerequisite to providing support, understanding, and love, something that every child, regardless of their gender identity, deserves from their parents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Critics of the judge’s decision argue that it represents a dangerous overreach of government into family life, eroding parental rights under the guise of protecting student privacy. They stress that the state should not and cannot replace the parent when it comes to matters of such personal importance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The need for parental notification becomes even more critical considering the lifelong implications of a child’s decision to transition. Medical interventions such as hormone therapies and surgeries have irreversible effects, and parents must be involved in making such life-altering decisions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conservatives also highlight the potential for schools to become environments of secrecy and mistrust, where students are encouraged to hide significant aspects of their lives from their parents. This not only undermines parental authority but also puts an undue burden on the child, who may be navigating complex feelings and emotions without the support of their family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this battle for parental rights, CVUSD stands as a champion of a belief held by many across the nation: that parents have the right, responsibility, and obligation to be intimately involved in their children’s lives, especially when it comes to something as profound as gender identity. As the legal proceedings continue, supporters of the policy are hopeful that parental rights will ultimately be upheld, ensuring that parents remain the primary caregivers and decision-makers in their children’s lives.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In the realm of education and parental rights, a storm is brewing in the Chino Valley Unified School District (CVUSD) in Southern California. A recent policy requiring schools to notify parents if their child identifies as transgender has come under legal fire, leading to a temporary blockage of parts of the policy by a Superior Court Judge. This situation has triggered an important conversation about the balance between protecting students’ privacy and upholding the fundamental rights of parents in the United States, a topic of paramount concern for many conservative Republicans. Implemented in July, the CVUSD policy is built on the premise that parents have an inherent right to know about and be involved in all significant aspects of their children’s lives, including their gender identity. California Attorney General Rob Bonta, however, swiftly took legal action against the district, alleging that the policy discriminates against LGBTQ students and infringes on their privacy rights. While Judge Michael A. Sachs of the San Bernardino County Superior Court granted a preliminary injunction to halt parts of the policy, conservatives argue that this decision overlooks the essential role of parents in a child’s life, especially during pivotal moments such as grappling with gender identity. For many parents and advocates of the policy, the issue at hand is not about discriminating against LGBTQ students; it’s about preserving the sanctity of the parent-child relationship and ensuring that parents are not kept in the dark about significant developments in their children’s lives. Parents are, after all, the primary caregivers and have a legal and moral obligation to look out for the welfare of their children. Being informed is a prerequisite to providing support, understanding, and love, something that every child, regardless of their gender identity, deserves from their parents. Critics of the judge’s decision argue that it represents a dangerous overreach of government into family life, eroding parental rights under the guise of protecting student privacy. They stress that the state should not and cannot replace the parent when it comes to matters of such personal importance. The need for parental notification becomes even more critical considering the lifelong implications of a child’s decision to transition. Medical interventions such as hormone therapies and surgeries have irreversible effects, and parents must be involved in making such life-altering decisions. Conservatives also highlight the potential for schools to become environments of secrecy and mistrust, where students are encouraged to hide significant aspects of their lives from their parents. This not only undermines parental authority but also puts an undue burden on the child, who may be navigating complex feelings and emotions without the support of their family. In this battle for parental rights, CVUSD stands as a champion of a belief held by many across the nation: that parents have the right, responsibility, and obligation to be intimately involved in their children’s lives, especially when it comes to something as profound as gender identity. As the legal proceedings continue, supporters of the policy are hopeful that parental rights will ultimately be upheld, ensuring that parents remain the primary caregivers and decision-makers in their children’s lives.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Navigating New Horizons: How AI is Reshaping the Book Industry</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/23/AI-Impact-on-Publishing/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Navigating New Horizons: How AI is Reshaping the Book Industry" /><published>2023-10-23T10:05:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-23T10:05:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/23/AI-Impact-on-Publishing</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/23/AI-Impact-on-Publishing/">&lt;p&gt;The introduction of ChatGPT and similar AI writing tools has sent ripples through various sectors, with the book industry being the latest to grapple with the ramifications of this technological advancement. The growing trend of AI-generated content has raised crucial questions about intellectual property, authorship, and the quality of computer-written books, highlighting a deep-seated insecurity within the literary world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During last week’s Frankfurt Book Fair—the largest of its kind globally—industry professionals expressed their concerns and sought answers to pressing questions. What happens to an author’s intellectual property in the age of AI? Who owns the rights to AI-generated content? How can this new form of content creation be integrated into existing value chains?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The potential of AI in the realm of writing is undeniable. With tools like ChatGPT, aspiring authors can now produce novels in a matter of days—a task that would traditionally take months, if not years. Amazon’s e-book self-publishing unit has seen a surge in titles listing ChatGPT as a co-author, although critics argue that the quality of these works leaves much to be desired.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prominent British author Salman Rushdie, during a rare public appearance since his near-fatal stabbing attack last year, shared his experience with AI writing tools. When asked to produce 300 words in Rushdie’s style, the result was “pure garbage,” he remarked, drawing laughter from the audience. “Anybody who has ever read 300 words of mine would immediately recognize that it could not possibly be by me.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite these shortcomings, some see potential in AI’s role in writing. German author and academic Jennifer Becker pointed out during a panel discussion that while AI-generated fiction is “still not that great,” there is room for collaborative use between humans and AI, although she does not foresee a future where AI autonomously takes over the writing process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Legal challenges are also on the horizon, as the industry tries to navigate the “grey area” of copyright ownership for AI-generated content. Last month, renowned authors including George RR Martin and Jodi Picoult filed a class-action lawsuit against OpenAI, accusing the company of copyright violation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the lines between human and computer-generated content blurring, efforts are being made to establish clearer guidelines. Amazon, for instance, now requires authors to disclose if their work includes AI-generated material when selling books through its self-publishing unit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the publishing industry ventures further into this uncharted territory, it faces a dual challenge: safeguarding the rights and integrity of human authors while exploring the potential benefits and innovations that AI can bring to the literary world.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">The introduction of ChatGPT and similar AI writing tools has sent ripples through various sectors, with the book industry being the latest to grapple with the ramifications of this technological advancement. The growing trend of AI-generated content has raised crucial questions about intellectual property, authorship, and the quality of computer-written books, highlighting a deep-seated insecurity within the literary world. During last week’s Frankfurt Book Fair—the largest of its kind globally—industry professionals expressed their concerns and sought answers to pressing questions. What happens to an author’s intellectual property in the age of AI? Who owns the rights to AI-generated content? How can this new form of content creation be integrated into existing value chains? The potential of AI in the realm of writing is undeniable. With tools like ChatGPT, aspiring authors can now produce novels in a matter of days—a task that would traditionally take months, if not years. Amazon’s e-book self-publishing unit has seen a surge in titles listing ChatGPT as a co-author, although critics argue that the quality of these works leaves much to be desired. Prominent British author Salman Rushdie, during a rare public appearance since his near-fatal stabbing attack last year, shared his experience with AI writing tools. When asked to produce 300 words in Rushdie’s style, the result was “pure garbage,” he remarked, drawing laughter from the audience. “Anybody who has ever read 300 words of mine would immediately recognize that it could not possibly be by me.” Despite these shortcomings, some see potential in AI’s role in writing. German author and academic Jennifer Becker pointed out during a panel discussion that while AI-generated fiction is “still not that great,” there is room for collaborative use between humans and AI, although she does not foresee a future where AI autonomously takes over the writing process. Legal challenges are also on the horizon, as the industry tries to navigate the “grey area” of copyright ownership for AI-generated content. Last month, renowned authors including George RR Martin and Jodi Picoult filed a class-action lawsuit against OpenAI, accusing the company of copyright violation. With the lines between human and computer-generated content blurring, efforts are being made to establish clearer guidelines. Amazon, for instance, now requires authors to disclose if their work includes AI-generated material when selling books through its self-publishing unit. As the publishing industry ventures further into this uncharted territory, it faces a dual challenge: safeguarding the rights and integrity of human authors while exploring the potential benefits and innovations that AI can bring to the literary world.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Clashing Titans: Jon Stewart’s China Stance Lead to Show Cancellation on Apple TV+</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/23/Jon-Stewart-Apple-TV-Show-Cancellation/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Clashing Titans: Jon Stewart’s China Stance Lead to Show Cancellation on Apple TV+" /><published>2023-10-23T09:01:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-23T09:01:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/23/Jon-Stewart-Apple-TV-Show-Cancellation</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/23/Jon-Stewart-Apple-TV-Show-Cancellation/">&lt;p&gt;The anticipated success story of “The Problem with Jon Stewart” on Apple TV+ took an unexpected turn as the show faces cancellation, not merely due to dwindling viewership, but reportedly stemming from creative clashes between Jon Stewart and Apple executives. The show, initially bathed in a flood of media attention, promised to bring Stewart’s characteristic wit and bold commentary back to the screen. Yet, the viewership did not meet expectations, plummeting to as low as 40,000 U.S. homes by the fifth episode.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the low ratings tell only part of the story. Reports from The New York Times and CNN reveal internal tensions between Stewart and Apple, centering around the handling of sensitive topics such as China, Israel, and artificial intelligence. While Apple granted Stewart creative control, this control was seemingly put to the test as these controversial subjects came into play.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;China stands out as a particularly thorny issue for Apple, a company that garners almost a fifth of its sales from the country and relies heavily on its manufacturing capabilities. Stewart’s inclination to delve into subjects that could ruffle feathers at Apple headquarters marks a divergence from the company’s usual approach to sensitive political topics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the rocky journey, “The Problem with Jon Stewart” did enjoy moments of popularity, initially ranking as the No. 1 unscripted series on Apple TV+ during its debut month. Stewart, known for his leftist views, occasionally stepped out of the expected narrative, challenging topics like the Biden family’s business dealings and the censorship surrounding the Wuhan coronavirus lab leak theory. However, these moments of divergence were not enough to sustain the show’s viewership or resolve the internal disputes over show content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the news of the show’s cancellation circulates, it raises questions about creative freedom in the face of corporate interests, the responsibility of platforms hosting political commentary, and the future of bold, unapologetic voices like Stewart’s in the mainstream media. Only time will tell how this cancellation impacts Stewart’s career and the broader landscape of political talk shows, but one thing is clear—the clash between creative integrity and corporate caution remains a central tension in today’s entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">The anticipated success story of “The Problem with Jon Stewart” on Apple TV+ took an unexpected turn as the show faces cancellation, not merely due to dwindling viewership, but reportedly stemming from creative clashes between Jon Stewart and Apple executives. The show, initially bathed in a flood of media attention, promised to bring Stewart’s characteristic wit and bold commentary back to the screen. Yet, the viewership did not meet expectations, plummeting to as low as 40,000 U.S. homes by the fifth episode. However, the low ratings tell only part of the story. Reports from The New York Times and CNN reveal internal tensions between Stewart and Apple, centering around the handling of sensitive topics such as China, Israel, and artificial intelligence. While Apple granted Stewart creative control, this control was seemingly put to the test as these controversial subjects came into play. China stands out as a particularly thorny issue for Apple, a company that garners almost a fifth of its sales from the country and relies heavily on its manufacturing capabilities. Stewart’s inclination to delve into subjects that could ruffle feathers at Apple headquarters marks a divergence from the company’s usual approach to sensitive political topics. Despite the rocky journey, “The Problem with Jon Stewart” did enjoy moments of popularity, initially ranking as the No. 1 unscripted series on Apple TV+ during its debut month. Stewart, known for his leftist views, occasionally stepped out of the expected narrative, challenging topics like the Biden family’s business dealings and the censorship surrounding the Wuhan coronavirus lab leak theory. However, these moments of divergence were not enough to sustain the show’s viewership or resolve the internal disputes over show content. As the news of the show’s cancellation circulates, it raises questions about creative freedom in the face of corporate interests, the responsibility of platforms hosting political commentary, and the future of bold, unapologetic voices like Stewart’s in the mainstream media. Only time will tell how this cancellation impacts Stewart’s career and the broader landscape of political talk shows, but one thing is clear—the clash between creative integrity and corporate caution remains a central tension in today’s entertainment industry.</summary></entry></feed>