<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-09-10T11:13:44-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/09/10/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-09-10T11:13:44-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-10T11:13:44-04:00</updated><id>/2023/09/10/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/10/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Tim Scott Denounces California Bill - Calls Punishing Non-Affirming Parents ‘Evil’</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/10/Tim-Scott-Reacts/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tim Scott Denounces California Bill - Calls Punishing Non-Affirming Parents ‘Evil’" /><published>2023-09-10T11:06:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-10T11:06:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/10/Tim-Scott-Reacts</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/10/Tim-Scott-Reacts/">&lt;p&gt;In a fierce rebuke of California’s recent legislative move, Republican presidential candidate Tim Scott labeled a bill penalizing parents who do not affirm their transgender children as “evil.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The contentious bill, AB 957, freshly passed by the California State Assembly, has come under intense scrutiny. This legislation obliges judges in child custody cases to evaluate if a parent has recognized and affirmed their child’s transgender identity. The core proposition of the bill originally intended courts to see whether parents were gender-affirming. A subsequent amendment further tightened these stipulations. It laid down that to be adjudged as fit parents in a court of law, acknowledgment and affirmation of a child’s gender identity become essential.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tim Scott, a stalwart defender of parental rights, voiced his profound dismay at this measure. He articulated, “&lt;em&gt;The radical Left is on a mission to make parents less important. They believe your kids belong to them.&lt;/em&gt;” He further pledged his unwavering commitment to reversing this narrative by emphatically stating, “&lt;em&gt;I will fight back, put parents back in charge, and shield the next generation of children from such overreach.&lt;/em&gt;”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Previously, Senator Scott unveiled an extensive plan aimed at safeguarding children and empowering families. Central to his “Empower Parents Plan” is the establishment of a robust family-first culture. Scott, the Senate’s only Black Republican, is resolute in championing traditional values. He stresses the significance of allowing children to grow naturally, free from societal pressures about their gender identities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to this, Scott demands that parents be granted unrestricted access to their children’s educational content, ensuring they are privy to all materials their children are exposed to in schools. A fervent advocate for school choice, Scott envisions weakening the stranglehold of teachers’ unions. He ardently supports granting parents a more substantial say in choosing the educational path best suited for their children, whether that’s public, private, charter, STEM schools, or homeschooling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a succinct summation of his educational vision, Scott declared his intent to “&lt;em&gt;replace indoctrination with education. ABC, not CRT.&lt;/em&gt;” With unwavering dedication to parental rights and a clear vision for America’s educational future, Senator Tim Scott continues to shape the discourse on this critical issue.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a fierce rebuke of California’s recent legislative move, Republican presidential candidate Tim Scott labeled a bill penalizing parents who do not affirm their transgender children as “evil.” The contentious bill, AB 957, freshly passed by the California State Assembly, has come under intense scrutiny. This legislation obliges judges in child custody cases to evaluate if a parent has recognized and affirmed their child’s transgender identity. The core proposition of the bill originally intended courts to see whether parents were gender-affirming. A subsequent amendment further tightened these stipulations. It laid down that to be adjudged as fit parents in a court of law, acknowledgment and affirmation of a child’s gender identity become essential. Tim Scott, a stalwart defender of parental rights, voiced his profound dismay at this measure. He articulated, “The radical Left is on a mission to make parents less important. They believe your kids belong to them.” He further pledged his unwavering commitment to reversing this narrative by emphatically stating, “I will fight back, put parents back in charge, and shield the next generation of children from such overreach.” Previously, Senator Scott unveiled an extensive plan aimed at safeguarding children and empowering families. Central to his “Empower Parents Plan” is the establishment of a robust family-first culture. Scott, the Senate’s only Black Republican, is resolute in championing traditional values. He stresses the significance of allowing children to grow naturally, free from societal pressures about their gender identities. In addition to this, Scott demands that parents be granted unrestricted access to their children’s educational content, ensuring they are privy to all materials their children are exposed to in schools. A fervent advocate for school choice, Scott envisions weakening the stranglehold of teachers’ unions. He ardently supports granting parents a more substantial say in choosing the educational path best suited for their children, whether that’s public, private, charter, STEM schools, or homeschooling. In a succinct summation of his educational vision, Scott declared his intent to “replace indoctrination with education. ABC, not CRT.” With unwavering dedication to parental rights and a clear vision for America’s educational future, Senator Tim Scott continues to shape the discourse on this critical issue.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Rapper’s Lyrics Lead to Arrest - Kenjuan McDaniel Faces Murder Charges</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/10/Rapper-Charged-With-Murder/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rapper’s Lyrics Lead to Arrest - Kenjuan McDaniel Faces Murder Charges" /><published>2023-09-10T10:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-10T10:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/10/Rapper-Charged-With-Murder</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/10/Rapper-Charged-With-Murder/">&lt;p&gt;In a shocking twist of events, Nevada-based rapper Kenjuan McDaniel is currently behind bars after being arrested on a murder charge. The Las Vegas Metropolitan Police Department claims that McDaniel’s own song lyrics serve as a confession to the crime.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Song that Spoke Too Much&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On August 29, the 25-year-old rapper was apprehended and is now facing an open murder charge involving a deadly weapon. The charge stems from a crime that occurred in 2021, where 32-year-old Randall Wallace was tragically shot dead in an apartment complex. It was previously noted that Wallace had been involved in a heated dispute with three then-unidentified individuals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;McDaniel’s song, “Fadee Free”, has been pinpointed by the authorities as the piece that contains incriminating evidence. Not only does the song, which was released on YouTube, allude to the homicide, but certain details highlighted in the lyrics weren’t public knowledge, making the police even more suspicious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Las Vegas Review-Journal unveiled a part of the police arrest report that dissects specific lyrics from “Fadee Free”. One particular line: “Brought it with that fire, hear that ‘ah’, see your body twitching,” was associated with Wallace’s unfortunate demise, especially given accounts of Wallace twitching before succumbing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another lyric, as highlighted by 8 News Now, reads: “Parked the car, doubled back on feet, the smartest way to slide.” The police found correlations between this line and the modus operandi of the murder. Additionally, McDaniel’s song allegedly includes a reference to a nickname familiar to Wallace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A High-Stakes Legal Battle Awaits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the preliminary hearing for McDaniel scheduled on September 14, the rapper’s fate hangs in the balance. His bail is currently set at a hefty $1 million, with mandated electronic monitoring, as indicated by the court records.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The case not only illuminates the dangerous line between art and real life but also prompts artists to ponder the implications of their work. As McDaniel’s story unfolds, the music industry and fans worldwide are left to grapple with the complexities of music’s power to both inspire and incriminate.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">In a shocking twist of events, Nevada-based rapper Kenjuan McDaniel is currently behind bars after being arrested on a murder charge. The Las Vegas Metropolitan Police Department claims that McDaniel’s own song lyrics serve as a confession to the crime. The Song that Spoke Too Much On August 29, the 25-year-old rapper was apprehended and is now facing an open murder charge involving a deadly weapon. The charge stems from a crime that occurred in 2021, where 32-year-old Randall Wallace was tragically shot dead in an apartment complex. It was previously noted that Wallace had been involved in a heated dispute with three then-unidentified individuals. McDaniel’s song, “Fadee Free”, has been pinpointed by the authorities as the piece that contains incriminating evidence. Not only does the song, which was released on YouTube, allude to the homicide, but certain details highlighted in the lyrics weren’t public knowledge, making the police even more suspicious. The Las Vegas Review-Journal unveiled a part of the police arrest report that dissects specific lyrics from “Fadee Free”. One particular line: “Brought it with that fire, hear that ‘ah’, see your body twitching,” was associated with Wallace’s unfortunate demise, especially given accounts of Wallace twitching before succumbing. Another lyric, as highlighted by 8 News Now, reads: “Parked the car, doubled back on feet, the smartest way to slide.” The police found correlations between this line and the modus operandi of the murder. Additionally, McDaniel’s song allegedly includes a reference to a nickname familiar to Wallace. A High-Stakes Legal Battle Awaits With the preliminary hearing for McDaniel scheduled on September 14, the rapper’s fate hangs in the balance. His bail is currently set at a hefty $1 million, with mandated electronic monitoring, as indicated by the court records. The case not only illuminates the dangerous line between art and real life but also prompts artists to ponder the implications of their work. As McDaniel’s story unfolds, the music industry and fans worldwide are left to grapple with the complexities of music’s power to both inspire and incriminate.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Unmasked - Scientist Admits to Sidestepping Whole Truth on Climate Study</title><link href="/news/2023/09/10/Climate-Truth-Revelation/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Unmasked - Scientist Admits to Sidestepping Whole Truth on Climate Study" /><published>2023-09-10T09:04:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-10T09:04:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/10/Climate-Truth-Revelation</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/10/Climate-Truth-Revelation/">&lt;p&gt;California’s wildfire crisis has long been a contentious point of debate. But now, the spotlight shines not on the fires themselves, but on the academic transparency surrounding research into their causes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Patrick T. Brown, a renowned earth and climate scientist from Johns Hopkins University, stirred the pot by admitting he “left out the full truth” in his research published in the distinguished science journal, Nature. He attributed this decision to pressures scientists face in getting their work published in esteemed journals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a candid confession, Brown shared that his study on the correlation between climate change and extreme wildfire behavior was “narrowly focused”. He concentrated predominantly on the human influence on wildfires, neglecting other crucial factors, such as poor forest management, that significantly impact fire behavior.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a compelling statement in The Free Press, Brown explained, “And the editors of these journals have made it abundantly clear… they want climate papers that support certain preapproved narratives—even when those narratives come at the expense of broader knowledge for society.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Brown’s revelations have significant implications. Not only do they raise questions about the objectivity of prestigious journals, but they also challenge the depth and authenticity of the discourse on climate change. As Brown himself emphasized, such skewed representations “misinform the public” and hinder the identification of real solutions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;California Assembly leader, James Gallagher, a Republican, was swift in his condemnation. He criticized liberals for manipulating data to fit a preconceived narrative, consequently pushing radical policies. “Patrick Brown is saying the quiet part out loud - liberals are cherry-picking data to fit an agenda and push radical policies that drive up the cost of living,” Gallagher conveyed to Fox News Digital.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Republican Assembly member Joe Patterson further stressed the issue, accusing Governor Gavin Newsom of pressuring scientists to ignore significant factors responsible for wildfires. “Republicans want scientists to consider all causes of massive wildfires, including climate change,” Patterson noted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As debate rages, one thing is crystal clear: the quest for academic and journalistic integrity in the climate debate remains as fiery as the wildfires themselves.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">California’s wildfire crisis has long been a contentious point of debate. But now, the spotlight shines not on the fires themselves, but on the academic transparency surrounding research into their causes. Patrick T. Brown, a renowned earth and climate scientist from Johns Hopkins University, stirred the pot by admitting he “left out the full truth” in his research published in the distinguished science journal, Nature. He attributed this decision to pressures scientists face in getting their work published in esteemed journals. In a candid confession, Brown shared that his study on the correlation between climate change and extreme wildfire behavior was “narrowly focused”. He concentrated predominantly on the human influence on wildfires, neglecting other crucial factors, such as poor forest management, that significantly impact fire behavior. In a compelling statement in The Free Press, Brown explained, “And the editors of these journals have made it abundantly clear… they want climate papers that support certain preapproved narratives—even when those narratives come at the expense of broader knowledge for society.” Brown’s revelations have significant implications. Not only do they raise questions about the objectivity of prestigious journals, but they also challenge the depth and authenticity of the discourse on climate change. As Brown himself emphasized, such skewed representations “misinform the public” and hinder the identification of real solutions. California Assembly leader, James Gallagher, a Republican, was swift in his condemnation. He criticized liberals for manipulating data to fit a preconceived narrative, consequently pushing radical policies. “Patrick Brown is saying the quiet part out loud - liberals are cherry-picking data to fit an agenda and push radical policies that drive up the cost of living,” Gallagher conveyed to Fox News Digital. Republican Assembly member Joe Patterson further stressed the issue, accusing Governor Gavin Newsom of pressuring scientists to ignore significant factors responsible for wildfires. “Republicans want scientists to consider all causes of massive wildfires, including climate change,” Patterson noted. As debate rages, one thing is crystal clear: the quest for academic and journalistic integrity in the climate debate remains as fiery as the wildfires themselves.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Unveiled - Cause of Death for Pee-wee Herman’s Paul Reubens</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/10/Reubens-Cause-of-Death/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Unveiled - Cause of Death for Pee-wee Herman’s Paul Reubens" /><published>2023-09-10T08:02:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-10T08:02:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/10/Reubens-Cause-of-Death</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/10/Reubens-Cause-of-Death/">&lt;p&gt;A month after the sorrowful news of Paul Reubens’ death at age 70, the world learns of the silent battle he endured. Reubens, globally celebrated for his portrayal of the lively Pee-wee Herman, fell to acute myelogenous leukemia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This form of leukemia, detailed by the National Cancer Institute as a cancer of the blood and bone marrow, stands as the most common acute leukemia afflicting adults. The disclosure surprised many, given Reubens’ private struggle with the illness for years. His representative confirmed the specifics of his demise to Fox News Digital.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Silent Struggle&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Reubens’ passing last month left countless fans in mourning, this recent revelation brings added gravity to his legacy. “Paul bravely and privately fought cancer for years with his trademark tenacity and wit,” his representative expressed in a heartfelt statement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reubens’ own words mirrored this sentiment. In a heartfelt note shared posthumously on his social platforms, the actor conveyed regret for not unveiling his health challenges sooner and accentuated his profound gratitude towards his fans, friends, and supporters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Legacy Beyond Entertainment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With this newly surfaced information, many reminisce about the joy and mirth Reubens introduced into their lives, both as Pee-wee Herman and in his diverse roles. As the world acknowledged him for his artistic brilliance, an increased admiration has emerged for his tenacity and grace in navigating personal adversities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, in a touching request, Reubens asked sympathizers to commemorate his late parents, Judy and Milton Rubenfeld, by endorsing organizations active in cancer research, as well as dementia and Alzheimer’s care.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As admirers and contemporaries reconcile with this revelation, a collective sentiment resonates: Paul Reubens was not merely an entertainment legend but also a beacon of resilience, courage, and unwavering strength.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">A month after the sorrowful news of Paul Reubens’ death at age 70, the world learns of the silent battle he endured. Reubens, globally celebrated for his portrayal of the lively Pee-wee Herman, fell to acute myelogenous leukemia. This form of leukemia, detailed by the National Cancer Institute as a cancer of the blood and bone marrow, stands as the most common acute leukemia afflicting adults. The disclosure surprised many, given Reubens’ private struggle with the illness for years. His representative confirmed the specifics of his demise to Fox News Digital. Silent Struggle While Reubens’ passing last month left countless fans in mourning, this recent revelation brings added gravity to his legacy. “Paul bravely and privately fought cancer for years with his trademark tenacity and wit,” his representative expressed in a heartfelt statement. Reubens’ own words mirrored this sentiment. In a heartfelt note shared posthumously on his social platforms, the actor conveyed regret for not unveiling his health challenges sooner and accentuated his profound gratitude towards his fans, friends, and supporters. A Legacy Beyond Entertainment With this newly surfaced information, many reminisce about the joy and mirth Reubens introduced into their lives, both as Pee-wee Herman and in his diverse roles. As the world acknowledged him for his artistic brilliance, an increased admiration has emerged for his tenacity and grace in navigating personal adversities. Furthermore, in a touching request, Reubens asked sympathizers to commemorate his late parents, Judy and Milton Rubenfeld, by endorsing organizations active in cancer research, as well as dementia and Alzheimer’s care. As admirers and contemporaries reconcile with this revelation, a collective sentiment resonates: Paul Reubens was not merely an entertainment legend but also a beacon of resilience, courage, and unwavering strength.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">McConnell’s Leadership Under Fire - Calls Mount for Change at the Top</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/10/McConnell-Leadership-Critique/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="McConnell’s Leadership Under Fire - Calls Mount for Change at the Top" /><published>2023-09-10T07:02:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-10T07:02:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/10/McConnell-Leadership-Critique</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/10/McConnell-Leadership-Critique/">&lt;p&gt;Tensions are rising within the Republican ranks of the Senate. At the center of this storm is Senate Minority Leader Mitch McConnell (R-KY), facing mounting criticism over his leadership style and tactics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The latest salvo came from Sen. Mike Lee (R-UT) who, citing a Wall Street Journal opinion piece by Kimberly Strassel, expressed concerns over McConnell’s alleged collaboration with Senate Majority Leader Chuck Schumer (D-NY) to force the House’s hand in approving $24 billion in aid to Ukraine. Strassel highlighted McConnell’s eagerness to align with Schumer to “ram the whole package down the House’s throat.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lee’s criticism of McConnell is sharp and direct. He bemoans the Senate Republican leadership’s inclination to support legislation heavily favored by Democrats, which ends up creating rifts within the Republican caucus. Lee’s sentiment was underscored by his statement, &lt;em&gt;“With Republicans like these, who needs Democrats? We need new leadership. Republicans nationwide have grown tired of Senate Republican leadership supporting bills that unite Democrats while sharply dividing Republicans.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Health concerns compound the doubts around McConnell’s leadership. With two recent incidents where the 81-year-old Senator appeared to momentarily freeze, questions about his health have amplified. Recent findings from an Economist/YouGov survey underline this concern, with a majority of Americans believing that McConnell’s age and health could be hampering his leadership capabilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lee isn’t alone in this chorus for change. Sen. Josh Hawley (R-MO) pointedly mentioned that McConnell was “not my choice for leader,” emphasizing the need for fresh leadership. Even Sen. Rand Paul (R-KY), bringing his medical expertise to the table, suggested that McConnell might have shown symptoms of a “focal neologic event” during one of his recent episodes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With a growing number of Senate Republicans voicing their discontent, it remains to be seen if the tide will turn against McConnell or if he can weather this storm and retain his leadership position. For now, the Republican party appears to be at a critical crossroads, determining the direction they wish to take in the coming years.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Tensions are rising within the Republican ranks of the Senate. At the center of this storm is Senate Minority Leader Mitch McConnell (R-KY), facing mounting criticism over his leadership style and tactics. The latest salvo came from Sen. Mike Lee (R-UT) who, citing a Wall Street Journal opinion piece by Kimberly Strassel, expressed concerns over McConnell’s alleged collaboration with Senate Majority Leader Chuck Schumer (D-NY) to force the House’s hand in approving $24 billion in aid to Ukraine. Strassel highlighted McConnell’s eagerness to align with Schumer to “ram the whole package down the House’s throat.” Lee’s criticism of McConnell is sharp and direct. He bemoans the Senate Republican leadership’s inclination to support legislation heavily favored by Democrats, which ends up creating rifts within the Republican caucus. Lee’s sentiment was underscored by his statement, “With Republicans like these, who needs Democrats? We need new leadership. Republicans nationwide have grown tired of Senate Republican leadership supporting bills that unite Democrats while sharply dividing Republicans.” Health concerns compound the doubts around McConnell’s leadership. With two recent incidents where the 81-year-old Senator appeared to momentarily freeze, questions about his health have amplified. Recent findings from an Economist/YouGov survey underline this concern, with a majority of Americans believing that McConnell’s age and health could be hampering his leadership capabilities. Lee isn’t alone in this chorus for change. Sen. Josh Hawley (R-MO) pointedly mentioned that McConnell was “not my choice for leader,” emphasizing the need for fresh leadership. Even Sen. Rand Paul (R-KY), bringing his medical expertise to the table, suggested that McConnell might have shown symptoms of a “focal neologic event” during one of his recent episodes. With a growing number of Senate Republicans voicing their discontent, it remains to be seen if the tide will turn against McConnell or if he can weather this storm and retain his leadership position. For now, the Republican party appears to be at a critical crossroads, determining the direction they wish to take in the coming years.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump Speaks Out - ‘COVID Hysteria’ Resurfaces Amid Election Fever</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/10/Trump-COVID-Hysteria/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump Speaks Out - ‘COVID Hysteria’ Resurfaces Amid Election Fever" /><published>2023-09-10T06:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-10T06:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/10/Trump-COVID-Hysteria</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/10/Trump-COVID-Hysteria/">&lt;p&gt;In a hard-hitting speech delivered to the South Dakota GOP convention, former President Donald Trump voiced concerns over the resurgence of “COVID hysteria.” A believer in political maneuvering, Trump suggested the return of heightened pandemic precautions may be linked to the upcoming elections, urging Republicans to be vigilant against potential overreaches.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Addressing a rapt audience and broadcast live on Newsmax, Trump stated, &lt;em&gt;“Congressional Republicans should also stop the Biden administration from bringing back COVID mandates, lockdowns, and restrictions of any kind, cutting off the money.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;South Dakota, under the leadership of GOP Gov. Kristi Noem, stands strong against such restrictions, a fact not lost on Trump. The former president lauded Noem’s approach, highlighting the freedoms enjoyed by South Dakotans compared to residents in other states. Gov. Noem’s endorsement of Trump the same evening has further ignited speculations about her possible vice-presidential candidacy alongside Trump in 2024.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking back at the 2020 presidential election, Trump remained consistent in his criticism, maintaining that Democrats “used COVID to cheat,” particularly focusing on the sudden adoption of mass mail-in balloting in pivotal states without the necessary constitutional authorization from their respective state legislatures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Continuing his critique, Trump didn’t mince words as he said, &lt;em&gt;“The radical Democrats are trying hard to restart COVID hysteria. I wonder why? Is there an election coming up by any chance?”&lt;/em&gt; His statement was underlined by his observation that talk of masks has resurfaced, drawing a line of connection between COVID precautions and the upcoming electoral showdown.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump’s warning is a call to action for Republicans. As America gears up for another critical electoral season, the interplay between pandemic management and political strategy remains a topic that will be fervently discussed and dissected in the months to come.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">In a hard-hitting speech delivered to the South Dakota GOP convention, former President Donald Trump voiced concerns over the resurgence of “COVID hysteria.” A believer in political maneuvering, Trump suggested the return of heightened pandemic precautions may be linked to the upcoming elections, urging Republicans to be vigilant against potential overreaches. Addressing a rapt audience and broadcast live on Newsmax, Trump stated, “Congressional Republicans should also stop the Biden administration from bringing back COVID mandates, lockdowns, and restrictions of any kind, cutting off the money.” South Dakota, under the leadership of GOP Gov. Kristi Noem, stands strong against such restrictions, a fact not lost on Trump. The former president lauded Noem’s approach, highlighting the freedoms enjoyed by South Dakotans compared to residents in other states. Gov. Noem’s endorsement of Trump the same evening has further ignited speculations about her possible vice-presidential candidacy alongside Trump in 2024. Looking back at the 2020 presidential election, Trump remained consistent in his criticism, maintaining that Democrats “used COVID to cheat,” particularly focusing on the sudden adoption of mass mail-in balloting in pivotal states without the necessary constitutional authorization from their respective state legislatures. Continuing his critique, Trump didn’t mince words as he said, “The radical Democrats are trying hard to restart COVID hysteria. I wonder why? Is there an election coming up by any chance?” His statement was underlined by his observation that talk of masks has resurfaced, drawing a line of connection between COVID precautions and the upcoming electoral showdown. Trump’s warning is a call to action for Republicans. As America gears up for another critical electoral season, the interplay between pandemic management and political strategy remains a topic that will be fervently discussed and dissected in the months to come.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Abbott’s Bold Play - More Migrant Buses to Blue States Amid Biden’s Texas Confinement Plan</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/09/Abbott-Migrant-Buses/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Abbott’s Bold Play - More Migrant Buses to Blue States Amid Biden’s Texas Confinement Plan" /><published>2023-09-09T18:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-09T18:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/09/Abbott-Migrant-Buses</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/09/Abbott-Migrant-Buses/">&lt;p&gt;In a strategic and pointed move, Texas Governor Greg Abbott vows to send more buses filled with migrants directly to blue states if President Biden persists with his controversial plan to keep migrants largely confined to Texas. The southern border state, already grappling with large migrant numbers, stands defiantly against the proposed confinement strategy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The potential Department of Homeland Security (DHS) policy, aiming to track certain illegal immigrant families in Texas through GPS monitoring devices, has evoked sharp criticism from Abbott. Mirroring a Reagan-era initiative that was dismissed in the past, this strategy seeks to hold migrants near the border, ensuring swift deportation if they fail the asylum process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With his characteristic straightforwardness, Governor Abbott declared on X (formerly Twitter), &lt;em&gt;“Biden considers forcing migrant families to remain in Texas. This scam was tried years ago &amp;amp; was shot down by a judge.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Abbott, a vocal critic of the Biden administration’s border management, underscored his intent to escalate his countering strategy. Since 2022, his administration has already directed more than 35,000 migrants to sanctuary cities via buses, with an astounding 13,300+ reaching New York City since August 2022 alone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contrary to the Biden administration’s claims of effective border management, with a DHS representative emphasizing the removal of 200,000+ individuals since May 2023, Democratic strongholds like New York City tell a story of strain and distress. The city has been swamped by over 100,000 migrants joining its shelter system within a year. Echoing the pressure of this surge, Mayor Eric Adams candidly voiced his concerns, stating, &lt;em&gt;“This issue will destroy New York City. Destroy New York City.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Biden’s strategy seems more tailored to mollify his progressive base than to address the actual problems on the ground, the schism between federal intent and city experiences grows wider. Offering a policy that draws heavily from past failures and turns a deaf ear to cities in turmoil showcases a worrying lack of foresight and adaptability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The unfolding chaos at the southern border, peaking in July with figures touching around 183,000, with Border Patrol sectors bursting at the seams, continues to spotlight the Biden administration’s faltering approach. Blame is squarely placed on Biden’s policies by Republicans like Abbott, juxtaposed against Democrats’ calls for increased funding and comprehensive immigration reforms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the year progresses, the border issue’s political dimension intensifies. But leaders like Abbott have sent a clear message: they are prepared to counteract perceived federal missteps with decisive actions of their own. The unfolding dynamics between state strategies and federal plans will undoubtedly be pivotal in the shaping of future U.S. immigration landscapes.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a strategic and pointed move, Texas Governor Greg Abbott vows to send more buses filled with migrants directly to blue states if President Biden persists with his controversial plan to keep migrants largely confined to Texas. The southern border state, already grappling with large migrant numbers, stands defiantly against the proposed confinement strategy. The potential Department of Homeland Security (DHS) policy, aiming to track certain illegal immigrant families in Texas through GPS monitoring devices, has evoked sharp criticism from Abbott. Mirroring a Reagan-era initiative that was dismissed in the past, this strategy seeks to hold migrants near the border, ensuring swift deportation if they fail the asylum process. With his characteristic straightforwardness, Governor Abbott declared on X (formerly Twitter), “Biden considers forcing migrant families to remain in Texas. This scam was tried years ago &amp;amp; was shot down by a judge.” Abbott, a vocal critic of the Biden administration’s border management, underscored his intent to escalate his countering strategy. Since 2022, his administration has already directed more than 35,000 migrants to sanctuary cities via buses, with an astounding 13,300+ reaching New York City since August 2022 alone. Contrary to the Biden administration’s claims of effective border management, with a DHS representative emphasizing the removal of 200,000+ individuals since May 2023, Democratic strongholds like New York City tell a story of strain and distress. The city has been swamped by over 100,000 migrants joining its shelter system within a year. Echoing the pressure of this surge, Mayor Eric Adams candidly voiced his concerns, stating, “This issue will destroy New York City. Destroy New York City.” While Biden’s strategy seems more tailored to mollify his progressive base than to address the actual problems on the ground, the schism between federal intent and city experiences grows wider. Offering a policy that draws heavily from past failures and turns a deaf ear to cities in turmoil showcases a worrying lack of foresight and adaptability. The unfolding chaos at the southern border, peaking in July with figures touching around 183,000, with Border Patrol sectors bursting at the seams, continues to spotlight the Biden administration’s faltering approach. Blame is squarely placed on Biden’s policies by Republicans like Abbott, juxtaposed against Democrats’ calls for increased funding and comprehensive immigration reforms. As the year progresses, the border issue’s political dimension intensifies. But leaders like Abbott have sent a clear message: they are prepared to counteract perceived federal missteps with decisive actions of their own. The unfolding dynamics between state strategies and federal plans will undoubtedly be pivotal in the shaping of future U.S. immigration landscapes.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Biden’s Energy Inconsistency - Alaska Left in the Cold</title><link href="/news/2023/09/09/Biden-Alaska-Oil-Lease-Reversal/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Biden’s Energy Inconsistency - Alaska Left in the Cold" /><published>2023-09-09T17:01:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-09T17:01:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/09/Biden-Alaska-Oil-Lease-Reversal</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/09/Biden-Alaska-Oil-Lease-Reversal/">&lt;p&gt;In a move emblematic of the Biden Administration’s inconsistent energy policy, the President’s Interior Department announced the cancellation of the oil and gas leases issued during the waning moments of President Donald Trump’s tenure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Biden, in an official statement, proclaimed a responsibility to protect nearly 20 million acres in the Arctic National Wildlife Refuge (ANWR) for polar bears and caribou. But many view this as mere posturing, as the decision starkly contrasts his approach to oil-rich nations like Iran and Venezuela.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;President Trump had greenlit the Alaska Industrial Development and Export Authority (AIDEA) with seven leases, a strategic move affirming America’s commitment to energy independence. Biden’s abrupt reversal, part of a wider trend to curtail domestic oil and gas exploration, casts a shadow over America’s energy future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“This latest action by the Department of the Interior shows arbitrary disregard for Federal law, based on campaign trail rhetoric. Campaign promises are not enough to justify this agency action,” came a statement from AIDEA, echoing the frustration of many Alaskans.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Republicans Cry Foul&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Biden’s decision has roused sharp criticism from Republicans who stress the importance of American energy sovereignty. Sen. Dan Sullivan (R-AK) channeled the indignation of his constituents, lamenting over the Biden administration’s “unrelenting assault” on Alaska’s economy and its right to access lands lawfully.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sen. Cynthia Lummis (R-WY) highlighted a worrying consequence of this decision – the increasing dependence on “dirty oil” from foreign adversaries. “Not only will this cause our nation to continue relying on dirty oil from foreign adversaries, it will also keep prices high at the pump which the American people cannot afford,” Lummis cautioned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A poignant statement came from Sen. Lisa Murkowski (R-AK): “It’s bad enough to tear up legal contracts and renege on federal commitments. But it’s even more unconscionable that the Biden administration is penalizing Alaska right as it allows Iran to produce more of its oil and solicits the same from Venezuela.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In essence, Biden’s energy policy appears riddled with contradictions. Why curtail domestic energy production, essential for American jobs and economy, while simultaneously encouraging global adversaries to ramp up their oil supply?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Randy Ruaro, executive director of AIDEA, encapsulated this sentiment, stressing the arbitrary nature of the Department of the Interior’s decision. He asserted that under the law, real facts and reasons must back the reversal, not mere campaign promises. With plans to challenge the decision in court, Ruaro hints at uncovering the real motives behind Biden’s move, ensuring that key figures, potentially including Secretary Haaland, are held accountable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As America stands at an energy crossroads, only time will tell if the nation can find a consistent, secure, and forward-looking energy policy.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a move emblematic of the Biden Administration’s inconsistent energy policy, the President’s Interior Department announced the cancellation of the oil and gas leases issued during the waning moments of President Donald Trump’s tenure. Biden, in an official statement, proclaimed a responsibility to protect nearly 20 million acres in the Arctic National Wildlife Refuge (ANWR) for polar bears and caribou. But many view this as mere posturing, as the decision starkly contrasts his approach to oil-rich nations like Iran and Venezuela. President Trump had greenlit the Alaska Industrial Development and Export Authority (AIDEA) with seven leases, a strategic move affirming America’s commitment to energy independence. Biden’s abrupt reversal, part of a wider trend to curtail domestic oil and gas exploration, casts a shadow over America’s energy future. “This latest action by the Department of the Interior shows arbitrary disregard for Federal law, based on campaign trail rhetoric. Campaign promises are not enough to justify this agency action,” came a statement from AIDEA, echoing the frustration of many Alaskans. Republicans Cry Foul Biden’s decision has roused sharp criticism from Republicans who stress the importance of American energy sovereignty. Sen. Dan Sullivan (R-AK) channeled the indignation of his constituents, lamenting over the Biden administration’s “unrelenting assault” on Alaska’s economy and its right to access lands lawfully. Sen. Cynthia Lummis (R-WY) highlighted a worrying consequence of this decision – the increasing dependence on “dirty oil” from foreign adversaries. “Not only will this cause our nation to continue relying on dirty oil from foreign adversaries, it will also keep prices high at the pump which the American people cannot afford,” Lummis cautioned. A poignant statement came from Sen. Lisa Murkowski (R-AK): “It’s bad enough to tear up legal contracts and renege on federal commitments. But it’s even more unconscionable that the Biden administration is penalizing Alaska right as it allows Iran to produce more of its oil and solicits the same from Venezuela.” In essence, Biden’s energy policy appears riddled with contradictions. Why curtail domestic energy production, essential for American jobs and economy, while simultaneously encouraging global adversaries to ramp up their oil supply? Randy Ruaro, executive director of AIDEA, encapsulated this sentiment, stressing the arbitrary nature of the Department of the Interior’s decision. He asserted that under the law, real facts and reasons must back the reversal, not mere campaign promises. With plans to challenge the decision in court, Ruaro hints at uncovering the real motives behind Biden’s move, ensuring that key figures, potentially including Secretary Haaland, are held accountable. As America stands at an energy crossroads, only time will tell if the nation can find a consistent, secure, and forward-looking energy policy.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Exposing the Hypocrisy - Chicago Teachers Union President Sends Own Child to Private School</title><link href="/news/2023/09/09/CTU-Hypocrisy-Exposed/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Exposing the Hypocrisy - Chicago Teachers Union President Sends Own Child to Private School" /><published>2023-09-09T16:03:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-09T16:03:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/09/CTU-Hypocrisy-Exposed</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/09/CTU-Hypocrisy-Exposed/">&lt;p&gt;In a revealing twist of irony, the Chicago Teachers Union (CTU) president, Stacy Davis Gates, who has staunchly opposed school choice and private education, has enrolled her own child in a Catholic high school. The CTU’s rhetoric has long positioned private schools and school choice as mechanisms of segregation and racism. Yet, the choices of its leaders seem to belie their public stance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;union-leader-talks-the-talk-but-does-she-walk-the-walk&quot;&gt;Union Leader Talks the Talk, but Does She Walk the Walk?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gates, having been elected CTU president in 2022, has frequently voiced her opinions on the matter. In a past post on X (previously Twitter), she had mentioned, “&lt;em&gt;School choice&lt;/em&gt; was actually the choice of racists.” Furthermore, she had equated private schools to “segregation academies.” Yet, recent revelations by NBC Chicago have shown that her son has been enrolled in a private Catholic high school.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Union Leader’s defense? She claims that quality education is a dream for Black families, not a reality. In a passionate statement, she outlined the struggles Black and Brown communities face, from food and healthcare deserts to a lack of quality options close to their homes. However, this reasoning seems to only strengthen the argument for school choice - giving parents the ability to choose the best environment for their child’s education, irrespective of socio-economic constraints.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;advocates-weigh-in&quot;&gt;Advocates Weigh In&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The revelation about Gates’s choice of education for her child has been met with stern criticism. Corey DeAngelis, a renowned school choice advocate, labeled Gates a “school choice hypocrite.” He commented, “She tried to defend her hypocrisy by pointing to a supposed ‘disinvestment’ in public schools. But that flimsy defense is a pile of garbage, because Chicago Public Schools spend over $27,000 per student per year, whereas her son’s private school tuition is less than $15,000 per year.” He highlighted the lack of accountability in public schools, leading to inefficiencies in utilizing the vast resources at their disposal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-maga-takeaway&quot;&gt;The MAGA Takeaway&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To our MAGA crowd, the story underscores what we’ve been saying all along - individuals, not unions or governing bodies, should be making decisions that best serve their interests and that of their families. If Gates believes in the public school system and its efficacy, why not let her child be a testament to its success?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Union Leader’s actions expose the growing chasm between what’s preached by the elites and their actual choices. It’s time for proponents of school choice to drive the narrative and ensure that every child, irrespective of their background, has access to quality education.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the saying goes, actions speak louder than words. It’s time for the Union Leader to either walk her talk or step aside and let families make the choices they deem best for their children.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a revealing twist of irony, the Chicago Teachers Union (CTU) president, Stacy Davis Gates, who has staunchly opposed school choice and private education, has enrolled her own child in a Catholic high school. The CTU’s rhetoric has long positioned private schools and school choice as mechanisms of segregation and racism. Yet, the choices of its leaders seem to belie their public stance. Union Leader Talks the Talk, but Does She Walk the Walk? Gates, having been elected CTU president in 2022, has frequently voiced her opinions on the matter. In a past post on X (previously Twitter), she had mentioned, “School choice was actually the choice of racists.” Furthermore, she had equated private schools to “segregation academies.” Yet, recent revelations by NBC Chicago have shown that her son has been enrolled in a private Catholic high school. The Union Leader’s defense? She claims that quality education is a dream for Black families, not a reality. In a passionate statement, she outlined the struggles Black and Brown communities face, from food and healthcare deserts to a lack of quality options close to their homes. However, this reasoning seems to only strengthen the argument for school choice - giving parents the ability to choose the best environment for their child’s education, irrespective of socio-economic constraints. Advocates Weigh In The revelation about Gates’s choice of education for her child has been met with stern criticism. Corey DeAngelis, a renowned school choice advocate, labeled Gates a “school choice hypocrite.” He commented, “She tried to defend her hypocrisy by pointing to a supposed ‘disinvestment’ in public schools. But that flimsy defense is a pile of garbage, because Chicago Public Schools spend over $27,000 per student per year, whereas her son’s private school tuition is less than $15,000 per year.” He highlighted the lack of accountability in public schools, leading to inefficiencies in utilizing the vast resources at their disposal. The MAGA Takeaway To our MAGA crowd, the story underscores what we’ve been saying all along - individuals, not unions or governing bodies, should be making decisions that best serve their interests and that of their families. If Gates believes in the public school system and its efficacy, why not let her child be a testament to its success? The Union Leader’s actions expose the growing chasm between what’s preached by the elites and their actual choices. It’s time for proponents of school choice to drive the narrative and ensure that every child, irrespective of their background, has access to quality education. As the saying goes, actions speak louder than words. It’s time for the Union Leader to either walk her talk or step aside and let families make the choices they deem best for their children.</summary></entry></feed>