<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-10-16T09:20:11-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/16/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-16T09:20:11-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-16T09:20:11-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/16/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/16/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/16/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-16T09:20:11-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-16T09:20:11-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/16/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/16/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/">&lt;p&gt;Recent surprise attacks by Hamas on Israel has fueled ongoing tensions between staunchly conservative commentators and the progressive “Squad” Democrats known for criticizing Israel. The intensity of the backlash highlights the deep political divide over foreign policy in the Middle East.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Hamas’ shocking attack, several members of the “Squad,” including Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.), called for a “ceasefire and de-escalation,” condemning the violence. The absence of a statement from Rep. Rashida Tlaib (D-Mich.) was notably called out by conservative media outlets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;South Carolina GOP Rep. Nancy Mace quickly labeled Ocasio-Cortez a “Hamas apologist” in response to her call for peace and de-escalation. Rep. Ilhan Omar (D-Minn.), no stranger to controversy surrounding her views on Israel, echoed the call for de-escalation and ceasefire. Omar’s prior statements comparing the US and Israel to terrorist groups like Hamas and the Taliban resurfaced in the debate, fueling more criticisms. Omar’s 2019 tweet, where she opined that “Israel has hypnotized the world,” also continues to haunt her political career, often cited by critics to challenge her stance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conservative commentators have been especially vocal. “FOX &amp;amp; Friends Weekend” co-host Rachel Campos-Duffy took aim at Omar, saying she fails to recognize the peace in the Middle East under Trump’s administration. Conservative pundit John Hasson also called out Omar, claiming she insinuated that attacks on IDF forces were acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Massachusetts Democrat Rep. Ayanna Pressley’s concerns over the “devastating attacks on Israelis” were met with skepticism. A prominent conservative online personality, Comfortably Smug, accused the “Squad” of advising Israel to back down after the nation suffered massive attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Jamaal Bowman’s call for an end to the Gaza blockade, in addition to condemning the Hamas attacks, was met with criticism from conservative radio host Jason Rantz. He accused Bowman of pairing his condemnation of terrorism with unwarranted criticisms of Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Cori Bush emphasized the urgent need for a ceasefire, while pushing for an end to “U.S. support for Israeli military occupation and apartheid.” Defense attorney Marina Medvin criticized Bush, suggesting that she equates the death of Palestinian terrorists to the horrific acts committed against Jewish civilians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amidst the political turmoil and intense debate, the attacks have taken a heavy toll. Israeli media report over 300 dead due to the wide-ranging assault. Gaza health officials note that at least 200 Palestinians have perished in the retaliatory Israeli air strikes following the initial Hamas attack. As the situation remains volatile, both sides continue to count their casualties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This divisive issue showcases the challenge America faces in crafting a unified approach to foreign policy, with deeply entrenched political divides at play. As the situation develops, the debate is bound to intensify, shedding light on the complexities of U.S. politics in the global arena.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump Promises to Repeal Biden’s EV Mandates: A Job Crisis Ahead?</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/16/Trump-Electric-Vehicle-Mandates/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump Promises to Repeal Biden’s EV Mandates: A Job Crisis Ahead?" /><published>2023-10-16T08:15:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-16T08:15:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/16/Trump-Electric-Vehicle-Mandates</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/16/Trump-Electric-Vehicle-Mandates/">&lt;p&gt;Former U.S. President Donald Trump, now leading in the Republican presidential primary, has promised to overturn President Joe Biden’s Electric Vehicle (EV) mandates. Additionally, Trump has cautioned American auto workers about a looming job crisis, predicting their roles will become redundant in just two years if the current policies continue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Breitbart News has reported on the escalating situation where approximately 34,000 auto workers from companies like General Motors (GM), Ford, and Stellantis are striking across the United States. These workers are striving to negotiate new contracts that would guarantee better wages amidst soaring inflation and job security assurances against the backdrop of Biden’s EV mandates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a video message targeting the United Auto Workers (UAW), Trump expressed his intent to abolish Biden’s EV mandates, which he believes would endanger their jobs in the near future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“If you’re an auto worker, be it in UAW or any other state, the future seems bleak. With the current trajectory, many of you might not have jobs in two years. I intend to rejuvenate the auto industry in our country, much like the golden days,” Trump emphasized.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The former President further advised union leaders to reconsider their political affiliations, warning that siding with the Democrats might result in the downfall of the auto industry. He added, “No matter your hourly wage, the reality is, without a job, it doesn’t matter. I aim to restore the prosperity of the auto industry and the workers behind it.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Car prices have surged, which Trump attributes to Biden’s policies. He stated, “Since my term ended, car prices have skyrocketed by nearly 30%, with the average new car price reaching a staggering $50,000. This isn’t just an attack on the automobile industry; it’s an attack on the American dream.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump criticized Biden’s EV mandates for pushing car companies to elevate prices and eventually phasing out their more affordable gas-powered models. As a result, consumers are being nudged towards the pricier electric models. If companies resist this change, they could face hefty fines amounting to hundreds of millions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many in the auto industry view Biden’s EV mandates as a potential cost-saving strategy, which could indirectly boost executive salaries. Furthermore, thanks to Biden’s Inflation Reduction Act (IRA), auto executives are on track to benefit from billions in tax credits, further promoting EV production and sales.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump’s strong stance on this matter highlights the ongoing debate about the trajectory of the American auto industry and the potential ramifications for workers and consumers alike.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Former U.S. President Donald Trump, now leading in the Republican presidential primary, has promised to overturn President Joe Biden’s Electric Vehicle (EV) mandates. Additionally, Trump has cautioned American auto workers about a looming job crisis, predicting their roles will become redundant in just two years if the current policies continue. Breitbart News has reported on the escalating situation where approximately 34,000 auto workers from companies like General Motors (GM), Ford, and Stellantis are striking across the United States. These workers are striving to negotiate new contracts that would guarantee better wages amidst soaring inflation and job security assurances against the backdrop of Biden’s EV mandates. In a video message targeting the United Auto Workers (UAW), Trump expressed his intent to abolish Biden’s EV mandates, which he believes would endanger their jobs in the near future. “If you’re an auto worker, be it in UAW or any other state, the future seems bleak. With the current trajectory, many of you might not have jobs in two years. I intend to rejuvenate the auto industry in our country, much like the golden days,” Trump emphasized. The former President further advised union leaders to reconsider their political affiliations, warning that siding with the Democrats might result in the downfall of the auto industry. He added, “No matter your hourly wage, the reality is, without a job, it doesn’t matter. I aim to restore the prosperity of the auto industry and the workers behind it.” Car prices have surged, which Trump attributes to Biden’s policies. He stated, “Since my term ended, car prices have skyrocketed by nearly 30%, with the average new car price reaching a staggering $50,000. This isn’t just an attack on the automobile industry; it’s an attack on the American dream.” Trump criticized Biden’s EV mandates for pushing car companies to elevate prices and eventually phasing out their more affordable gas-powered models. As a result, consumers are being nudged towards the pricier electric models. If companies resist this change, they could face hefty fines amounting to hundreds of millions. Many in the auto industry view Biden’s EV mandates as a potential cost-saving strategy, which could indirectly boost executive salaries. Furthermore, thanks to Biden’s Inflation Reduction Act (IRA), auto executives are on track to benefit from billions in tax credits, further promoting EV production and sales. Trump’s strong stance on this matter highlights the ongoing debate about the trajectory of the American auto industry and the potential ramifications for workers and consumers alike.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Bear Grylls Realizes Lifelong Dream: Baptism in Jordan River</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/16/Bear-Grylls-Baptism-Jordan-River/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bear Grylls Realizes Lifelong Dream: Baptism in Jordan River" /><published>2023-10-16T07:06:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-16T07:06:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/16/Bear-Grylls-Baptism-Jordan-River</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/16/Bear-Grylls-Baptism-Jordan-River/">&lt;p&gt;Renowned survivalist, TV personality, and author Bear Grylls recently lived a dream come true as he got baptized in the Jordan River, a location deeply significant in Christian traditions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Grylls shared his profound moment with fans, expressing his elation at experiencing a sacrament in the very waters where, according to Christian beliefs, Jesus was baptized by John the Baptist. “It had always been a dream of mine to get in the water that Jesus was baptized in by my hero John the Baptist,” Grylls penned on his social media. Alongside his heartfelt message, he posted a photo capturing the poignant moment of his baptism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bear Grylls, over the years, has never shied away from discussing his faith. In 2022, during an engaging chat with Steven Bartlett on ‘The Diary of a CEO’, Grylls shed light on how his faith anchors him. He reminisced about his childhood, saying, “As a kid, I had a really natural faith, always felt there was something greater around.” However, he expressed regret over how modern perceptions of Christianity have been “tarnished”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He further delved into his beliefs, emphasizing the power of faith as a guiding light. “Faith is in your heart, knowing that you are not alone. There’s something bigger than us out there,” he elaborated, highlighting the importance of love, trust, and empowerment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adding to this sentiment, in a conversation with the Christian Post, Grylls shared his concerns about the contemporary practices of many churches. Expressing his thoughts, he mentioned, “I think Jesus would really struggle with 99% of churches nowadays.” Grylls emphasized that the crux of faith lies in love, community, honesty, and staying close to one’s beliefs rather than being embroiled in the theatrics of religious practices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Born in Ireland, the TV star proudly associates with the UK’s Anglican Church.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Grylls’ baptism in the Jordan River and his candid discussions about faith reflect the TV star’s deep-rooted beliefs. As fans continue to admire him for his thrilling survival shows, moments like these offer a glimpse into the man behind the adventure, showcasing a side that’s grounded in faith and spiritual reflection.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Renowned survivalist, TV personality, and author Bear Grylls recently lived a dream come true as he got baptized in the Jordan River, a location deeply significant in Christian traditions. Grylls shared his profound moment with fans, expressing his elation at experiencing a sacrament in the very waters where, according to Christian beliefs, Jesus was baptized by John the Baptist. “It had always been a dream of mine to get in the water that Jesus was baptized in by my hero John the Baptist,” Grylls penned on his social media. Alongside his heartfelt message, he posted a photo capturing the poignant moment of his baptism. Bear Grylls, over the years, has never shied away from discussing his faith. In 2022, during an engaging chat with Steven Bartlett on ‘The Diary of a CEO’, Grylls shed light on how his faith anchors him. He reminisced about his childhood, saying, “As a kid, I had a really natural faith, always felt there was something greater around.” However, he expressed regret over how modern perceptions of Christianity have been “tarnished”. He further delved into his beliefs, emphasizing the power of faith as a guiding light. “Faith is in your heart, knowing that you are not alone. There’s something bigger than us out there,” he elaborated, highlighting the importance of love, trust, and empowerment. Adding to this sentiment, in a conversation with the Christian Post, Grylls shared his concerns about the contemporary practices of many churches. Expressing his thoughts, he mentioned, “I think Jesus would really struggle with 99% of churches nowadays.” Grylls emphasized that the crux of faith lies in love, community, honesty, and staying close to one’s beliefs rather than being embroiled in the theatrics of religious practices. Born in Ireland, the TV star proudly associates with the UK’s Anglican Church. Grylls’ baptism in the Jordan River and his candid discussions about faith reflect the TV star’s deep-rooted beliefs. As fans continue to admire him for his thrilling survival shows, moments like these offer a glimpse into the man behind the adventure, showcasing a side that’s grounded in faith and spiritual reflection.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">CBP Apprehends Fourth Iranian ‘Special Interest Alien’ in Texas</title><link href="/news/2023/10/16/Iranian-Special-Interest-Alien-Texas/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="CBP Apprehends Fourth Iranian ‘Special Interest Alien’ in Texas" /><published>2023-10-16T06:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-16T06:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/16/Iranian-Special-Interest-Alien-Texas</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/16/Iranian-Special-Interest-Alien-Texas/">&lt;p&gt;Recent apprehensions at the US southern border have heightened concerns over national security. U.S. Customs and Border Protection (CBP) has confirmed that a fourth Iranian, identified as a “special interest alien”, was detained this month in Eagle Pass, Texas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The term “special interest alien” is used for individuals from countries believed by the US government to either protect or promote terrorism, or those that might pose a potential national security risk to the United States. Such detainees undergo added vetting and questioning following their apprehension.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CBP sources informed Fox News that the recently apprehended Iranian man, in his 40s, was taken into custody after crossing the border around 3 a.m. in Eagle Pass. Notably, he voluntarily surrendered to the border agents after the illegal crossing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This month, Eagle Pass has seen a surge in the apprehension of “special interest aliens”. In a separate incident, two Lebanese nationals were detained. Given Lebanon’s proximity to Israel and its association with Hezbollah, a group funded by Iran and labeled a terror organization by the State Department, these apprehensions are particularly alarming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moreover, in the Rio Grande Valley Sector, CBP officials have reported the detention of 19 Iranians and 17 Syrians in a span of a week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These apprehensions coincide with growing security concerns, especially in the aftermath of the Hamas-led attack on Israel on October 7th, which resulted in the death of 1,300 Israelis and left thousands injured.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The National Security Council’s spokesman, John Kirby, stated last week that while Iran shows “broad complicity” due to its backing of Hamas, there is no evidence to suggest Iran’s involvement in planning or executing the recent Hamas attack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, a threat assessment released by the Department of Homeland Security last month emphasized the potential security threats. The document noted an uptick in agents encountering individuals on the watch list and highlighted concerns that “terrorists and criminal actors may exploit the elevated flow and increasingly complex security environment to enter the United States.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The consistent rise in apprehensions at the southern border underscores the growing challenges faced by CBP agents. With global tensions on the rise, the focus on securing borders and ensuring the safety of citizens becomes paramount.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Recent apprehensions at the US southern border have heightened concerns over national security. U.S. Customs and Border Protection (CBP) has confirmed that a fourth Iranian, identified as a “special interest alien”, was detained this month in Eagle Pass, Texas. The term “special interest alien” is used for individuals from countries believed by the US government to either protect or promote terrorism, or those that might pose a potential national security risk to the United States. Such detainees undergo added vetting and questioning following their apprehension. CBP sources informed Fox News that the recently apprehended Iranian man, in his 40s, was taken into custody after crossing the border around 3 a.m. in Eagle Pass. Notably, he voluntarily surrendered to the border agents after the illegal crossing. This month, Eagle Pass has seen a surge in the apprehension of “special interest aliens”. In a separate incident, two Lebanese nationals were detained. Given Lebanon’s proximity to Israel and its association with Hezbollah, a group funded by Iran and labeled a terror organization by the State Department, these apprehensions are particularly alarming. Moreover, in the Rio Grande Valley Sector, CBP officials have reported the detention of 19 Iranians and 17 Syrians in a span of a week. These apprehensions coincide with growing security concerns, especially in the aftermath of the Hamas-led attack on Israel on October 7th, which resulted in the death of 1,300 Israelis and left thousands injured. The National Security Council’s spokesman, John Kirby, stated last week that while Iran shows “broad complicity” due to its backing of Hamas, there is no evidence to suggest Iran’s involvement in planning or executing the recent Hamas attack. However, a threat assessment released by the Department of Homeland Security last month emphasized the potential security threats. The document noted an uptick in agents encountering individuals on the watch list and highlighted concerns that “terrorists and criminal actors may exploit the elevated flow and increasingly complex security environment to enter the United States.” The consistent rise in apprehensions at the southern border underscores the growing challenges faced by CBP agents. With global tensions on the rise, the focus on securing borders and ensuring the safety of citizens becomes paramount.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">DC Crime Wave: Robbery Victim’s Harrowing Testimony Exposes Lenient Policies</title><link href="/news/2023/10/15/DC-Crime-Surge/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="DC Crime Wave: Robbery Victim’s Harrowing Testimony Exposes Lenient Policies" /><published>2023-10-15T13:06:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-15T13:06:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/15/DC-Crime-Surge</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/15/DC-Crime-Surge/">&lt;p&gt;Recent testimony by Mitchell Sobolevsky, a robbery victim, has reignited the debate about crime rates and sentencing policies in Washington, D.C. Sobolevsky shared his harrowing story of being robbed at gunpoint near the White House and expressed concern about the leniency of sentencing for violent offenders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During a walk from his apartment to the grocery store in December 2020, Sobolevsky noticed a suspicious man eyeing him. The initially peaceful walk soon turned into a nightmare as the man demanded money and brandished a gun at Sobolevsky’s face. Recounting the incident, Sobolevsky stated he felt as though he’d become “just another statistic” in a city marred by rising violent crime.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The narrative took an alarming turn when Sobolevsky revealed that the perpetrator had his sentence reduced, even after robbing multiple victims and businesses. Not long after his release, the same criminal committed two more armed robberies. Sobolevsky pleaded with the court for a stricter sentence, fearing that a lenient stance would embolden the criminal, but his pleas fell on deaf ears.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His experience sheds light on a disturbing trend in D.C. Although overall crime rates showed a decrease between 2021 and 2022, violent crimes have surged in 2023, with an increase of nearly 40% from the previous year. Notably, motor vehicle thefts and robberies have soared, seeing hikes of 106% and 65%, respectively.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further intensifying the issue is the fact that federal prosecutors in D.C. declined to prosecute 67% of people arrested in the past fiscal year for cases usually tried in the D.C. Superior Court. This alarming statistic has nearly doubled since 2015.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In an effort to combat the surging crime wave, Congress recently overturned a D.C. criminal code that was under fire for being too lenient. The city council also passed an emergency public safety bill, which aimed to increase penalties for specific crimes, like firing weapons in public areas and carjackings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The challenges D.C. faces are significant, with crime rates reaching levels reminiscent of the 1990s. Sobolevsky’s account serves as a stark reminder of the personal toll behind the statistics. While measures are being implemented to counteract the spike in crime, the testimonies of victims like Sobolevsky underscore the urgency and importance of more effective solutions.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Recent testimony by Mitchell Sobolevsky, a robbery victim, has reignited the debate about crime rates and sentencing policies in Washington, D.C. Sobolevsky shared his harrowing story of being robbed at gunpoint near the White House and expressed concern about the leniency of sentencing for violent offenders. During a walk from his apartment to the grocery store in December 2020, Sobolevsky noticed a suspicious man eyeing him. The initially peaceful walk soon turned into a nightmare as the man demanded money and brandished a gun at Sobolevsky’s face. Recounting the incident, Sobolevsky stated he felt as though he’d become “just another statistic” in a city marred by rising violent crime. The narrative took an alarming turn when Sobolevsky revealed that the perpetrator had his sentence reduced, even after robbing multiple victims and businesses. Not long after his release, the same criminal committed two more armed robberies. Sobolevsky pleaded with the court for a stricter sentence, fearing that a lenient stance would embolden the criminal, but his pleas fell on deaf ears. His experience sheds light on a disturbing trend in D.C. Although overall crime rates showed a decrease between 2021 and 2022, violent crimes have surged in 2023, with an increase of nearly 40% from the previous year. Notably, motor vehicle thefts and robberies have soared, seeing hikes of 106% and 65%, respectively. Further intensifying the issue is the fact that federal prosecutors in D.C. declined to prosecute 67% of people arrested in the past fiscal year for cases usually tried in the D.C. Superior Court. This alarming statistic has nearly doubled since 2015. In an effort to combat the surging crime wave, Congress recently overturned a D.C. criminal code that was under fire for being too lenient. The city council also passed an emergency public safety bill, which aimed to increase penalties for specific crimes, like firing weapons in public areas and carjackings. The challenges D.C. faces are significant, with crime rates reaching levels reminiscent of the 1990s. Sobolevsky’s account serves as a stark reminder of the personal toll behind the statistics. While measures are being implemented to counteract the spike in crime, the testimonies of victims like Sobolevsky underscore the urgency and importance of more effective solutions.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Race for Louisiana: Trump-Backed Jeff Landry in the Spotlight</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/15/Louisiana-Gubernatorial-Race/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Race for Louisiana: Trump-Backed Jeff Landry in the Spotlight" /><published>2023-10-15T11:56:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-15T11:56:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/15/Louisiana-Gubernatorial-Race</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/15/Louisiana-Gubernatorial-Race/">&lt;p&gt;Amid a crowded political arena, Louisiana’s gubernatorial race is grabbing national headlines. With Governor John Bel Edwards stepping down due to term limits, the seat has opened up, presenting Republicans with a golden opportunity to reclaim the top spot after eight years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Out of the fourteen candidates contesting under the “jungle primary” system, Attorney General Jeff Landry, backed by former President Donald Trump, stands out. Landry has not only gained significant endorsements but also enjoys a dominant fundraising advantage. Yet, with prominence comes scrutiny. Landry’s campaign has been marred by accusations of political bullying and backroom dealings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Louisiana’s electoral climate reflects a microcosm of broader national political trends. The state, which gave Trump a majority in the last two presidential elections, is seeing Republicans eagerly push to win the governor’s mansion. Conversely, Democrats, who have enjoyed the governor’s seat for the last eight years, are putting their weight behind Shawn Wilson, hoping their strategy of consolidating behind one candidate pays off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the gubernatorial race isn’t the only one catching attention. The secretary of state’s race has also drawn eyes nationwide, particularly concerning the replacement of Louisiana’s outdated voting machines. Current Secretary of State, Republican Kyle Ardoin, chose not to run for re-election. The ensuing race has been engulfed in controversies, with conspiracy theorists advocating for hand-counted paper ballots. Leading candidates, including GOP state House Speaker Clay Schexnayder and Democrat Gwen Collins-Greenup, have voiced opposition to hand-counting, underscoring the importance of reliable voting systems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the immediate outcomes, this election cycle will set the tone for Louisiana’s political future. A Republican win, especially one with Trump’s endorsement, might solidify the party’s hold, aligning state policies closer to national GOP stances. On the other hand, a Democratic victory would underline the party’s resilience in the Deep South, possibly indicating a broader regional trend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the clock ticks down to the final voting hour, one thing is certain: Louisiana’s 2023 political battles will have lasting implications, not just for the state but potentially for the nation’s political landscape.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Amid a crowded political arena, Louisiana’s gubernatorial race is grabbing national headlines. With Governor John Bel Edwards stepping down due to term limits, the seat has opened up, presenting Republicans with a golden opportunity to reclaim the top spot after eight years. Out of the fourteen candidates contesting under the “jungle primary” system, Attorney General Jeff Landry, backed by former President Donald Trump, stands out. Landry has not only gained significant endorsements but also enjoys a dominant fundraising advantage. Yet, with prominence comes scrutiny. Landry’s campaign has been marred by accusations of political bullying and backroom dealings. Louisiana’s electoral climate reflects a microcosm of broader national political trends. The state, which gave Trump a majority in the last two presidential elections, is seeing Republicans eagerly push to win the governor’s mansion. Conversely, Democrats, who have enjoyed the governor’s seat for the last eight years, are putting their weight behind Shawn Wilson, hoping their strategy of consolidating behind one candidate pays off. However, the gubernatorial race isn’t the only one catching attention. The secretary of state’s race has also drawn eyes nationwide, particularly concerning the replacement of Louisiana’s outdated voting machines. Current Secretary of State, Republican Kyle Ardoin, chose not to run for re-election. The ensuing race has been engulfed in controversies, with conspiracy theorists advocating for hand-counted paper ballots. Leading candidates, including GOP state House Speaker Clay Schexnayder and Democrat Gwen Collins-Greenup, have voiced opposition to hand-counting, underscoring the importance of reliable voting systems. Beyond the immediate outcomes, this election cycle will set the tone for Louisiana’s political future. A Republican win, especially one with Trump’s endorsement, might solidify the party’s hold, aligning state policies closer to national GOP stances. On the other hand, a Democratic victory would underline the party’s resilience in the Deep South, possibly indicating a broader regional trend. As the clock ticks down to the final voting hour, one thing is certain: Louisiana’s 2023 political battles will have lasting implications, not just for the state but potentially for the nation’s political landscape.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Shifting Sands in West Virginia: Justice Overtakes Manchin in Senate Race</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/15/Justice-vs-Manchin/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Shifting Sands in West Virginia: Justice Overtakes Manchin in Senate Race" /><published>2023-10-15T10:45:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-15T10:45:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/15/Justice-vs-Manchin</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/15/Justice-vs-Manchin/">&lt;p&gt;In a surprising turn of events, a new Emerson College Poll suggests that Republican Governor Jim Justice holds a clear lead against Democratic Senator Joe Manchin in the upcoming Senate race to represent West Virginia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This noteworthy shift in the political landscape shows Manchin, the Democratic incumbent, only garnering 28% of the vote in the projected 2024 race. In contrast, Governor Justice boasts 41% support, positioning him as the favorite for the general election. Additionally, the poll indicates that 15% of voters lean towards alternative candidates, while another 16% remain undecided, leaving room for potential swings in sentiment as the race progresses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Senator Manchin currently lags behind Justice, the same poll indicates a slight lead over Republican Representative Alex Mooney, 37% to 31%. Mooney, who declared his intention to compete for Manchin’s Senate seat just days after clinching re-election to the House in November, expressed confidence in his ability to overcome his long-established opponent. Justice, on the other hand, announced his Senate candidacy in April during a memorable 72nd birthday celebration. He emphasized his commitment to the West Virginia people, vowing to execute a role that would leave them proud.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The political debate has already commenced, with Mooney challenging Justice’s GOP primary record in April, and Manchin affirming his determination to secure re-election. In a statement, Manchin emphasized, “I am laser-focused on fulfilling my duties to West Virginians — from reducing healthcare costs to strengthening American energy security. But let there be no confusion, I intend to win any race I enter.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Emerson poll sheds light on additional political sentiments in West Virginia. It reveals a 50% job approval rating for Justice, contrasting sharply with President Joe Biden’s 71% disapproval rating. Furthermore, even among state Democrats, the Governor secures a 34% job approval rate, closely followed by a 35% approval from independent voters. Notably, the poll underscores the divisive opinions on the 2020 presidential election, with 51% of West Virginian voters alleging election fraud against President Biden.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the political landscape remains fluid and often unpredictable, these poll numbers signal the potential for further shifts and surprises as we draw closer to the 2024 elections. Only time will reveal if these early projections hold firm or if the tides of voter sentiment shift once again.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a surprising turn of events, a new Emerson College Poll suggests that Republican Governor Jim Justice holds a clear lead against Democratic Senator Joe Manchin in the upcoming Senate race to represent West Virginia. This noteworthy shift in the political landscape shows Manchin, the Democratic incumbent, only garnering 28% of the vote in the projected 2024 race. In contrast, Governor Justice boasts 41% support, positioning him as the favorite for the general election. Additionally, the poll indicates that 15% of voters lean towards alternative candidates, while another 16% remain undecided, leaving room for potential swings in sentiment as the race progresses. While Senator Manchin currently lags behind Justice, the same poll indicates a slight lead over Republican Representative Alex Mooney, 37% to 31%. Mooney, who declared his intention to compete for Manchin’s Senate seat just days after clinching re-election to the House in November, expressed confidence in his ability to overcome his long-established opponent. Justice, on the other hand, announced his Senate candidacy in April during a memorable 72nd birthday celebration. He emphasized his commitment to the West Virginia people, vowing to execute a role that would leave them proud. The political debate has already commenced, with Mooney challenging Justice’s GOP primary record in April, and Manchin affirming his determination to secure re-election. In a statement, Manchin emphasized, “I am laser-focused on fulfilling my duties to West Virginians — from reducing healthcare costs to strengthening American energy security. But let there be no confusion, I intend to win any race I enter.” The Emerson poll sheds light on additional political sentiments in West Virginia. It reveals a 50% job approval rating for Justice, contrasting sharply with President Joe Biden’s 71% disapproval rating. Furthermore, even among state Democrats, the Governor secures a 34% job approval rate, closely followed by a 35% approval from independent voters. Notably, the poll underscores the divisive opinions on the 2020 presidential election, with 51% of West Virginian voters alleging election fraud against President Biden. As the political landscape remains fluid and often unpredictable, these poll numbers signal the potential for further shifts and surprises as we draw closer to the 2024 elections. Only time will reveal if these early projections hold firm or if the tides of voter sentiment shift once again.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">US COVID Relief Funds Under Scrutiny Amid Ties to Controversial Palestinian Group</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/15/US-Relief-Funds-Controversy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="US COVID Relief Funds Under Scrutiny Amid Ties to Controversial Palestinian Group" /><published>2023-10-15T09:30:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-15T09:30:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/15/US-Relief-Funds-Controversy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/15/US-Relief-Funds-Controversy/">&lt;p&gt;In a move that has sent shockwaves across political spheres, the Biden administration has allocated a staggering $33.7 million from the American Rescue Plan – a bill fundamentally devised for COVID relief – to the United Nations Relief &amp;amp; Works Agency (UNRWA). This comes amid growing concerns regarding the Palestinian relief organization’s alleged affiliations with Hamas, a militant group. Some critics have gone so far as to label UNRWA as “effectively a branch of Hamas.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The allocation was made through the State Department’s Migration and Refugee Assistance program, a part of a more considerable $500 million provision earmarked in the relief bill for the State Department’s refugee and migration assistance initiatives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Controversies surrounding UNRWA are not new. Over the years, they’ve been scrutinized for purportedly not doing enough to curtail aid from reaching the clutches of Hamas terrorists. There have been reports suggesting that UNRWA facilities have been used to further Hamas propaganda in schools and even shelter Hamas activities. The left-leaning New Republic, back in 2014, even painted UNRWA as “effectively a branch of Hamas.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, an alarming revelation by UN Watch earlier this year put UNRWA schools in the hot seat for allegedly propagating hatred against Jewish individuals and endorsing terrorism. While UNRWA accepted the mistakes of some of its teachers in spreading such material, they assured that no such materials are currently in circulation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To add more layers to this complex situation, President Donald Trump, during his term, had cut off UNRWA’s funding, a move that drew criticism from several quarters, suggesting that this cut-off jeopardized the essential aid needed by Gaza’s impoverished residents. Fast forward to the Biden administration, and the funding was reinstated despite the undercurrent of concerns that Hamas might indirectly benefit from such foreign aid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The revelations from an internal State Department document in March 2021 pointed out potential risks. The document conceded that there was a “high risk Hamas could potentially derive indirect, unintentional benefit from U.S. assistance to Gaza.” Yet, it also argued that such risks were justified for national security purposes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In July 2022, the Biden administration declared its contribution to UNRWA surpassed that of any other entity globally, amounting to over $618 million. The New York Post puts this number even higher, estimating a total of $730 million.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Supporters of UNRWA emphasize its crucial role in the region, highlighting the humanitarian services it provides, such as education, health care, relief, and emergency response. Currently, as per the United Nations, over 220,000 individuals are sheltered in 92 UNRWA schools.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The fundamental question that looms large is whether the aid is reaching the intended recipients without falling into the wrong hands. While UNRWA’s role in the region is undeniably significant, ensuring transparency and integrity in its operations is paramount. The debate over the US’s funding to UNRWA underscores the intricate balance between humanitarian support and ensuring national security.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As discussions continue and the world watches closely, the onus is on the Biden administration and UNRWA to operate with transparency and responsibility.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a move that has sent shockwaves across political spheres, the Biden administration has allocated a staggering $33.7 million from the American Rescue Plan – a bill fundamentally devised for COVID relief – to the United Nations Relief &amp;amp; Works Agency (UNRWA). This comes amid growing concerns regarding the Palestinian relief organization’s alleged affiliations with Hamas, a militant group. Some critics have gone so far as to label UNRWA as “effectively a branch of Hamas.” The allocation was made through the State Department’s Migration and Refugee Assistance program, a part of a more considerable $500 million provision earmarked in the relief bill for the State Department’s refugee and migration assistance initiatives. Controversies surrounding UNRWA are not new. Over the years, they’ve been scrutinized for purportedly not doing enough to curtail aid from reaching the clutches of Hamas terrorists. There have been reports suggesting that UNRWA facilities have been used to further Hamas propaganda in schools and even shelter Hamas activities. The left-leaning New Republic, back in 2014, even painted UNRWA as “effectively a branch of Hamas.” Furthermore, an alarming revelation by UN Watch earlier this year put UNRWA schools in the hot seat for allegedly propagating hatred against Jewish individuals and endorsing terrorism. While UNRWA accepted the mistakes of some of its teachers in spreading such material, they assured that no such materials are currently in circulation. To add more layers to this complex situation, President Donald Trump, during his term, had cut off UNRWA’s funding, a move that drew criticism from several quarters, suggesting that this cut-off jeopardized the essential aid needed by Gaza’s impoverished residents. Fast forward to the Biden administration, and the funding was reinstated despite the undercurrent of concerns that Hamas might indirectly benefit from such foreign aid. The revelations from an internal State Department document in March 2021 pointed out potential risks. The document conceded that there was a “high risk Hamas could potentially derive indirect, unintentional benefit from U.S. assistance to Gaza.” Yet, it also argued that such risks were justified for national security purposes. In July 2022, the Biden administration declared its contribution to UNRWA surpassed that of any other entity globally, amounting to over $618 million. The New York Post puts this number even higher, estimating a total of $730 million. Supporters of UNRWA emphasize its crucial role in the region, highlighting the humanitarian services it provides, such as education, health care, relief, and emergency response. Currently, as per the United Nations, over 220,000 individuals are sheltered in 92 UNRWA schools. The fundamental question that looms large is whether the aid is reaching the intended recipients without falling into the wrong hands. While UNRWA’s role in the region is undeniably significant, ensuring transparency and integrity in its operations is paramount. The debate over the US’s funding to UNRWA underscores the intricate balance between humanitarian support and ensuring national security. As discussions continue and the world watches closely, the onus is on the Biden administration and UNRWA to operate with transparency and responsibility.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">US Migrant Influx Challenges Democrat Cities: A Crisis in the Making</title><link href="/news/2023/10/15/Migrant-Crisis-US/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="US Migrant Influx Challenges Democrat Cities: A Crisis in the Making" /><published>2023-10-15T08:12:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-15T08:12:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/15/Migrant-Crisis-US</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/15/Migrant-Crisis-US/">&lt;p&gt;Amid the expansive wall marking the U.S.-Mexico divide in southern California, a significant migrant surge puts immense pressure on American cities. These new arrivals stretch local resources thin, sparking significant concerns, particularly in Democrat-led cities like San Diego, New York, and Chicago.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;San Diego stands as a prime example of the distress this surge has caused. “The reality is that we don’t have sufficient funds,” voiced Nora Vargas, a prominent Democrat in San Diego’s governance. “As we continue to plan, the numbers continue to increase.” Consequently, the city recently declared the situation a “humanitarian crisis.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Historically, immigration has been a divisive issue in the U.S. politics. But the recent record-breaking influx – with reports citing a staggering 2.4 million migrant encounters at the southern border in the past year – challenges the traditional Democratic approach of welcoming all, regardless of their entry method.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In San Diego, migrants, predominantly fleeing dire circumstances in Latin America, are tracked with wristbands indicating their crossing date. However, a massive backlog in the immigration system causes most to remain in limbo. They wait for years for a hearing, only to be moved from one crowded processing center to another and then to interstate buses. This pattern is consistently seen across southern U.S. border communities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, in Republican-led Texas, Governor Greg Abbott’s strategy has been to transport migrants to major cities like New York and Chicago, shifting the responsibility to their Democrat leadership. Mayor Eric Adams of New York, having absorbed over 100,000 migrants in a year, stated, “The president and the White House have failed this city.” The mounting crisis, estimated to cost New York nearly $5 billion, forced Adams to declare a state of emergency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Illinois Governor JB Pritzker shared similar sentiments, remarking, “The federal government’s lack of intervention and coordination at the border has created an untenable situation for Illinois.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The criticism comes at a critical time, just a year before the presidential elections, painting the Biden administration in a precarious light. As American households grapple with rising living costs, the narrative that the borders are left unchecked becomes more potent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Robert Vivar, associated with the San Diego Episcopal Diocese, highlighted the broader issue – a system ill-equipped for the current challenges. With neither political party providing a comprehensive solution, the country remains at an impasse. “Decisions are made about our border 3,000 miles away,” Vargas concluded. It’s a clear call to action, urging policymakers to witness the issues firsthand and develop tangible solutions.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Amid the expansive wall marking the U.S.-Mexico divide in southern California, a significant migrant surge puts immense pressure on American cities. These new arrivals stretch local resources thin, sparking significant concerns, particularly in Democrat-led cities like San Diego, New York, and Chicago. San Diego stands as a prime example of the distress this surge has caused. “The reality is that we don’t have sufficient funds,” voiced Nora Vargas, a prominent Democrat in San Diego’s governance. “As we continue to plan, the numbers continue to increase.” Consequently, the city recently declared the situation a “humanitarian crisis.” Historically, immigration has been a divisive issue in the U.S. politics. But the recent record-breaking influx – with reports citing a staggering 2.4 million migrant encounters at the southern border in the past year – challenges the traditional Democratic approach of welcoming all, regardless of their entry method. In San Diego, migrants, predominantly fleeing dire circumstances in Latin America, are tracked with wristbands indicating their crossing date. However, a massive backlog in the immigration system causes most to remain in limbo. They wait for years for a hearing, only to be moved from one crowded processing center to another and then to interstate buses. This pattern is consistently seen across southern U.S. border communities. Interestingly, in Republican-led Texas, Governor Greg Abbott’s strategy has been to transport migrants to major cities like New York and Chicago, shifting the responsibility to their Democrat leadership. Mayor Eric Adams of New York, having absorbed over 100,000 migrants in a year, stated, “The president and the White House have failed this city.” The mounting crisis, estimated to cost New York nearly $5 billion, forced Adams to declare a state of emergency. Illinois Governor JB Pritzker shared similar sentiments, remarking, “The federal government’s lack of intervention and coordination at the border has created an untenable situation for Illinois.” The criticism comes at a critical time, just a year before the presidential elections, painting the Biden administration in a precarious light. As American households grapple with rising living costs, the narrative that the borders are left unchecked becomes more potent. Robert Vivar, associated with the San Diego Episcopal Diocese, highlighted the broader issue – a system ill-equipped for the current challenges. With neither political party providing a comprehensive solution, the country remains at an impasse. “Decisions are made about our border 3,000 miles away,” Vargas concluded. It’s a clear call to action, urging policymakers to witness the issues firsthand and develop tangible solutions.</summary></entry></feed>