<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-10-15T16:14:52-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/15/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-15T16:14:52-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-15T16:14:52-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/15/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/15/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/15/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-15T16:14:52-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-15T16:14:52-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/15/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/15/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/">&lt;p&gt;Recent surprise attacks by Hamas on Israel has fueled ongoing tensions between staunchly conservative commentators and the progressive “Squad” Democrats known for criticizing Israel. The intensity of the backlash highlights the deep political divide over foreign policy in the Middle East.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Hamas’ shocking attack, several members of the “Squad,” including Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.), called for a “ceasefire and de-escalation,” condemning the violence. The absence of a statement from Rep. Rashida Tlaib (D-Mich.) was notably called out by conservative media outlets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;South Carolina GOP Rep. Nancy Mace quickly labeled Ocasio-Cortez a “Hamas apologist” in response to her call for peace and de-escalation. Rep. Ilhan Omar (D-Minn.), no stranger to controversy surrounding her views on Israel, echoed the call for de-escalation and ceasefire. Omar’s prior statements comparing the US and Israel to terrorist groups like Hamas and the Taliban resurfaced in the debate, fueling more criticisms. Omar’s 2019 tweet, where she opined that “Israel has hypnotized the world,” also continues to haunt her political career, often cited by critics to challenge her stance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conservative commentators have been especially vocal. “FOX &amp;amp; Friends Weekend” co-host Rachel Campos-Duffy took aim at Omar, saying she fails to recognize the peace in the Middle East under Trump’s administration. Conservative pundit John Hasson also called out Omar, claiming she insinuated that attacks on IDF forces were acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Massachusetts Democrat Rep. Ayanna Pressley’s concerns over the “devastating attacks on Israelis” were met with skepticism. A prominent conservative online personality, Comfortably Smug, accused the “Squad” of advising Israel to back down after the nation suffered massive attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Jamaal Bowman’s call for an end to the Gaza blockade, in addition to condemning the Hamas attacks, was met with criticism from conservative radio host Jason Rantz. He accused Bowman of pairing his condemnation of terrorism with unwarranted criticisms of Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Cori Bush emphasized the urgent need for a ceasefire, while pushing for an end to “U.S. support for Israeli military occupation and apartheid.” Defense attorney Marina Medvin criticized Bush, suggesting that she equates the death of Palestinian terrorists to the horrific acts committed against Jewish civilians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amidst the political turmoil and intense debate, the attacks have taken a heavy toll. Israeli media report over 300 dead due to the wide-ranging assault. Gaza health officials note that at least 200 Palestinians have perished in the retaliatory Israeli air strikes following the initial Hamas attack. As the situation remains volatile, both sides continue to count their casualties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This divisive issue showcases the challenge America faces in crafting a unified approach to foreign policy, with deeply entrenched political divides at play. As the situation develops, the debate is bound to intensify, shedding light on the complexities of U.S. politics in the global arena.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">DC Crime Wave: Robbery Victim’s Harrowing Testimony Exposes Lenient Policies</title><link href="/news/2023/10/15/DC-Crime-Surge/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="DC Crime Wave: Robbery Victim’s Harrowing Testimony Exposes Lenient Policies" /><published>2023-10-15T13:06:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-15T13:06:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/15/DC-Crime-Surge</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/15/DC-Crime-Surge/">&lt;p&gt;Recent testimony by Mitchell Sobolevsky, a robbery victim, has reignited the debate about crime rates and sentencing policies in Washington, D.C. Sobolevsky shared his harrowing story of being robbed at gunpoint near the White House and expressed concern about the leniency of sentencing for violent offenders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During a walk from his apartment to the grocery store in December 2020, Sobolevsky noticed a suspicious man eyeing him. The initially peaceful walk soon turned into a nightmare as the man demanded money and brandished a gun at Sobolevsky’s face. Recounting the incident, Sobolevsky stated he felt as though he’d become “just another statistic” in a city marred by rising violent crime.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The narrative took an alarming turn when Sobolevsky revealed that the perpetrator had his sentence reduced, even after robbing multiple victims and businesses. Not long after his release, the same criminal committed two more armed robberies. Sobolevsky pleaded with the court for a stricter sentence, fearing that a lenient stance would embolden the criminal, but his pleas fell on deaf ears.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His experience sheds light on a disturbing trend in D.C. Although overall crime rates showed a decrease between 2021 and 2022, violent crimes have surged in 2023, with an increase of nearly 40% from the previous year. Notably, motor vehicle thefts and robberies have soared, seeing hikes of 106% and 65%, respectively.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further intensifying the issue is the fact that federal prosecutors in D.C. declined to prosecute 67% of people arrested in the past fiscal year for cases usually tried in the D.C. Superior Court. This alarming statistic has nearly doubled since 2015.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In an effort to combat the surging crime wave, Congress recently overturned a D.C. criminal code that was under fire for being too lenient. The city council also passed an emergency public safety bill, which aimed to increase penalties for specific crimes, like firing weapons in public areas and carjackings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The challenges D.C. faces are significant, with crime rates reaching levels reminiscent of the 1990s. Sobolevsky’s account serves as a stark reminder of the personal toll behind the statistics. While measures are being implemented to counteract the spike in crime, the testimonies of victims like Sobolevsky underscore the urgency and importance of more effective solutions.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Recent testimony by Mitchell Sobolevsky, a robbery victim, has reignited the debate about crime rates and sentencing policies in Washington, D.C. Sobolevsky shared his harrowing story of being robbed at gunpoint near the White House and expressed concern about the leniency of sentencing for violent offenders. During a walk from his apartment to the grocery store in December 2020, Sobolevsky noticed a suspicious man eyeing him. The initially peaceful walk soon turned into a nightmare as the man demanded money and brandished a gun at Sobolevsky’s face. Recounting the incident, Sobolevsky stated he felt as though he’d become “just another statistic” in a city marred by rising violent crime. The narrative took an alarming turn when Sobolevsky revealed that the perpetrator had his sentence reduced, even after robbing multiple victims and businesses. Not long after his release, the same criminal committed two more armed robberies. Sobolevsky pleaded with the court for a stricter sentence, fearing that a lenient stance would embolden the criminal, but his pleas fell on deaf ears. His experience sheds light on a disturbing trend in D.C. Although overall crime rates showed a decrease between 2021 and 2022, violent crimes have surged in 2023, with an increase of nearly 40% from the previous year. Notably, motor vehicle thefts and robberies have soared, seeing hikes of 106% and 65%, respectively. Further intensifying the issue is the fact that federal prosecutors in D.C. declined to prosecute 67% of people arrested in the past fiscal year for cases usually tried in the D.C. Superior Court. This alarming statistic has nearly doubled since 2015. In an effort to combat the surging crime wave, Congress recently overturned a D.C. criminal code that was under fire for being too lenient. The city council also passed an emergency public safety bill, which aimed to increase penalties for specific crimes, like firing weapons in public areas and carjackings. The challenges D.C. faces are significant, with crime rates reaching levels reminiscent of the 1990s. Sobolevsky’s account serves as a stark reminder of the personal toll behind the statistics. While measures are being implemented to counteract the spike in crime, the testimonies of victims like Sobolevsky underscore the urgency and importance of more effective solutions.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Race for Louisiana: Trump-Backed Jeff Landry in the Spotlight</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/15/Louisiana-Gubernatorial-Race/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Race for Louisiana: Trump-Backed Jeff Landry in the Spotlight" /><published>2023-10-15T11:56:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-15T11:56:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/15/Louisiana-Gubernatorial-Race</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/15/Louisiana-Gubernatorial-Race/">&lt;p&gt;Amid a crowded political arena, Louisiana’s gubernatorial race is grabbing national headlines. With Governor John Bel Edwards stepping down due to term limits, the seat has opened up, presenting Republicans with a golden opportunity to reclaim the top spot after eight years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Out of the fourteen candidates contesting under the “jungle primary” system, Attorney General Jeff Landry, backed by former President Donald Trump, stands out. Landry has not only gained significant endorsements but also enjoys a dominant fundraising advantage. Yet, with prominence comes scrutiny. Landry’s campaign has been marred by accusations of political bullying and backroom dealings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Louisiana’s electoral climate reflects a microcosm of broader national political trends. The state, which gave Trump a majority in the last two presidential elections, is seeing Republicans eagerly push to win the governor’s mansion. Conversely, Democrats, who have enjoyed the governor’s seat for the last eight years, are putting their weight behind Shawn Wilson, hoping their strategy of consolidating behind one candidate pays off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the gubernatorial race isn’t the only one catching attention. The secretary of state’s race has also drawn eyes nationwide, particularly concerning the replacement of Louisiana’s outdated voting machines. Current Secretary of State, Republican Kyle Ardoin, chose not to run for re-election. The ensuing race has been engulfed in controversies, with conspiracy theorists advocating for hand-counted paper ballots. Leading candidates, including GOP state House Speaker Clay Schexnayder and Democrat Gwen Collins-Greenup, have voiced opposition to hand-counting, underscoring the importance of reliable voting systems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the immediate outcomes, this election cycle will set the tone for Louisiana’s political future. A Republican win, especially one with Trump’s endorsement, might solidify the party’s hold, aligning state policies closer to national GOP stances. On the other hand, a Democratic victory would underline the party’s resilience in the Deep South, possibly indicating a broader regional trend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the clock ticks down to the final voting hour, one thing is certain: Louisiana’s 2023 political battles will have lasting implications, not just for the state but potentially for the nation’s political landscape.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Amid a crowded political arena, Louisiana’s gubernatorial race is grabbing national headlines. With Governor John Bel Edwards stepping down due to term limits, the seat has opened up, presenting Republicans with a golden opportunity to reclaim the top spot after eight years. Out of the fourteen candidates contesting under the “jungle primary” system, Attorney General Jeff Landry, backed by former President Donald Trump, stands out. Landry has not only gained significant endorsements but also enjoys a dominant fundraising advantage. Yet, with prominence comes scrutiny. Landry’s campaign has been marred by accusations of political bullying and backroom dealings. Louisiana’s electoral climate reflects a microcosm of broader national political trends. The state, which gave Trump a majority in the last two presidential elections, is seeing Republicans eagerly push to win the governor’s mansion. Conversely, Democrats, who have enjoyed the governor’s seat for the last eight years, are putting their weight behind Shawn Wilson, hoping their strategy of consolidating behind one candidate pays off. However, the gubernatorial race isn’t the only one catching attention. The secretary of state’s race has also drawn eyes nationwide, particularly concerning the replacement of Louisiana’s outdated voting machines. Current Secretary of State, Republican Kyle Ardoin, chose not to run for re-election. The ensuing race has been engulfed in controversies, with conspiracy theorists advocating for hand-counted paper ballots. Leading candidates, including GOP state House Speaker Clay Schexnayder and Democrat Gwen Collins-Greenup, have voiced opposition to hand-counting, underscoring the importance of reliable voting systems. Beyond the immediate outcomes, this election cycle will set the tone for Louisiana’s political future. A Republican win, especially one with Trump’s endorsement, might solidify the party’s hold, aligning state policies closer to national GOP stances. On the other hand, a Democratic victory would underline the party’s resilience in the Deep South, possibly indicating a broader regional trend. As the clock ticks down to the final voting hour, one thing is certain: Louisiana’s 2023 political battles will have lasting implications, not just for the state but potentially for the nation’s political landscape.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Shifting Sands in West Virginia: Justice Overtakes Manchin in Senate Race</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/15/Justice-vs-Manchin/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Shifting Sands in West Virginia: Justice Overtakes Manchin in Senate Race" /><published>2023-10-15T10:45:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-15T10:45:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/15/Justice-vs-Manchin</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/15/Justice-vs-Manchin/">&lt;p&gt;In a surprising turn of events, a new Emerson College Poll suggests that Republican Governor Jim Justice holds a clear lead against Democratic Senator Joe Manchin in the upcoming Senate race to represent West Virginia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This noteworthy shift in the political landscape shows Manchin, the Democratic incumbent, only garnering 28% of the vote in the projected 2024 race. In contrast, Governor Justice boasts 41% support, positioning him as the favorite for the general election. Additionally, the poll indicates that 15% of voters lean towards alternative candidates, while another 16% remain undecided, leaving room for potential swings in sentiment as the race progresses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Senator Manchin currently lags behind Justice, the same poll indicates a slight lead over Republican Representative Alex Mooney, 37% to 31%. Mooney, who declared his intention to compete for Manchin’s Senate seat just days after clinching re-election to the House in November, expressed confidence in his ability to overcome his long-established opponent. Justice, on the other hand, announced his Senate candidacy in April during a memorable 72nd birthday celebration. He emphasized his commitment to the West Virginia people, vowing to execute a role that would leave them proud.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The political debate has already commenced, with Mooney challenging Justice’s GOP primary record in April, and Manchin affirming his determination to secure re-election. In a statement, Manchin emphasized, “I am laser-focused on fulfilling my duties to West Virginians — from reducing healthcare costs to strengthening American energy security. But let there be no confusion, I intend to win any race I enter.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Emerson poll sheds light on additional political sentiments in West Virginia. It reveals a 50% job approval rating for Justice, contrasting sharply with President Joe Biden’s 71% disapproval rating. Furthermore, even among state Democrats, the Governor secures a 34% job approval rate, closely followed by a 35% approval from independent voters. Notably, the poll underscores the divisive opinions on the 2020 presidential election, with 51% of West Virginian voters alleging election fraud against President Biden.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the political landscape remains fluid and often unpredictable, these poll numbers signal the potential for further shifts and surprises as we draw closer to the 2024 elections. Only time will reveal if these early projections hold firm or if the tides of voter sentiment shift once again.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a surprising turn of events, a new Emerson College Poll suggests that Republican Governor Jim Justice holds a clear lead against Democratic Senator Joe Manchin in the upcoming Senate race to represent West Virginia. This noteworthy shift in the political landscape shows Manchin, the Democratic incumbent, only garnering 28% of the vote in the projected 2024 race. In contrast, Governor Justice boasts 41% support, positioning him as the favorite for the general election. Additionally, the poll indicates that 15% of voters lean towards alternative candidates, while another 16% remain undecided, leaving room for potential swings in sentiment as the race progresses. While Senator Manchin currently lags behind Justice, the same poll indicates a slight lead over Republican Representative Alex Mooney, 37% to 31%. Mooney, who declared his intention to compete for Manchin’s Senate seat just days after clinching re-election to the House in November, expressed confidence in his ability to overcome his long-established opponent. Justice, on the other hand, announced his Senate candidacy in April during a memorable 72nd birthday celebration. He emphasized his commitment to the West Virginia people, vowing to execute a role that would leave them proud. The political debate has already commenced, with Mooney challenging Justice’s GOP primary record in April, and Manchin affirming his determination to secure re-election. In a statement, Manchin emphasized, “I am laser-focused on fulfilling my duties to West Virginians — from reducing healthcare costs to strengthening American energy security. But let there be no confusion, I intend to win any race I enter.” The Emerson poll sheds light on additional political sentiments in West Virginia. It reveals a 50% job approval rating for Justice, contrasting sharply with President Joe Biden’s 71% disapproval rating. Furthermore, even among state Democrats, the Governor secures a 34% job approval rate, closely followed by a 35% approval from independent voters. Notably, the poll underscores the divisive opinions on the 2020 presidential election, with 51% of West Virginian voters alleging election fraud against President Biden. As the political landscape remains fluid and often unpredictable, these poll numbers signal the potential for further shifts and surprises as we draw closer to the 2024 elections. Only time will reveal if these early projections hold firm or if the tides of voter sentiment shift once again.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">US COVID Relief Funds Under Scrutiny Amid Ties to Controversial Palestinian Group</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/15/US-Relief-Funds-Controversy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="US COVID Relief Funds Under Scrutiny Amid Ties to Controversial Palestinian Group" /><published>2023-10-15T09:30:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-15T09:30:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/15/US-Relief-Funds-Controversy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/15/US-Relief-Funds-Controversy/">&lt;p&gt;In a move that has sent shockwaves across political spheres, the Biden administration has allocated a staggering $33.7 million from the American Rescue Plan – a bill fundamentally devised for COVID relief – to the United Nations Relief &amp;amp; Works Agency (UNRWA). This comes amid growing concerns regarding the Palestinian relief organization’s alleged affiliations with Hamas, a militant group. Some critics have gone so far as to label UNRWA as “effectively a branch of Hamas.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The allocation was made through the State Department’s Migration and Refugee Assistance program, a part of a more considerable $500 million provision earmarked in the relief bill for the State Department’s refugee and migration assistance initiatives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Controversies surrounding UNRWA are not new. Over the years, they’ve been scrutinized for purportedly not doing enough to curtail aid from reaching the clutches of Hamas terrorists. There have been reports suggesting that UNRWA facilities have been used to further Hamas propaganda in schools and even shelter Hamas activities. The left-leaning New Republic, back in 2014, even painted UNRWA as “effectively a branch of Hamas.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, an alarming revelation by UN Watch earlier this year put UNRWA schools in the hot seat for allegedly propagating hatred against Jewish individuals and endorsing terrorism. While UNRWA accepted the mistakes of some of its teachers in spreading such material, they assured that no such materials are currently in circulation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To add more layers to this complex situation, President Donald Trump, during his term, had cut off UNRWA’s funding, a move that drew criticism from several quarters, suggesting that this cut-off jeopardized the essential aid needed by Gaza’s impoverished residents. Fast forward to the Biden administration, and the funding was reinstated despite the undercurrent of concerns that Hamas might indirectly benefit from such foreign aid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The revelations from an internal State Department document in March 2021 pointed out potential risks. The document conceded that there was a “high risk Hamas could potentially derive indirect, unintentional benefit from U.S. assistance to Gaza.” Yet, it also argued that such risks were justified for national security purposes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In July 2022, the Biden administration declared its contribution to UNRWA surpassed that of any other entity globally, amounting to over $618 million. The New York Post puts this number even higher, estimating a total of $730 million.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Supporters of UNRWA emphasize its crucial role in the region, highlighting the humanitarian services it provides, such as education, health care, relief, and emergency response. Currently, as per the United Nations, over 220,000 individuals are sheltered in 92 UNRWA schools.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The fundamental question that looms large is whether the aid is reaching the intended recipients without falling into the wrong hands. While UNRWA’s role in the region is undeniably significant, ensuring transparency and integrity in its operations is paramount. The debate over the US’s funding to UNRWA underscores the intricate balance between humanitarian support and ensuring national security.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As discussions continue and the world watches closely, the onus is on the Biden administration and UNRWA to operate with transparency and responsibility.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a move that has sent shockwaves across political spheres, the Biden administration has allocated a staggering $33.7 million from the American Rescue Plan – a bill fundamentally devised for COVID relief – to the United Nations Relief &amp;amp; Works Agency (UNRWA). This comes amid growing concerns regarding the Palestinian relief organization’s alleged affiliations with Hamas, a militant group. Some critics have gone so far as to label UNRWA as “effectively a branch of Hamas.” The allocation was made through the State Department’s Migration and Refugee Assistance program, a part of a more considerable $500 million provision earmarked in the relief bill for the State Department’s refugee and migration assistance initiatives. Controversies surrounding UNRWA are not new. Over the years, they’ve been scrutinized for purportedly not doing enough to curtail aid from reaching the clutches of Hamas terrorists. There have been reports suggesting that UNRWA facilities have been used to further Hamas propaganda in schools and even shelter Hamas activities. The left-leaning New Republic, back in 2014, even painted UNRWA as “effectively a branch of Hamas.” Furthermore, an alarming revelation by UN Watch earlier this year put UNRWA schools in the hot seat for allegedly propagating hatred against Jewish individuals and endorsing terrorism. While UNRWA accepted the mistakes of some of its teachers in spreading such material, they assured that no such materials are currently in circulation. To add more layers to this complex situation, President Donald Trump, during his term, had cut off UNRWA’s funding, a move that drew criticism from several quarters, suggesting that this cut-off jeopardized the essential aid needed by Gaza’s impoverished residents. Fast forward to the Biden administration, and the funding was reinstated despite the undercurrent of concerns that Hamas might indirectly benefit from such foreign aid. The revelations from an internal State Department document in March 2021 pointed out potential risks. The document conceded that there was a “high risk Hamas could potentially derive indirect, unintentional benefit from U.S. assistance to Gaza.” Yet, it also argued that such risks were justified for national security purposes. In July 2022, the Biden administration declared its contribution to UNRWA surpassed that of any other entity globally, amounting to over $618 million. The New York Post puts this number even higher, estimating a total of $730 million. Supporters of UNRWA emphasize its crucial role in the region, highlighting the humanitarian services it provides, such as education, health care, relief, and emergency response. Currently, as per the United Nations, over 220,000 individuals are sheltered in 92 UNRWA schools. The fundamental question that looms large is whether the aid is reaching the intended recipients without falling into the wrong hands. While UNRWA’s role in the region is undeniably significant, ensuring transparency and integrity in its operations is paramount. The debate over the US’s funding to UNRWA underscores the intricate balance between humanitarian support and ensuring national security. As discussions continue and the world watches closely, the onus is on the Biden administration and UNRWA to operate with transparency and responsibility.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">US Migrant Influx Challenges Democrat Cities: A Crisis in the Making</title><link href="/news/2023/10/15/Migrant-Crisis-US/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="US Migrant Influx Challenges Democrat Cities: A Crisis in the Making" /><published>2023-10-15T08:12:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-15T08:12:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/15/Migrant-Crisis-US</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/15/Migrant-Crisis-US/">&lt;p&gt;Amid the expansive wall marking the U.S.-Mexico divide in southern California, a significant migrant surge puts immense pressure on American cities. These new arrivals stretch local resources thin, sparking significant concerns, particularly in Democrat-led cities like San Diego, New York, and Chicago.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;San Diego stands as a prime example of the distress this surge has caused. “The reality is that we don’t have sufficient funds,” voiced Nora Vargas, a prominent Democrat in San Diego’s governance. “As we continue to plan, the numbers continue to increase.” Consequently, the city recently declared the situation a “humanitarian crisis.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Historically, immigration has been a divisive issue in the U.S. politics. But the recent record-breaking influx – with reports citing a staggering 2.4 million migrant encounters at the southern border in the past year – challenges the traditional Democratic approach of welcoming all, regardless of their entry method.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In San Diego, migrants, predominantly fleeing dire circumstances in Latin America, are tracked with wristbands indicating their crossing date. However, a massive backlog in the immigration system causes most to remain in limbo. They wait for years for a hearing, only to be moved from one crowded processing center to another and then to interstate buses. This pattern is consistently seen across southern U.S. border communities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, in Republican-led Texas, Governor Greg Abbott’s strategy has been to transport migrants to major cities like New York and Chicago, shifting the responsibility to their Democrat leadership. Mayor Eric Adams of New York, having absorbed over 100,000 migrants in a year, stated, “The president and the White House have failed this city.” The mounting crisis, estimated to cost New York nearly $5 billion, forced Adams to declare a state of emergency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Illinois Governor JB Pritzker shared similar sentiments, remarking, “The federal government’s lack of intervention and coordination at the border has created an untenable situation for Illinois.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The criticism comes at a critical time, just a year before the presidential elections, painting the Biden administration in a precarious light. As American households grapple with rising living costs, the narrative that the borders are left unchecked becomes more potent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Robert Vivar, associated with the San Diego Episcopal Diocese, highlighted the broader issue – a system ill-equipped for the current challenges. With neither political party providing a comprehensive solution, the country remains at an impasse. “Decisions are made about our border 3,000 miles away,” Vargas concluded. It’s a clear call to action, urging policymakers to witness the issues firsthand and develop tangible solutions.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Amid the expansive wall marking the U.S.-Mexico divide in southern California, a significant migrant surge puts immense pressure on American cities. These new arrivals stretch local resources thin, sparking significant concerns, particularly in Democrat-led cities like San Diego, New York, and Chicago. San Diego stands as a prime example of the distress this surge has caused. “The reality is that we don’t have sufficient funds,” voiced Nora Vargas, a prominent Democrat in San Diego’s governance. “As we continue to plan, the numbers continue to increase.” Consequently, the city recently declared the situation a “humanitarian crisis.” Historically, immigration has been a divisive issue in the U.S. politics. But the recent record-breaking influx – with reports citing a staggering 2.4 million migrant encounters at the southern border in the past year – challenges the traditional Democratic approach of welcoming all, regardless of their entry method. In San Diego, migrants, predominantly fleeing dire circumstances in Latin America, are tracked with wristbands indicating their crossing date. However, a massive backlog in the immigration system causes most to remain in limbo. They wait for years for a hearing, only to be moved from one crowded processing center to another and then to interstate buses. This pattern is consistently seen across southern U.S. border communities. Interestingly, in Republican-led Texas, Governor Greg Abbott’s strategy has been to transport migrants to major cities like New York and Chicago, shifting the responsibility to their Democrat leadership. Mayor Eric Adams of New York, having absorbed over 100,000 migrants in a year, stated, “The president and the White House have failed this city.” The mounting crisis, estimated to cost New York nearly $5 billion, forced Adams to declare a state of emergency. Illinois Governor JB Pritzker shared similar sentiments, remarking, “The federal government’s lack of intervention and coordination at the border has created an untenable situation for Illinois.” The criticism comes at a critical time, just a year before the presidential elections, painting the Biden administration in a precarious light. As American households grapple with rising living costs, the narrative that the borders are left unchecked becomes more potent. Robert Vivar, associated with the San Diego Episcopal Diocese, highlighted the broader issue – a system ill-equipped for the current challenges. With neither political party providing a comprehensive solution, the country remains at an impasse. “Decisions are made about our border 3,000 miles away,” Vargas concluded. It’s a clear call to action, urging policymakers to witness the issues firsthand and develop tangible solutions.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Whiteman Air Force Base Oversight: Kids Exposed to Dangerous Radon Levels</title><link href="/news/2023/10/15/Air-Force-Radon-Exposure/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Whiteman Air Force Base Oversight: Kids Exposed to Dangerous Radon Levels" /><published>2023-10-15T07:02:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-15T07:02:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/15/Air-Force-Radon-Exposure</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/15/Air-Force-Radon-Exposure/">&lt;p&gt;Whiteman Air Force Base in Missouri is facing intense scrutiny and public concern after a memo revealed that they overlooked alarming radon gas levels at a base daycare center for over a year. This lapse in action could have potentially exposed children to the toxic gas, which is a leading cause of lung cancer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to the memo, shared with the “Air Force amn/nco/snco” Facebook page and confirmed authentic by the Air Force, tests from 2022 revealed toxic gas levels above the federally accepted limit in the daycare’s baby and toddler rooms. Despite the concerning readings, there were no immediate actions taken until an audit in September 2023 brought the oversight to light.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Radon, a naturally occurring radioactive gas, is undetectable to human senses. It emerges from the decay of uranium in soil, water, and rocks and can infiltrate buildings through foundation gaps. Prolonged exposure to radon is the second most common cause of lung cancer in the U.S., following smoking. The memo highlighted readings of 1.24 WLM/year in the baby room and 6.33 WLM/year in the toddler room, both of which surpass the acceptable exposure limit of 0.8 WLM/year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a bid to control the fallout from this revelation, the base has initiated a series of actions. The civil engineering department will undertake additional testing in the facility, and rooms with concerning radon levels will be temporarily closed. Collaborations with the Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) are in place to implement effective mitigation measures swiftly. Moreover, a prioritized medical appointment system has been established for children potentially exposed to the harmful gas, and efforts are underway to identify all potentially affected individuals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the grim nature of the findings, the Air Force seeks to reassure parents and the public. The memo stated that the risk of children developing lung cancer due to exposure at the Child Development Center is “significantly less than 1%.” However, this attempt at reassurance will likely be little consolation to families who trusted the base to provide a safe environment for their children.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An Air Force spokesperson emphasized their commitment to rectifying the situation, stating, “It goes without saying that we take this seriously. We are implementing steps to ensure the safety of children and workers at the site.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This incident underscores the necessity for stringent safety checks and immediate action when potential hazards are identified, especially in facilities catering to vulnerable populations like children. As the investigation continues, the Air Force Base pledges regular updates to keep the community informed.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Whiteman Air Force Base in Missouri is facing intense scrutiny and public concern after a memo revealed that they overlooked alarming radon gas levels at a base daycare center for over a year. This lapse in action could have potentially exposed children to the toxic gas, which is a leading cause of lung cancer. According to the memo, shared with the “Air Force amn/nco/snco” Facebook page and confirmed authentic by the Air Force, tests from 2022 revealed toxic gas levels above the federally accepted limit in the daycare’s baby and toddler rooms. Despite the concerning readings, there were no immediate actions taken until an audit in September 2023 brought the oversight to light. Radon, a naturally occurring radioactive gas, is undetectable to human senses. It emerges from the decay of uranium in soil, water, and rocks and can infiltrate buildings through foundation gaps. Prolonged exposure to radon is the second most common cause of lung cancer in the U.S., following smoking. The memo highlighted readings of 1.24 WLM/year in the baby room and 6.33 WLM/year in the toddler room, both of which surpass the acceptable exposure limit of 0.8 WLM/year. In a bid to control the fallout from this revelation, the base has initiated a series of actions. The civil engineering department will undertake additional testing in the facility, and rooms with concerning radon levels will be temporarily closed. Collaborations with the Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) are in place to implement effective mitigation measures swiftly. Moreover, a prioritized medical appointment system has been established for children potentially exposed to the harmful gas, and efforts are underway to identify all potentially affected individuals. Despite the grim nature of the findings, the Air Force seeks to reassure parents and the public. The memo stated that the risk of children developing lung cancer due to exposure at the Child Development Center is “significantly less than 1%.” However, this attempt at reassurance will likely be little consolation to families who trusted the base to provide a safe environment for their children. An Air Force spokesperson emphasized their commitment to rectifying the situation, stating, “It goes without saying that we take this seriously. We are implementing steps to ensure the safety of children and workers at the site.” This incident underscores the necessity for stringent safety checks and immediate action when potential hazards are identified, especially in facilities catering to vulnerable populations like children. As the investigation continues, the Air Force Base pledges regular updates to keep the community informed.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Olympic Icon Mary Lou Retton Battles Rare Pneumonia, Shows Inspiring Recovery</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/15/Mary-Lou-Retton-Recovery/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Olympic Icon Mary Lou Retton Battles Rare Pneumonia, Shows Inspiring Recovery" /><published>2023-10-15T06:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-15T06:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/15/Mary-Lou-Retton-Recovery</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/15/Mary-Lou-Retton-Recovery/">&lt;p&gt;In an update that has brought relief to millions of fans, Olympic gold medalist Mary Lou Retton is making a “remarkable” recovery from a rare form of pneumonia. The gymnastics legend, often dubbed as “America’s Sweetheart” for her iconic performance in the 1984 Olympics, faced a life-threatening situation and had been in intensive care, relying on machines to breathe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shayla Schrepfer, Retton’s daughter, shared the heartening news on her Instagram. She emphasized how the prayers and well-wishes from countless fans have been felt and appear to have been answered. While Retton continues her recovery in the ICU, she’s showcasing the same fighting spirit that once won her a gold medal. Notably, her reliance on breathing machines is reducing, and her overall health is improving.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The news of Retton’s hospitalization had deeply affected fans and supporters, leading to an overwhelming display of love and concern. Demonstrating the depth of admiration and love the nation holds for the gymnast, a fundraising page set up to aid in her treatment collected over $400,000 in donations by Saturday afternoon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mary Lou Retton’s memorable performance at the 1984 Olympic Games in Los Angeles isn’t just a testament to her talent, but it also symbolizes hope and determination. The same spirit seems to be guiding her through this challenging time. Shayla Schrepfer’s update gives a ray of hope, stating, “Though it’s a lengthy journey, witnessing these improvements is incredibly heartening. She’s responding so well to treatments.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This incident serves as a reminder of the transient nature of life and the unpredictable challenges it brings. However, with determination, support, and the right care, even the most daunting obstacles can be overcome. The entire nation watches with bated breath, hoping and praying for the full recovery of their beloved Olympic icon.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">In an update that has brought relief to millions of fans, Olympic gold medalist Mary Lou Retton is making a “remarkable” recovery from a rare form of pneumonia. The gymnastics legend, often dubbed as “America’s Sweetheart” for her iconic performance in the 1984 Olympics, faced a life-threatening situation and had been in intensive care, relying on machines to breathe. Shayla Schrepfer, Retton’s daughter, shared the heartening news on her Instagram. She emphasized how the prayers and well-wishes from countless fans have been felt and appear to have been answered. While Retton continues her recovery in the ICU, she’s showcasing the same fighting spirit that once won her a gold medal. Notably, her reliance on breathing machines is reducing, and her overall health is improving. The news of Retton’s hospitalization had deeply affected fans and supporters, leading to an overwhelming display of love and concern. Demonstrating the depth of admiration and love the nation holds for the gymnast, a fundraising page set up to aid in her treatment collected over $400,000 in donations by Saturday afternoon. Mary Lou Retton’s memorable performance at the 1984 Olympic Games in Los Angeles isn’t just a testament to her talent, but it also symbolizes hope and determination. The same spirit seems to be guiding her through this challenging time. Shayla Schrepfer’s update gives a ray of hope, stating, “Though it’s a lengthy journey, witnessing these improvements is incredibly heartening. She’s responding so well to treatments.” This incident serves as a reminder of the transient nature of life and the unpredictable challenges it brings. However, with determination, support, and the right care, even the most daunting obstacles can be overcome. The entire nation watches with bated breath, hoping and praying for the full recovery of their beloved Olympic icon.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Rising Concerns Among Democrats Over Biden’s Age and Health</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/14/Biden-Age-Concerns/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rising Concerns Among Democrats Over Biden’s Age and Health" /><published>2023-10-14T16:15:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-14T16:15:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/14/Biden-Age-Concerns</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/14/Biden-Age-Concerns/">&lt;p&gt;As President Joe Biden’s term unfolds, a growing chorus of concerns has emerged from the Democratic ranks, as recent polling suggests a majority of voters perceive him as “old, slowing down,” and even “feeble.” These worries are further fueled by the President’s age, which stands at 80, leading to skepticism about his ability to seek another term.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The polling data, which paint a picture of an aging President, is reportedly causing unease among Democrats. The spotlight on Biden’s age is further intensified by focus groups, where swing voters frequently label him using terms like “old, slowing down”, or more critically as having “dementia” or being “feeble”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Senator Jeanne Shaheen (D-NH) recently voiced the need for the Democratic Party to address these growing apprehensions, especially with the looming possibility of a rematch against former President Donald Trump. Another vocal Senator, Jon Tester (D-MT), highlighted the undeniable reality of Biden’s age, pointing out that he would be 82 during the next election.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As party members grapple with this data, there’s an overarching sentiment that President Biden hasn’t done enough to challenge these perceptions. Politico’s insights suggest that the President has shown little interest in countering the negative image that’s slowly being cemented in the public’s view.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adding to concerns are Biden’s physical health issues. Though he suffers from atrial fibrillation, peripheral neuropathy in his feet, and hyperlipidemia, his physician, Dr. Kevin O’Connor, after a physical examination in February, confirmed that the President is fit to conduct presidential duties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, Politico’s Jonathan Martin notes certain limitations in Biden’s interactions with the media, which has a cascading effect on his public perception. Instead of directly addressing questions about the economy and public sentiment, Biden often digresses, losing potential opportunities to challenge his opponents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amidst these age-related concerns, some Republicans suggest that focusing on Biden’s mental or physical capacity isn’t a fruitful strategy for the upcoming elections. They believe the spotlight should be on Biden’s policy decisions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Poll results emphasize the President’s challenges, revealing approval ratings below 50% across critical issues such as inflation, immigration, crime, terrorism, and foreign affairs. With such figures in play, it’s evident that the coming months will be crucial for Biden and the Democratic Party as they strategize for the 2024 elections.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">As President Joe Biden’s term unfolds, a growing chorus of concerns has emerged from the Democratic ranks, as recent polling suggests a majority of voters perceive him as “old, slowing down,” and even “feeble.” These worries are further fueled by the President’s age, which stands at 80, leading to skepticism about his ability to seek another term. The polling data, which paint a picture of an aging President, is reportedly causing unease among Democrats. The spotlight on Biden’s age is further intensified by focus groups, where swing voters frequently label him using terms like “old, slowing down”, or more critically as having “dementia” or being “feeble”. Senator Jeanne Shaheen (D-NH) recently voiced the need for the Democratic Party to address these growing apprehensions, especially with the looming possibility of a rematch against former President Donald Trump. Another vocal Senator, Jon Tester (D-MT), highlighted the undeniable reality of Biden’s age, pointing out that he would be 82 during the next election. As party members grapple with this data, there’s an overarching sentiment that President Biden hasn’t done enough to challenge these perceptions. Politico’s insights suggest that the President has shown little interest in countering the negative image that’s slowly being cemented in the public’s view. Adding to concerns are Biden’s physical health issues. Though he suffers from atrial fibrillation, peripheral neuropathy in his feet, and hyperlipidemia, his physician, Dr. Kevin O’Connor, after a physical examination in February, confirmed that the President is fit to conduct presidential duties. However, Politico’s Jonathan Martin notes certain limitations in Biden’s interactions with the media, which has a cascading effect on his public perception. Instead of directly addressing questions about the economy and public sentiment, Biden often digresses, losing potential opportunities to challenge his opponents. Amidst these age-related concerns, some Republicans suggest that focusing on Biden’s mental or physical capacity isn’t a fruitful strategy for the upcoming elections. They believe the spotlight should be on Biden’s policy decisions. Poll results emphasize the President’s challenges, revealing approval ratings below 50% across critical issues such as inflation, immigration, crime, terrorism, and foreign affairs. With such figures in play, it’s evident that the coming months will be crucial for Biden and the Democratic Party as they strategize for the 2024 elections.</summary></entry></feed>