<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-11-09T12:14:07-05:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/11/09/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-11-09T12:14:07-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-09T12:14:07-05:00</updated><id>/2023/11/09/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/11/09/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/11/09/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-11-09T12:14:07-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-09T12:14:07-05:00</updated><id>/2023/11/09/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/11/09/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/">&lt;p&gt;Recent surprise attacks by Hamas on Israel has fueled ongoing tensions between staunchly conservative commentators and the progressive “Squad” Democrats known for criticizing Israel. The intensity of the backlash highlights the deep political divide over foreign policy in the Middle East.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Hamas’ shocking attack, several members of the “Squad,” including Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.), called for a “ceasefire and de-escalation,” condemning the violence. The absence of a statement from Rep. Rashida Tlaib (D-Mich.) was notably called out by conservative media outlets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;South Carolina GOP Rep. Nancy Mace quickly labeled Ocasio-Cortez a “Hamas apologist” in response to her call for peace and de-escalation. Rep. Ilhan Omar (D-Minn.), no stranger to controversy surrounding her views on Israel, echoed the call for de-escalation and ceasefire. Omar’s prior statements comparing the US and Israel to terrorist groups like Hamas and the Taliban resurfaced in the debate, fueling more criticisms. Omar’s 2019 tweet, where she opined that “Israel has hypnotized the world,” also continues to haunt her political career, often cited by critics to challenge her stance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conservative commentators have been especially vocal. “FOX &amp;amp; Friends Weekend” co-host Rachel Campos-Duffy took aim at Omar, saying she fails to recognize the peace in the Middle East under Trump’s administration. Conservative pundit John Hasson also called out Omar, claiming she insinuated that attacks on IDF forces were acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Massachusetts Democrat Rep. Ayanna Pressley’s concerns over the “devastating attacks on Israelis” were met with skepticism. A prominent conservative online personality, Comfortably Smug, accused the “Squad” of advising Israel to back down after the nation suffered massive attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Jamaal Bowman’s call for an end to the Gaza blockade, in addition to condemning the Hamas attacks, was met with criticism from conservative radio host Jason Rantz. He accused Bowman of pairing his condemnation of terrorism with unwarranted criticisms of Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Cori Bush emphasized the urgent need for a ceasefire, while pushing for an end to “U.S. support for Israeli military occupation and apartheid.” Defense attorney Marina Medvin criticized Bush, suggesting that she equates the death of Palestinian terrorists to the horrific acts committed against Jewish civilians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amidst the political turmoil and intense debate, the attacks have taken a heavy toll. Israeli media report over 300 dead due to the wide-ranging assault. Gaza health officials note that at least 200 Palestinians have perished in the retaliatory Israeli air strikes following the initial Hamas attack. As the situation remains volatile, both sides continue to count their casualties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This divisive issue showcases the challenge America faces in crafting a unified approach to foreign policy, with deeply entrenched political divides at play. As the situation develops, the debate is bound to intensify, shedding light on the complexities of U.S. politics in the global arena.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Donald Trump Jr. Takes Aim at McConnell’s Ukraine Stance at Florida Rally</title><link href="/news/2023/11/09/Mitch-McConnell-Mockery/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Donald Trump Jr. Takes Aim at McConnell’s Ukraine Stance at Florida Rally" /><published>2023-11-09T10:58:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-09T10:58:00-05:00</updated><id>/news/2023/11/09/Mitch-McConnell-Mockery</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/11/09/Mitch-McConnell-Mockery/">&lt;p&gt;In a fiery display of political theater, Donald Trump Jr. lambasted Senate Minority Leader Mitch McConnell’s stance on Ukraine, coining the term ‘Mitch glitch’ to mock the veteran senator’s recent public freeze-ups. The crowd at the Hialeah, Florida rally, which was held concurrently with the third Republican primary debate, roared with laughter as Don Jr. theatrically mimicked McConnell’s infamous mid-speech pauses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The rally, spearheaded by former President Donald Trump, turned into a referendum on GOP leadership and priorities as Don Jr. questioned the audience about their stance on U.S. aid to Ukraine. The overwhelming response from the attendees signaled a stark disconnect between the GOP base and McConnell’s policy focus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The term ‘Mitch glitch’ quickly resonated with the crowd, encapsulating their discontent with McConnell’s unwavering support for Ukraine amidst a plethora of domestic issues that rally-goers feel should take precedence. Don Jr.’s performance tapped into a vein of frustration among conservative voters who are calling for a shift away from what they perceive as establishment-driven, interventionist foreign policy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a rhetorical survey of the audience, Don Jr. challenged them to raise their hands if they considered funding Ukraine to be among their top priorities. The lack of any hands raised painted a clear picture of the crowd’s stance, which Don Jr. highlighted by declaring no one saw it as even a top ten issue. His point was underscored by an anecdote that, out of 30,000 people surveyed at various rallies, only one hand had gone up in support — and that was from a Ukrainian national.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don Jr.’s critique extended beyond McConnell, as he called out Senate Republicans and so-called “RINOs” (Republicans In Name Only) to heed the voice of the people. His plea for “actual representation” from elected officials resonated with the attendees, who are yearning for a Republican party that aligns more closely with their values and concerns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The sharp critique of McConnell’s foreign policy stance by the former First Son at this rally highlights a growing rift within the Republican Party, as grassroots energy pushes against established norms. The ‘Mitch glitch’ moment at the rally has become symbolic of this tension, emphasizing the desire for a reorientation of the GOP’s priorities towards the pressing needs of the American people.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a fiery display of political theater, Donald Trump Jr. lambasted Senate Minority Leader Mitch McConnell’s stance on Ukraine, coining the term ‘Mitch glitch’ to mock the veteran senator’s recent public freeze-ups. The crowd at the Hialeah, Florida rally, which was held concurrently with the third Republican primary debate, roared with laughter as Don Jr. theatrically mimicked McConnell’s infamous mid-speech pauses. The rally, spearheaded by former President Donald Trump, turned into a referendum on GOP leadership and priorities as Don Jr. questioned the audience about their stance on U.S. aid to Ukraine. The overwhelming response from the attendees signaled a stark disconnect between the GOP base and McConnell’s policy focus. The term ‘Mitch glitch’ quickly resonated with the crowd, encapsulating their discontent with McConnell’s unwavering support for Ukraine amidst a plethora of domestic issues that rally-goers feel should take precedence. Don Jr.’s performance tapped into a vein of frustration among conservative voters who are calling for a shift away from what they perceive as establishment-driven, interventionist foreign policy. In a rhetorical survey of the audience, Don Jr. challenged them to raise their hands if they considered funding Ukraine to be among their top priorities. The lack of any hands raised painted a clear picture of the crowd’s stance, which Don Jr. highlighted by declaring no one saw it as even a top ten issue. His point was underscored by an anecdote that, out of 30,000 people surveyed at various rallies, only one hand had gone up in support — and that was from a Ukrainian national. Don Jr.’s critique extended beyond McConnell, as he called out Senate Republicans and so-called “RINOs” (Republicans In Name Only) to heed the voice of the people. His plea for “actual representation” from elected officials resonated with the attendees, who are yearning for a Republican party that aligns more closely with their values and concerns. The sharp critique of McConnell’s foreign policy stance by the former First Son at this rally highlights a growing rift within the Republican Party, as grassroots energy pushes against established norms. The ‘Mitch glitch’ moment at the rally has become symbolic of this tension, emphasizing the desire for a reorientation of the GOP’s priorities towards the pressing needs of the American people.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">House Oversight Subpoenas Biden Family in Sweeping Business Dealings Inquiry</title><link href="/politics/2023/11/09/Biden-Family-Subpoena/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="House Oversight Subpoenas Biden Family in Sweeping Business Dealings Inquiry" /><published>2023-11-09T09:45:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-09T09:45:00-05:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/11/09/Biden-Family-Subpoena</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/11/09/Biden-Family-Subpoena/">&lt;p&gt;In a striking escalation of their probe into the Biden family’s business engagements, the House Oversight Committee has issued subpoenas for testimony from Hunter Biden, James Biden, and business associate Rob Walker. This decisive move signals the committee’s intensified efforts to unravel the intricacies of the Biden family’s global business operations and any potential involvement of President Biden.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The sweeping investigation, spearheaded by the House Oversight Committee, digs deeper into the complex web of the Biden family’s financial transactions. The panel’s action includes a call for transcribed interviews from several close associates and family members of President Biden, further expanding the scope of the inquiry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The subpoenas come on the heels of earlier financial record subpoenas that unveiled over $1 million in payments to Bidens from accounts associated with Rob Walker. This revelation has added fuel to the House GOP’s determination to uncover the full extent of the Biden family’s dealings, particularly those that could link President Biden to various business ventures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the heart of the investigation is a contentious debate over whether the President was privy to or financially benefited from these enterprises. The subpoenas and interviews are poised to play a pivotal role in the ongoing impeachment inquiry against President Biden, led by a trio of key GOP committee chairmen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The call for testimony from Hunter and James Biden, as well as Rob Walker, punctuates a series of probes that have scrutinized bank records and financial transactions linked to the Biden family. Revelations from these records have sparked new lines of questioning about the extent of the President’s awareness and involvement in his family’s business pursuits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hunter Biden, a central figure in the controversy, has faced intense scrutiny over his business ties, with financial dealings involving Chinese energy firms and other overseas interests drawing particular attention. The discovery of significant payments to members of the Biden family, and the subsequent subpoena for Hunter Biden, underscores the gravity of the committee’s investigation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Oversight Committee’s bold steps send a clear message of accountability and transparency, underscoring the GOP’s commitment to examining the intersection of private business and public service. As the investigation unfolds, the testimonies of Hunter and James Biden, along with their associates, could shed light on a saga that has captured the nation’s attention and raised serious ethical questions.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a striking escalation of their probe into the Biden family’s business engagements, the House Oversight Committee has issued subpoenas for testimony from Hunter Biden, James Biden, and business associate Rob Walker. This decisive move signals the committee’s intensified efforts to unravel the intricacies of the Biden family’s global business operations and any potential involvement of President Biden. The sweeping investigation, spearheaded by the House Oversight Committee, digs deeper into the complex web of the Biden family’s financial transactions. The panel’s action includes a call for transcribed interviews from several close associates and family members of President Biden, further expanding the scope of the inquiry. The subpoenas come on the heels of earlier financial record subpoenas that unveiled over $1 million in payments to Bidens from accounts associated with Rob Walker. This revelation has added fuel to the House GOP’s determination to uncover the full extent of the Biden family’s dealings, particularly those that could link President Biden to various business ventures. At the heart of the investigation is a contentious debate over whether the President was privy to or financially benefited from these enterprises. The subpoenas and interviews are poised to play a pivotal role in the ongoing impeachment inquiry against President Biden, led by a trio of key GOP committee chairmen. The call for testimony from Hunter and James Biden, as well as Rob Walker, punctuates a series of probes that have scrutinized bank records and financial transactions linked to the Biden family. Revelations from these records have sparked new lines of questioning about the extent of the President’s awareness and involvement in his family’s business pursuits. Hunter Biden, a central figure in the controversy, has faced intense scrutiny over his business ties, with financial dealings involving Chinese energy firms and other overseas interests drawing particular attention. The discovery of significant payments to members of the Biden family, and the subsequent subpoena for Hunter Biden, underscores the gravity of the committee’s investigation. The Oversight Committee’s bold steps send a clear message of accountability and transparency, underscoring the GOP’s commitment to examining the intersection of private business and public service. As the investigation unfolds, the testimonies of Hunter and James Biden, along with their associates, could shed light on a saga that has captured the nation’s attention and raised serious ethical questions.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump Promises Unprecedented Deportation Effort to Reinforce U.S. Borders</title><link href="/politics/2023/11/09/Deportation-Operation/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump Promises Unprecedented Deportation Effort to Reinforce U.S. Borders" /><published>2023-11-09T08:34:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-09T08:34:00-05:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/11/09/Deportation-Operation</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/11/09/Deportation-Operation/">&lt;p&gt;In a decisive declaration at his Hialeah, Florida rally, former President Donald Trump committed to what he termed the “largest domestic deportation operation” in U.S. history, as part of his campaign promises. The bold statement came Wednesday night as Trump outlined his vision to reinforce U.S. borders and restore immigration policies that were dismantled under the Biden administration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump’s commitment underscores a return to his hallmark border security policies, which include staunch measures against illegal immigration. Addressing a charged crowd, he expressed a sense of urgency to address what he perceives as a national security threat, stating, “We have bad people, terrorists at levels that nobody has ever seen.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The former president criticized the current administration’s handling of border policies, suggesting that it has allowed terrorists to infiltrate the U.S. amid the ongoing Middle Eastern unrest. Trump emphasized the need for legal immigration processes, saying, “We wanted people to come to our country, but we wanted them to come in legally, legally.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With national security at the forefront of his address, Trump extended his rhetoric to those who participated in protests he described as pro-jihadist, indicating a zero-tolerance approach. “To all the resident aliens who joined in the pro-jihadist protests… We put you on notice, Come 2025, we will find you and we will deport you,” he declared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump’s promises at the rally reflect his continued commitment to conservative principles on immigration and border control, a cornerstone of his previous administration and a key issue for his campaign. His resolve to conduct a sweeping deportation operation aims to resonate with voters who prioritize the integrity of national borders and the rule of law.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the rally concluded, Trump’s message was clear: a reinvigorated focus on deporting individuals who are in the country illegally and pose a threat to national security. While the specifics of such an operation remain to be detailed, Trump’s address in Florida has undoubtedly set a definitive tone for his campaign’s approach to immigration and homeland security.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a decisive declaration at his Hialeah, Florida rally, former President Donald Trump committed to what he termed the “largest domestic deportation operation” in U.S. history, as part of his campaign promises. The bold statement came Wednesday night as Trump outlined his vision to reinforce U.S. borders and restore immigration policies that were dismantled under the Biden administration. Trump’s commitment underscores a return to his hallmark border security policies, which include staunch measures against illegal immigration. Addressing a charged crowd, he expressed a sense of urgency to address what he perceives as a national security threat, stating, “We have bad people, terrorists at levels that nobody has ever seen.” The former president criticized the current administration’s handling of border policies, suggesting that it has allowed terrorists to infiltrate the U.S. amid the ongoing Middle Eastern unrest. Trump emphasized the need for legal immigration processes, saying, “We wanted people to come to our country, but we wanted them to come in legally, legally.” With national security at the forefront of his address, Trump extended his rhetoric to those who participated in protests he described as pro-jihadist, indicating a zero-tolerance approach. “To all the resident aliens who joined in the pro-jihadist protests… We put you on notice, Come 2025, we will find you and we will deport you,” he declared. Trump’s promises at the rally reflect his continued commitment to conservative principles on immigration and border control, a cornerstone of his previous administration and a key issue for his campaign. His resolve to conduct a sweeping deportation operation aims to resonate with voters who prioritize the integrity of national borders and the rule of law. As the rally concluded, Trump’s message was clear: a reinvigorated focus on deporting individuals who are in the country illegally and pose a threat to national security. While the specifics of such an operation remain to be detailed, Trump’s address in Florida has undoubtedly set a definitive tone for his campaign’s approach to immigration and homeland security.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Strike Curtain Call: SAG-AFTRA Reaches Historic Deal with Studios</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/11/09/Hollywood-Strike-End/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Strike Curtain Call: SAG-AFTRA Reaches Historic Deal with Studios" /><published>2023-11-09T07:24:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-09T07:24:00-05:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/11/09/Hollywood-Strike-End</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/11/09/Hollywood-Strike-End/">&lt;p&gt;After more than three months of stalled productions and fervent negotiations, the stage is set for a return to normalcy in Hollywood. SAG-AFTRA, the union representing actors, and the Alliance of Motion Picture and Television Producers (AMPTP) have reached a tentative agreement, bringing an end to the historic 118-day strike that shook the core of the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The agreement, which was reached with a unanimous vote, signals a new era of protections and pay raises for actors. With the ink set to dry at 12:01 a.m. on Thursday, the entertainment industry breathes a collective sigh of relief. The union touted the deal as historic, particularly highlighting the first-ever protections against artificial intelligence that could impact actors’ livelihoods.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The resolution of the strike hinged on a pivotal and unanimous vote, with details of the agreement eagerly anticipated to be disclosed following a national board vote on Friday. Among the key victories for SAG-AFTRA members are the significant increases in minimums—up by 7%, which overshadows the increases secured by other industry guilds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the most complex issues—artificial intelligence and its potential to revolutionize or disrupt the traditional ways of Hollywood—was among the last to be ironed out. Duncan Crabtree-Ireland, SAG-AFTRA’s chief negotiator, and Carol Lombardini, AMPTP’s CEO, engaged in critical discussions to finalize the terms that would eventually lead to the strike’s conclusion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Hollywood community, both on and offline, celebrated the end of the strike, which was felt by everyone from the most celebrated on-screen talents to the hardworking crews behind the scenes. The deal’s conclusion was not only a win for the actors but also signaled a positive shift for an industry grappling with technological advancements and new forms of content delivery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The SAG-AFTRA strike’s conclusion is a testament to the power of collective bargaining and the resilience of union members. As the industry prepares to return to its bustling activity, the summer of 2024 looks brighter for both the creators and the audiences who cherish the magic of movies and television.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">After more than three months of stalled productions and fervent negotiations, the stage is set for a return to normalcy in Hollywood. SAG-AFTRA, the union representing actors, and the Alliance of Motion Picture and Television Producers (AMPTP) have reached a tentative agreement, bringing an end to the historic 118-day strike that shook the core of the entertainment industry. The agreement, which was reached with a unanimous vote, signals a new era of protections and pay raises for actors. With the ink set to dry at 12:01 a.m. on Thursday, the entertainment industry breathes a collective sigh of relief. The union touted the deal as historic, particularly highlighting the first-ever protections against artificial intelligence that could impact actors’ livelihoods. The resolution of the strike hinged on a pivotal and unanimous vote, with details of the agreement eagerly anticipated to be disclosed following a national board vote on Friday. Among the key victories for SAG-AFTRA members are the significant increases in minimums—up by 7%, which overshadows the increases secured by other industry guilds. One of the most complex issues—artificial intelligence and its potential to revolutionize or disrupt the traditional ways of Hollywood—was among the last to be ironed out. Duncan Crabtree-Ireland, SAG-AFTRA’s chief negotiator, and Carol Lombardini, AMPTP’s CEO, engaged in critical discussions to finalize the terms that would eventually lead to the strike’s conclusion. The Hollywood community, both on and offline, celebrated the end of the strike, which was felt by everyone from the most celebrated on-screen talents to the hardworking crews behind the scenes. The deal’s conclusion was not only a win for the actors but also signaled a positive shift for an industry grappling with technological advancements and new forms of content delivery. The SAG-AFTRA strike’s conclusion is a testament to the power of collective bargaining and the resilience of union members. As the industry prepares to return to its bustling activity, the summer of 2024 looks brighter for both the creators and the audiences who cherish the magic of movies and television.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ex-Jill Biden Spox Calls Out President’s Team Amid Dismal Poll Performance</title><link href="/news/2023/11/09/Biden-Poll-Numbers/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ex-Jill Biden Spox Calls Out President’s Team Amid Dismal Poll Performance" /><published>2023-11-09T06:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-09T06:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/news/2023/11/09/Biden-Poll-Numbers</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/11/09/Biden-Poll-Numbers/">&lt;p&gt;In an outspoken critique, Michael LaRosa, a former spokesperson for First Lady Jill Biden, unleashed a blistering attack on President Biden’s team in light of recent polling that spells trouble for the administration. LaRosa’s candid remarks come amid a crescendo of concerns regarding Biden’s sagging favorability ratings, suggesting an urgent need for a strategic shake-up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;LaRosa, a seasoned communications and political strategist, conveyed his frustration through a series of social media posts. In a direct and unvarnished manner, he slammed the team for allowing a decline in the President’s public image and character perception, branding it as “inexcusable” and a result of failing to counteract negative narratives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The spotlight on Biden’s team intensified following a CNN poll that placed Trump ahead of Biden in favorability—a signal, according to LaRosa, of the current team’s inability to effectively manage and respond to partisan attacks. His criticism underscored the sentiment that an administration reshuffle could demonstrate the President’s acknowledgment of the issue and a commitment to addressing it head-on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;LaRosa’s admonishment extended to the tactical aspect, condemning the Biden team for what he perceives as a lack of action against smears and misinformation. He called for the First Lady’s intervention to instigate changes, highlighting the significant impact of the team’s approach on pivotal electoral outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The former spokesperson’s comments underscore a broader sentiment within certain political circles, where there’s a palpable demand for greater responsiveness and agility from Biden’s camp in combatting political onslaughts. LaRosa’s sharp reprimand mirrors the urgency of rectifying the administration’s course to reclaim the narrative.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While LaRosa has since deleted part of his original thread, his message remains resonant with those advocating for a revitalized strategy within the Biden administration. The call to action is clear: a recalibration of the team could inject new life into Biden’s political machinery, potentially reversing the adverse trends that threaten to undermine his presidency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As this story unfolds, it’s evident that LaRosa’s critique is more than a personal outburst—it’s a reflection of the growing impatience for change among political insiders. The upcoming months could reveal whether the Biden administration heeds these warnings or continues along its current trajectory, with all the inherent risks that such a path entails.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In an outspoken critique, Michael LaRosa, a former spokesperson for First Lady Jill Biden, unleashed a blistering attack on President Biden’s team in light of recent polling that spells trouble for the administration. LaRosa’s candid remarks come amid a crescendo of concerns regarding Biden’s sagging favorability ratings, suggesting an urgent need for a strategic shake-up. LaRosa, a seasoned communications and political strategist, conveyed his frustration through a series of social media posts. In a direct and unvarnished manner, he slammed the team for allowing a decline in the President’s public image and character perception, branding it as “inexcusable” and a result of failing to counteract negative narratives. The spotlight on Biden’s team intensified following a CNN poll that placed Trump ahead of Biden in favorability—a signal, according to LaRosa, of the current team’s inability to effectively manage and respond to partisan attacks. His criticism underscored the sentiment that an administration reshuffle could demonstrate the President’s acknowledgment of the issue and a commitment to addressing it head-on. LaRosa’s admonishment extended to the tactical aspect, condemning the Biden team for what he perceives as a lack of action against smears and misinformation. He called for the First Lady’s intervention to instigate changes, highlighting the significant impact of the team’s approach on pivotal electoral outcomes. The former spokesperson’s comments underscore a broader sentiment within certain political circles, where there’s a palpable demand for greater responsiveness and agility from Biden’s camp in combatting political onslaughts. LaRosa’s sharp reprimand mirrors the urgency of rectifying the administration’s course to reclaim the narrative. While LaRosa has since deleted part of his original thread, his message remains resonant with those advocating for a revitalized strategy within the Biden administration. The call to action is clear: a recalibration of the team could inject new life into Biden’s political machinery, potentially reversing the adverse trends that threaten to undermine his presidency. As this story unfolds, it’s evident that LaRosa’s critique is more than a personal outburst—it’s a reflection of the growing impatience for change among political insiders. The upcoming months could reveal whether the Biden administration heeds these warnings or continues along its current trajectory, with all the inherent risks that such a path entails.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">House GOP Votes to Slash Transportation Secretary’s Paycheck to a Single Dollar</title><link href="/news/2023/11/08/Buttigieg-Salary-Cut/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="House GOP Votes to Slash Transportation Secretary’s Paycheck to a Single Dollar" /><published>2023-11-08T19:45:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-08T19:45:00-05:00</updated><id>/news/2023/11/08/Buttigieg-Salary-Cut</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/11/08/Buttigieg-Salary-Cut/">&lt;p&gt;In a bold statement of disapproval, House Republicans have taken a swipe at Transportation Secretary Pete Buttigieg by pushing forward an amendment to trim his salary down to a mere dollar. The measure, led by Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene of Georgia, reflects growing Republican discontent with Buttigieg’s handling of transportation issues and use of public funds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Greene, known for her fiery rhetoric and no-holds-barred approach, spearheaded the initiative as part of the 2024 Transportation, Housing, and Urban Development Appropriations Act. The amendment, which passed through a voice vote, has been framed as a means to effectively “fire” Buttigieg from his position, an outcome Greene suggests is warranted due to his alleged misuse of taxpayer dollars.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Republican lawmaker took to social media to air her grievances, where she criticized Buttigieg for what she perceives as staged photo ops and the misuse of government aircraft for personal travel, including attending events for LGBTQ rights awards. Greene’s assertion is that Buttigieg’s actions are an undue financial burden on American taxpayers who should not be responsible for funding these trips or his salary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The vote to cut Buttigieg’s salary to one dollar is largely symbolic, reflecting the House GOP’s dissatisfaction with what they see as failures and mismanagement during his tenure as transportation secretary. One of the most contentious issues is Buttigieg’s response to the toxic train derailment in East Palestine, Ohio. His delayed response to the crisis drew ire from the public and lawmakers alike, raising questions about his leadership in managing the nation’s transportation challenges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Buttigieg’s use of private jets has also come under scrutiny. Reports indicate that he has used government-managed private aircraft for travel numerous times since assuming office, drawing criticism for opting for private flights amidst widespread commercial flight cancellations and delays.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s worth noting, however, that the amendment’s passage does not guarantee a change in Buttigieg’s salary. The House GOP’s spending bills, laden with partisan goals, must contend with a Democratic-controlled Senate and an executive branch unlikely to endorse a pay cut for one of its cabinet members. Thus, while the move reflects House Republicans’ stance, it faces an uphill battle to materialize into actual policy change.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the debate over Buttigieg’s salary unfolds, it underscores the broader political tensions between the current administration and Republican lawmakers who are eager to reverse policies and decisions they deem ineffective or extravagant. The symbolic dollar salary is a sharp critique from the GOP, illustrating their intent to hold Cabinet members accountable for their performance and fiscal responsibility.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a bold statement of disapproval, House Republicans have taken a swipe at Transportation Secretary Pete Buttigieg by pushing forward an amendment to trim his salary down to a mere dollar. The measure, led by Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene of Georgia, reflects growing Republican discontent with Buttigieg’s handling of transportation issues and use of public funds. Greene, known for her fiery rhetoric and no-holds-barred approach, spearheaded the initiative as part of the 2024 Transportation, Housing, and Urban Development Appropriations Act. The amendment, which passed through a voice vote, has been framed as a means to effectively “fire” Buttigieg from his position, an outcome Greene suggests is warranted due to his alleged misuse of taxpayer dollars. The Republican lawmaker took to social media to air her grievances, where she criticized Buttigieg for what she perceives as staged photo ops and the misuse of government aircraft for personal travel, including attending events for LGBTQ rights awards. Greene’s assertion is that Buttigieg’s actions are an undue financial burden on American taxpayers who should not be responsible for funding these trips or his salary. The vote to cut Buttigieg’s salary to one dollar is largely symbolic, reflecting the House GOP’s dissatisfaction with what they see as failures and mismanagement during his tenure as transportation secretary. One of the most contentious issues is Buttigieg’s response to the toxic train derailment in East Palestine, Ohio. His delayed response to the crisis drew ire from the public and lawmakers alike, raising questions about his leadership in managing the nation’s transportation challenges. Buttigieg’s use of private jets has also come under scrutiny. Reports indicate that he has used government-managed private aircraft for travel numerous times since assuming office, drawing criticism for opting for private flights amidst widespread commercial flight cancellations and delays. It’s worth noting, however, that the amendment’s passage does not guarantee a change in Buttigieg’s salary. The House GOP’s spending bills, laden with partisan goals, must contend with a Democratic-controlled Senate and an executive branch unlikely to endorse a pay cut for one of its cabinet members. Thus, while the move reflects House Republicans’ stance, it faces an uphill battle to materialize into actual policy change. As the debate over Buttigieg’s salary unfolds, it underscores the broader political tensions between the current administration and Republican lawmakers who are eager to reverse policies and decisions they deem ineffective or extravagant. The symbolic dollar salary is a sharp critique from the GOP, illustrating their intent to hold Cabinet members accountable for their performance and fiscal responsibility.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Kat Von D’s Awakening: Celebrity Tattoo Artist Speaks Out on Extremism</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/11/08/Reflections-of-Kat-Von-D/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Kat Von D’s Awakening: Celebrity Tattoo Artist Speaks Out on Extremism" /><published>2023-11-08T17:53:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-08T17:53:00-05:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/11/08/Reflections-of-Kat-Von-D</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/11/08/Reflections-of-Kat-Von-D/">&lt;p&gt;Celebrity tattoo artist Kat Von D has shared a candid look into the personal transformation that led her to re-evaluate her beliefs amidst the race riots of 2020. Witnessing firsthand the tumult caused by Black Lives Matter and Antifa in Los Angeles, Von D confided that the reality of these events was “much worse” than the broadcasted narratives, prompting a significant shift in her religious and political convictions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During a heartfelt interview on the “Relatable” podcast with host Allie Beth Stuckey, Von D reflected on her life in the epicenter of the violent, left-wing riots that rocked the city. The artist, who lived a stone’s throw away from the mayor’s residence, experienced Antifa’s threats up close. The gravity of these moments pierced through the veil of media representation, revealing a harsher truth that spurred her to question the path she was on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The journey of self-discovery and spiritual awakening saw Von D turn away from her former occult practices and find solace in a Baptist church in Indiana. Last month, she took to social media to share the profound moment of her baptism, signaling a new chapter in her life. Her transformative experiences have not only altered her personal views but have also reshaped her role as a wife and mother, as she distances herself from past allurements that now repulse her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kat Von D’s revelations strike a chord with many who have found themselves disillusioned by extreme ideologies. Her story is a testament to the power of personal transformation and the courage it takes to break free from the echo chambers that often cloud judgment. As she embraces her newfound path, Von D expresses a heartfelt wish to articulate the depth of the positive changes she’s undergone, changes that have redefined her identity and purpose.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her candid discussion provides a stark reminder of the complex layers behind public figures and the pivotal experiences that can lead to profound personal evolutions. As Von D steps forward in her journey, she not only sheds the ink of her past but also the ideological bindings, emerging with a fresh perspective that celebrates growth, change, and the pursuit of authenticity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those watching, Kat Von D’s metamorphosis is not just a tale of personal rebirth but a narrative that challenges perceptions, urging others to look beyond the screen and question the world around them. As she continues to navigate her path, her story of reclamation and redemption is set to inspire others to seek their own truths in an ever-changing landscape.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Celebrity tattoo artist Kat Von D has shared a candid look into the personal transformation that led her to re-evaluate her beliefs amidst the race riots of 2020. Witnessing firsthand the tumult caused by Black Lives Matter and Antifa in Los Angeles, Von D confided that the reality of these events was “much worse” than the broadcasted narratives, prompting a significant shift in her religious and political convictions. During a heartfelt interview on the “Relatable” podcast with host Allie Beth Stuckey, Von D reflected on her life in the epicenter of the violent, left-wing riots that rocked the city. The artist, who lived a stone’s throw away from the mayor’s residence, experienced Antifa’s threats up close. The gravity of these moments pierced through the veil of media representation, revealing a harsher truth that spurred her to question the path she was on. The journey of self-discovery and spiritual awakening saw Von D turn away from her former occult practices and find solace in a Baptist church in Indiana. Last month, she took to social media to share the profound moment of her baptism, signaling a new chapter in her life. Her transformative experiences have not only altered her personal views but have also reshaped her role as a wife and mother, as she distances herself from past allurements that now repulse her. Kat Von D’s revelations strike a chord with many who have found themselves disillusioned by extreme ideologies. Her story is a testament to the power of personal transformation and the courage it takes to break free from the echo chambers that often cloud judgment. As she embraces her newfound path, Von D expresses a heartfelt wish to articulate the depth of the positive changes she’s undergone, changes that have redefined her identity and purpose. Her candid discussion provides a stark reminder of the complex layers behind public figures and the pivotal experiences that can lead to profound personal evolutions. As Von D steps forward in her journey, she not only sheds the ink of her past but also the ideological bindings, emerging with a fresh perspective that celebrates growth, change, and the pursuit of authenticity. For those watching, Kat Von D’s metamorphosis is not just a tale of personal rebirth but a narrative that challenges perceptions, urging others to look beyond the screen and question the world around them. As she continues to navigate her path, her story of reclamation and redemption is set to inspire others to seek their own truths in an ever-changing landscape.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Susanna Gibson’s Controversial Campaign Ends in Defeat in Virginia</title><link href="/politics/2023/11/08/Virginia-Election-Outcome/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Susanna Gibson’s Controversial Campaign Ends in Defeat in Virginia" /><published>2023-11-08T16:33:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-08T16:33:00-05:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/11/08/Virginia-Election-Outcome</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/11/08/Virginia-Election-Outcome/">&lt;p&gt;In a victory for traditional values and a rebuke of scandal-plagued politics, Republican David Owen has clinched a narrow win over Democrat Susanna Gibson in the race for Virginia House District 57. The election was marked by the controversy that enveloped Gibson’s campaign after reports of her involvement in online sexual content came to light.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Susanna Gibson’s campaign, overshadowed by her own actions on livestreaming platforms, ended not with the triumph she had hoped for, but with the electorate decisively turning their backs on her bid for office. Despite Gibson’s attempts to deflect the scandal as a political attack, it was her decisions that ultimately led voters to question her judgment and suitability for public office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Associated Press called the race for Owen, signaling a clear preference for a candidate who steered clear of the personal controversies that plagued his opponent. Gibson, a 40-year-old nurse practitioner and mother of two, found herself at the center of a media storm after The Washington Post’s report on her participation in explicit livestreams.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gibson’s attempt to remain in the race, even after the revelations, sparked intense debate within the district. Her insistence that the scandal was an “illegal invasion” of her privacy and a tactic to “silence women” did little to sway public opinion in her favor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Republican Party of Virginia took a firm stance on reminding voters of Gibson’s choices, distributing mailers that highlighted the issue. Their strategy was clear: to ensure that voters were fully informed about the character and conduct of the Democratic candidate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a district that the nonpartisan Virginia Public Access Project had rated as highly competitive, the outcome of this election sends a strong message about the values and expectations voters hold for their elected officials. The electorate’s decision suggests a repudiation of behavior they deemed unbecoming of a public servant, choosing instead to support a candidate who maintained a focus on policy and public service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gibson’s defeat in this closely watched race may serve as a cautionary tale for future candidates, underscoring the importance of personal conduct in the public’s evaluation of their potential leaders. As the dust settles on this contentious campaign, the voters of Virginia House District 57 have made their stance clear, opting for a representative who embodies the principles they wish to see in their government.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the Republican victor prepares to take office, the community looks forward to leadership that can move beyond the tumult of the campaign and focus on addressing the pressing issues facing Virginians today.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a victory for traditional values and a rebuke of scandal-plagued politics, Republican David Owen has clinched a narrow win over Democrat Susanna Gibson in the race for Virginia House District 57. The election was marked by the controversy that enveloped Gibson’s campaign after reports of her involvement in online sexual content came to light. Susanna Gibson’s campaign, overshadowed by her own actions on livestreaming platforms, ended not with the triumph she had hoped for, but with the electorate decisively turning their backs on her bid for office. Despite Gibson’s attempts to deflect the scandal as a political attack, it was her decisions that ultimately led voters to question her judgment and suitability for public office. The Associated Press called the race for Owen, signaling a clear preference for a candidate who steered clear of the personal controversies that plagued his opponent. Gibson, a 40-year-old nurse practitioner and mother of two, found herself at the center of a media storm after The Washington Post’s report on her participation in explicit livestreams. Gibson’s attempt to remain in the race, even after the revelations, sparked intense debate within the district. Her insistence that the scandal was an “illegal invasion” of her privacy and a tactic to “silence women” did little to sway public opinion in her favor. The Republican Party of Virginia took a firm stance on reminding voters of Gibson’s choices, distributing mailers that highlighted the issue. Their strategy was clear: to ensure that voters were fully informed about the character and conduct of the Democratic candidate. In a district that the nonpartisan Virginia Public Access Project had rated as highly competitive, the outcome of this election sends a strong message about the values and expectations voters hold for their elected officials. The electorate’s decision suggests a repudiation of behavior they deemed unbecoming of a public servant, choosing instead to support a candidate who maintained a focus on policy and public service. Gibson’s defeat in this closely watched race may serve as a cautionary tale for future candidates, underscoring the importance of personal conduct in the public’s evaluation of their potential leaders. As the dust settles on this contentious campaign, the voters of Virginia House District 57 have made their stance clear, opting for a representative who embodies the principles they wish to see in their government. As the Republican victor prepares to take office, the community looks forward to leadership that can move beyond the tumult of the campaign and focus on addressing the pressing issues facing Virginians today.</summary></entry></feed>