<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-12-03T12:13:06-05:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/12/03/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-12-03T12:13:06-05:00</published><updated>2023-12-03T12:13:06-05:00</updated><id>/2023/12/03/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/12/03/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/12/03/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-12-03T12:13:06-05:00</published><updated>2023-12-03T12:13:06-05:00</updated><id>/2023/12/03/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/12/03/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/">&lt;p&gt;Recent surprise attacks by Hamas on Israel has fueled ongoing tensions between staunchly conservative commentators and the progressive “Squad” Democrats known for criticizing Israel. The intensity of the backlash highlights the deep political divide over foreign policy in the Middle East.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Hamas’ shocking attack, several members of the “Squad,” including Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.), called for a “ceasefire and de-escalation,” condemning the violence. The absence of a statement from Rep. Rashida Tlaib (D-Mich.) was notably called out by conservative media outlets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;South Carolina GOP Rep. Nancy Mace quickly labeled Ocasio-Cortez a “Hamas apologist” in response to her call for peace and de-escalation. Rep. Ilhan Omar (D-Minn.), no stranger to controversy surrounding her views on Israel, echoed the call for de-escalation and ceasefire. Omar’s prior statements comparing the US and Israel to terrorist groups like Hamas and the Taliban resurfaced in the debate, fueling more criticisms. Omar’s 2019 tweet, where she opined that “Israel has hypnotized the world,” also continues to haunt her political career, often cited by critics to challenge her stance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conservative commentators have been especially vocal. “FOX &amp;amp; Friends Weekend” co-host Rachel Campos-Duffy took aim at Omar, saying she fails to recognize the peace in the Middle East under Trump’s administration. Conservative pundit John Hasson also called out Omar, claiming she insinuated that attacks on IDF forces were acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Massachusetts Democrat Rep. Ayanna Pressley’s concerns over the “devastating attacks on Israelis” were met with skepticism. A prominent conservative online personality, Comfortably Smug, accused the “Squad” of advising Israel to back down after the nation suffered massive attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Jamaal Bowman’s call for an end to the Gaza blockade, in addition to condemning the Hamas attacks, was met with criticism from conservative radio host Jason Rantz. He accused Bowman of pairing his condemnation of terrorism with unwarranted criticisms of Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Cori Bush emphasized the urgent need for a ceasefire, while pushing for an end to “U.S. support for Israeli military occupation and apartheid.” Defense attorney Marina Medvin criticized Bush, suggesting that she equates the death of Palestinian terrorists to the horrific acts committed against Jewish civilians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amidst the political turmoil and intense debate, the attacks have taken a heavy toll. Israeli media report over 300 dead due to the wide-ranging assault. Gaza health officials note that at least 200 Palestinians have perished in the retaliatory Israeli air strikes following the initial Hamas attack. As the situation remains volatile, both sides continue to count their casualties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This divisive issue showcases the challenge America faces in crafting a unified approach to foreign policy, with deeply entrenched political divides at play. As the situation develops, the debate is bound to intensify, shedding light on the complexities of U.S. politics in the global arena.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Third GOP Debate Viewership Dips, Sparking Party Reflection</title><link href="/news/2023/11/10/GOP-Debate-Viewership/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Third GOP Debate Viewership Dips, Sparking Party Reflection" /><published>2023-11-10T15:31:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-10T15:31:00-05:00</updated><id>/news/2023/11/10/GOP-Debate-Viewership</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/11/10/GOP-Debate-Viewership/">&lt;p&gt;The latest GOP presidential primary debate has hit a new viewership low, with numbers plummeting by 71% since the raucous 2015 debate season. The dwindling audience, mirrored by concerning election outcomes, has sent a ripple of urgency through the Republican party to reassess its strategies and messaging.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As NBC News hosted the third debate, only 6.8 million viewers tuned in, a stark contrast to the record-breaking 24 million viewers who watched the same event eight years ago. The decline not only points to a lack of viewer engagement but also signals a broader challenge for Republicans as they prepare for the 2024 general election.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With a dip in viewership and disappointing election results in states like Virginia and Kentucky, party leaders are taking a hard look at their approach. Frustrations are mounting, with some laying blame at former President Trump’s feet, while others call for a change in leadership at the Republican National Committee (RNC).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The debate’s decline in interest also raises questions about the impact of candidate selection and public fatigue with political infighting. As Republicans work to refine their message to better resonate with voters, the pressure is on to deliver convincing arguments and policies that can mobilize the base and attract independents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amid calls for RNC Chairwoman Ronna McDaniel’s resignation, the party is grappling with how to bounce back and regain momentum. With the fourth GOP primary debate on the horizon, set to be hosted by alternative media outlets, Republicans are considering new platforms and tactics to re-engage the electorate and shore up support.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This period of reflection is crucial for the GOP as it aims to unite its base and present a compelling alternative to Democratic policies ahead of the next election cycle. As they face the challenge of a shifting political landscape, Republicans are reminded that adaptability and a clear, cohesive vision are essential for success at the polls.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">The latest GOP presidential primary debate has hit a new viewership low, with numbers plummeting by 71% since the raucous 2015 debate season. The dwindling audience, mirrored by concerning election outcomes, has sent a ripple of urgency through the Republican party to reassess its strategies and messaging. As NBC News hosted the third debate, only 6.8 million viewers tuned in, a stark contrast to the record-breaking 24 million viewers who watched the same event eight years ago. The decline not only points to a lack of viewer engagement but also signals a broader challenge for Republicans as they prepare for the 2024 general election. With a dip in viewership and disappointing election results in states like Virginia and Kentucky, party leaders are taking a hard look at their approach. Frustrations are mounting, with some laying blame at former President Trump’s feet, while others call for a change in leadership at the Republican National Committee (RNC). The debate’s decline in interest also raises questions about the impact of candidate selection and public fatigue with political infighting. As Republicans work to refine their message to better resonate with voters, the pressure is on to deliver convincing arguments and policies that can mobilize the base and attract independents. Amid calls for RNC Chairwoman Ronna McDaniel’s resignation, the party is grappling with how to bounce back and regain momentum. With the fourth GOP primary debate on the horizon, set to be hosted by alternative media outlets, Republicans are considering new platforms and tactics to re-engage the electorate and shore up support. This period of reflection is crucial for the GOP as it aims to unite its base and present a compelling alternative to Democratic policies ahead of the next election cycle. As they face the challenge of a shifting political landscape, Republicans are reminded that adaptability and a clear, cohesive vision are essential for success at the polls.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Alabama Leader’s Tragic End Amid Personal Scandal Shakes Community</title><link href="/news/2023/11/10/Double-Life-Tragedy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Alabama Leader’s Tragic End Amid Personal Scandal Shakes Community" /><published>2023-11-10T13:17:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-10T13:17:00-05:00</updated><id>/news/2023/11/10/Double-Life-Tragedy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/11/10/Double-Life-Tragedy/">&lt;p&gt;The town of Smiths Station, Alabama, mourns the loss of Mayor F.L. “Bubba” Copeland, 49, who also served as a senior pastor at First Baptist Church in Phenix City. The shocking twist came after Copeland ended his life following the exposure of his secret life as a cross-dresser by a conservative news site. This revelation has rocked the small community, sparking a discourse on privacy, mental health, and the pressures of public life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Copeland, a married father of three, was a fixture in his community where he was seen as a leader and spiritual guide. His untimely demise came just days after photos of him dressed in women’s clothing were made public, showing a starkly different side to the public figure known to his townspeople. Operating under the pseudonym Brittini Blaire Summerlin, Copeland’s online persona featured him in various states of dress and undress, something he described as a stress-relieving hobby.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This news has left the community grappling with mixed emotions—from shock and disbelief to sympathy and sadness. Copeland’s role as a pastor and mayor is now overshadowed by the controversy and his tragic response to it. The incident raises questions about the invasion of privacy and the impact of public shaming, especially pertaining to individuals in positions of authority and trust.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The repercussions of this scandal are complex. On one hand, there’s a personal tragedy that ended in the most heartbreaking way possible. On the other, there are questions about the responsibility of public figures to maintain an image that reflects their professional roles. Copeland’s case particularly highlights the tension between personal freedoms and public expectations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In his final days, Copeland addressed his congregation, apologizing for any embarrassment his private actions might have caused. He emphasized that his private life did not reflect his public service. However, the stress and public scrutiny seemed too much for the pastor, who chose to end his life rather than face the aftermath of the exposé.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This situation serves as a poignant reminder of the human behind the title, the person behind the persona. It also calls for a reflective examination of how society deals with the private lives of public individuals and the harsh spotlight that often comes with leadership positions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the town of Smiths Station grieves, many are calling for compassion and understanding. The tragedy of F.L. “Bubba” Copeland’s life and death will undoubtedly leave an indelible mark on the community he served and the conversations about privacy in the digital age.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">The town of Smiths Station, Alabama, mourns the loss of Mayor F.L. “Bubba” Copeland, 49, who also served as a senior pastor at First Baptist Church in Phenix City. The shocking twist came after Copeland ended his life following the exposure of his secret life as a cross-dresser by a conservative news site. This revelation has rocked the small community, sparking a discourse on privacy, mental health, and the pressures of public life. Copeland, a married father of three, was a fixture in his community where he was seen as a leader and spiritual guide. His untimely demise came just days after photos of him dressed in women’s clothing were made public, showing a starkly different side to the public figure known to his townspeople. Operating under the pseudonym Brittini Blaire Summerlin, Copeland’s online persona featured him in various states of dress and undress, something he described as a stress-relieving hobby. This news has left the community grappling with mixed emotions—from shock and disbelief to sympathy and sadness. Copeland’s role as a pastor and mayor is now overshadowed by the controversy and his tragic response to it. The incident raises questions about the invasion of privacy and the impact of public shaming, especially pertaining to individuals in positions of authority and trust. The repercussions of this scandal are complex. On one hand, there’s a personal tragedy that ended in the most heartbreaking way possible. On the other, there are questions about the responsibility of public figures to maintain an image that reflects their professional roles. Copeland’s case particularly highlights the tension between personal freedoms and public expectations. In his final days, Copeland addressed his congregation, apologizing for any embarrassment his private actions might have caused. He emphasized that his private life did not reflect his public service. However, the stress and public scrutiny seemed too much for the pastor, who chose to end his life rather than face the aftermath of the exposé. This situation serves as a poignant reminder of the human behind the title, the person behind the persona. It also calls for a reflective examination of how society deals with the private lives of public individuals and the harsh spotlight that often comes with leadership positions. As the town of Smiths Station grieves, many are calling for compassion and understanding. The tragedy of F.L. “Bubba” Copeland’s life and death will undoubtedly leave an indelible mark on the community he served and the conversations about privacy in the digital age.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Massachusetts Governor Urges Migrant Redistribution Amid Shelter Strain</title><link href="/news/2023/11/10/Migrant-Surge/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Massachusetts Governor Urges Migrant Redistribution Amid Shelter Strain" /><published>2023-11-10T11:59:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-10T11:59:00-05:00</updated><id>/news/2023/11/10/Migrant-Surge</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/11/10/Migrant-Surge/">&lt;p&gt;Massachusetts, standing as the sole ‘right-to-shelter’ state in America, is currently grappling with an unprecedented surge in migrants that has Governor Maura Healy sounding the alarm. With daily arrivals pushing the state’s shelter system to its brink, the governor has voiced a compelling case for a national dialogue on migrant resettlement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Governor Healy, a Democrat, openly expressed her concern that Massachusetts is nearing its 7,500-family shelter limit, with the influx of families, many lacking legal U.S. presence, seeking state housing assistance. These circumstances have sparked intense discussions about the sustainability of the right-to-shelter law and the broader implications for taxpayer-funded emergency housing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The escalating situation has prompted Gov. Healy to reconsider Massachusetts’ capacity to handle the crisis alone. With a staggering 40 to 50 new families arriving daily, the governor hinted that other states might need to step up and share the responsibility of providing shelter for migrants, underscoring the urgency for a collective approach to this national challenge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This week’s announcement that the state can no longer sustain the current demand has led to the implementation of a waitlist, prioritizing those in dire need, such as women, young children, and those facing acute medical issues. The state is also contemplating capping the duration a family can reside in a shelter, as part of a multifaceted plan to manage the shelter crisis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gov. Healy’s statements have echoed across the state, stirring debates on the efficacy of Massachusetts’ unique right-to-shelter law and raising questions about the state’s preparedness to deal with the ongoing surge. Her remarks come as communities across Massachusetts, much like those in New York, are strained under the pressures of accommodating the continuous stream of migrants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In response to the mounting crisis, Massachusetts has sought the assistance of the National Guard, boosting the number of service members available to aid unstaffed shelter sites, as well as tapping into federal funds to establish overnight shelter sites for families without alternative options.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The gravity of the situation is not lost on Republican lawmakers like State Representative Peter Durant, who has proposed an amendment to ensure that the benefits of the right-to-shelter law are reserved for legal residents with a minimum of three years in the state. While the amendment awaits legislative action, it reflects the growing sentiment for reform amidst the ongoing migrant surge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the debate continues, one thing is clear: the Bay State’s current predicament is a microcosm of a larger national issue that requires immediate attention and a unified response to the challenge of migrant resettlement.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Massachusetts, standing as the sole ‘right-to-shelter’ state in America, is currently grappling with an unprecedented surge in migrants that has Governor Maura Healy sounding the alarm. With daily arrivals pushing the state’s shelter system to its brink, the governor has voiced a compelling case for a national dialogue on migrant resettlement. Governor Healy, a Democrat, openly expressed her concern that Massachusetts is nearing its 7,500-family shelter limit, with the influx of families, many lacking legal U.S. presence, seeking state housing assistance. These circumstances have sparked intense discussions about the sustainability of the right-to-shelter law and the broader implications for taxpayer-funded emergency housing. The escalating situation has prompted Gov. Healy to reconsider Massachusetts’ capacity to handle the crisis alone. With a staggering 40 to 50 new families arriving daily, the governor hinted that other states might need to step up and share the responsibility of providing shelter for migrants, underscoring the urgency for a collective approach to this national challenge. This week’s announcement that the state can no longer sustain the current demand has led to the implementation of a waitlist, prioritizing those in dire need, such as women, young children, and those facing acute medical issues. The state is also contemplating capping the duration a family can reside in a shelter, as part of a multifaceted plan to manage the shelter crisis. Gov. Healy’s statements have echoed across the state, stirring debates on the efficacy of Massachusetts’ unique right-to-shelter law and raising questions about the state’s preparedness to deal with the ongoing surge. Her remarks come as communities across Massachusetts, much like those in New York, are strained under the pressures of accommodating the continuous stream of migrants. In response to the mounting crisis, Massachusetts has sought the assistance of the National Guard, boosting the number of service members available to aid unstaffed shelter sites, as well as tapping into federal funds to establish overnight shelter sites for families without alternative options. The gravity of the situation is not lost on Republican lawmakers like State Representative Peter Durant, who has proposed an amendment to ensure that the benefits of the right-to-shelter law are reserved for legal residents with a minimum of three years in the state. While the amendment awaits legislative action, it reflects the growing sentiment for reform amidst the ongoing migrant surge. As the debate continues, one thing is clear: the Bay State’s current predicament is a microcosm of a larger national issue that requires immediate attention and a unified response to the challenge of migrant resettlement.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Senate GOP in Self-Reflection After Election Setbacks: Time to Regroup</title><link href="/politics/2023/11/10/Reflecting-on-Elections/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Senate GOP in Self-Reflection After Election Setbacks: Time to Regroup" /><published>2023-11-10T10:48:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-10T10:48:00-05:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/11/10/Reflecting-on-Elections</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/11/10/Reflecting-on-Elections/">&lt;p&gt;In the aftermath of Tuesday’s nationwide elections, Senate Republicans are introspectively analyzing the party’s performance, signaling a time for strategic reassessment. The results, which saw the GOP face unexpected setbacks including the loss of the governor’s race in traditionally Republican Kentucky, have sparked a candid discourse on the need for enhanced voter turnout and refined messaging.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The echo of footsteps in empty polling stations has not only rung alarm bells for next year’s general election but has also instigated a bout of soul-searching within the party. “We didn’t show up,” Senator Thom Tillis from North Carolina stated, pinpointing a lackluster turnout as one of the crucial factors in the Republican shortfall. His sentiments underscored a collective acknowledgment that it’s time to bolster efforts and rekindle the Republican flame in the hearts of voters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the corridors of the Capitol to the streets where campaign posters are now just relics of hope and aspiration, the GOP is confronted with a stark reality: change is imperative. Senator Mitt Romney of Utah reflected on the influence of past political stances, particularly the association with claims of election fraud in 2020, and how such a focus may have deterred voters looking forward to addressing current and future challenges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The call for a recalibrated approach is clear, with Senate Minority Whip John Thune of South Dakota highlighting the necessity of appealing to a broader electorate. In the political chessboard that is the U.S. electoral landscape, capturing the allegiance of independents and moderate Republicans is pivotal to crafting a winning strategy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Montana’s Senator Steve Daines, chair of the National Republican Senatorial Committee, pointed to the need for a tactical pivot in addressing contentious issues like abortion. He suggests that framing positions in a manner that resonates with the electorate is key, steering clear of endorsing sweeping federal bans.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As Republicans stand at the crossroads, contemplating the paths that led to the current political juncture, there is a growing consensus that the blueprint for success in 2024 involves a shift from retrospective to prospective campaigning. The issues at the forefront are expected to revolve around President Joe Biden’s administration, with inflation, border security, and global geopolitical shifts being the likely battleground topics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the dust settles on this election cycle, the GOP’s commitment to introspection and reformulation of campaign strategies signals a reinvigoration of efforts to sway the American voter. The coming months will be a testament to the party’s ability to adapt and reassert itself as a formidable political force.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In the aftermath of Tuesday’s nationwide elections, Senate Republicans are introspectively analyzing the party’s performance, signaling a time for strategic reassessment. The results, which saw the GOP face unexpected setbacks including the loss of the governor’s race in traditionally Republican Kentucky, have sparked a candid discourse on the need for enhanced voter turnout and refined messaging. The echo of footsteps in empty polling stations has not only rung alarm bells for next year’s general election but has also instigated a bout of soul-searching within the party. “We didn’t show up,” Senator Thom Tillis from North Carolina stated, pinpointing a lackluster turnout as one of the crucial factors in the Republican shortfall. His sentiments underscored a collective acknowledgment that it’s time to bolster efforts and rekindle the Republican flame in the hearts of voters. From the corridors of the Capitol to the streets where campaign posters are now just relics of hope and aspiration, the GOP is confronted with a stark reality: change is imperative. Senator Mitt Romney of Utah reflected on the influence of past political stances, particularly the association with claims of election fraud in 2020, and how such a focus may have deterred voters looking forward to addressing current and future challenges. The call for a recalibrated approach is clear, with Senate Minority Whip John Thune of South Dakota highlighting the necessity of appealing to a broader electorate. In the political chessboard that is the U.S. electoral landscape, capturing the allegiance of independents and moderate Republicans is pivotal to crafting a winning strategy. Montana’s Senator Steve Daines, chair of the National Republican Senatorial Committee, pointed to the need for a tactical pivot in addressing contentious issues like abortion. He suggests that framing positions in a manner that resonates with the electorate is key, steering clear of endorsing sweeping federal bans. As Republicans stand at the crossroads, contemplating the paths that led to the current political juncture, there is a growing consensus that the blueprint for success in 2024 involves a shift from retrospective to prospective campaigning. The issues at the forefront are expected to revolve around President Joe Biden’s administration, with inflation, border security, and global geopolitical shifts being the likely battleground topics. As the dust settles on this election cycle, the GOP’s commitment to introspection and reformulation of campaign strategies signals a reinvigoration of efforts to sway the American voter. The coming months will be a testament to the party’s ability to adapt and reassert itself as a formidable political force.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Home Depot Co-Founder Rallies Behind Trump’s 2024 Vision</title><link href="/politics/2023/11/10/Trump-Endorsement/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Home Depot Co-Founder Rallies Behind Trump’s 2024 Vision" /><published>2023-11-10T09:35:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-10T09:35:00-05:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/11/10/Trump-Endorsement</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/11/10/Trump-Endorsement/">&lt;p&gt;Bernie Marcus, the esteemed co-founder of Home Depot and a titan in the business world, has thrown his weight behind former President Donald Trump’s bid for the 2024 presidential race. At 94 years old, Marcus’s endorsement comes as a robust vote of confidence for Trump, reflecting a commitment to the American Dream and the values upon which the country was founded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Marcus, who is also renowned for his involvement with the Job Creators Network, took to Real Clear Politics to express his endorsement. He highlighted his concerns about the nation’s trajectory under the current administration, pointing to rising violent crime rates, uncontrolled borders, and the homelessness crisis as signs of America veering away from its foundational principles. The business mogul lamented that the very conditions that enabled him to build Home Depot from the ground up are deteriorating, potentially stifling the future of American entrepreneurship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump’s nomination for the upcoming election seems almost a certainty in Marcus’s eyes, who acknowledges the misgivings some Republicans may have about Trump’s abrasive style. Yet, Marcus urges voters to look beyond Trump’s brash exterior to recognize the substantial accomplishments of his first term, particularly in stewardship and foreign policy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Marcus specifically praised Trump’s decisive actions, such as the strike on Iranian General Qasem Soleimani, which sent a strong message to American adversaries. He suggests that Trump’s firm approach on the global stage, especially his stance on Israel and the war in Ukraine, is crucial in the current geopolitical climate. Marcus’s endorsement implies a belief that Trump’s presence in the Oval Office would deter the aggressions of hostile forces.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This endorsement is particularly timely, given the increasing turmoil in the Middle East and the ongoing conflict in Ukraine. Marcus posits that Trump’s assertive foreign policy is essential for maintaining peace and order, as it commands respect and, critically, fear from international adversaries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The backing of a figure like Bernie Marcus not only boosts Trump’s campaign but also sends a clear message to conservatives: despite any reservations about Trump’s demeanor, his track record on economic and foreign policy fronts could be the decisive leadership America needs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the 2024 presidential race heats up, endorsements from key figures like Marcus will likely play a pivotal role in shaping the narrative and rallying the Republican base. Trump’s campaign, gaining momentum with such support, continues to emphasize a return to policies and leadership that prioritize American interests at home and abroad.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Bernie Marcus, the esteemed co-founder of Home Depot and a titan in the business world, has thrown his weight behind former President Donald Trump’s bid for the 2024 presidential race. At 94 years old, Marcus’s endorsement comes as a robust vote of confidence for Trump, reflecting a commitment to the American Dream and the values upon which the country was founded. Marcus, who is also renowned for his involvement with the Job Creators Network, took to Real Clear Politics to express his endorsement. He highlighted his concerns about the nation’s trajectory under the current administration, pointing to rising violent crime rates, uncontrolled borders, and the homelessness crisis as signs of America veering away from its foundational principles. The business mogul lamented that the very conditions that enabled him to build Home Depot from the ground up are deteriorating, potentially stifling the future of American entrepreneurship. Trump’s nomination for the upcoming election seems almost a certainty in Marcus’s eyes, who acknowledges the misgivings some Republicans may have about Trump’s abrasive style. Yet, Marcus urges voters to look beyond Trump’s brash exterior to recognize the substantial accomplishments of his first term, particularly in stewardship and foreign policy. Marcus specifically praised Trump’s decisive actions, such as the strike on Iranian General Qasem Soleimani, which sent a strong message to American adversaries. He suggests that Trump’s firm approach on the global stage, especially his stance on Israel and the war in Ukraine, is crucial in the current geopolitical climate. Marcus’s endorsement implies a belief that Trump’s presence in the Oval Office would deter the aggressions of hostile forces. This endorsement is particularly timely, given the increasing turmoil in the Middle East and the ongoing conflict in Ukraine. Marcus posits that Trump’s assertive foreign policy is essential for maintaining peace and order, as it commands respect and, critically, fear from international adversaries. The backing of a figure like Bernie Marcus not only boosts Trump’s campaign but also sends a clear message to conservatives: despite any reservations about Trump’s demeanor, his track record on economic and foreign policy fronts could be the decisive leadership America needs. As the 2024 presidential race heats up, endorsements from key figures like Marcus will likely play a pivotal role in shaping the narrative and rallying the Republican base. Trump’s campaign, gaining momentum with such support, continues to emphasize a return to policies and leadership that prioritize American interests at home and abroad.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Outrage as Biden Officials Extend Unprecedented Access to CCP Leaders</title><link href="/politics/2023/11/10/CCP-Invitation/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Outrage as Biden Officials Extend Unprecedented Access to CCP Leaders" /><published>2023-11-10T08:24:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-10T08:24:00-05:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/11/10/CCP-Invitation</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/11/10/CCP-Invitation/">&lt;p&gt;In a move that has sparked fierce backlash from conservative quarters, Energy Secretary Jennifer Granholm has come under fire for extending an invitation to Chinese Communist Party (CCP) leaders to tour a highly sensitive U.S. nuclear testing site. The decision, which has led to Republicans sounding the alarm over national security, is seen as yet another questionable call from an administration already facing criticism for its handling of foreign policy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Nevada National Security Site, a cornerstone in maintaining America’s nuclear deterrence, has historically been shrouded in secrecy due to the sensitive nature of the work conducted within its confines. However, the Department of Energy’s (DOE) recent invitation to foreign powers, particularly the CCP, has raised questions about the Biden administration’s judgment when it comes to safeguarding the nation’s security interests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GOP Conference Chair Elise Stefanik, alongside a coalition of 18 House Republicans, has taken a stand, penning a letter to Granholm demanding answers. The Republicans’ letter highlights the inappropriateness of offering China and Russia such “unprecedented access” and expresses concerns over the potential for foreign adversaries to glean insights into the U.S.’s nuclear capabilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The controversy stems from a Bloomberg report that revealed the DOE’s National Nuclear Security Administration’s invitations to the Nevada site were intended to demonstrate the U.S.’s commitment to a moratorium against nuclear weapons testing. Yet, GOP leaders argue this gesture compromises the integrity of U.S. defenses and sends a signal of weakness at a time when geopolitical tensions are at a boiling point.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This latest episode is another notch in what critics of the Biden administration view as a series of missteps in foreign policy, particularly regarding relations with China and Russia. With China’s nuclear capabilities rapidly expanding and Russia’s increasing assertiveness on the global stage, the wisdom of allowing potential rivals such access is being questioned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The House Republicans’ letter does not mince words, warning that such actions could “lead to our own destruction” and potentially embolden China’s refusal to halt its nuclear development. Representatives like Doug Lamborn and Rob Wittman have echoed these sentiments, suggesting that the DOE’s actions are not only alarming but “fundamentally absurd.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The GOP’s outcry has not only reverberated through the halls of Congress but has also garnered attention from citizens concerned about national security. As the Biden administration continues to navigate complex international waters, decisions like this one will undoubtedly remain under the microscope, with conservative voices holding them to account.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a move that has sparked fierce backlash from conservative quarters, Energy Secretary Jennifer Granholm has come under fire for extending an invitation to Chinese Communist Party (CCP) leaders to tour a highly sensitive U.S. nuclear testing site. The decision, which has led to Republicans sounding the alarm over national security, is seen as yet another questionable call from an administration already facing criticism for its handling of foreign policy. The Nevada National Security Site, a cornerstone in maintaining America’s nuclear deterrence, has historically been shrouded in secrecy due to the sensitive nature of the work conducted within its confines. However, the Department of Energy’s (DOE) recent invitation to foreign powers, particularly the CCP, has raised questions about the Biden administration’s judgment when it comes to safeguarding the nation’s security interests. GOP Conference Chair Elise Stefanik, alongside a coalition of 18 House Republicans, has taken a stand, penning a letter to Granholm demanding answers. The Republicans’ letter highlights the inappropriateness of offering China and Russia such “unprecedented access” and expresses concerns over the potential for foreign adversaries to glean insights into the U.S.’s nuclear capabilities. The controversy stems from a Bloomberg report that revealed the DOE’s National Nuclear Security Administration’s invitations to the Nevada site were intended to demonstrate the U.S.’s commitment to a moratorium against nuclear weapons testing. Yet, GOP leaders argue this gesture compromises the integrity of U.S. defenses and sends a signal of weakness at a time when geopolitical tensions are at a boiling point. This latest episode is another notch in what critics of the Biden administration view as a series of missteps in foreign policy, particularly regarding relations with China and Russia. With China’s nuclear capabilities rapidly expanding and Russia’s increasing assertiveness on the global stage, the wisdom of allowing potential rivals such access is being questioned. The House Republicans’ letter does not mince words, warning that such actions could “lead to our own destruction” and potentially embolden China’s refusal to halt its nuclear development. Representatives like Doug Lamborn and Rob Wittman have echoed these sentiments, suggesting that the DOE’s actions are not only alarming but “fundamentally absurd.” The GOP’s outcry has not only reverberated through the halls of Congress but has also garnered attention from citizens concerned about national security. As the Biden administration continues to navigate complex international waters, decisions like this one will undoubtedly remain under the microscope, with conservative voices holding them to account.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">AI Revolution in Animation: A Drastic Cut in Workforce Looms</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/11/10/AI-Animation-Industry/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="AI Revolution in Animation: A Drastic Cut in Workforce Looms" /><published>2023-11-10T07:15:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-10T07:15:00-05:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/11/10/AI-Animation-Industry</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/11/10/AI-Animation-Industry/">&lt;p&gt;The world of animation is on the brink of a technological upheaval that could render a vast majority of traditional jobs obsolete. Jeffrey Katzenberg, a former titan of the Hollywood industry, forecasts that artificial intelligence (AI) will eliminate 90% of animation roles within a mere three years, marking a tectonic shift in the creative landscape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At a recent panel discussion, Katzenberg, known for his influential roles in big studios, shared his insights on the imminent impact of AI on media, entertainment, and content creation. He emphasized the drastic reduction in the workforce and time required to produce animated features, which historically involved hundreds of artists and multiple years of painstaking work. The future, he suggests, will see AI-driven processes streamline this to a fraction of the current input.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This prediction speaks volumes about the ongoing digital transformation in the entertainment industry, with AI poised to accelerate changes tenfold. The traditional cost of animation, often reaching the hundreds of millions due to labor-intensive processes, is set to plummet as AI algorithms learn to animate with minimal human intervention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the integration of AI in animation could result in more efficient production pipelines and potentially lower costs for consumers, the looming job cuts present a sobering reality. Animators, many of whom may lean towards progressive ideologies, are faced with a future that mirrors the past struggles of blue-collar workers who watched automation reshape manufacturing industries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The irony is not lost on those who recall the lack of empathy for manual labor jobs lost to machines, as now the same sword of technological advancement hangs over the heads of those in creative sectors. Nonetheless, the potential reduction in ‘woke’ influence on animation content, often attributed to pressure from within the industry’s workforce, could mark a return to less politicized family entertainment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the animation community braces for this impending wave of AI, there may be a silver lining. The skill set of animators, often inclusive of coding and digital expertise, could provide a safety net, allowing them to pivot to emerging roles within the tech-driven landscape of entertainment production.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The integration of AI in animation is not just a tale of job loss but also a narrative of adaptation and the inevitable march of progress. As AI transforms how stories are brought to life on screen, the industry must prepare for a new era where creativity meets cutting-edge technology, bringing forth both challenges and opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">The world of animation is on the brink of a technological upheaval that could render a vast majority of traditional jobs obsolete. Jeffrey Katzenberg, a former titan of the Hollywood industry, forecasts that artificial intelligence (AI) will eliminate 90% of animation roles within a mere three years, marking a tectonic shift in the creative landscape. At a recent panel discussion, Katzenberg, known for his influential roles in big studios, shared his insights on the imminent impact of AI on media, entertainment, and content creation. He emphasized the drastic reduction in the workforce and time required to produce animated features, which historically involved hundreds of artists and multiple years of painstaking work. The future, he suggests, will see AI-driven processes streamline this to a fraction of the current input. This prediction speaks volumes about the ongoing digital transformation in the entertainment industry, with AI poised to accelerate changes tenfold. The traditional cost of animation, often reaching the hundreds of millions due to labor-intensive processes, is set to plummet as AI algorithms learn to animate with minimal human intervention. While the integration of AI in animation could result in more efficient production pipelines and potentially lower costs for consumers, the looming job cuts present a sobering reality. Animators, many of whom may lean towards progressive ideologies, are faced with a future that mirrors the past struggles of blue-collar workers who watched automation reshape manufacturing industries. The irony is not lost on those who recall the lack of empathy for manual labor jobs lost to machines, as now the same sword of technological advancement hangs over the heads of those in creative sectors. Nonetheless, the potential reduction in ‘woke’ influence on animation content, often attributed to pressure from within the industry’s workforce, could mark a return to less politicized family entertainment. As the animation community braces for this impending wave of AI, there may be a silver lining. The skill set of animators, often inclusive of coding and digital expertise, could provide a safety net, allowing them to pivot to emerging roles within the tech-driven landscape of entertainment production. The integration of AI in animation is not just a tale of job loss but also a narrative of adaptation and the inevitable march of progress. As AI transforms how stories are brought to life on screen, the industry must prepare for a new era where creativity meets cutting-edge technology, bringing forth both challenges and opportunities.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">U.S. Launches Decisive Airstrike on Iranian-Utilized Syrian Weapons Facility</title><link href="/news/2023/11/10/Iran-Airstrike/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="U.S. Launches Decisive Airstrike on Iranian-Utilized Syrian Weapons Facility" /><published>2023-11-10T06:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-11-10T06:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/news/2023/11/10/Iran-Airstrike</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/11/10/Iran-Airstrike/">&lt;p&gt;In a powerful response to repeated attacks on American forces, the U.S. military executed a precise airstrike on a Syrian facility known to store weapons for Iranian forces. This bold move came as a direct answer to a series of hostile actions targeting U.S. personnel in the Middle East.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After enduring no less than 46 attacks since mid-October, with one resulting in a tragic contractor fatality and several causing injuries among U.S. troops, the Department of Defense authorized two F-15 fighter jets to strike the Maysulun weapons storage facility in eastern Syria. This decisive action was a clear message from the U.S.: the protection of American forces is a top priority.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Secretary of Defense Lloyd Austin reaffirmed this stance, emphasizing that the United States will not hesitate to defend its personnel, its interests, and its integrity against any threats. The facility, identified as a hub for Iranian-backed operations, was neutralized under the direct orders of the President, showcasing the administration’s unwavering commitment to the safety of its military personnel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Footage of the operation captured the precise moment of impact, followed by secondary explosions, signaling a successful hit on the intended target. The operation’s success is attributed to the vigilance and preparedness of U.S. and coalition defenses, which have been instrumental in disrupting the majority of attempted attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the formidable defenses in place, the recent assault that caused the death of an American contractor and left 56 U.S. troops with injuries, including 25 with traumatic brain injuries, marked a turning point. All injured service members have since returned to duty, but the attacks’ escalation prompted a robust response.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pentagon Deputy Press Secretary Sabrina Singh pointed out that the attacks, originating from drones and rockets, have targeted U.S. and coalition forces stationed at strategic sites in Iraq and Syria. The spike in violence is tied to the ongoing tensions between Israel and Hamas, with the U.S. openly supporting Israel’s right to defend itself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the U.S. stands ready to take further measures to ensure the security of its forces, the message to Iran and its proxies is unmistakable: aggression against U.S. personnel will be met with uncompromising force. The U.S. has made it clear that while it does not seek conflict, it will not stand by as its troops come under fire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The recent airstrike not only served as a necessary act of self-defense but also as a deterrent against future provocations. As tensions in the region remain high, the U.S. continues to demonstrate its resolve to protect its interests and ensure the safety of its brave service members.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a powerful response to repeated attacks on American forces, the U.S. military executed a precise airstrike on a Syrian facility known to store weapons for Iranian forces. This bold move came as a direct answer to a series of hostile actions targeting U.S. personnel in the Middle East. After enduring no less than 46 attacks since mid-October, with one resulting in a tragic contractor fatality and several causing injuries among U.S. troops, the Department of Defense authorized two F-15 fighter jets to strike the Maysulun weapons storage facility in eastern Syria. This decisive action was a clear message from the U.S.: the protection of American forces is a top priority. Secretary of Defense Lloyd Austin reaffirmed this stance, emphasizing that the United States will not hesitate to defend its personnel, its interests, and its integrity against any threats. The facility, identified as a hub for Iranian-backed operations, was neutralized under the direct orders of the President, showcasing the administration’s unwavering commitment to the safety of its military personnel. Footage of the operation captured the precise moment of impact, followed by secondary explosions, signaling a successful hit on the intended target. The operation’s success is attributed to the vigilance and preparedness of U.S. and coalition defenses, which have been instrumental in disrupting the majority of attempted attacks. Despite the formidable defenses in place, the recent assault that caused the death of an American contractor and left 56 U.S. troops with injuries, including 25 with traumatic brain injuries, marked a turning point. All injured service members have since returned to duty, but the attacks’ escalation prompted a robust response. Pentagon Deputy Press Secretary Sabrina Singh pointed out that the attacks, originating from drones and rockets, have targeted U.S. and coalition forces stationed at strategic sites in Iraq and Syria. The spike in violence is tied to the ongoing tensions between Israel and Hamas, with the U.S. openly supporting Israel’s right to defend itself. As the U.S. stands ready to take further measures to ensure the security of its forces, the message to Iran and its proxies is unmistakable: aggression against U.S. personnel will be met with uncompromising force. The U.S. has made it clear that while it does not seek conflict, it will not stand by as its troops come under fire. The recent airstrike not only served as a necessary act of self-defense but also as a deterrent against future provocations. As tensions in the region remain high, the U.S. continues to demonstrate its resolve to protect its interests and ensure the safety of its brave service members.</summary></entry></feed>