<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-09-29T19:15:00-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/09/29/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-09-29T19:15:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-29T19:15:00-04:00</updated><id>/2023/09/29/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/29/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Groundbreaking Decision - Gov. Newsom Approves Protection for Abortion Pill Providers</title><link href="/news/2023/09/29/Newsom-Abortion-Bill-Signing/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Groundbreaking Decision - Gov. Newsom Approves Protection for Abortion Pill Providers" /><published>2023-09-29T17:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-29T17:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/29/Newsom-Abortion-Bill-Signing</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/29/Newsom-Abortion-Bill-Signing/">&lt;p&gt;In a groundbreaking move, California’s Democratic Governor Gavin Newsom has enacted a bill that protects health care providers who mail abortion pills to pro-life states, preventing their prosecution. This significant legislation extends the already existing law in California that protects doctors providing abortion services to out-of-state patients traveling to California.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;extending-protection-to-providers&quot;&gt;Extending Protection to Providers&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;California had pre-existing laws safeguarding doctors who offer abortion services from judgments stemming from other states. However, the newly signed legislation amplifies the protection, ensuring authorities do not collaborate with out-of-state investigations into providers mailing abortion pills to other states. The law also prohibits bail agents or bounty hunters from detaining doctors and pharmacists in California and transporting them to another state to face trials for providing an abortion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-lifeline-to-essential-care&quot;&gt;A Lifeline to Essential Care&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Health care providers, physically located in California, will be able to offer a lifeline to people in states that have cut off access to essential care, and be shielded from the draconian laws of those states,” stated the bill’s author, Democrat state Sen. Nancy Skinner. The law, akin to those in New York and Massachusetts, even restricts state-based media companies, like Facebook, from cooperating with out-of-state investigations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-stand-for-womens-rights&quot;&gt;A Stand for Women’s Rights&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Governor Newsom, reinforcing his commitment to protecting women and health care workers providing basic care, signed this landmark bill, emphasizing California’s stance on women’s rights and medical freedom. This law is crucial for those seeking essential care, especially in states with stringent pro-life laws, thus enabling a supportive network for women in need.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;boundaries-overstepped&quot;&gt;Boundaries Overstepped?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, this monumental legislation hasn’t been welcomed by all. Pro-life groups, like Susan B. Anthony Pro-Life America, condemned the law, asserting that the California government is disregarding state borders and imposing its will. They argued that California’s protections for abortion providers overshadow the diverse values and laws of other states.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;impact-of-the-legislation&quot;&gt;Impact of the Legislation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While the new law shields health care providers within California, those leaving the state and prescribing abortion pills will not enjoy the protection offered by the law. This legislation not only fosters medical freedom and women’s rights but also invites discussions about state sovereignty and the extent to which one state can offer protections that might infringe upon the laws of another.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;concluding-thoughts&quot;&gt;Concluding Thoughts&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This revolutionary bill signed by Gov. Newsom symbolizes a pivotal advancement in women’s health care rights and medical freedom. It facilitates the provision of essential care to those residing in pro-life states and asserts California’s stance on protecting women’s reproductive rights. Nonetheless, the ramifications of this legislation on state relationships and the ongoing debate between pro-life and pro-choice proponents will continue to unfold in the coming times.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a groundbreaking move, California’s Democratic Governor Gavin Newsom has enacted a bill that protects health care providers who mail abortion pills to pro-life states, preventing their prosecution. This significant legislation extends the already existing law in California that protects doctors providing abortion services to out-of-state patients traveling to California. Extending Protection to Providers California had pre-existing laws safeguarding doctors who offer abortion services from judgments stemming from other states. However, the newly signed legislation amplifies the protection, ensuring authorities do not collaborate with out-of-state investigations into providers mailing abortion pills to other states. The law also prohibits bail agents or bounty hunters from detaining doctors and pharmacists in California and transporting them to another state to face trials for providing an abortion. A Lifeline to Essential Care “Health care providers, physically located in California, will be able to offer a lifeline to people in states that have cut off access to essential care, and be shielded from the draconian laws of those states,” stated the bill’s author, Democrat state Sen. Nancy Skinner. The law, akin to those in New York and Massachusetts, even restricts state-based media companies, like Facebook, from cooperating with out-of-state investigations. A Stand for Women’s Rights Governor Newsom, reinforcing his commitment to protecting women and health care workers providing basic care, signed this landmark bill, emphasizing California’s stance on women’s rights and medical freedom. This law is crucial for those seeking essential care, especially in states with stringent pro-life laws, thus enabling a supportive network for women in need. Boundaries Overstepped? However, this monumental legislation hasn’t been welcomed by all. Pro-life groups, like Susan B. Anthony Pro-Life America, condemned the law, asserting that the California government is disregarding state borders and imposing its will. They argued that California’s protections for abortion providers overshadow the diverse values and laws of other states. Impact of the Legislation While the new law shields health care providers within California, those leaving the state and prescribing abortion pills will not enjoy the protection offered by the law. This legislation not only fosters medical freedom and women’s rights but also invites discussions about state sovereignty and the extent to which one state can offer protections that might infringe upon the laws of another. Concluding Thoughts This revolutionary bill signed by Gov. Newsom symbolizes a pivotal advancement in women’s health care rights and medical freedom. It facilitates the provision of essential care to those residing in pro-life states and asserts California’s stance on protecting women’s reproductive rights. Nonetheless, the ramifications of this legislation on state relationships and the ongoing debate between pro-life and pro-choice proponents will continue to unfold in the coming times.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Unwavering Allegiance - Trump Maintains Favor Despite Debates Absence!</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/29/Trump-GOP-Favorite/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Unwavering Allegiance - Trump Maintains Favor Despite Debates Absence!" /><published>2023-09-29T16:17:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-29T16:17:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/29/Trump-GOP-Favorite</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/29/Trump-GOP-Favorite/">&lt;p&gt;In a surprising turn of events, former President Donald Trump retains solid support and remains the top choice among Republican voters, despite not participating in the initial GOP debates. This steadfast loyalty surfaces amidst legal disputes and a recent ruling by a Manhattan judge on fraud allegations related to his business practices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;trumps-unyielding-fandom&quot;&gt;Trump’s Unyielding Fandom&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A poll, undertaken for the New York Post by Leger, reveals a substantial 62% of GOP voters preferring Trump as the party’s nominee, overshadowing Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis, who trails significantly at 10%. Notably, Trump’s support saw a 2% rise following his absence from the first debate, highlighting the unwavering allegiance from his voter base.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-sustaining-grip-of-trumpism&quot;&gt;The Sustaining Grip of Trumpism&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite the legal turbulence and the debate absenteeism, the stronghold of Trumpism seems unscathed. “I’ve sort of kind of had to convince myself nothing’s gonna surprise me anymore with that, with this individual, but I just think that there’s a strong segment of Republican voters that there’s not much that’s gonna sway them,” conveyed Andrew Enns, Leger’s Executive Vice President.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;views-from-the-other-side&quot;&gt;Views from the Other Side&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remarkably, 37% of Democrat-leaning voters anticipate Trump securing the nomination and contending against President Joe Biden in the general election. Out of those surveyed, 43% believe Trump would triumph over Biden, while 32% are in Biden’s corner, and 26% remain undecided.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;impact-of-legal-outcomes&quot;&gt;Impact of Legal Outcomes&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, the support for Trump experiences a decline when posed with hypothetical scenarios of guilt or imprisonment before the elections, with only 36% backing him to defeat Biden under such circumstances.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-battle-of-unwavering-belief-vs-reality&quot;&gt;A Battle of Unwavering Belief vs Reality?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This enduring support raises questions about the impact of legal accusations and political behavior on voter preferences and loyalty. It delves into whether unwavering belief can override reality, legal standings, and ethical considerations in political landscapes, affecting electoral outcomes and political trajectories.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;conclusions&quot;&gt;Conclusions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trump’s steadfast popularity amidst controversies and legal skirmishes reflects a deeper narrative about political allegiance and voter psychology. It underscores the inherent complexities within the political sphere, where loyalty often intertwines with perception and belief, regardless of objective truth and legal realities. This phenomenon reiterates the multifaceted dynamics in play within the electoral realm, showcasing how perceptions, loyalties, and beliefs can mold political landscapes, shaping the course of political discourse and determining the actors on the political stage.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a surprising turn of events, former President Donald Trump retains solid support and remains the top choice among Republican voters, despite not participating in the initial GOP debates. This steadfast loyalty surfaces amidst legal disputes and a recent ruling by a Manhattan judge on fraud allegations related to his business practices. Trump’s Unyielding Fandom A poll, undertaken for the New York Post by Leger, reveals a substantial 62% of GOP voters preferring Trump as the party’s nominee, overshadowing Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis, who trails significantly at 10%. Notably, Trump’s support saw a 2% rise following his absence from the first debate, highlighting the unwavering allegiance from his voter base. The Sustaining Grip of Trumpism Despite the legal turbulence and the debate absenteeism, the stronghold of Trumpism seems unscathed. “I’ve sort of kind of had to convince myself nothing’s gonna surprise me anymore with that, with this individual, but I just think that there’s a strong segment of Republican voters that there’s not much that’s gonna sway them,” conveyed Andrew Enns, Leger’s Executive Vice President. Views from the Other Side Remarkably, 37% of Democrat-leaning voters anticipate Trump securing the nomination and contending against President Joe Biden in the general election. Out of those surveyed, 43% believe Trump would triumph over Biden, while 32% are in Biden’s corner, and 26% remain undecided. Impact of Legal Outcomes However, the support for Trump experiences a decline when posed with hypothetical scenarios of guilt or imprisonment before the elections, with only 36% backing him to defeat Biden under such circumstances. A Battle of Unwavering Belief vs Reality? This enduring support raises questions about the impact of legal accusations and political behavior on voter preferences and loyalty. It delves into whether unwavering belief can override reality, legal standings, and ethical considerations in political landscapes, affecting electoral outcomes and political trajectories. Conclusions Trump’s steadfast popularity amidst controversies and legal skirmishes reflects a deeper narrative about political allegiance and voter psychology. It underscores the inherent complexities within the political sphere, where loyalty often intertwines with perception and belief, regardless of objective truth and legal realities. This phenomenon reiterates the multifaceted dynamics in play within the electoral realm, showcasing how perceptions, loyalties, and beliefs can mold political landscapes, shaping the course of political discourse and determining the actors on the political stage.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Unanticipated Visit - Elon Musk Surveys Texas Border Crisis</title><link href="/news/2023/09/29/Musk-Texas-Border-Visit/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Unanticipated Visit - Elon Musk Surveys Texas Border Crisis" /><published>2023-09-29T15:01:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-29T15:01:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/29/Musk-Texas-Border-Visit</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/29/Musk-Texas-Border-Visit/">&lt;p&gt;In a rather surprising move, tech magnate Elon Musk recently made an unexpected visit to the Texas border, a current hotspot of migrant crisis, alongside U.S. Representative Tony Gonzales (R-TX). The visit shed light on the ongoing severe situations occurring under the international bridge in Eagle Pass, where numerous migrants are being held.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-spotlight-on-the-crisis&quot;&gt;A Spotlight on the Crisis&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The unanticipated visit by Elon Musk, the CEO of Tesla and SpaceX, has brought a renewed focus on the worsening border situation. It seems that Musk and Rep. Gonzales were there to observe the conditions in which migrants are being detained. This area under the international bridge has been the center of attention due to the escalating number of migrants who cross and are subsequently held, awaiting transportation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;behind-the-scenes&quot;&gt;Behind the Scenes&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rep. Gonzales had hinted at a potential visit with Musk earlier in the day. “Can’t say anything, stay tuned!” was Gonzales’ suspense-filled message to Breitbart Texas. Musk himself subtly hinted at this visit in a previous post on ‘X’. The intrigue ended when Musk, along with several Texas sheriffs and Rep. Gonzales, was spotted at around 5:30 PM starting his visit under the international bridge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;musks-unexpected-venture&quot;&gt;Musk’s Unexpected Venture&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Elon Musk, known predominantly for his advancements in electric vehicles and space exploration technology, entering the fray of border politics is a surprising turn of events. His visit, accompanied by law enforcement officers and Rep. Gonzales, raises curiosity about his intentions and role in addressing or understanding the border crisis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-situation-on-ground&quot;&gt;The Situation on Ground&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The migrant detention area has become notorious for holding record numbers of migrants who, after crossing, are left in limbo as they await further transportation. This visibility of the Texas border crisis has seen numerous dignitaries and officials visit to witness the conditions first hand. Musk and Gonzales gathering with Texas sheriffs under the international bridge emphasizes the gravity of the ongoing crisis and the urgent need for resolutions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Musk’s unexpected visit to the Texas border, accompanied by Rep. Gonzales, will likely instigate discussions and possibly incite actions or proposals to address the crisis. The current situations at the Texas border, with rising numbers of migrants and ensuing challenges, require urgent and substantial interventions, and involvement by figures like Elon Musk may escalate the attention and resolutions this crisis demands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With Musk’s diverse array of innovations and endeavors, could this visit signify a new chapter involving him in social and political discussions? Only time will reveal the impact and outcomes of this unanticipated venture by Elon Musk into the border crisis hotspot.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a rather surprising move, tech magnate Elon Musk recently made an unexpected visit to the Texas border, a current hotspot of migrant crisis, alongside U.S. Representative Tony Gonzales (R-TX). The visit shed light on the ongoing severe situations occurring under the international bridge in Eagle Pass, where numerous migrants are being held. A Spotlight on the Crisis The unanticipated visit by Elon Musk, the CEO of Tesla and SpaceX, has brought a renewed focus on the worsening border situation. It seems that Musk and Rep. Gonzales were there to observe the conditions in which migrants are being detained. This area under the international bridge has been the center of attention due to the escalating number of migrants who cross and are subsequently held, awaiting transportation. Behind the Scenes Rep. Gonzales had hinted at a potential visit with Musk earlier in the day. “Can’t say anything, stay tuned!” was Gonzales’ suspense-filled message to Breitbart Texas. Musk himself subtly hinted at this visit in a previous post on ‘X’. The intrigue ended when Musk, along with several Texas sheriffs and Rep. Gonzales, was spotted at around 5:30 PM starting his visit under the international bridge. Musk’s Unexpected Venture Elon Musk, known predominantly for his advancements in electric vehicles and space exploration technology, entering the fray of border politics is a surprising turn of events. His visit, accompanied by law enforcement officers and Rep. Gonzales, raises curiosity about his intentions and role in addressing or understanding the border crisis. The Situation on Ground The migrant detention area has become notorious for holding record numbers of migrants who, after crossing, are left in limbo as they await further transportation. This visibility of the Texas border crisis has seen numerous dignitaries and officials visit to witness the conditions first hand. Musk and Gonzales gathering with Texas sheriffs under the international bridge emphasizes the gravity of the ongoing crisis and the urgent need for resolutions. Conclusion Musk’s unexpected visit to the Texas border, accompanied by Rep. Gonzales, will likely instigate discussions and possibly incite actions or proposals to address the crisis. The current situations at the Texas border, with rising numbers of migrants and ensuing challenges, require urgent and substantial interventions, and involvement by figures like Elon Musk may escalate the attention and resolutions this crisis demands. With Musk’s diverse array of innovations and endeavors, could this visit signify a new chapter involving him in social and political discussions? Only time will reveal the impact and outcomes of this unanticipated venture by Elon Musk into the border crisis hotspot.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Explosive Encounters - GOP Faces Internal Clash!</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/29/GOP-Fireworks/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Explosive Encounters - GOP Faces Internal Clash!" /><published>2023-09-29T14:03:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-29T14:03:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/29/GOP-Fireworks</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/29/GOP-Fireworks/">&lt;p&gt;The GOP landscape is experiencing a turbulent shakeup as internal conflicts and accusations are brought to light. At the heart of the storm is a fiery confrontation between Rep. Matt Gaetz (R-Fla.) and House Speaker Kevin McCarthy (R-Calif.). The clash transpired in a closed-door House GOP conference, with allegations and fiery words exchanged, offering a glimpse into the tempestuous relations within the GOP ranks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;gaetz-vs-mccarthy---a-battle-of-words&quot;&gt;Gaetz vs McCarthy - A Battle of Words&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A heated encounter ensued as Gaetz accused McCarthy of orchestrating an online campaign to tarnish his reputation. Gaetz alleges that McCarthy employed “MAGA influencers” to post derogatory content about him on social media platforms. McCarthy, vehemently denying the accusations, dismissed Gaetz’s claims, stating he wouldn’t “waste his time” on such endeavors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;rising-tensions-within&quot;&gt;Rising Tensions Within&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This confrontation symbolizes more than just a personal squabble; it reflects the rising tensions and fragmented relations within the party. Other GOP members reportedly expressed their frustrations with Gaetz during the meeting, with one calling him to “f— off,” and another labeling him a “scumbag.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-war-of-accusations&quot;&gt;A War of Accusations&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gaetz seems unyielding in his stance, confronting McCarthy about the alleged payments to influencers. The strife continued as Gaetz claimed that McCarthy would rather focus on expanding the majority than resolving the alleged smear campaigns. A spokesperson for McCarthy refuted the involvement in any such campaigns, pointing instead to potential Democrat-backed initiatives against Gaetz.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;unresolved-allegations&quot;&gt;Unresolved Allegations&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The battle between Gaetz and McCarthy further intensifies as Gaetz threatens a floor vote to oust McCarthy from leadership positions due to alleged deal violations. The rising turmoil and unresolved allegations between the two showcase the increasing instability and discord within the GOP, with both parties remaining firm on their stands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;implications-on-governance&quot;&gt;Implications on Governance&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The internal strife comes at a pivotal time, with crucial government decisions and legislations on the line, affecting the party’s collective stance and ability to navigate through pressing issues. The discord within poses a significant challenge in presenting a united front, with the potential to impact decisions on government shutdowns and spending.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The internal conflagrations within the GOP, epitomized by the Gaetz-McCarthy clash, bring forth questions about unity, leadership, and the direction in which the party is heading. It remains to be seen whether these internal battles will forge stronger alliances or lead to deeper fractures within the party, impacting its approach to governance and legislation in the process.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">The GOP landscape is experiencing a turbulent shakeup as internal conflicts and accusations are brought to light. At the heart of the storm is a fiery confrontation between Rep. Matt Gaetz (R-Fla.) and House Speaker Kevin McCarthy (R-Calif.). The clash transpired in a closed-door House GOP conference, with allegations and fiery words exchanged, offering a glimpse into the tempestuous relations within the GOP ranks. Gaetz vs McCarthy - A Battle of Words A heated encounter ensued as Gaetz accused McCarthy of orchestrating an online campaign to tarnish his reputation. Gaetz alleges that McCarthy employed “MAGA influencers” to post derogatory content about him on social media platforms. McCarthy, vehemently denying the accusations, dismissed Gaetz’s claims, stating he wouldn’t “waste his time” on such endeavors. Rising Tensions Within This confrontation symbolizes more than just a personal squabble; it reflects the rising tensions and fragmented relations within the party. Other GOP members reportedly expressed their frustrations with Gaetz during the meeting, with one calling him to “f— off,” and another labeling him a “scumbag.” A War of Accusations Gaetz seems unyielding in his stance, confronting McCarthy about the alleged payments to influencers. The strife continued as Gaetz claimed that McCarthy would rather focus on expanding the majority than resolving the alleged smear campaigns. A spokesperson for McCarthy refuted the involvement in any such campaigns, pointing instead to potential Democrat-backed initiatives against Gaetz. Unresolved Allegations The battle between Gaetz and McCarthy further intensifies as Gaetz threatens a floor vote to oust McCarthy from leadership positions due to alleged deal violations. The rising turmoil and unresolved allegations between the two showcase the increasing instability and discord within the GOP, with both parties remaining firm on their stands. Implications on Governance The internal strife comes at a pivotal time, with crucial government decisions and legislations on the line, affecting the party’s collective stance and ability to navigate through pressing issues. The discord within poses a significant challenge in presenting a united front, with the potential to impact decisions on government shutdowns and spending. Conclusion The internal conflagrations within the GOP, epitomized by the Gaetz-McCarthy clash, bring forth questions about unity, leadership, and the direction in which the party is heading. It remains to be seen whether these internal battles will forge stronger alliances or lead to deeper fractures within the party, impacting its approach to governance and legislation in the process.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Dazzle and Dance - Usher’s Vision for 2024 Super Bowl Halftime Show</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/29/Usher-Super-Bowl-Performance/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dazzle and Dance - Usher’s Vision for 2024 Super Bowl Halftime Show" /><published>2023-09-29T13:08:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-29T13:08:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/29/Usher-Super-Bowl-Performance</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/29/Usher-Super-Bowl-Performance/">&lt;p&gt;Usher, the acclaimed “DJ Got Us Falling In Love” singer, is preparing to deliver an unforgettable performance during the 2024 Super Bowl Halftime Show. Sources close to the pop icon reveal plans to integrate “tastefully dressed” pole dancers and roller skaters, aiming to create a spectacle that is both family-friendly and groundbreaking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-vision-of-elegance-and-excitement&quot;&gt;A Vision of Elegance and Excitement&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Usher is no stranger to incorporating dynamic and provocative elements into his shows, often featuring dancers in striking outfits that echo the vibrant atmosphere of his Las Vegas stage performances. For the Super Bowl, he envisions a balanced aesthetic that respects the diverse audience, ensuring the entertainment is suitable for fans of all ages. “He is definitely keeping in mind that his younger fans will be watching,” a source shared with PageSix.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;crafting-a-legacy&quot;&gt;Crafting a Legacy&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Usher aspires to craft a historic moment that will resonate with audiences worldwide, setting himself apart from previous iconic performers like Beyoncé, Rihanna, Dr. Dre, Prince, and Michael Jackson. He is determined to bring something fresh, exciting, and memorable to the global stage, elevating the entertainment value of the event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;an-album-launch-to-remember&quot;&gt;An Album Launch to Remember&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Beyond his ambitious performance plans, Usher is also set to launch his new album, “Coming Home,” on Super Bowl Sunday, marking his first album release since 2016. The artist expressed his excitement and gratitude for the opportunity, stating, “It’s an honor of a lifetime to finally check a Super Bowl performance off my bucket list.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;aiming-for-history&quot;&gt;Aiming for History&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The NFL is equally thrilled about Usher’s upcoming performance, anticipating a show that will leave a lasting imprint on the cultural landscape. Seth Dudowsky, the head of music for the NFL, said, “Usher is an icon whose music has left an indelible mark… We look forward to working with Usher, Roc Nation, and Apple Music to bring fans another Halftime Show for the history books.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;balancing-act&quot;&gt;Balancing Act&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While aiming to set new standards, Usher and the NFL are mindful of the controversies that have marred previous Super Bowl Halftime Shows, such as the infamous “wardrobe malfunction” incident involving Janet Jackson and Justin Timberlake in 2004. The intention is to deliver a performance that is spectacular yet respectful, avoiding any elements that could potentially spark outrage or discomfort.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Usher’s planned performance for the 2024 Super Bowl Halftime Show is set to be a harmonious blend of elegance, excitement, and innovation. By integrating tastefully attired dancers and thrilling elements, he aims to create a show that is inclusive, entertaining, and memorable, contributing to the rich legacy of Super Bowl Halftime Shows. With the world watching, Usher is ready to dazzle fans and create history on February 11, 2024, in Las Vegas.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Usher, the acclaimed “DJ Got Us Falling In Love” singer, is preparing to deliver an unforgettable performance during the 2024 Super Bowl Halftime Show. Sources close to the pop icon reveal plans to integrate “tastefully dressed” pole dancers and roller skaters, aiming to create a spectacle that is both family-friendly and groundbreaking. A Vision of Elegance and Excitement Usher is no stranger to incorporating dynamic and provocative elements into his shows, often featuring dancers in striking outfits that echo the vibrant atmosphere of his Las Vegas stage performances. For the Super Bowl, he envisions a balanced aesthetic that respects the diverse audience, ensuring the entertainment is suitable for fans of all ages. “He is definitely keeping in mind that his younger fans will be watching,” a source shared with PageSix. Crafting a Legacy Usher aspires to craft a historic moment that will resonate with audiences worldwide, setting himself apart from previous iconic performers like Beyoncé, Rihanna, Dr. Dre, Prince, and Michael Jackson. He is determined to bring something fresh, exciting, and memorable to the global stage, elevating the entertainment value of the event. An Album Launch to Remember Beyond his ambitious performance plans, Usher is also set to launch his new album, “Coming Home,” on Super Bowl Sunday, marking his first album release since 2016. The artist expressed his excitement and gratitude for the opportunity, stating, “It’s an honor of a lifetime to finally check a Super Bowl performance off my bucket list.” Aiming for History The NFL is equally thrilled about Usher’s upcoming performance, anticipating a show that will leave a lasting imprint on the cultural landscape. Seth Dudowsky, the head of music for the NFL, said, “Usher is an icon whose music has left an indelible mark… We look forward to working with Usher, Roc Nation, and Apple Music to bring fans another Halftime Show for the history books.” Balancing Act While aiming to set new standards, Usher and the NFL are mindful of the controversies that have marred previous Super Bowl Halftime Shows, such as the infamous “wardrobe malfunction” incident involving Janet Jackson and Justin Timberlake in 2004. The intention is to deliver a performance that is spectacular yet respectful, avoiding any elements that could potentially spark outrage or discomfort. Conclusion Usher’s planned performance for the 2024 Super Bowl Halftime Show is set to be a harmonious blend of elegance, excitement, and innovation. By integrating tastefully attired dancers and thrilling elements, he aims to create a show that is inclusive, entertaining, and memorable, contributing to the rich legacy of Super Bowl Halftime Shows. With the world watching, Usher is ready to dazzle fans and create history on February 11, 2024, in Las Vegas.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Massive Bust in Florida - Teacher and Disney Employees Among Arrested</title><link href="/news/2023/09/29/Major-Human-Trafficking-Bust-Florida/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Massive Bust in Florida - Teacher and Disney Employees Among Arrested" /><published>2023-09-29T12:11:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-29T12:11:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/29/Major-Human-Trafficking-Bust-Florida</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/29/Major-Human-Trafficking-Bust-Florida/">&lt;h3 id=&quot;massive-sweep---exposing-hidden-crimes-in-florida&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Massive Sweep - Exposing Hidden Crimes in Florida&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a shocking revelation, Polk County, Florida unveiled the results of a substantial human trafficking operation, leading to the arrest of 219 individuals, which included a high school teacher and three Disney employees. This extensive operation exposed the grim reality of hidden crimes happening under the day-to-day life of the sun-soaked state, shaking the local community to its core.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;details-of-the-operation&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details of The Operation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Initiated earlier this month, the operation was a strategic move to unveil the extensive network of human trafficking and related criminal activities in the region. A harrowing find was the presence of individuals residing in the country illegally and those who were in professions of trust, including education.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sheriff Grady Judd announced the daunting results, revealing that out of 119 arrested prostitutes, 21 were possible victims of human trafficking. The operation charged a total of 44 felonies and 242 misdemeanors, setting a record in the number of arrests made during a single operation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-suspects---a-closer-look&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Suspects - A Closer Look&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Among the arrested, Freddy Escalona and Maria Guzman, both residing in the U.S. illegally, were charged with human trafficking and deriving proceeds from prostitution. Escalona, after lending money to a victim, allegedly forced her into prostitution when she couldn’t repay him. Meanwhile, Guzman supposedly trafficked victims from a hotel in Orlando, organizing their “dates” and profiting from the earnings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;shock-and-disappointment-in-educational-institutions&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shock and Disappointment in Educational Institutions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Among the apprehended was Russell Rogers, an athletic director at Vanguard School and a teacher at Auburndale High School REAL Academy. The arrest has caused a stir, and Polk County Schools expressed their disappointment and are moving forward with terminating Rogers’ employment, emphasizing the higher standards educators are held to both in and out of the classroom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;disney-employees---a-concerning-discovery&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disney Employees - A Concerning Discovery&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The arrest of three Disney employees is raising eyebrows and bringing forward concerns about the presence of such individuals in family-oriented establishments. It uncovers an unsettling truth about the people entrusted with maintaining a safe and enjoyable environment for families and children.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;conclusion---a-step-toward-eradicating-hidden-crimes&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conclusion - A Step Toward Eradicating Hidden Crimes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This extensive operation has not only exposed the deep-seated issues related to human trafficking and related crimes in Florida but also highlighted the presence of such illicit activities in professional settings. The substantial arrests and the identification of human trafficking victims show a significant step forward in uncovering and combatting such hidden crimes, hoping to bring justice to the victims and maintain community safety.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The cooperation between different sheriff’s offices and agencies including the Florida Department of Children and Families, proves invaluable in such operations, emphasizing the need for unified efforts in eradicating human trafficking and ensuring community welfare.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Massive Sweep - Exposing Hidden Crimes in Florida In a shocking revelation, Polk County, Florida unveiled the results of a substantial human trafficking operation, leading to the arrest of 219 individuals, which included a high school teacher and three Disney employees. This extensive operation exposed the grim reality of hidden crimes happening under the day-to-day life of the sun-soaked state, shaking the local community to its core. Details of The Operation Initiated earlier this month, the operation was a strategic move to unveil the extensive network of human trafficking and related criminal activities in the region. A harrowing find was the presence of individuals residing in the country illegally and those who were in professions of trust, including education. Sheriff Grady Judd announced the daunting results, revealing that out of 119 arrested prostitutes, 21 were possible victims of human trafficking. The operation charged a total of 44 felonies and 242 misdemeanors, setting a record in the number of arrests made during a single operation. The Suspects - A Closer Look Among the arrested, Freddy Escalona and Maria Guzman, both residing in the U.S. illegally, were charged with human trafficking and deriving proceeds from prostitution. Escalona, after lending money to a victim, allegedly forced her into prostitution when she couldn’t repay him. Meanwhile, Guzman supposedly trafficked victims from a hotel in Orlando, organizing their “dates” and profiting from the earnings. Shock and Disappointment in Educational Institutions Among the apprehended was Russell Rogers, an athletic director at Vanguard School and a teacher at Auburndale High School REAL Academy. The arrest has caused a stir, and Polk County Schools expressed their disappointment and are moving forward with terminating Rogers’ employment, emphasizing the higher standards educators are held to both in and out of the classroom. Disney Employees - A Concerning Discovery The arrest of three Disney employees is raising eyebrows and bringing forward concerns about the presence of such individuals in family-oriented establishments. It uncovers an unsettling truth about the people entrusted with maintaining a safe and enjoyable environment for families and children. Conclusion - A Step Toward Eradicating Hidden Crimes This extensive operation has not only exposed the deep-seated issues related to human trafficking and related crimes in Florida but also highlighted the presence of such illicit activities in professional settings. The substantial arrests and the identification of human trafficking victims show a significant step forward in uncovering and combatting such hidden crimes, hoping to bring justice to the victims and maintain community safety. The cooperation between different sheriff’s offices and agencies including the Florida Department of Children and Families, proves invaluable in such operations, emphasizing the need for unified efforts in eradicating human trafficking and ensuring community welfare.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Fair Use or Foul Play? - Barry Diller Criticizes WGA Deal Over AI</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/29/AI-Copyright-Controversy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Fair Use or Foul Play? - Barry Diller Criticizes WGA Deal Over AI" /><published>2023-09-29T11:02:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-29T11:02:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/29/AI-Copyright-Controversy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/29/AI-Copyright-Controversy/">&lt;p&gt;The debate between Artificial Intelligence (AI) and copyright laws is heating up as Barry Diller, Chairman of IAC and Expedia, voices his concerns over the current agreement between the Writers Guild of America (WGA) and studios, claiming it falls short of protecting copyright holders from the expansive reach of AI.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;ai-and-copyright---a-tumultuous-encounter&quot;&gt;AI and Copyright - A Tumultuous Encounter&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Diller argues that the process of feeding entire copyrighted materials into AI systems to refine their writing abilities compromises the intellectual property rights of the authors. Prominent authors, including George R.R. Martin and Jodi Picoult, have already raised their concerns and filed suits against AI entities like OpenAI for copyright infringement, striving to guard their creations against unauthorized utilization by AI technologies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-battle-over-fair-use&quot;&gt;The Battle over Fair Use&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Diller contends that “fair use” needs to be redefined. In his view, AI’s ability to consume extensive amounts of information violates the core principles of copyright law. “All we want to do is establish that there is no such thing as fair use for AI,” Diller emphasized on CNBC’s “Squawk Box.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His comments come after the WGA’s tentative agreement with Hollywood studios to conclude a nearly 150-day strike. Diller expressed his dissatisfaction with the agreement’s lack of adequate provisions to protect writers from AI, describing it as a paragraph that “protected nothing from no one.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;ai---a-threat-or-opportunity&quot;&gt;AI - A Threat or Opportunity?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While the ongoing tussle mainly revolves around compensation and the unauthorized use of copyrighted work, it also brings to light the broader implications of AI in the creative realm. Some see AI as a potential threat to the creative industry, fearing it could take over human roles in content creation. Others view AI as an opportunity for additional revenue, leveraging AI technologies to enhance their work and reach wider audiences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, this raises the question of whether the true motive behind these class-action suits is to halt the progress of AI or to ensure due compensation for the use of intellectual property. If AI indeed posed a severe threat to creativity and originality, efforts would likely be geared towards restraining its development rather than seeking monetary consideration for its use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;conclusion---balancing-innovation-and-rights&quot;&gt;Conclusion - Balancing Innovation and Rights&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This ongoing conflict underscores the need to strike a balance between technological innovation and the protection of intellectual property rights. As the entertainment industry grapples with the advancements in AI, it’s crucial to establish clear and fair regulations that safeguard the interests of creators while fostering innovation and progress in AI technology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether it’s a quest for compensation or genuine concern over intellectual rights, the current scenario necessitates thoughtful deliberation and inclusive dialogue to reconcile the interests of all stakeholders in the ever-evolving landscape of art and technology.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">The debate between Artificial Intelligence (AI) and copyright laws is heating up as Barry Diller, Chairman of IAC and Expedia, voices his concerns over the current agreement between the Writers Guild of America (WGA) and studios, claiming it falls short of protecting copyright holders from the expansive reach of AI. AI and Copyright - A Tumultuous Encounter Diller argues that the process of feeding entire copyrighted materials into AI systems to refine their writing abilities compromises the intellectual property rights of the authors. Prominent authors, including George R.R. Martin and Jodi Picoult, have already raised their concerns and filed suits against AI entities like OpenAI for copyright infringement, striving to guard their creations against unauthorized utilization by AI technologies. The Battle over Fair Use Diller contends that “fair use” needs to be redefined. In his view, AI’s ability to consume extensive amounts of information violates the core principles of copyright law. “All we want to do is establish that there is no such thing as fair use for AI,” Diller emphasized on CNBC’s “Squawk Box.” His comments come after the WGA’s tentative agreement with Hollywood studios to conclude a nearly 150-day strike. Diller expressed his dissatisfaction with the agreement’s lack of adequate provisions to protect writers from AI, describing it as a paragraph that “protected nothing from no one.” AI - A Threat or Opportunity? While the ongoing tussle mainly revolves around compensation and the unauthorized use of copyrighted work, it also brings to light the broader implications of AI in the creative realm. Some see AI as a potential threat to the creative industry, fearing it could take over human roles in content creation. Others view AI as an opportunity for additional revenue, leveraging AI technologies to enhance their work and reach wider audiences. However, this raises the question of whether the true motive behind these class-action suits is to halt the progress of AI or to ensure due compensation for the use of intellectual property. If AI indeed posed a severe threat to creativity and originality, efforts would likely be geared towards restraining its development rather than seeking monetary consideration for its use. Conclusion - Balancing Innovation and Rights This ongoing conflict underscores the need to strike a balance between technological innovation and the protection of intellectual property rights. As the entertainment industry grapples with the advancements in AI, it’s crucial to establish clear and fair regulations that safeguard the interests of creators while fostering innovation and progress in AI technology. Whether it’s a quest for compensation or genuine concern over intellectual rights, the current scenario necessitates thoughtful deliberation and inclusive dialogue to reconcile the interests of all stakeholders in the ever-evolving landscape of art and technology.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Battle Over Birthright - GOP Aims to Redefine Citizenship Rules</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/29/Birthright-Citizenship-Debate/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Battle Over Birthright - GOP Aims to Redefine Citizenship Rules" /><published>2023-09-29T10:01:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-29T10:01:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/29/Birthright-Citizenship-Debate</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/29/Birthright-Citizenship-Debate/">&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;battle over birthright citizenship&lt;/strong&gt; is intensifying within the Republican party as the majority of GOP Presidential candidates have rallied behind the idea of abolishing the policy of awarding citizenship to all children born on U.S. soil, regardless of their parents’ immigration status.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;anchor-babies---a-central-issue&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Anchor Babies - A Central Issue&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every year, approximately 400,000 children are born in the United States to parents who are illegal immigrants. These children, often referred to as “anchor babies,” receive U.S. citizenship by birthright, anchoring their families to the United States for generations. This practice has sparked controversy and debate, especially among Republicans, with some viewing it as a magnet for illegal immigration and a misinterpretation of the 14th Amendment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During recent debates, prominent GOP candidates such as Vivek Ramaswamy and Donald Trump have explicitly stated their intentions to &lt;strong&gt;end birthright citizenship&lt;/strong&gt;, a policy that seems to resonate with a significant number of Republican voters. A 2021 Cato Institute survey revealed that more than 60% of GOP voters oppose birthright citizenship, and a 2018 Rasmussen Reports poll showed 72% opposition within the party.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;gop-candidates-stand-united&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GOP Candidates Stand United&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Businessman Vivek Ramaswamy emphasized that he would abolish birthright citizenship for children of illegal immigrants. He highlighted the importance of reading and interpreting the 14th Amendment correctly, stating, “What it says is that ‘all persons born or naturalized in the United States and subject to the laws and jurisdictions thereof are citizens.’”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Former President Donald Trump, consistent with his stance since 2015, proclaimed that he would sign an executive order to abolish the policy on the first day of his term, if re-elected.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis has included ending birthright citizenship as part of his presidential bid’s official immigration platform, pledging action against the “major driver of illegal migration.” Nikki Haley and other Republican personalities have also expressed their opposition to the policy, although not outlining explicit plans to end it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;differing-interpretations-and-implications&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Differing Interpretations and Implications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The 14th Amendment was originally drafted concerning slaves, not illegal immigrants, but over time, it has been applied to illegal immigration. The ongoing debate centers around whether individuals who enter the U.S. illegally are truly under the jurisdiction of U.S. laws and whether their U.S.-born children should automatically receive citizenship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ending birthright citizenship would align the United States with several other developed nations like Australia, France, and New Zealand, which reserve citizenship for children with at least one citizen parent. However, any moves to end this policy are likely to face stiff resistance and legal battles, with opponents arguing such changes would violate the Constitution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conclusion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The united front presented by GOP candidates on the birthright citizenship debate reveals a significant shift in the party’s stance, echoing the sentiments of a majority of Republican voters. However, despite the newfound consensus within the party, any concrete moves to abolish birthright citizenship are bound to stir controversy and ignite fierce legal and constitutional battles, with the Supreme Court possibly having the final say in this contentious issue. Whether this shared stance will translate into actual policy change remains to be seen, but it’s clear that the debate over birthright citizenship is far from over.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">The battle over birthright citizenship is intensifying within the Republican party as the majority of GOP Presidential candidates have rallied behind the idea of abolishing the policy of awarding citizenship to all children born on U.S. soil, regardless of their parents’ immigration status. Anchor Babies - A Central Issue Every year, approximately 400,000 children are born in the United States to parents who are illegal immigrants. These children, often referred to as “anchor babies,” receive U.S. citizenship by birthright, anchoring their families to the United States for generations. This practice has sparked controversy and debate, especially among Republicans, with some viewing it as a magnet for illegal immigration and a misinterpretation of the 14th Amendment. During recent debates, prominent GOP candidates such as Vivek Ramaswamy and Donald Trump have explicitly stated their intentions to end birthright citizenship, a policy that seems to resonate with a significant number of Republican voters. A 2021 Cato Institute survey revealed that more than 60% of GOP voters oppose birthright citizenship, and a 2018 Rasmussen Reports poll showed 72% opposition within the party. GOP Candidates Stand United Businessman Vivek Ramaswamy emphasized that he would abolish birthright citizenship for children of illegal immigrants. He highlighted the importance of reading and interpreting the 14th Amendment correctly, stating, “What it says is that ‘all persons born or naturalized in the United States and subject to the laws and jurisdictions thereof are citizens.’” Former President Donald Trump, consistent with his stance since 2015, proclaimed that he would sign an executive order to abolish the policy on the first day of his term, if re-elected. Even Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis has included ending birthright citizenship as part of his presidential bid’s official immigration platform, pledging action against the “major driver of illegal migration.” Nikki Haley and other Republican personalities have also expressed their opposition to the policy, although not outlining explicit plans to end it. Differing Interpretations and Implications The 14th Amendment was originally drafted concerning slaves, not illegal immigrants, but over time, it has been applied to illegal immigration. The ongoing debate centers around whether individuals who enter the U.S. illegally are truly under the jurisdiction of U.S. laws and whether their U.S.-born children should automatically receive citizenship. Ending birthright citizenship would align the United States with several other developed nations like Australia, France, and New Zealand, which reserve citizenship for children with at least one citizen parent. However, any moves to end this policy are likely to face stiff resistance and legal battles, with opponents arguing such changes would violate the Constitution. Conclusion The united front presented by GOP candidates on the birthright citizenship debate reveals a significant shift in the party’s stance, echoing the sentiments of a majority of Republican voters. However, despite the newfound consensus within the party, any concrete moves to abolish birthright citizenship are bound to stir controversy and ignite fierce legal and constitutional battles, with the Supreme Court possibly having the final say in this contentious issue. Whether this shared stance will translate into actual policy change remains to be seen, but it’s clear that the debate over birthright citizenship is far from over.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A Green Leap Forward - Phasing Out Plastics in America’s National Parks</title><link href="/news/2023/09/29/Plastics-Phaseout-National-Parks/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Green Leap Forward - Phasing Out Plastics in America’s National Parks" /><published>2023-09-29T09:15:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-29T09:15:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/29/Plastics-Phaseout-National-Parks</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/29/Plastics-Phaseout-National-Parks/">&lt;p&gt;The U.S. government, in a historic and environmentally-conscious move, announced its commitment to phasing out single-use plastics in federally managed lands, including iconic national parks, by 2032. This initiative seeks to mitigate the detrimental impact of plastic waste on wildlife and ecosystems and enhance the sustainability of these cherished public lands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;saying-goodbye-to-single-use-plastics&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Saying Goodbye to Single-Use Plastics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Interior Department spearheads this green initiative, addressing the pressing environmental issue of plastic waste. The focus is on eliminating predominant single-use plastics like water bottles, bags, and utensils that currently plague national parks, wildlife refuges, and conservation lands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-vision-for-sustainability&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Vision for Sustainability&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Secretary Deb Haaland initiated this ecological endeavor in 2022, intending to phase out single-use plastics within a decade. The commitment to this vision is manifesting through the implementation of sustainable procurement plans across all bureaus and offices, as was announced on Thursday. This signifies a concerted effort to foster sustainability and conservation on public lands, contributing to global environmental preservation efforts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;progress-and-praise&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Progress and Praise&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;National parks and other interior facilities are already observing significant progress, with the installation of water bottle filling stations, enhanced recycling initiatives, and collaborations with concession operators to diminish the availability of single-use plastics. The environmental organization Oceana, represented by campaign director Christy Leavitt, commended the progress while urging an expedited implementation of the phase-out plans.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;future-plans-and-updates&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Future Plans and Updates&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While the commitment to a plastic-free environment on federally managed lands is resolute, plans will undergo revisions in 2024. These updates will incorporate stepdown targets and elaborate details on the modality and locality of the single-use plastics elimination, providing clearer paths and strategies for achieving the envisioned sustainable future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;environmental-impact-and-global-concern&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Environmental Impact and Global Concern&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Plastic waste is acknowledged globally as a severe environmental problem. With less than 10% of produced plastic ever being recycled, the need for strategic initiatives like this phase-out is paramount. The inherent non-biodegradable nature of plastics poses catastrophic threats to marine and terrestrial wildlife, which inadvertently consume plastics, leading to dire consequences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conclusion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The United States government’s initiative to phase out single-use plastics from national parks and other federally managed lands is a monumental step towards environmental preservation and sustainability. This move, reflecting a synergistic approach to ecological conservation, is poised to inspire similar initiatives globally, fostering a unified combat against plastic pollution. A cleaner, more sustainable future is the beacon of hope, guiding these endeavors and promising a harmonious coexistence of humanity and the environment.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">The U.S. government, in a historic and environmentally-conscious move, announced its commitment to phasing out single-use plastics in federally managed lands, including iconic national parks, by 2032. This initiative seeks to mitigate the detrimental impact of plastic waste on wildlife and ecosystems and enhance the sustainability of these cherished public lands. Saying Goodbye to Single-Use Plastics The Interior Department spearheads this green initiative, addressing the pressing environmental issue of plastic waste. The focus is on eliminating predominant single-use plastics like water bottles, bags, and utensils that currently plague national parks, wildlife refuges, and conservation lands. A Vision for Sustainability Secretary Deb Haaland initiated this ecological endeavor in 2022, intending to phase out single-use plastics within a decade. The commitment to this vision is manifesting through the implementation of sustainable procurement plans across all bureaus and offices, as was announced on Thursday. This signifies a concerted effort to foster sustainability and conservation on public lands, contributing to global environmental preservation efforts. Progress and Praise National parks and other interior facilities are already observing significant progress, with the installation of water bottle filling stations, enhanced recycling initiatives, and collaborations with concession operators to diminish the availability of single-use plastics. The environmental organization Oceana, represented by campaign director Christy Leavitt, commended the progress while urging an expedited implementation of the phase-out plans. Future Plans and Updates While the commitment to a plastic-free environment on federally managed lands is resolute, plans will undergo revisions in 2024. These updates will incorporate stepdown targets and elaborate details on the modality and locality of the single-use plastics elimination, providing clearer paths and strategies for achieving the envisioned sustainable future. Environmental Impact and Global Concern Plastic waste is acknowledged globally as a severe environmental problem. With less than 10% of produced plastic ever being recycled, the need for strategic initiatives like this phase-out is paramount. The inherent non-biodegradable nature of plastics poses catastrophic threats to marine and terrestrial wildlife, which inadvertently consume plastics, leading to dire consequences. Conclusion The United States government’s initiative to phase out single-use plastics from national parks and other federally managed lands is a monumental step towards environmental preservation and sustainability. This move, reflecting a synergistic approach to ecological conservation, is poised to inspire similar initiatives globally, fostering a unified combat against plastic pollution. A cleaner, more sustainable future is the beacon of hope, guiding these endeavors and promising a harmonious coexistence of humanity and the environment.</summary></entry></feed>