<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-10-31T13:14:05-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/31/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-31T13:14:05-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-31T13:14:05-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/31/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/31/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/31/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-31T13:14:05-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-31T13:14:05-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/31/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/31/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/">&lt;p&gt;Recent surprise attacks by Hamas on Israel has fueled ongoing tensions between staunchly conservative commentators and the progressive “Squad” Democrats known for criticizing Israel. The intensity of the backlash highlights the deep political divide over foreign policy in the Middle East.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Hamas’ shocking attack, several members of the “Squad,” including Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.), called for a “ceasefire and de-escalation,” condemning the violence. The absence of a statement from Rep. Rashida Tlaib (D-Mich.) was notably called out by conservative media outlets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;South Carolina GOP Rep. Nancy Mace quickly labeled Ocasio-Cortez a “Hamas apologist” in response to her call for peace and de-escalation. Rep. Ilhan Omar (D-Minn.), no stranger to controversy surrounding her views on Israel, echoed the call for de-escalation and ceasefire. Omar’s prior statements comparing the US and Israel to terrorist groups like Hamas and the Taliban resurfaced in the debate, fueling more criticisms. Omar’s 2019 tweet, where she opined that “Israel has hypnotized the world,” also continues to haunt her political career, often cited by critics to challenge her stance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conservative commentators have been especially vocal. “FOX &amp;amp; Friends Weekend” co-host Rachel Campos-Duffy took aim at Omar, saying she fails to recognize the peace in the Middle East under Trump’s administration. Conservative pundit John Hasson also called out Omar, claiming she insinuated that attacks on IDF forces were acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Massachusetts Democrat Rep. Ayanna Pressley’s concerns over the “devastating attacks on Israelis” were met with skepticism. A prominent conservative online personality, Comfortably Smug, accused the “Squad” of advising Israel to back down after the nation suffered massive attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Jamaal Bowman’s call for an end to the Gaza blockade, in addition to condemning the Hamas attacks, was met with criticism from conservative radio host Jason Rantz. He accused Bowman of pairing his condemnation of terrorism with unwarranted criticisms of Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Cori Bush emphasized the urgent need for a ceasefire, while pushing for an end to “U.S. support for Israeli military occupation and apartheid.” Defense attorney Marina Medvin criticized Bush, suggesting that she equates the death of Palestinian terrorists to the horrific acts committed against Jewish civilians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amidst the political turmoil and intense debate, the attacks have taken a heavy toll. Israeli media report over 300 dead due to the wide-ranging assault. Gaza health officials note that at least 200 Palestinians have perished in the retaliatory Israeli air strikes following the initial Hamas attack. As the situation remains volatile, both sides continue to count their casualties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This divisive issue showcases the challenge America faces in crafting a unified approach to foreign policy, with deeply entrenched political divides at play. As the situation develops, the debate is bound to intensify, shedding light on the complexities of U.S. politics in the global arena.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Bidenflation Bites: McDonald’s Profits Soar as Burger Prices Skyrocket</title><link href="/news/2023/10/31/Bidenflation-Boosts-Burger-Prices/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bidenflation Bites: McDonald’s Profits Soar as Burger Prices Skyrocket" /><published>2023-10-31T13:12:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-31T13:12:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/31/Bidenflation-Boosts-Burger-Prices</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/31/Bidenflation-Boosts-Burger-Prices/">&lt;p&gt;In an era of skyrocketing prices and economic uncertainty, McDonald’s has found a way to turn the tide in its favor, reporting soaring profits and sales in the third quarter. The culprit? None other than the ominous Bidenflation, as rising burger prices contribute to the fast-food giant’s unexpected financial upswing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company’s profits and sales have beaten all estimates, pushing shares higher and leaving investors satisfied. However, this leaves the average American grappling with the reality of rising costs and a strained budget. Revenue shot up by 14 percent, reaching an astounding $6.69 billion, surpassing the expected $6.56 billion. Comparable store sales grew by 8.8 percent, leaving analysts’ 8.0 percent increase prediction in the dust.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chris Kempczinski, McDonald’s Chief Executive, confidently stated, “The macroeconomic environment is unfolding in line with our expectations for the year, and we continued to deliver convenience and value for our customers.” But at what cost?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the U.S. alone, comparable store sales witnessed an 8.1 percent increase, outpacing the forecasted 7.5 percent growth. “Comparable sales results benefited from strong average check growth driven by strategic menu price increases,” McDonald’s admitted. The stark reality is that these “strategic” price hikes are a direct result of the rampant inflation under the Biden administration, coined as Bidenflation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The increase in prices did manage to counteract a noticeable decline in foot traffic to McDonald’s locations. Yet, this reveals a concerning trend: higher costs are driving customers away, particularly those in lower income brackets. Kempczinski noted, “One of the things that we saw industry-wide is that that low-income consumer, which we would say is $45,000 and under, was negative from an industry standpoint.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Net income saw a boost, rising to $2.32 billion, or $3.17 a share, a significant increase from the previous year’s $1.98 billion, or $2.68 a share. Adjusted earnings per share settled at $3.19, surpassing the estimated $3.00 per share.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While McDonald’s might be reveling in its financial success, the harsh reality of Bidenflation looms large, with everyday Americans bearing the brunt of rising prices and a cost of living crisis. The fast-food giant’s prosperity serves as a stark reminder of the urgent need for economic reform and relief from the financial strain imposed by the current administration. It’s high time for a change, and the American people deserve nothing less.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In an era of skyrocketing prices and economic uncertainty, McDonald’s has found a way to turn the tide in its favor, reporting soaring profits and sales in the third quarter. The culprit? None other than the ominous Bidenflation, as rising burger prices contribute to the fast-food giant’s unexpected financial upswing. The company’s profits and sales have beaten all estimates, pushing shares higher and leaving investors satisfied. However, this leaves the average American grappling with the reality of rising costs and a strained budget. Revenue shot up by 14 percent, reaching an astounding $6.69 billion, surpassing the expected $6.56 billion. Comparable store sales grew by 8.8 percent, leaving analysts’ 8.0 percent increase prediction in the dust. Chris Kempczinski, McDonald’s Chief Executive, confidently stated, “The macroeconomic environment is unfolding in line with our expectations for the year, and we continued to deliver convenience and value for our customers.” But at what cost? In the U.S. alone, comparable store sales witnessed an 8.1 percent increase, outpacing the forecasted 7.5 percent growth. “Comparable sales results benefited from strong average check growth driven by strategic menu price increases,” McDonald’s admitted. The stark reality is that these “strategic” price hikes are a direct result of the rampant inflation under the Biden administration, coined as Bidenflation. The increase in prices did manage to counteract a noticeable decline in foot traffic to McDonald’s locations. Yet, this reveals a concerning trend: higher costs are driving customers away, particularly those in lower income brackets. Kempczinski noted, “One of the things that we saw industry-wide is that that low-income consumer, which we would say is $45,000 and under, was negative from an industry standpoint.” Net income saw a boost, rising to $2.32 billion, or $3.17 a share, a significant increase from the previous year’s $1.98 billion, or $2.68 a share. Adjusted earnings per share settled at $3.19, surpassing the estimated $3.00 per share. While McDonald’s might be reveling in its financial success, the harsh reality of Bidenflation looms large, with everyday Americans bearing the brunt of rising prices and a cost of living crisis. The fast-food giant’s prosperity serves as a stark reminder of the urgent need for economic reform and relief from the financial strain imposed by the current administration. It’s high time for a change, and the American people deserve nothing less.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Phil Murphy’s Pricey Party: Taxpayer Dollars at a Taylor Swift Concert</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/31/Phil-Murphy-Taylor-Swift-Concert/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Phil Murphy’s Pricey Party: Taxpayer Dollars at a Taylor Swift Concert" /><published>2023-10-31T11:53:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-31T11:53:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/31/Phil-Murphy-Taylor-Swift-Concert</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/31/Phil-Murphy-Taylor-Swift-Concert/">&lt;p&gt;Governor Phil Murphy has come under intense scrutiny for his extravagant spending of taxpayer money. Shockingly, Murphy used a whopping $12,000 in state funds to revel in food and drinks at a Taylor Swift concert and various other stadium events, as initially reported by Politico.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Governor Murphy’s indiscretions were exposed when his office revealed that it had dipped into a $95,000 personal expense account, which is explicitly set up for “Official Receptions, Official Residence, and Other Official Expenses.” The guidelines are clear – these funds are not to be used for personal purposes. Yet, Murphy saw fit to spend lavishly on his own enjoyment, leaving taxpayers to foot the bill for his entertainment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When confronted with this gross misuse of funds, Murphy’s office hastily claimed that they intended for the state Democratic Party to cover the costs and that they are now “pursuing reimbursement” for the expenses incurred at MetLife Stadium. But the question remains: Why did the Governor believe it was appropriate to use taxpayer money for his personal partying in the first place?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jennifer Sciortino, a spokeswoman for Murphy, tried to justify the expenditures by stating, “Once it was clear that there were outstanding bills that had not been paid, the state stepped up to meet this responsibility.” However, this statement does little to appease the rightly angered public who are tired of politicians misusing their hard-earned money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What makes this situation even more galling is the fact that former New Jersey Governor Chris Christie, a Republican, found himself in a similar situation but chose to have the state Republican Party reimburse the approximately $82,000 spent at MetLife Stadium. Christie’s actions demonstrate a level of accountability and responsibility that Murphy seems to lack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Public records have laid bare the extent of Murphy’s frivolous spending, including nearly $1,000 at a Taylor Swift concert in 2018 and thousands more at various sporting events. This level of extravagance is unacceptable, especially when it is funded by the taxpayer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the Governor’s office scrambles to do damage control, it is clear that Phil Murphy has shown a blatant disregard for the responsible use of taxpayer money. New Jersey residents deserve better than a Governor who parties on their dime, and it is time for Murphy to be held accountable for his actions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a state already grappling with its share of political scandals, including charges against Senator Bob Menendez for acting as a foreign agent, Murphy’s lavish spending adds insult to injury. New Jerseyans are left wondering: when will enough be enough?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Governor Phil Murphy has come under intense scrutiny for his extravagant spending of taxpayer money. Shockingly, Murphy used a whopping $12,000 in state funds to revel in food and drinks at a Taylor Swift concert and various other stadium events, as initially reported by Politico. Governor Murphy’s indiscretions were exposed when his office revealed that it had dipped into a $95,000 personal expense account, which is explicitly set up for “Official Receptions, Official Residence, and Other Official Expenses.” The guidelines are clear – these funds are not to be used for personal purposes. Yet, Murphy saw fit to spend lavishly on his own enjoyment, leaving taxpayers to foot the bill for his entertainment. When confronted with this gross misuse of funds, Murphy’s office hastily claimed that they intended for the state Democratic Party to cover the costs and that they are now “pursuing reimbursement” for the expenses incurred at MetLife Stadium. But the question remains: Why did the Governor believe it was appropriate to use taxpayer money for his personal partying in the first place? Jennifer Sciortino, a spokeswoman for Murphy, tried to justify the expenditures by stating, “Once it was clear that there were outstanding bills that had not been paid, the state stepped up to meet this responsibility.” However, this statement does little to appease the rightly angered public who are tired of politicians misusing their hard-earned money. What makes this situation even more galling is the fact that former New Jersey Governor Chris Christie, a Republican, found himself in a similar situation but chose to have the state Republican Party reimburse the approximately $82,000 spent at MetLife Stadium. Christie’s actions demonstrate a level of accountability and responsibility that Murphy seems to lack. Public records have laid bare the extent of Murphy’s frivolous spending, including nearly $1,000 at a Taylor Swift concert in 2018 and thousands more at various sporting events. This level of extravagance is unacceptable, especially when it is funded by the taxpayer. As the Governor’s office scrambles to do damage control, it is clear that Phil Murphy has shown a blatant disregard for the responsible use of taxpayer money. New Jersey residents deserve better than a Governor who parties on their dime, and it is time for Murphy to be held accountable for his actions. In a state already grappling with its share of political scandals, including charges against Senator Bob Menendez for acting as a foreign agent, Murphy’s lavish spending adds insult to injury. New Jerseyans are left wondering: when will enough be enough?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Amy Schumer Boldly Stands for Israel: Losing Friends but Gaining Freedom</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/31/Amy-Schumer-Support-Israel/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Amy Schumer Boldly Stands for Israel: Losing Friends but Gaining Freedom" /><published>2023-10-31T10:44:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-31T10:44:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/31/Amy-Schumer-Support-Israel</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/31/Amy-Schumer-Support-Israel/">&lt;p&gt;Comedian Amy Schumer has recently come forward, sharing the personal sacrifices she has made due to her staunch support for Israel. Despite facing backlash and losing friends, Schumer stands firm, embracing her identity and her right to voice her opinions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a heartfelt Instagram post, Schumer, known for her roles in hit films like “Trainwreck,” expressed her unwavering support for Israel, particularly in light of the recent violent escalations with Hamas. “I’m a proud Jewish woman and have every right to be,” she affirmed, reflecting her commitment to her heritage and her beliefs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Schumer didn’t shy away from addressing the cost of her stance, acknowledging the loss of many friends in recent weeks. However, she emphasizes feeling “powerful and free,” deriving strength from standing up for what she believes to be the truth. Her post sheds light on the ongoing conflict between Israel and Hamas, bringing attention to the grim realities, including the Israeli hostages still in captivity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The comedian’s bold position has not been without controversy, as she faces severe criticism from her fellow leftists. Schumer’s adamant support for Israel’s right to defend itself against Hamas’ aggression has made her a target of vicious attacks. A senior advisor to a Los Angeles City Councilman recently resigned after making Holocaust-themed jokes about Schumer, highlighting the intense polarization and animosity stemming from her stance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Schumer’s critique extends beyond social circles; she has boldly challenged major news outlets, accusing them of spreading Hamas propaganda. She demanded accountability and the resignation of senior editors at the New York Times and CNN, showcasing her readiness to hold powerful entities to account.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In taking such a public and firm stance, Schumer sets an example of resilience and the importance of standing up for one’s beliefs, even in the face of personal loss and public scrutiny. Her story underscores the complexities and personal toll of the Israel-Hamas conflict, illustrating how these global issues ripple through individual lives, influencing relationships, and shaping public discourse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amy Schumer’s narrative serves as a powerful reminder that voicing support for what one believes to be just and true may come at a significant personal cost, but it also brings a sense of empowerment and freedom that is irreplaceable.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Comedian Amy Schumer has recently come forward, sharing the personal sacrifices she has made due to her staunch support for Israel. Despite facing backlash and losing friends, Schumer stands firm, embracing her identity and her right to voice her opinions. In a heartfelt Instagram post, Schumer, known for her roles in hit films like “Trainwreck,” expressed her unwavering support for Israel, particularly in light of the recent violent escalations with Hamas. “I’m a proud Jewish woman and have every right to be,” she affirmed, reflecting her commitment to her heritage and her beliefs. Schumer didn’t shy away from addressing the cost of her stance, acknowledging the loss of many friends in recent weeks. However, she emphasizes feeling “powerful and free,” deriving strength from standing up for what she believes to be the truth. Her post sheds light on the ongoing conflict between Israel and Hamas, bringing attention to the grim realities, including the Israeli hostages still in captivity. The comedian’s bold position has not been without controversy, as she faces severe criticism from her fellow leftists. Schumer’s adamant support for Israel’s right to defend itself against Hamas’ aggression has made her a target of vicious attacks. A senior advisor to a Los Angeles City Councilman recently resigned after making Holocaust-themed jokes about Schumer, highlighting the intense polarization and animosity stemming from her stance. Schumer’s critique extends beyond social circles; she has boldly challenged major news outlets, accusing them of spreading Hamas propaganda. She demanded accountability and the resignation of senior editors at the New York Times and CNN, showcasing her readiness to hold powerful entities to account. In taking such a public and firm stance, Schumer sets an example of resilience and the importance of standing up for one’s beliefs, even in the face of personal loss and public scrutiny. Her story underscores the complexities and personal toll of the Israel-Hamas conflict, illustrating how these global issues ripple through individual lives, influencing relationships, and shaping public discourse. Amy Schumer’s narrative serves as a powerful reminder that voicing support for what one believes to be just and true may come at a significant personal cost, but it also brings a sense of empowerment and freedom that is irreplaceable.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Comedian Jim Gaffigan Stands with Jewish Community Amid Rising Anti-Semitism</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/31/Jim-Gaffigan-Anti-Semitism/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Comedian Jim Gaffigan Stands with Jewish Community Amid Rising Anti-Semitism" /><published>2023-10-31T09:32:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-31T09:32:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/31/Jim-Gaffigan-Anti-Semitism</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/31/Jim-Gaffigan-Anti-Semitism/">&lt;p&gt;Renowned comedian Jim Gaffigan has recently voiced his concern and support for the Jewish community, addressing the alarming surge in anti-Semitic incidents occurring in major cities and college campuses. With a reputation for his candid and thoughtful commentary, Gaffigan has made it clear that the fears and concerns of the Jewish people are not unfounded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Monday, Gaffigan, who practices Catholicism, took to social media to express his sentiments. His message was straightforward and impactful, acknowledging the long-standing stereotype of paranoia within the Jewish community, often perpetuated by comedians themselves. Gaffigan’s recognition of the severity of the current situation marks a significant moment, challenging existing stereotypes and urging for a reevaluation of the narratives we create and propagate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In recent weeks, cities governed by Democratic leadership and various college campuses, including prestigious Ivy League institutions, have witnessed a noticeable uptick in anti-Semitic incidents. This includes public demonstrations expressing support for Hamas, a Palestinian organization designated as a terrorist group by multiple countries, including the United States. The blatant hatred directed at Jewish people during these events has been disturbing, prompting major donors to retract their financial support from affected institutions, such as the University of Pennsylvania.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gaffigan’s voice joins a chorus of individuals from various political and entertainment spheres who are speaking out against this wave of anti-Semitism. Interestingly, Gaffigan, a self-identified member of the left-wing community, is calling attention to the issue within his own political alignment, echoing sentiments previously expressed by comedian Amy Schumer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Schumer, who is Jewish, has been vocal in her support for Israel and her condemnation of Hamas, as well as the left’s apparent growing support for the organization. She has also criticized major news outlets, including the New York Times and CNN, demanding accountability and the resignation of senior editors involved in spreading what she identifies as Hamas propaganda.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As anti-Semitic incidents continue to rise, the need for voices like Gaffigan’s becomes increasingly crucial. His decision to speak out not only provides support to the Jewish community but also encourages others to reflect on their own biases and the narratives they contribute to. In doing so, Gaffigan exemplifies the role that individuals, particularly those with public platforms, can play in challenging harmful stereotypes and advocating for change.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Renowned comedian Jim Gaffigan has recently voiced his concern and support for the Jewish community, addressing the alarming surge in anti-Semitic incidents occurring in major cities and college campuses. With a reputation for his candid and thoughtful commentary, Gaffigan has made it clear that the fears and concerns of the Jewish people are not unfounded. On Monday, Gaffigan, who practices Catholicism, took to social media to express his sentiments. His message was straightforward and impactful, acknowledging the long-standing stereotype of paranoia within the Jewish community, often perpetuated by comedians themselves. Gaffigan’s recognition of the severity of the current situation marks a significant moment, challenging existing stereotypes and urging for a reevaluation of the narratives we create and propagate. In recent weeks, cities governed by Democratic leadership and various college campuses, including prestigious Ivy League institutions, have witnessed a noticeable uptick in anti-Semitic incidents. This includes public demonstrations expressing support for Hamas, a Palestinian organization designated as a terrorist group by multiple countries, including the United States. The blatant hatred directed at Jewish people during these events has been disturbing, prompting major donors to retract their financial support from affected institutions, such as the University of Pennsylvania. Gaffigan’s voice joins a chorus of individuals from various political and entertainment spheres who are speaking out against this wave of anti-Semitism. Interestingly, Gaffigan, a self-identified member of the left-wing community, is calling attention to the issue within his own political alignment, echoing sentiments previously expressed by comedian Amy Schumer. Schumer, who is Jewish, has been vocal in her support for Israel and her condemnation of Hamas, as well as the left’s apparent growing support for the organization. She has also criticized major news outlets, including the New York Times and CNN, demanding accountability and the resignation of senior editors involved in spreading what she identifies as Hamas propaganda. As anti-Semitic incidents continue to rise, the need for voices like Gaffigan’s becomes increasingly crucial. His decision to speak out not only provides support to the Jewish community but also encourages others to reflect on their own biases and the narratives they contribute to. In doing so, Gaffigan exemplifies the role that individuals, particularly those with public platforms, can play in challenging harmful stereotypes and advocating for change.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Unspoken Truth About Vice President Kamala Harris</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/31/Kamala-Harris-Disaster/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Unspoken Truth About Vice President Kamala Harris" /><published>2023-10-31T08:23:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-31T08:23:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/31/Kamala-Harris-Disaster</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/31/Kamala-Harris-Disaster/">&lt;p&gt;Whispers of discontent within the Democratic Party are starting to become audible as party members begin to voice their concerns about Vice President Kamala Harris. For a long time, the criticism surrounding Harris’s capabilities and performance has been a topic of discussion on conservative platforms, but it appears the skepticism is now making its way into Democratic circles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vice President Harris has been in the political spotlight since her nomination, with expectations sky-high due to her historical position as the first female Vice President and the highest-ranking female official in U.S. history. However, her time in office has been anything but smooth, with numerous instances of questionable competence and lack of leadership. Her handling of the border crisis and inability to provide clear answers in interviews have left both the public and her colleagues doubting her readiness for such a high-stakes role.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The “60 Minutes” interview served as a catalyst, bringing to light the growing unease among Democrat donors and party members about Harris’s potential to lead the nation if the need arises. The Vice President’s performance during the interview, marked by her signature laughter at inappropriate times and inability to address the questions head-on, did little to assuage the concerns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her track record speaks volumes, polling at less than 1% in the Democratic primary, yet she was chosen as Biden’s running mate. Critics argue this decision was based more on checking diversity boxes than on her actual merit or capabilities, a move that may have seemed beneficial at the time but is now coming back to haunt the Democratic Party.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The possibility of California Governor Gavin Newsom stepping up as a 2024 contender adds another layer of complexity to the situation. While some may see him as a fresh alternative, his leadership in California has been far from exemplary, with the state facing a multitude of issues, from homelessness to mismanagement of resources. The American people are wary of importing California’s failed policies to the rest of the country, and Newsom’s association with these failures makes him a less-than-ideal candidate for the Democrats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the 2024 elections draw nearer, the Democratic Party finds itself at a crossroads. Acknowledging the elephant in the room – Vice President Harris’s inadequacies – is a step in the right direction, but it also raises the question: who is the right person to lead the Democrats and potentially the country? The conservatives have been saying it all along, and now, it seems, the Democrats are starting to listen.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Whispers of discontent within the Democratic Party are starting to become audible as party members begin to voice their concerns about Vice President Kamala Harris. For a long time, the criticism surrounding Harris’s capabilities and performance has been a topic of discussion on conservative platforms, but it appears the skepticism is now making its way into Democratic circles. Vice President Harris has been in the political spotlight since her nomination, with expectations sky-high due to her historical position as the first female Vice President and the highest-ranking female official in U.S. history. However, her time in office has been anything but smooth, with numerous instances of questionable competence and lack of leadership. Her handling of the border crisis and inability to provide clear answers in interviews have left both the public and her colleagues doubting her readiness for such a high-stakes role. The “60 Minutes” interview served as a catalyst, bringing to light the growing unease among Democrat donors and party members about Harris’s potential to lead the nation if the need arises. The Vice President’s performance during the interview, marked by her signature laughter at inappropriate times and inability to address the questions head-on, did little to assuage the concerns. Her track record speaks volumes, polling at less than 1% in the Democratic primary, yet she was chosen as Biden’s running mate. Critics argue this decision was based more on checking diversity boxes than on her actual merit or capabilities, a move that may have seemed beneficial at the time but is now coming back to haunt the Democratic Party. The possibility of California Governor Gavin Newsom stepping up as a 2024 contender adds another layer of complexity to the situation. While some may see him as a fresh alternative, his leadership in California has been far from exemplary, with the state facing a multitude of issues, from homelessness to mismanagement of resources. The American people are wary of importing California’s failed policies to the rest of the country, and Newsom’s association with these failures makes him a less-than-ideal candidate for the Democrats. As the 2024 elections draw nearer, the Democratic Party finds itself at a crossroads. Acknowledging the elephant in the room – Vice President Harris’s inadequacies – is a step in the right direction, but it also raises the question: who is the right person to lead the Democrats and potentially the country? The conservatives have been saying it all along, and now, it seems, the Democrats are starting to listen.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Chicago’s Unmanageable Migrant Influx: A Crisis in the Making</title><link href="/news/2023/10/31/Chicago-Migrant-Crisis/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Chicago’s Unmanageable Migrant Influx: A Crisis in the Making" /><published>2023-10-31T07:12:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-31T07:12:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/31/Chicago-Migrant-Crisis</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/31/Chicago-Migrant-Crisis/">&lt;p&gt;The city of Chicago is at a crossroads, struggling to cope with the overwhelming number of migrants flooding into the city, all while facing the imminent threat of a harsh winter. Mayor Brandon Johnson’s office has been scrambling to provide “warming buses” and winter clothes, but the question on many Chicagoans’ minds is: how did we get here?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since August 2022, Chicago has welcomed more than 19,000 migrants, a number that has stretched the city’s resources thin. Shelters are at capacity, and many migrants are left to face the winter in tents that offer little protection against the freezing temperatures. The city’s residents are feeling the strain, with over 68,000 Chicagoans already experiencing homelessness, according to a recent study.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Critics argue that this crisis is a direct result of encouraging open borders and lax immigration policies. The message being sent is clear: come to Chicago, and we will take you in, regardless of the impact on our city’s infrastructure and the well-being of our existing residents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mayor Johnson’s administration has proudly touted their efforts to assist migrants, but the reality is that the city is ill-equipped to handle the influx. This is not a sustainable solution, and it puts both migrants and Chicagoans at risk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reports from FOX 32 highlight the plight of migrants currently living in tents, and Major Kendall Matthew of the Salvation Army acknowledges the challenges ahead, stating, “We know the weather is getting ready to get cold… But we’ll be here to help them as well.” But the question remains, is help enough?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The city continues to receive migrants from Texas, New York, and Denver, further exacerbating the problem. Local residents are left wondering when enough is enough, and when their voices will be heard. Community meetings have turned ugly, as residents protest the establishment of migrant camps in their neighborhoods, feeling blindsided and ignored by their elected officials.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chicago’s migrant crisis is a stark reminder of the consequences of encouraging open borders without proper planning and resources. It is a wake-up call for cities across the nation, showcasing the dire need for immigration reform and responsible governance. As winter approaches, the eyes of the nation are on Chicago, watching as the city grapples with the human cost of its open-door policies.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">The city of Chicago is at a crossroads, struggling to cope with the overwhelming number of migrants flooding into the city, all while facing the imminent threat of a harsh winter. Mayor Brandon Johnson’s office has been scrambling to provide “warming buses” and winter clothes, but the question on many Chicagoans’ minds is: how did we get here? Since August 2022, Chicago has welcomed more than 19,000 migrants, a number that has stretched the city’s resources thin. Shelters are at capacity, and many migrants are left to face the winter in tents that offer little protection against the freezing temperatures. The city’s residents are feeling the strain, with over 68,000 Chicagoans already experiencing homelessness, according to a recent study. Critics argue that this crisis is a direct result of encouraging open borders and lax immigration policies. The message being sent is clear: come to Chicago, and we will take you in, regardless of the impact on our city’s infrastructure and the well-being of our existing residents. Mayor Johnson’s administration has proudly touted their efforts to assist migrants, but the reality is that the city is ill-equipped to handle the influx. This is not a sustainable solution, and it puts both migrants and Chicagoans at risk. Reports from FOX 32 highlight the plight of migrants currently living in tents, and Major Kendall Matthew of the Salvation Army acknowledges the challenges ahead, stating, “We know the weather is getting ready to get cold… But we’ll be here to help them as well.” But the question remains, is help enough? The city continues to receive migrants from Texas, New York, and Denver, further exacerbating the problem. Local residents are left wondering when enough is enough, and when their voices will be heard. Community meetings have turned ugly, as residents protest the establishment of migrant camps in their neighborhoods, feeling blindsided and ignored by their elected officials. Chicago’s migrant crisis is a stark reminder of the consequences of encouraging open borders without proper planning and resources. It is a wake-up call for cities across the nation, showcasing the dire need for immigration reform and responsible governance. As winter approaches, the eyes of the nation are on Chicago, watching as the city grapples with the human cost of its open-door policies.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">George Soros-Backed DA Pamela Price Faces Irony of Crime in Oakland</title><link href="/news/2023/10/31/George-Soros-Backed-DA/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="George Soros-Backed DA Pamela Price Faces Irony of Crime in Oakland" /><published>2023-10-31T06:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-31T06:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/31/George-Soros-Backed-DA</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/31/George-Soros-Backed-DA/">&lt;p&gt;In a cruel twist of irony, Alameda County District Attorney Pamela Price, a beneficiary of George Soros’s deep pockets, recently found herself at the mercy of the very crime wave she is accused of enabling. Last Friday, in broad daylight and the heart of crime-ridden Oakland, Price’s work laptop was stolen right out of her vehicle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The incident occurred near a family justice center, a supposed safe space, revealing the extent of lawlessness that has gripped Oakland. Price’s bodyguard, despite driving a $90,000 county Tahoe SUV, could do nothing but watch as the thieves made off with vital equipment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This disturbing event raises critical questions about Price’s capability and willingness to tackle the rampant crime in Oakland, the largest city in her jurisdiction. Since her election in 2022, backed by none other than leftist billionaire George Soros, crime in Oakland has skyrocketed. Her soft-on-crime policies, a hallmark of Soros-backed district attorneys, have created an environment where criminals operate with impunity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oakland’s descent into chaos can be traced back to the city’s embrace of the “Defund the Police” movement. Former Mayor Libby Schaaf led the charge, advocating for not just defunding, but replacing the police. The city even went as far as to abolish its school police department. These radical moves have left residents and law enforcement demoralized and defenseless.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Price’s response to this lawlessness? In a stunning display of disconnect, she claimed to feel safe living in East Oakland, a statement that flies in the face of the experiences of countless residents and victims of crime. These residents, once hopeful, are now disillusioned, living in fear in what they describe as a failed progressive utopia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even law enforcement is feeling the pressure, with police encouraging residents to use air horns to deter thieves. Meanwhile, Price’s response to the crime spree, her stolen laptop, and the recall filed against her in August remains to be seen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the end, the theft of Price’s laptop is not just a personal loss; it is a symbolic representation of the failed policies and lack of leadership that have left Oakland in disarray. It serves as a stark reminder to conservatives everywhere of the dangers of Soros-backed officials and the high price of progressive, soft-on-crime policies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This incident should serve as a wake-up call for voters in Oakland and across the country. The need for strong, law-and-order leadership has never been more apparent, and the time for accountability is now.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a cruel twist of irony, Alameda County District Attorney Pamela Price, a beneficiary of George Soros’s deep pockets, recently found herself at the mercy of the very crime wave she is accused of enabling. Last Friday, in broad daylight and the heart of crime-ridden Oakland, Price’s work laptop was stolen right out of her vehicle. The incident occurred near a family justice center, a supposed safe space, revealing the extent of lawlessness that has gripped Oakland. Price’s bodyguard, despite driving a $90,000 county Tahoe SUV, could do nothing but watch as the thieves made off with vital equipment. This disturbing event raises critical questions about Price’s capability and willingness to tackle the rampant crime in Oakland, the largest city in her jurisdiction. Since her election in 2022, backed by none other than leftist billionaire George Soros, crime in Oakland has skyrocketed. Her soft-on-crime policies, a hallmark of Soros-backed district attorneys, have created an environment where criminals operate with impunity. Oakland’s descent into chaos can be traced back to the city’s embrace of the “Defund the Police” movement. Former Mayor Libby Schaaf led the charge, advocating for not just defunding, but replacing the police. The city even went as far as to abolish its school police department. These radical moves have left residents and law enforcement demoralized and defenseless. Price’s response to this lawlessness? In a stunning display of disconnect, she claimed to feel safe living in East Oakland, a statement that flies in the face of the experiences of countless residents and victims of crime. These residents, once hopeful, are now disillusioned, living in fear in what they describe as a failed progressive utopia. Even law enforcement is feeling the pressure, with police encouraging residents to use air horns to deter thieves. Meanwhile, Price’s response to the crime spree, her stolen laptop, and the recall filed against her in August remains to be seen. In the end, the theft of Price’s laptop is not just a personal loss; it is a symbolic representation of the failed policies and lack of leadership that have left Oakland in disarray. It serves as a stark reminder to conservatives everywhere of the dangers of Soros-backed officials and the high price of progressive, soft-on-crime policies. This incident should serve as a wake-up call for voters in Oakland and across the country. The need for strong, law-and-order leadership has never been more apparent, and the time for accountability is now.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Los Angeles Model Found Dead and Bound in Her Refrigerator</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/30/LA-Model-Found-Dead/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Los Angeles Model Found Dead and Bound in Her Refrigerator" /><published>2023-10-30T19:52:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-30T19:52:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/30/LA-Model-Found-Dead</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/30/LA-Model-Found-Dead/">&lt;p&gt;A 31-year-old freelance model and real estate agent, Maleesa Mooney, was found dead inside her refrigerator last month. Her wrists and ankles were bound, and her body bore the brutal marks of a violent altercation. This gruesome discovery has sent shockwaves through the community, as authorities and loved ones alike scramble for answers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maleesa Mooney, a shining star with a promising career in both modeling and real estate, was last seen alive on surveillance footage in her apartment complex on September 6. Six days later, her lifeless body was discovered by the police, responding to a welfare check requested by her distraught family. They had been unable to reach Mooney for over 24 hours, sparking concerns for her safety.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When the police and building management accessed her residence at the Bunker Hill Towers Apartments, they were met with a horrifying scene. Mooney’s body was wedged inside her refrigerator, severely beaten, and with a gag made of clothing stuffed in her mouth. Electrical cords and clothing bound her extremities. Blood was found outside the refrigerator, and the apartment bore signs of a violent struggle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The autopsy report, released last Friday, confirmed the brutal nature of Mooney’s demise. She had suffered from blunt force trauma, evidenced by abrasions, lacerations, contusions, and a fractured rib. While none of the injuries were acutely life-threatening on their own, the examiner noted that they indicated a violent physical altercation prior to her death. Suffocation may have played a role, and traces of cocaine were found in her system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the intensive ongoing investigation by the Los Angeles Police Department, the man seen entering Mooney’s apartment remains unidentified, and no arrests have been made. The authorities have not publicly named any suspects, leaving the community and Mooney’s family in a state of anguish and uncertainty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maleesa Mooney is remembered by her sister, Jourdin Pauline, as “the most amazing girl ever,” a sentiment echoed by all who knew her. Mooney, who was in the process of closing deals on million-dollar homes, is described as kind-hearted, intelligent, and genuinely caring. Her tragic and untimely death has left a void in the hearts of her family, friends, and the community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In these trying times, the call for justice grows louder. Mooney’s family and friends have taken to social media, using the hashtag #JUSTICEFORMALEESA, to demand answers and action. The community stands united in their grief, urging anyone with information to come forward and assist in solving this heinous crime.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the wake of this tragedy, it is vital to remember Maleesa Mooney for the vibrant life she lived, and ensure that every effort is made to bring her killer to justice. The authorities must relentlessly pursue the truth, ensuring that justice is served and that Mooney’s family can find some semblance of peace.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">A 31-year-old freelance model and real estate agent, Maleesa Mooney, was found dead inside her refrigerator last month. Her wrists and ankles were bound, and her body bore the brutal marks of a violent altercation. This gruesome discovery has sent shockwaves through the community, as authorities and loved ones alike scramble for answers. Maleesa Mooney, a shining star with a promising career in both modeling and real estate, was last seen alive on surveillance footage in her apartment complex on September 6. Six days later, her lifeless body was discovered by the police, responding to a welfare check requested by her distraught family. They had been unable to reach Mooney for over 24 hours, sparking concerns for her safety. When the police and building management accessed her residence at the Bunker Hill Towers Apartments, they were met with a horrifying scene. Mooney’s body was wedged inside her refrigerator, severely beaten, and with a gag made of clothing stuffed in her mouth. Electrical cords and clothing bound her extremities. Blood was found outside the refrigerator, and the apartment bore signs of a violent struggle. The autopsy report, released last Friday, confirmed the brutal nature of Mooney’s demise. She had suffered from blunt force trauma, evidenced by abrasions, lacerations, contusions, and a fractured rib. While none of the injuries were acutely life-threatening on their own, the examiner noted that they indicated a violent physical altercation prior to her death. Suffocation may have played a role, and traces of cocaine were found in her system. Despite the intensive ongoing investigation by the Los Angeles Police Department, the man seen entering Mooney’s apartment remains unidentified, and no arrests have been made. The authorities have not publicly named any suspects, leaving the community and Mooney’s family in a state of anguish and uncertainty. Maleesa Mooney is remembered by her sister, Jourdin Pauline, as “the most amazing girl ever,” a sentiment echoed by all who knew her. Mooney, who was in the process of closing deals on million-dollar homes, is described as kind-hearted, intelligent, and genuinely caring. Her tragic and untimely death has left a void in the hearts of her family, friends, and the community. In these trying times, the call for justice grows louder. Mooney’s family and friends have taken to social media, using the hashtag #JUSTICEFORMALEESA, to demand answers and action. The community stands united in their grief, urging anyone with information to come forward and assist in solving this heinous crime. In the wake of this tragedy, it is vital to remember Maleesa Mooney for the vibrant life she lived, and ensure that every effort is made to bring her killer to justice. The authorities must relentlessly pursue the truth, ensuring that justice is served and that Mooney’s family can find some semblance of peace.</summary></entry></feed>