<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-10-12T19:15:52-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/12/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-12T19:15:52-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-12T19:15:52-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/12/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/12/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/12/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-12T19:15:52-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-12T19:15:52-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/12/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/12/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/">&lt;p&gt;Recent surprise attacks by Hamas on Israel has fueled ongoing tensions between staunchly conservative commentators and the progressive “Squad” Democrats known for criticizing Israel. The intensity of the backlash highlights the deep political divide over foreign policy in the Middle East.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Hamas’ shocking attack, several members of the “Squad,” including Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.), called for a “ceasefire and de-escalation,” condemning the violence. The absence of a statement from Rep. Rashida Tlaib (D-Mich.) was notably called out by conservative media outlets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;South Carolina GOP Rep. Nancy Mace quickly labeled Ocasio-Cortez a “Hamas apologist” in response to her call for peace and de-escalation. Rep. Ilhan Omar (D-Minn.), no stranger to controversy surrounding her views on Israel, echoed the call for de-escalation and ceasefire. Omar’s prior statements comparing the US and Israel to terrorist groups like Hamas and the Taliban resurfaced in the debate, fueling more criticisms. Omar’s 2019 tweet, where she opined that “Israel has hypnotized the world,” also continues to haunt her political career, often cited by critics to challenge her stance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conservative commentators have been especially vocal. “FOX &amp;amp; Friends Weekend” co-host Rachel Campos-Duffy took aim at Omar, saying she fails to recognize the peace in the Middle East under Trump’s administration. Conservative pundit John Hasson also called out Omar, claiming she insinuated that attacks on IDF forces were acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Massachusetts Democrat Rep. Ayanna Pressley’s concerns over the “devastating attacks on Israelis” were met with skepticism. A prominent conservative online personality, Comfortably Smug, accused the “Squad” of advising Israel to back down after the nation suffered massive attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Jamaal Bowman’s call for an end to the Gaza blockade, in addition to condemning the Hamas attacks, was met with criticism from conservative radio host Jason Rantz. He accused Bowman of pairing his condemnation of terrorism with unwarranted criticisms of Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Cori Bush emphasized the urgent need for a ceasefire, while pushing for an end to “U.S. support for Israeli military occupation and apartheid.” Defense attorney Marina Medvin criticized Bush, suggesting that she equates the death of Palestinian terrorists to the horrific acts committed against Jewish civilians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amidst the political turmoil and intense debate, the attacks have taken a heavy toll. Israeli media report over 300 dead due to the wide-ranging assault. Gaza health officials note that at least 200 Palestinians have perished in the retaliatory Israeli air strikes following the initial Hamas attack. As the situation remains volatile, both sides continue to count their casualties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This divisive issue showcases the challenge America faces in crafting a unified approach to foreign policy, with deeply entrenched political divides at play. As the situation develops, the debate is bound to intensify, shedding light on the complexities of U.S. politics in the global arena.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Disney’s ‘Loki’ in Hot Water: AI Allegedly Used for Promotional Poster</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/12/Disney-Loki-AI-Controversy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Disney’s ‘Loki’ in Hot Water: AI Allegedly Used for Promotional Poster" /><published>2023-10-12T17:37:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-12T17:37:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/12/Disney-Loki-AI-Controversy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/12/Disney-Loki-AI-Controversy/">&lt;p&gt;In a controversial revelation, Disney’s hit television series “Loki” has been put in the spotlight for its alleged use of artificial intelligence (AI) in crafting its season 2 promotional poster. The incident has led to a wider discussion about AI’s growing role in the entertainment and design industry, raising both eyebrows and concerns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to a report by The Verge, the recent promotional poster for “Loki” seems to have ties to an image from Shutterstock, a renowned stock photography company. Such a connection becomes problematic when considering Disney Plus’s stringent licensing agreement, which highlights regulations against AI-generated content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Illustrator Katria Raden was one of the first professionals to express her disappointment in the company. She shared her concerns on X (previously known as Twitter), pointing out the AI-generated characteristics evident in the “Loki” poster. Amid various opinions on the matter, Raden emphasized the unnatural aspects of the poster, noting the bizarre transformations akin to “meaningless squiggles” often seen in AI-created imagery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The heart of the controversy stems from the observation that the “Loki” poster’s background seemingly resembles a Shutterstock stock image titled “Surreal Infinity Time Spiral Space Antique.” Notably, AI image checkers have identified this stock image as AI-generated. Shutterstock’s own guidelines are strict against licensing AI-generated content unless it is produced by their proprietary AI-image generator. This internal tool ensures Shutterstock maintains intellectual property rights over the content on their platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this digital age, it’s imperative for artists and creators to be assured of the authenticity and uniqueness of their creations. With tools like AI, the lines between creativity and technology blur. As Katria Raden pointed out, countless artists rely on stock sites to earn a livelihood. She believes that using AI-generated imagery, a byproduct of tech built on “mass exploitation and wage theft,” is no different from sidelining Disney’s own dedicated employees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Disney’s relationship with AI seems to be a recurring topic. Earlier this year, the entertainment giant faced criticism for reportedly employing AI in the opening credits for another Disney+ Marvel series, “Secret Invasion.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As AI continues to advance, industries across the board will need to determine its ethical and appropriate use. The “Loki” controversy underscores the vital conversation about AI’s place in artistic expression and the potential challenges it poses to creative professions.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">In a controversial revelation, Disney’s hit television series “Loki” has been put in the spotlight for its alleged use of artificial intelligence (AI) in crafting its season 2 promotional poster. The incident has led to a wider discussion about AI’s growing role in the entertainment and design industry, raising both eyebrows and concerns. According to a report by The Verge, the recent promotional poster for “Loki” seems to have ties to an image from Shutterstock, a renowned stock photography company. Such a connection becomes problematic when considering Disney Plus’s stringent licensing agreement, which highlights regulations against AI-generated content. Illustrator Katria Raden was one of the first professionals to express her disappointment in the company. She shared her concerns on X (previously known as Twitter), pointing out the AI-generated characteristics evident in the “Loki” poster. Amid various opinions on the matter, Raden emphasized the unnatural aspects of the poster, noting the bizarre transformations akin to “meaningless squiggles” often seen in AI-created imagery. The heart of the controversy stems from the observation that the “Loki” poster’s background seemingly resembles a Shutterstock stock image titled “Surreal Infinity Time Spiral Space Antique.” Notably, AI image checkers have identified this stock image as AI-generated. Shutterstock’s own guidelines are strict against licensing AI-generated content unless it is produced by their proprietary AI-image generator. This internal tool ensures Shutterstock maintains intellectual property rights over the content on their platform. In this digital age, it’s imperative for artists and creators to be assured of the authenticity and uniqueness of their creations. With tools like AI, the lines between creativity and technology blur. As Katria Raden pointed out, countless artists rely on stock sites to earn a livelihood. She believes that using AI-generated imagery, a byproduct of tech built on “mass exploitation and wage theft,” is no different from sidelining Disney’s own dedicated employees. Disney’s relationship with AI seems to be a recurring topic. Earlier this year, the entertainment giant faced criticism for reportedly employing AI in the opening credits for another Disney+ Marvel series, “Secret Invasion.” As AI continues to advance, industries across the board will need to determine its ethical and appropriate use. The “Loki” controversy underscores the vital conversation about AI’s place in artistic expression and the potential challenges it poses to creative professions.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">BWI Airport Faces Bomb Scare: Fast Response Ensures Public Safety</title><link href="/news/2023/10/12/BWI-Airport-Bomb-Threat/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="BWI Airport Faces Bomb Scare: Fast Response Ensures Public Safety" /><published>2023-10-12T16:18:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-12T16:18:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/12/BWI-Airport-Bomb-Threat</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/12/BWI-Airport-Bomb-Threat/">&lt;p&gt;In a nerve-wracking series of events on Wednesday afternoon, officials at Baltimore/Washington International (BWI) Thurgood Marshall Airport went on high alert due to a potential bomb threat. Quick action and a coordinated response ensured that the situation was deftly handled, with the suspect swiftly taken into custody.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At approximately 3:10 p.m., BWI officials announced via social media that they had closed Terminal Roadway for a pressing law enforcement investigation. As a result, all vehicular traffic inching towards the airport was halted. Additionally, individuals present in the lower level terminal were instructed to stay put for their safety.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This rapid response was spurred by a distressing report. According to FOX 5 in Washington, D.C., a man made a chilling declaration to law enforcement: he claimed to have explosives stashed in his vehicle, which he had parked at the airport. Such alarming statements demand immediate and robust reactions, and that’s exactly what ensued.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In just a little over an hour after the initial announcement, by 4:30 p.m., the Maryland Transportation Authority Police provided a much-needed update. They confirmed that the upper level of the airport terminal road was safe and reopened for traffic. More importantly, they assured the public that there was no prevailing threat to their safety.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Maryland Transportation Authority Police have since confirmed that they have the individual, who sparked the entire incident, under arrest. They said, “Based on statements made by the individual, officers took precautionary measures.” Ensuring public safety remains a top priority, and the authority’s prompt actions certainly reflect their commitment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Transportation Security Administration (TSA), when probed for deeper insights, directed inquiries to the Maryland Transportation Authority Police, underlining the latter’s role as the primary law enforcement agency overseeing this case.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The situation at BWI serves as a stark reminder of the constant vigilance required in today’s age. Threats, be they genuine or mere claims, can’t be taken lightly. While the reasons behind the individual’s actions remain unclear, what stands out is the efficient and effective response of the law enforcement agencies involved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As investigations continue into the precise nature of the threat and the motivations behind it, one thing is clear: the quick-thinking and decisive actions of the Maryland Transportation Authority Police played a crucial role in averting a potential crisis.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a nerve-wracking series of events on Wednesday afternoon, officials at Baltimore/Washington International (BWI) Thurgood Marshall Airport went on high alert due to a potential bomb threat. Quick action and a coordinated response ensured that the situation was deftly handled, with the suspect swiftly taken into custody. At approximately 3:10 p.m., BWI officials announced via social media that they had closed Terminal Roadway for a pressing law enforcement investigation. As a result, all vehicular traffic inching towards the airport was halted. Additionally, individuals present in the lower level terminal were instructed to stay put for their safety. This rapid response was spurred by a distressing report. According to FOX 5 in Washington, D.C., a man made a chilling declaration to law enforcement: he claimed to have explosives stashed in his vehicle, which he had parked at the airport. Such alarming statements demand immediate and robust reactions, and that’s exactly what ensued. In just a little over an hour after the initial announcement, by 4:30 p.m., the Maryland Transportation Authority Police provided a much-needed update. They confirmed that the upper level of the airport terminal road was safe and reopened for traffic. More importantly, they assured the public that there was no prevailing threat to their safety. The Maryland Transportation Authority Police have since confirmed that they have the individual, who sparked the entire incident, under arrest. They said, “Based on statements made by the individual, officers took precautionary measures.” Ensuring public safety remains a top priority, and the authority’s prompt actions certainly reflect their commitment. The Transportation Security Administration (TSA), when probed for deeper insights, directed inquiries to the Maryland Transportation Authority Police, underlining the latter’s role as the primary law enforcement agency overseeing this case. The situation at BWI serves as a stark reminder of the constant vigilance required in today’s age. Threats, be they genuine or mere claims, can’t be taken lightly. While the reasons behind the individual’s actions remain unclear, what stands out is the efficient and effective response of the law enforcement agencies involved. As investigations continue into the precise nature of the threat and the motivations behind it, one thing is clear: the quick-thinking and decisive actions of the Maryland Transportation Authority Police played a crucial role in averting a potential crisis.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Biden’s Controversial Palestine Funding: Flirting with Anti-Terrorism Laws?</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/12/Biden-Palestine-Funding-Critique/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Biden’s Controversial Palestine Funding: Flirting with Anti-Terrorism Laws?" /><published>2023-10-12T15:08:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-12T15:08:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/12/Biden-Palestine-Funding-Critique</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/12/Biden-Palestine-Funding-Critique/">&lt;p&gt;In what many critics describe as a questionable move, President Joe Biden’s decision to resume hefty financial support to Palestinian entities is now under judicial scrutiny. U.S. District Court Judge Matthew J. Kacsmaryk has stepped in to grant a much-needed review, prompted by concerns that Biden’s generosity may be in stark violation of established anti-terrorism laws.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This legal review comes on the heels of a lawsuit initiated by Rep. Ronny Jackson, R-Texas, and the America First Legal Foundation (AFL). Their shared contention is that the Biden administration may be carelessly allowing Economic Support Funds, meant for humanitarian purposes, to be misused. Such funds, instead of uplifting the Palestinian people, could be financing terrorist activities in the West Bank and Gaza.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Biden’s decision to rekindle financial relations with the Palestinian National Authority stands in sharp contrast to the more cautious approach of his predecessor. Former President Donald Trump had prudently halted any payments, heeding the Taylor Force Act of 2018, which clearly restricts U.S. financial assistance to Palestine while it continues supporting imprisoned terrorists and their dependents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the heart of the issue is a staggering sum of approximately $500 million greenlit by Biden, representing a lion’s share of the total U.S. aid to Palestine. And as if to add fuel to the fire, an additional $700 million was routed to a UN agency in the region — an agency Trump had wisely exited.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The gravity of this decision becomes even more palpable against the backdrop of the recent devastating terrorist attacks on Israel, attributed to Hamas and Hezbollah. Both groups, as The Wall Street Journal points out, are under the financial and operational umbrella of Iran.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The human toll of these conflicts is alarming: Israel mourns the loss of over 1,200 souls, with another 3,400 nursing injuries and more than 200 held hostage. Palestinian sources too paint a grim picture with over 1,100 dead, 5,400 wounded, and a startling 263,000 individuals displaced, according to the United Nations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Washington Free Beacon has also unearthed unsettling findings. Despite being armed with internal reports suggesting that such funding might embolden Hamas, the Biden administration moved forward, seemingly undeterred.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the judicial review progresses, many hope it brings clarity to the situation. However, Biden’s decision to potentially put U.S. funds in the hands of extremist groups, directly or indirectly, is a matter that will undoubtedly cast a long shadow over his presidency.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In what many critics describe as a questionable move, President Joe Biden’s decision to resume hefty financial support to Palestinian entities is now under judicial scrutiny. U.S. District Court Judge Matthew J. Kacsmaryk has stepped in to grant a much-needed review, prompted by concerns that Biden’s generosity may be in stark violation of established anti-terrorism laws. This legal review comes on the heels of a lawsuit initiated by Rep. Ronny Jackson, R-Texas, and the America First Legal Foundation (AFL). Their shared contention is that the Biden administration may be carelessly allowing Economic Support Funds, meant for humanitarian purposes, to be misused. Such funds, instead of uplifting the Palestinian people, could be financing terrorist activities in the West Bank and Gaza. Biden’s decision to rekindle financial relations with the Palestinian National Authority stands in sharp contrast to the more cautious approach of his predecessor. Former President Donald Trump had prudently halted any payments, heeding the Taylor Force Act of 2018, which clearly restricts U.S. financial assistance to Palestine while it continues supporting imprisoned terrorists and their dependents. At the heart of the issue is a staggering sum of approximately $500 million greenlit by Biden, representing a lion’s share of the total U.S. aid to Palestine. And as if to add fuel to the fire, an additional $700 million was routed to a UN agency in the region — an agency Trump had wisely exited. The gravity of this decision becomes even more palpable against the backdrop of the recent devastating terrorist attacks on Israel, attributed to Hamas and Hezbollah. Both groups, as The Wall Street Journal points out, are under the financial and operational umbrella of Iran. The human toll of these conflicts is alarming: Israel mourns the loss of over 1,200 souls, with another 3,400 nursing injuries and more than 200 held hostage. Palestinian sources too paint a grim picture with over 1,100 dead, 5,400 wounded, and a startling 263,000 individuals displaced, according to the United Nations. The Washington Free Beacon has also unearthed unsettling findings. Despite being armed with internal reports suggesting that such funding might embolden Hamas, the Biden administration moved forward, seemingly undeterred. As the judicial review progresses, many hope it brings clarity to the situation. However, Biden’s decision to potentially put U.S. funds in the hands of extremist groups, directly or indirectly, is a matter that will undoubtedly cast a long shadow over his presidency.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Arnold Schwarzenegger’s Bold Take on Democrats</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/12/Schwarzenegger-Democrats-Statement/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Arnold Schwarzenegger’s Bold Take on Democrats" /><published>2023-10-12T14:06:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-12T14:06:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/12/Schwarzenegger-Democrats-Statement</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/12/Schwarzenegger-Democrats-Statement/">&lt;p&gt;In an upcoming episode of the “Literally” podcast hosted by Rob Lowe, Hollywood legend and former California Governor Arnold Schwarzenegger shared some strong views on the Democratic Party. Known for his no-holds-barred commentary, the &lt;em&gt;Terminator&lt;/em&gt; star stated that Democrats aim to “&lt;em&gt;ruin every city in America&lt;/em&gt;.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the interview, when Lowe recounted Republican principles as explained by former California Republican Congressman David Dreier, Schwarzenegger pointed out that a key principle missing from the list was “Strong law enforcement.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When Lowe queried the &lt;em&gt;Predator&lt;/em&gt; star about his thoughts on what Democrats stand for, Schwarzenegger responded emphatically, saying, “&lt;em&gt;We want to f&lt;/em&gt;ck up every city in America. That seems to be the theme right now*.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The statement was a reflection of the actor’s view of Democrat-led regimes in major American cities, which are currently grappling with debt, crime, and a decline in citizens and businesses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, Schwarzenegger’s controversial statements and political stance have been a matter of debate even among Republicans. Despite being a self-proclaimed Republican, Schwarzenegger’s views often tilt towards the left. His support for issues such as pro-choice and climate change, and his strong stance on COVID-19 safety measures, have sometimes clashed with conservative ideals. In fact, in 2021, he famously told conservatives “&lt;em&gt;screw your freedom&lt;/em&gt;” when many opposed the government’s measures to combat the pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moreover, Schwarzenegger’s 2021 comparison of Trump’s administration to Adolf Hitler’s Nazi Party further drew ire from many conservatives. Yet, in a recent interview with the New York Times, the &lt;em&gt;Commando&lt;/em&gt; actor reaffirmed his allegiance to the Republican Party.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether or not you agree with Schwarzenegger’s opinions, his outspoken nature ensures that he continues to remain a significant and polarizing figure in both the entertainment and political arenas. The full episode of the “Literally with Rob Lowe” podcast featuring Arnold Schwarzenegger is set to release this Thursday.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">In an upcoming episode of the “Literally” podcast hosted by Rob Lowe, Hollywood legend and former California Governor Arnold Schwarzenegger shared some strong views on the Democratic Party. Known for his no-holds-barred commentary, the Terminator star stated that Democrats aim to “ruin every city in America.” During the interview, when Lowe recounted Republican principles as explained by former California Republican Congressman David Dreier, Schwarzenegger pointed out that a key principle missing from the list was “Strong law enforcement.” When Lowe queried the Predator star about his thoughts on what Democrats stand for, Schwarzenegger responded emphatically, saying, “We want to fck up every city in America. That seems to be the theme right now*.” The statement was a reflection of the actor’s view of Democrat-led regimes in major American cities, which are currently grappling with debt, crime, and a decline in citizens and businesses. However, Schwarzenegger’s controversial statements and political stance have been a matter of debate even among Republicans. Despite being a self-proclaimed Republican, Schwarzenegger’s views often tilt towards the left. His support for issues such as pro-choice and climate change, and his strong stance on COVID-19 safety measures, have sometimes clashed with conservative ideals. In fact, in 2021, he famously told conservatives “screw your freedom” when many opposed the government’s measures to combat the pandemic. Moreover, Schwarzenegger’s 2021 comparison of Trump’s administration to Adolf Hitler’s Nazi Party further drew ire from many conservatives. Yet, in a recent interview with the New York Times, the Commando actor reaffirmed his allegiance to the Republican Party. Whether or not you agree with Schwarzenegger’s opinions, his outspoken nature ensures that he continues to remain a significant and polarizing figure in both the entertainment and political arenas. The full episode of the “Literally with Rob Lowe” podcast featuring Arnold Schwarzenegger is set to release this Thursday.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Jada Pinkett Smith Reveals 7-Year Separation from Will Smith</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/12/Jada-Will-Separation/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Jada Pinkett Smith Reveals 7-Year Separation from Will Smith" /><published>2023-10-12T13:01:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-12T13:01:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/12/Jada-Will-Separation</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/12/Jada-Will-Separation/">&lt;p&gt;In a recent revelation, actress Jada Pinkett Smith has shared that she and Hollywood superstar Will Smith have been living separate lives since 2016, despite still making public appearances as a couple.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During an interview on the “Today” show with Hoda Kotb, Pinkett Smith made the disclosure while discussing her new book titled “Worthy.” She stated, “&lt;em&gt;We live separately&lt;/em&gt;,” emphasizing that despite the separation, the idea of divorce is off the table. “&lt;em&gt;I made a promise that there will never be a reason for us to get a divorce. We will work through whatever. And I just haven’t been able to break that promise,&lt;/em&gt;” she explained.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The separation came about in 2016 after the couple “were just exhausted with trying” to maintain their union. Both had varying expectations of each other, leading them to drift apart. Yet, despite the challenges, they chose not to publicize their separation, even amidst intense media scrutiny. This scrutiny peaked when rumors circulated about Jada’s relationship with family friend, August Alsina. The actress confirmed this relationship in 2021 on her show, “Red Table Talk,” referring to her involvement with Alsina as an “entanglement.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, the revelation also indicates that the couple was separated during Will Smith’s notorious 2022 Oscar incident, wherein he slapped comedian Chris Rock. The incident occurred after Rock made a joke referencing Jada’s alopecia condition. Recalling the event, Jada expressed her disbelief, “&lt;em&gt;I thought, ‘This is a skit. I was like, ‘There’s no way that Will hit him.’ It wasn’t until Will started to walk back to his chair that I even realized it wasn’t a skit.&lt;/em&gt;”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the complexities in their relationship, the bond between the two remains strong. “&lt;em&gt;We’ve been doing some really heavy-duty work together. We just got deep love for each other and we are going to figure out what that looks like for us,&lt;/em&gt;” Pinkett Smith said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The couple, who tied the knot in 1997, share two children: Jaden, 25, and Willow, 22. Will Smith also has a son, Trey, 30, from a previous marriage to Sheree Zampino, whom Jada lovingly refers to as her “bonus son.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This unexpected revelation from Jada Pinkett Smith offers a fresh perspective on the couple’s relationship, further illustrating the uniqueness of their bond and the strength they share in navigating through life’s challenges.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">In a recent revelation, actress Jada Pinkett Smith has shared that she and Hollywood superstar Will Smith have been living separate lives since 2016, despite still making public appearances as a couple. During an interview on the “Today” show with Hoda Kotb, Pinkett Smith made the disclosure while discussing her new book titled “Worthy.” She stated, “We live separately,” emphasizing that despite the separation, the idea of divorce is off the table. “I made a promise that there will never be a reason for us to get a divorce. We will work through whatever. And I just haven’t been able to break that promise,” she explained. The separation came about in 2016 after the couple “were just exhausted with trying” to maintain their union. Both had varying expectations of each other, leading them to drift apart. Yet, despite the challenges, they chose not to publicize their separation, even amidst intense media scrutiny. This scrutiny peaked when rumors circulated about Jada’s relationship with family friend, August Alsina. The actress confirmed this relationship in 2021 on her show, “Red Table Talk,” referring to her involvement with Alsina as an “entanglement.” Interestingly, the revelation also indicates that the couple was separated during Will Smith’s notorious 2022 Oscar incident, wherein he slapped comedian Chris Rock. The incident occurred after Rock made a joke referencing Jada’s alopecia condition. Recalling the event, Jada expressed her disbelief, “I thought, ‘This is a skit. I was like, ‘There’s no way that Will hit him.’ It wasn’t until Will started to walk back to his chair that I even realized it wasn’t a skit.” Despite the complexities in their relationship, the bond between the two remains strong. “We’ve been doing some really heavy-duty work together. We just got deep love for each other and we are going to figure out what that looks like for us,” Pinkett Smith said. The couple, who tied the knot in 1997, share two children: Jaden, 25, and Willow, 22. Will Smith also has a son, Trey, 30, from a previous marriage to Sheree Zampino, whom Jada lovingly refers to as her “bonus son.” This unexpected revelation from Jada Pinkett Smith offers a fresh perspective on the couple’s relationship, further illustrating the uniqueness of their bond and the strength they share in navigating through life’s challenges.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump Surpasses Biden by 9 Points in Pennsylvania: New Poll Reveals</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/12/Trump-Lead-Pennsylvania/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump Surpasses Biden by 9 Points in Pennsylvania: New Poll Reveals" /><published>2023-10-12T11:52:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-12T11:52:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/12/Trump-Lead-Pennsylvania</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/12/Trump-Lead-Pennsylvania/">&lt;p&gt;Pennsylvania, often considered a critical battleground state in U.S. elections, seems to be leaning towards former President Donald Trump over the incumbent, President Joe Biden. According to a recent Emerson College poll, Trump leads by a significant 9-point margin in a potential face-off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Takeaways from the Poll:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trump’s Lead:&lt;/strong&gt; 45% of the registered voters in Pennsylvania expressed support for Trump, compared to Biden’s 36%. Interestingly, this shows a shift in voter sentiment, as 43% voted for Biden and 42% for Trump in the 2020 elections.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Independent Voters:&lt;/strong&gt; Trump appears to resonate with independent voters, securing a remarkable 44% of their support, while Biden trails at 14%. The remaining voters are split between other candidates or are still making up their minds.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Biden’s Approval Rating:&lt;/strong&gt; Notably, Biden’s approval rating in the state is at a concerning low. Only 31% of Pennsylvanians have a positive view of his presidency, while a significant 51% disapprove, rendering his net approval rating at -20.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Loyalty among Supporters:&lt;/strong&gt; Half of Trump’s supporters firmly assert that nothing could deter their support for him in the 2024 presidential race. On the flip side, 53% of Biden’s supporters echo the same unwavering loyalty.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senate Race Insights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though Trump is soaring in popularity, it’s interesting to note that this surge isn’t necessarily translating to other Republicans. In a potential U.S. Senate race, the Democratic Senator Bob Casey leads over Republican Dave McCormick by eight points, standing at 41% to McCormick’s 33%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Emerson College Polling’s Executive Director, Spencer Kimball, shed light on these variances, especially concerning age demographics. Biden holds an edge over Trump among voters under 40 (44% to 39%). Yet, among those below 30, Trump gains traction, leading 45% to 39%. Senator Casey, however, retains dominance across both age brackets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Education also plays a significant role. Voters with a high school degree or less significantly favor Trump (53% to 27%). Yet, when it comes to the Senate race, Casey just slightly outpaces McCormick among the same group.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the 2024 elections approaching, these poll results, derived from 430 registered Pennsylvanian voters, will be pivotal for campaign strategies. The poll’s credibility interval is ±4.7%, and it follows another by the Marketing Resource Group, where Trump had a seven-point lead over Biden.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given the ever-shifting political landscape and the critical role Pennsylvania has played in recent elections, it remains to be seen how these preliminary sentiments translate to votes in the coming year.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Pennsylvania, often considered a critical battleground state in U.S. elections, seems to be leaning towards former President Donald Trump over the incumbent, President Joe Biden. According to a recent Emerson College poll, Trump leads by a significant 9-point margin in a potential face-off. Key Takeaways from the Poll: Trump’s Lead: 45% of the registered voters in Pennsylvania expressed support for Trump, compared to Biden’s 36%. Interestingly, this shows a shift in voter sentiment, as 43% voted for Biden and 42% for Trump in the 2020 elections. Independent Voters: Trump appears to resonate with independent voters, securing a remarkable 44% of their support, while Biden trails at 14%. The remaining voters are split between other candidates or are still making up their minds. Biden’s Approval Rating: Notably, Biden’s approval rating in the state is at a concerning low. Only 31% of Pennsylvanians have a positive view of his presidency, while a significant 51% disapprove, rendering his net approval rating at -20. Loyalty among Supporters: Half of Trump’s supporters firmly assert that nothing could deter their support for him in the 2024 presidential race. On the flip side, 53% of Biden’s supporters echo the same unwavering loyalty. Senate Race Insights: Though Trump is soaring in popularity, it’s interesting to note that this surge isn’t necessarily translating to other Republicans. In a potential U.S. Senate race, the Democratic Senator Bob Casey leads over Republican Dave McCormick by eight points, standing at 41% to McCormick’s 33%. Emerson College Polling’s Executive Director, Spencer Kimball, shed light on these variances, especially concerning age demographics. Biden holds an edge over Trump among voters under 40 (44% to 39%). Yet, among those below 30, Trump gains traction, leading 45% to 39%. Senator Casey, however, retains dominance across both age brackets. Education also plays a significant role. Voters with a high school degree or less significantly favor Trump (53% to 27%). Yet, when it comes to the Senate race, Casey just slightly outpaces McCormick among the same group. With the 2024 elections approaching, these poll results, derived from 430 registered Pennsylvanian voters, will be pivotal for campaign strategies. The poll’s credibility interval is ±4.7%, and it follows another by the Marketing Resource Group, where Trump had a seven-point lead over Biden. Given the ever-shifting political landscape and the critical role Pennsylvania has played in recent elections, it remains to be seen how these preliminary sentiments translate to votes in the coming year.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Steve Scalise Emerges as GOP’s Choice for House Speaker</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/12/Scalise-Nominee-Speaker/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Steve Scalise Emerges as GOP’s Choice for House Speaker" /><published>2023-10-12T10:45:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-12T10:45:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/12/Scalise-Nominee-Speaker</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/12/Scalise-Nominee-Speaker/">&lt;p&gt;In a significant political move, House Republicans have elected Majority Leader Steve Scalise, representing Louisiana, as their leading candidate for the esteemed role of House Speaker. This decision comes on the heels of an extensive, closed-door meeting that spanned more than two hours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The GOP’s decision-making process took the form of a secret ballot, wherein Scalise secured a notable 113 votes, outpacing Judiciary Committee Chairman Jim Jordan, who managed to garner 99 votes. Prior to this vote, House Republicans had deliberated and eventually voted against a motion that proposed elevating the threshold for electing the House speaker to 217 votes, amounting to a majority of the conference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This unfolding of events comes in the wake of the unanticipated ousting of former Speaker Kevin McCarthy, a California Republican. McCarthy’s removal marked an unparalleled moment in American political history, as it was the first occasion the U.S. House of Representatives made the collective decision to unseat its leader. Eight members of McCarthy’s party, in tandem with all House Democrats, catalyzed his fall from grace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the scramble to fill the speaker vacancy intensified, the spotlight inevitably narrowed down to two frontrunners: Scalise and Jordan, a Republican representative from Ohio. Scalise, a seasoned political figure, has been recognized as McCarthy’s right-hand man for a significant duration, notwithstanding the simmering rivalry that exists between the pair.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In contrast, Jordan, known for his closer ties to McCarthy, initially received an outpouring of support from influential conservatives within the GOP. Key figures like House Freedom Caucus Policy Chair Chip Roy, a Republican representative from Texas, openly endorsed Jordan. It’s worth noting that Jordan’s political career boasts of being a co-founder of the influential House Freedom Caucus group.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The political realm, as it stands, is rife with conjecture and anticipation regarding the future of the House’s leadership. As tensions simmer and factions within the GOP rally behind their preferred candidates, the stage is set for a monumental showdown in the race for the House Speaker position.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a significant political move, House Republicans have elected Majority Leader Steve Scalise, representing Louisiana, as their leading candidate for the esteemed role of House Speaker. This decision comes on the heels of an extensive, closed-door meeting that spanned more than two hours. The GOP’s decision-making process took the form of a secret ballot, wherein Scalise secured a notable 113 votes, outpacing Judiciary Committee Chairman Jim Jordan, who managed to garner 99 votes. Prior to this vote, House Republicans had deliberated and eventually voted against a motion that proposed elevating the threshold for electing the House speaker to 217 votes, amounting to a majority of the conference. This unfolding of events comes in the wake of the unanticipated ousting of former Speaker Kevin McCarthy, a California Republican. McCarthy’s removal marked an unparalleled moment in American political history, as it was the first occasion the U.S. House of Representatives made the collective decision to unseat its leader. Eight members of McCarthy’s party, in tandem with all House Democrats, catalyzed his fall from grace. As the scramble to fill the speaker vacancy intensified, the spotlight inevitably narrowed down to two frontrunners: Scalise and Jordan, a Republican representative from Ohio. Scalise, a seasoned political figure, has been recognized as McCarthy’s right-hand man for a significant duration, notwithstanding the simmering rivalry that exists between the pair. In contrast, Jordan, known for his closer ties to McCarthy, initially received an outpouring of support from influential conservatives within the GOP. Key figures like House Freedom Caucus Policy Chair Chip Roy, a Republican representative from Texas, openly endorsed Jordan. It’s worth noting that Jordan’s political career boasts of being a co-founder of the influential House Freedom Caucus group. The political realm, as it stands, is rife with conjecture and anticipation regarding the future of the House’s leadership. As tensions simmer and factions within the GOP rally behind their preferred candidates, the stage is set for a monumental showdown in the race for the House Speaker position.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hamas Declares Worldwide ‘Day of Jihad’ on Infamous Friday the 13th</title><link href="/news/2023/10/12/Hamas-Day-of-Jihad/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hamas Declares Worldwide ‘Day of Jihad’ on Infamous Friday the 13th" /><published>2023-10-12T09:34:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-12T09:34:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/12/Hamas-Day-of-Jihad</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/12/Hamas-Day-of-Jihad/">&lt;p&gt;In a chilling announcement, the Palestinian Hamas terror group, simply known as Hamas, has urged Muslims globally to mark a “Day of Jihad” on Friday, October 13th. Strikingly, this date is commonly associated with horror movies and the popular Halloween holiday, further deepening concerns about the group’s intentions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dubbing the day as “Al-Aqsa Flood” Friday, Hamas recalls their past operation, which resulted in the death of over 1,200 Israelis, leaving approximately 3,000 injured and more than 100 kidnapped.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Middle East Media Research Institute (MEMRI), in its report, cites Hamas stating:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“We declare next Friday, ‘The Friday of the Al-Aqsa Flood,’ as a day of general mobilization in our Arab and Islamic world and among the free people of the world. It is a day to rally support, offer aid, and participate actively. It is a day to expose the crimes of the occupation, isolate it, and foil all its aggressive schemes.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hamas continues to stress the importance of the day as an opportunity to express profound love for Palestine, Jerusalem, and Al-Aqsa, urging it to be a day of sacrifice, heroism, and dedication.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hamas has further beckoned Palestinians in the West Bank (which Israelis refer to as Judea and Samaria) to rise against Israeli forces. Moreover, they appeal to Arab citizens residing in Israel, referring to them as “our people within the occupied territories of 1948”, to rebel against the state.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In popular culture, particularly in the entertainment sector, Friday the 13th has long been a day linked with horror, often chosen for the launch of horror film releases, captivating audiences with fictional tales of terror. However, the atrocities committed by Hamas in Israel paint a stark and grim reality, far from fiction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It remains to be seen how the world will react to this ominous call to arms on a day already shrouded in superstition and horror. The global community must remain vigilant and united in the face of such threats, ensuring peace and security for all.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a chilling announcement, the Palestinian Hamas terror group, simply known as Hamas, has urged Muslims globally to mark a “Day of Jihad” on Friday, October 13th. Strikingly, this date is commonly associated with horror movies and the popular Halloween holiday, further deepening concerns about the group’s intentions. Dubbing the day as “Al-Aqsa Flood” Friday, Hamas recalls their past operation, which resulted in the death of over 1,200 Israelis, leaving approximately 3,000 injured and more than 100 kidnapped. The Middle East Media Research Institute (MEMRI), in its report, cites Hamas stating: “We declare next Friday, ‘The Friday of the Al-Aqsa Flood,’ as a day of general mobilization in our Arab and Islamic world and among the free people of the world. It is a day to rally support, offer aid, and participate actively. It is a day to expose the crimes of the occupation, isolate it, and foil all its aggressive schemes.” Hamas continues to stress the importance of the day as an opportunity to express profound love for Palestine, Jerusalem, and Al-Aqsa, urging it to be a day of sacrifice, heroism, and dedication. Hamas has further beckoned Palestinians in the West Bank (which Israelis refer to as Judea and Samaria) to rise against Israeli forces. Moreover, they appeal to Arab citizens residing in Israel, referring to them as “our people within the occupied territories of 1948”, to rebel against the state. In popular culture, particularly in the entertainment sector, Friday the 13th has long been a day linked with horror, often chosen for the launch of horror film releases, captivating audiences with fictional tales of terror. However, the atrocities committed by Hamas in Israel paint a stark and grim reality, far from fiction. It remains to be seen how the world will react to this ominous call to arms on a day already shrouded in superstition and horror. The global community must remain vigilant and united in the face of such threats, ensuring peace and security for all.</summary></entry></feed>