<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-09-18T04:20:21-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/09/18/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-09-18T04:20:21-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-18T04:20:21-04:00</updated><id>/2023/09/18/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/18/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump Talks Competency - Age Limits ‘Not Necessary’</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/17/Trump-Competency-Tests/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump Talks Competency - Age Limits ‘Not Necessary’" /><published>2023-09-17T16:45:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-17T16:45:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/17/Trump-Competency-Tests</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/17/Trump-Competency-Tests/">&lt;p&gt;While age limits for politicians are gaining traction in public discourse, former President Donald Trump has a different take. Instead of focusing on age, he believes competency tests would be more beneficial.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a recent interview on NBC’s “Meet the Press,” Trump, at age 77, shared his views. He responded to host Kristen Welker’s questions about age limits, especially since Trump and current President Joe Biden, who’s 80, are potential opponents in the 2024 elections.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recalling a test he took a few years ago at Walter Reed, Trump said, “I aced it. I get everything right. I’m all for testing. I frankly think testing would be a good thing.” But is it constitutional? The former president believes some might see it that way, though he isn’t certain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump added, “[You] know, some of the greatest world leaders have been in their 80s. I’m not anywhere very near 80, by the way.” He emphasized that it’s not about Biden’s age but his competence, which he sees as a bigger concern.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But what about Trump’s age? If he wins the 2024 elections, he’ll be nearing 80 in his term. Biden, if re-elected, would be 82 at the beginning of his next term. Biden’s age has been a frequent topic of discussion due to occasional lapses in memory and stuttered speeches.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another vocal advocate for competency testing is former South Carolina Governor Nikki Haley. She’s been proactive in pushing for cognitive tests for politicians, particularly for those over 75. Notably, she hasn’t supported age limits. Mockingly referring to the U.S. Senate as “the most privileged nursing home in the country,” she called for legislation that would require competency tests for both presidential candidates and Congress members.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Haley’s comments came in the wake of health concerns involving Senate minority leader Mitch McConnell and Sen. Dianne Feinstein, D-Calif. Discussing their health episodes, she remarked, “It’s sad. No one should feel good about seeing that.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the upcoming 2024 Republican Presidential Primary, Haley is set to challenge Trump. However, current polls indicate Trump’s lead over other candidates remains significant. Despite this, Trump voiced his appreciation for the idea of a female vice president, assuring that he would “pick the best person.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The debate around age and competence is unlikely to subside, especially as the 2024 elections approach. But one thing is clear: the need for efficient and competent leadership is paramount, no matter the age.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">While age limits for politicians are gaining traction in public discourse, former President Donald Trump has a different take. Instead of focusing on age, he believes competency tests would be more beneficial. In a recent interview on NBC’s “Meet the Press,” Trump, at age 77, shared his views. He responded to host Kristen Welker’s questions about age limits, especially since Trump and current President Joe Biden, who’s 80, are potential opponents in the 2024 elections. Recalling a test he took a few years ago at Walter Reed, Trump said, “I aced it. I get everything right. I’m all for testing. I frankly think testing would be a good thing.” But is it constitutional? The former president believes some might see it that way, though he isn’t certain. Trump added, “[You] know, some of the greatest world leaders have been in their 80s. I’m not anywhere very near 80, by the way.” He emphasized that it’s not about Biden’s age but his competence, which he sees as a bigger concern. But what about Trump’s age? If he wins the 2024 elections, he’ll be nearing 80 in his term. Biden, if re-elected, would be 82 at the beginning of his next term. Biden’s age has been a frequent topic of discussion due to occasional lapses in memory and stuttered speeches. Another vocal advocate for competency testing is former South Carolina Governor Nikki Haley. She’s been proactive in pushing for cognitive tests for politicians, particularly for those over 75. Notably, she hasn’t supported age limits. Mockingly referring to the U.S. Senate as “the most privileged nursing home in the country,” she called for legislation that would require competency tests for both presidential candidates and Congress members. Haley’s comments came in the wake of health concerns involving Senate minority leader Mitch McConnell and Sen. Dianne Feinstein, D-Calif. Discussing their health episodes, she remarked, “It’s sad. No one should feel good about seeing that.” In the upcoming 2024 Republican Presidential Primary, Haley is set to challenge Trump. However, current polls indicate Trump’s lead over other candidates remains significant. Despite this, Trump voiced his appreciation for the idea of a female vice president, assuring that he would “pick the best person.” The debate around age and competence is unlikely to subside, especially as the 2024 elections approach. But one thing is clear: the need for efficient and competent leadership is paramount, no matter the age.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Biden’s Oversight - Texas Border Town Overrun by Unprecedented Migrant Numbers</title><link href="/news/2023/09/17/Biden-Texas-Migrant-Surge/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Biden’s Oversight - Texas Border Town Overrun by Unprecedented Migrant Numbers" /><published>2023-09-17T15:52:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-17T15:52:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/17/Biden-Texas-Migrant-Surge</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/17/Biden-Texas-Migrant-Surge/">&lt;p&gt;The Texas border town of Eagle Pass experienced an extraordinary and concerning day when, in just 24 hours, over 1,300 migrants were apprehended. This number surpassed the combined total from all eleven El Paso Border Patrol Sector stations, highlighting a serious surge in this small town.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-strained-system&quot;&gt;A Strained System&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eagle Pass, with a population of only around 30,000 residents, is feeling the pressure. The apprehensions in a single day have overwhelmed the town’s Border Patrol processing facility and the ability of non-government (NGO) shelters to accommodate such a surge. This immense inflow has left the local system stretched thin, with one source noting, “In just one eight-hour shift, more than 700 migrants were taken into custody. We lack the capacity to deal with it. This system is broken.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;overburdened-facilities&quot;&gt;Overburdened Facilities&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With only one soft-sided processing facility operating in the area, the number of detained migrants skyrocketed to over 3,000. This volume is three times its designated capacity. Unfortunately, this overload prompted the Border Patrol to conduct mass releases into the town. Migrants, without sufficient funds for travel, were observed attempting the daunting walk from Eagle Pass to San Antonio, Texas, a journey spanning over 150 miles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-failing-response&quot;&gt;A Failing Response&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The strategy from the top seems disconnected from the ground reality. Instead of effectively addressing the growing crisis, the response appears to be one of surrender. “Our facilities are full, the NGO shelters have exceeded their capacity as well, and we are releasing every migrant we can just to stay afloat,” an inside source shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Local residents are feeling the brunt of this surge firsthand. Migrants wander the city streets, lacking funds for bus tickets or meals. The only NGO shelter, Mission Border Hope, has had to turn away migrants who can’t afford the $50 bus ticket to San Antonio. This situation puts these migrants in an even more vulnerable position, expecting them to travel hundreds of miles without adequate resources.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the town’s Border Patrol aims to release migrants to the shelter, intending to prevent adding to the homeless population, the lack of proper planning and infrastructure has made this a losing strategy. “We had no knowledge that the poorest of migrants would be thrown out on the streets and expected to walk more than 150 miles to the next largest city, but that is where we are,” the source added.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s evident that Eagle Pass, and Texas at large, needs an effective solution that addresses the immediate concerns of overwhelmed facilities and the long-term implications of mass releases into small towns. At the core of this crisis is the Biden administration, which must acknowledge its role and take definitive action to mend this worsening situation.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">The Texas border town of Eagle Pass experienced an extraordinary and concerning day when, in just 24 hours, over 1,300 migrants were apprehended. This number surpassed the combined total from all eleven El Paso Border Patrol Sector stations, highlighting a serious surge in this small town. A Strained System Eagle Pass, with a population of only around 30,000 residents, is feeling the pressure. The apprehensions in a single day have overwhelmed the town’s Border Patrol processing facility and the ability of non-government (NGO) shelters to accommodate such a surge. This immense inflow has left the local system stretched thin, with one source noting, “In just one eight-hour shift, more than 700 migrants were taken into custody. We lack the capacity to deal with it. This system is broken.” Overburdened Facilities With only one soft-sided processing facility operating in the area, the number of detained migrants skyrocketed to over 3,000. This volume is three times its designated capacity. Unfortunately, this overload prompted the Border Patrol to conduct mass releases into the town. Migrants, without sufficient funds for travel, were observed attempting the daunting walk from Eagle Pass to San Antonio, Texas, a journey spanning over 150 miles. A Failing Response The strategy from the top seems disconnected from the ground reality. Instead of effectively addressing the growing crisis, the response appears to be one of surrender. “Our facilities are full, the NGO shelters have exceeded their capacity as well, and we are releasing every migrant we can just to stay afloat,” an inside source shared. Local residents are feeling the brunt of this surge firsthand. Migrants wander the city streets, lacking funds for bus tickets or meals. The only NGO shelter, Mission Border Hope, has had to turn away migrants who can’t afford the $50 bus ticket to San Antonio. This situation puts these migrants in an even more vulnerable position, expecting them to travel hundreds of miles without adequate resources. While the town’s Border Patrol aims to release migrants to the shelter, intending to prevent adding to the homeless population, the lack of proper planning and infrastructure has made this a losing strategy. “We had no knowledge that the poorest of migrants would be thrown out on the streets and expected to walk more than 150 miles to the next largest city, but that is where we are,” the source added. It’s evident that Eagle Pass, and Texas at large, needs an effective solution that addresses the immediate concerns of overwhelmed facilities and the long-term implications of mass releases into small towns. At the core of this crisis is the Biden administration, which must acknowledge its role and take definitive action to mend this worsening situation.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Oher - Tuohy Relationship Sparks Legal Debate</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/17/Family-Ties-Controversy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Oher - Tuohy Relationship Sparks Legal Debate" /><published>2023-09-17T13:45:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-17T13:45:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/17/Family-Ties-Controversy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/17/Family-Ties-Controversy/">&lt;p&gt;Michael Oher, whose life story was the inspiration behind the hit movie “The Blind Side,” is once again making headlines. This time, it’s not for his skills on the football field but for a dispute over family ties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;adopted-or-not&quot;&gt;Adopted or Not?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently, Oher filed a lawsuit against Sean and Leigh Anne Tuohy, the family that took him in during high school. In the lawsuit, he accused them of falsely presenting themselves as his adoptive parents. He also claimed they kept financial details hidden from him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Tuohys responded in court. They said they never intended to legally adopt Oher but always saw him as part of their family. They admit calling him their son, but they say it was only in a casual way, not in a legal sense.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2023/08/720/405/michael-oher-tuohy-family.jpg?ve=1&amp;amp;tl=1&quot; alt=&quot;Michael Oher and the Tuohy family&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Michael Oher with the Tuohy family during a game in 2008. Photo by Matthew Sharpe/Getty Images.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;more-than-just-words&quot;&gt;More Than Just Words&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why is this a big deal? Well, Oher believes the Tuohys used their relationship to make money from him. But the Tuohys say they’ve always supported Oher, giving him a home, food, and even cars. They also mentioned that the only reason they became Oher’s conservators (people who make legal decisions for someone) was to follow college sports rules. Without being a part of the Tuohy family, Oher might not have been able to play football for the University of Mississippi.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Tuohys also pointed out that in Oher’s book from 2011, “I Beat the Odds,” he knew they were his conservators and not his adoptive parents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-story-still-unfolding&quot;&gt;A Story Still Unfolding&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This lawsuit shows that family ties can be complex, especially when money and fame are involved. Both Oher and the Tuohys have shared a bond for years, but now that bond is being tested in court. Whatever happens, their story reminds us that family is about more than just names and legal papers. It’s about love, trust, and understanding.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Michael Oher, whose life story was the inspiration behind the hit movie “The Blind Side,” is once again making headlines. This time, it’s not for his skills on the football field but for a dispute over family ties. Adopted or Not? Recently, Oher filed a lawsuit against Sean and Leigh Anne Tuohy, the family that took him in during high school. In the lawsuit, he accused them of falsely presenting themselves as his adoptive parents. He also claimed they kept financial details hidden from him. The Tuohys responded in court. They said they never intended to legally adopt Oher but always saw him as part of their family. They admit calling him their son, but they say it was only in a casual way, not in a legal sense. Michael Oher with the Tuohy family during a game in 2008. Photo by Matthew Sharpe/Getty Images. More Than Just Words Why is this a big deal? Well, Oher believes the Tuohys used their relationship to make money from him. But the Tuohys say they’ve always supported Oher, giving him a home, food, and even cars. They also mentioned that the only reason they became Oher’s conservators (people who make legal decisions for someone) was to follow college sports rules. Without being a part of the Tuohy family, Oher might not have been able to play football for the University of Mississippi. The Tuohys also pointed out that in Oher’s book from 2011, “I Beat the Odds,” he knew they were his conservators and not his adoptive parents. A Story Still Unfolding This lawsuit shows that family ties can be complex, especially when money and fame are involved. Both Oher and the Tuohys have shared a bond for years, but now that bond is being tested in court. Whatever happens, their story reminds us that family is about more than just names and legal papers. It’s about love, trust, and understanding.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Resilient Half-Jawed Gator - New Star Attraction at Gatorland</title><link href="/news/2023/09/17/Resilient-Gator/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Resilient Half-Jawed Gator - New Star Attraction at Gatorland" /><published>2023-09-17T11:04:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-17T11:04:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/17/Resilient-Gator</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/17/Resilient-Gator/">&lt;p&gt;Alligators have been a key part of Florida’s wildlife for eons, but a recent discovery of a half-jawed gator has captured the nation’s attention. This unique reptile’s story of survival has now earned it a home at Gatorland Orlando.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-survivors-tale&quot;&gt;A Survivor’s Tale&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It isn’t every day you come across an alligator missing half of its upper jaw. When local resident Eustacia Kanter spotted the young reptile in Sanford, even she had trouble processing what she was seeing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“At first, my brain couldn’t comprehend that its entire upper jaw was missing,” recounted Kanter. Once the initial shock wore off, her compassion kicked in. Kanter promptly captured a photo from a safe distance, aiming to share it with those who might offer assistance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;from-wild-to-safe-haven&quot;&gt;From Wild to Safe Haven&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kanter’s initiative led her to contact the Florida Fish and Wildlife Conservation Commission and an environmental conservation nonprofit. The goal? Find and safely rescue this rare gator.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The alligator, believed to be between four to five years old, managed to avoid capture for several weeks, displaying a level of resilience that is truly awe-inspiring. It’s estimated that this fighter had been living in the wild in its present condition for at least six months, subsisting mainly on smaller prey like snails and frogs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The suspected cause of the gator’s injury is a boat’s engine propeller. Despite the drastic injury, the creature’s vitality remains intact. “Alligators and crocodiles are amazing survivors,” emphasized Savannah Boan from Gatorland. “They can survive almost anything.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-new-home&quot;&gt;A New Home&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reptile, which made national headlines due to its unique condition, has found a comfortable new abode at Gatorland Orlando. Officials have mentioned that it will remain separated from other animals initially and be placed on a special diet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“She’s a little bit skinny, but she looks to be pretty healthy and feisty,” Boan observed, expressing optimism about the gator’s future at the park.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;got-a-name-in-mind&quot;&gt;Got a Name in Mind?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The story of this incredible survivor is still unfolding, and now, Gatorland is inviting the public to contribute. They are encouraging people to suggest names for this distinctive gator via the park’s social media channels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To many, this gator represents the epitome of resilience. It’s a testament to the fact that even when faced with the harshest of life’s trials, with a little help and a lot of spirit, one can find a way to not just survive, but thrive.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Alligators have been a key part of Florida’s wildlife for eons, but a recent discovery of a half-jawed gator has captured the nation’s attention. This unique reptile’s story of survival has now earned it a home at Gatorland Orlando. A Survivor’s Tale It isn’t every day you come across an alligator missing half of its upper jaw. When local resident Eustacia Kanter spotted the young reptile in Sanford, even she had trouble processing what she was seeing. “At first, my brain couldn’t comprehend that its entire upper jaw was missing,” recounted Kanter. Once the initial shock wore off, her compassion kicked in. Kanter promptly captured a photo from a safe distance, aiming to share it with those who might offer assistance. From Wild to Safe Haven Kanter’s initiative led her to contact the Florida Fish and Wildlife Conservation Commission and an environmental conservation nonprofit. The goal? Find and safely rescue this rare gator. The alligator, believed to be between four to five years old, managed to avoid capture for several weeks, displaying a level of resilience that is truly awe-inspiring. It’s estimated that this fighter had been living in the wild in its present condition for at least six months, subsisting mainly on smaller prey like snails and frogs. The suspected cause of the gator’s injury is a boat’s engine propeller. Despite the drastic injury, the creature’s vitality remains intact. “Alligators and crocodiles are amazing survivors,” emphasized Savannah Boan from Gatorland. “They can survive almost anything.” A New Home The reptile, which made national headlines due to its unique condition, has found a comfortable new abode at Gatorland Orlando. Officials have mentioned that it will remain separated from other animals initially and be placed on a special diet. “She’s a little bit skinny, but she looks to be pretty healthy and feisty,” Boan observed, expressing optimism about the gator’s future at the park. Got a Name in Mind? The story of this incredible survivor is still unfolding, and now, Gatorland is inviting the public to contribute. They are encouraging people to suggest names for this distinctive gator via the park’s social media channels. To many, this gator represents the epitome of resilience. It’s a testament to the fact that even when faced with the harshest of life’s trials, with a little help and a lot of spirit, one can find a way to not just survive, but thrive.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Pence Backs Tuberville - ‘Pentagon Is Wrong’</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/17/Pence-Military-Holds/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Pence Backs Tuberville - ‘Pentagon Is Wrong’" /><published>2023-09-17T10:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-17T10:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/17/Pence-Military-Holds</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/17/Pence-Military-Holds/">&lt;p&gt;The Pentagon’s abortion policy has stirred controversy, and now it’s influencing military promotions. Former Vice President Mike Pence, eyeing the 2024 GOP presidential nomination, showed his backing for Sen. Tommy Tuberville, R-Ala., who’s actively blocked multiple military appointments. Why? He’s protesting the Pentagon’s abortion policy which was introduced earlier this year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pence firmly stated his views during a speech on Friday. “Sen. Tommy Tuberville is right, and the Pentagon is wrong,” Pence declared, committing to halt taxpayer dollars from undermining pro-life laws if he takes office. Tuberville’s stance, however, has led to a six-month holdup in the Senate, affecting over 300 pending military promotions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The protest also means that Army, Marine Corps, and Navy leaders are currently in interim positions, which curtails their authority. This occurs because of the Senate’s delay in confirming them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, what’s the Pentagon’s policy that’s causing this ripple? They’ve pledged to cover the travel costs for service members either seeking abortions or supporting their spouses during such procedures. This policy allows up to five months, or 20 weeks into a pregnancy, for service members to inform their departments and ask for travel assistance for these purposes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet Pence is not alone in his support for Tuberville. Other Republicans have also echoed similar sentiments. Nevertheless, there’s also criticism from both sides of the aisle and the military. For instance, Minority Leader Mitch McConnell, R-Ky, critiqued Tuberville’s strategy, saying, “holding these non-policymaking career military [officials] is a mistake.” Similarly, House Foreign Affairs Committee Chairman Michael McCaul, R-Texas, pointed out the national security risks, stating Tuberville’s holds are “paralyzing the Department of Defense.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pence, who’s been vocal about his anti-abortion stance, was the first 2024 presidential candidate to back a 15-week national abortion ban. He stated, “I’m pro-life. I don’t apologize for it,” emphasizing his commitment to the cause.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the hold on promotions doesn’t sit well with many. Inside sources claim it compromises national security and might even push those awaiting promotions to look for jobs outside the military. A joint op-ed by the chiefs of the Army, Navy, and Air Force emphasized the negative impact, stating, “Any claim that holding up the promotions of top officers does not directly damage the military is wrong.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With mounting criticism from both Democrats and Republicans, recent polls among Alabama voters suggest that the majority would prefer Tuberville to end his block on military promotions.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">The Pentagon’s abortion policy has stirred controversy, and now it’s influencing military promotions. Former Vice President Mike Pence, eyeing the 2024 GOP presidential nomination, showed his backing for Sen. Tommy Tuberville, R-Ala., who’s actively blocked multiple military appointments. Why? He’s protesting the Pentagon’s abortion policy which was introduced earlier this year. Pence firmly stated his views during a speech on Friday. “Sen. Tommy Tuberville is right, and the Pentagon is wrong,” Pence declared, committing to halt taxpayer dollars from undermining pro-life laws if he takes office. Tuberville’s stance, however, has led to a six-month holdup in the Senate, affecting over 300 pending military promotions. The protest also means that Army, Marine Corps, and Navy leaders are currently in interim positions, which curtails their authority. This occurs because of the Senate’s delay in confirming them. So, what’s the Pentagon’s policy that’s causing this ripple? They’ve pledged to cover the travel costs for service members either seeking abortions or supporting their spouses during such procedures. This policy allows up to five months, or 20 weeks into a pregnancy, for service members to inform their departments and ask for travel assistance for these purposes. Yet Pence is not alone in his support for Tuberville. Other Republicans have also echoed similar sentiments. Nevertheless, there’s also criticism from both sides of the aisle and the military. For instance, Minority Leader Mitch McConnell, R-Ky, critiqued Tuberville’s strategy, saying, “holding these non-policymaking career military [officials] is a mistake.” Similarly, House Foreign Affairs Committee Chairman Michael McCaul, R-Texas, pointed out the national security risks, stating Tuberville’s holds are “paralyzing the Department of Defense.” Pence, who’s been vocal about his anti-abortion stance, was the first 2024 presidential candidate to back a 15-week national abortion ban. He stated, “I’m pro-life. I don’t apologize for it,” emphasizing his commitment to the cause. However, the hold on promotions doesn’t sit well with many. Inside sources claim it compromises national security and might even push those awaiting promotions to look for jobs outside the military. A joint op-ed by the chiefs of the Army, Navy, and Air Force emphasized the negative impact, stating, “Any claim that holding up the promotions of top officers does not directly damage the military is wrong.” With mounting criticism from both Democrats and Republicans, recent polls among Alabama voters suggest that the majority would prefer Tuberville to end his block on military promotions.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Sharna Burgess Expresses Shock - Adrian Peterson Joins DWTS Cast</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/17/DWTS-Casting-Controversy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sharna Burgess Expresses Shock - Adrian Peterson Joins DWTS Cast" /><published>2023-09-17T09:02:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-17T09:02:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/17/DWTS-Casting-Controversy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/17/DWTS-Casting-Controversy/">&lt;p&gt;“Dancing with the Stars” is a show many people love. It’s all about celebrities pairing up with pro dancers to show off their moves. But recently, one choice of celebrity has many people, including former DWTS pro dancer Sharna Burgess, feeling a bit upset.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;speaking-out-loud&quot;&gt;Speaking Out Loud&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sharna Burgess used her podcast, “Old-ish”, to share her thoughts. She was really surprised when she found out that Adrian Peterson, a famous football player, was joining the new season of “Dancing with the Stars.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Why?” you might ask.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, in 2014, Peterson was in big trouble. He got charged with child abuse. He had used a switch (a thin tree branch) to spank his young son, who was only four years old at that time. The child had lots of cuts and bruises. Later, in 2018, Peterson said in an interview that he still uses a belt to punish his son.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For Burgess, this was really hard to hear. She said, “The man has been charged with child abuse… and that is just devastating for me.” She even mentioned that if she were still on the show and got paired up with Peterson, she would just leave.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;other-troubles&quot;&gt;Other Troubles&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earlier this year, Peterson had another problem. He was arrested at an airport. There was a report that he and his wife, Ashley, had a big argument on a plane. However, later, the couple shared happy news: they were expecting their third child.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many fans of “Dancing with the Stars” are not happy with Peterson joining the show. When they found out he’d be dancing with pro dancer Britt Stewart, lots of them went online to share their feelings. Britt’s Instagram account got many negative comments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;why-all-this-matters&quot;&gt;Why All This Matters&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This story shows us how choices made by TV shows can stir feelings and debates. Some people think that Peterson should get a second chance. Others feel that his past actions should keep him off the show. It’s a reminder that the world of entertainment is not just about fun and games; it can also spark important discussions about right and wrong.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">“Dancing with the Stars” is a show many people love. It’s all about celebrities pairing up with pro dancers to show off their moves. But recently, one choice of celebrity has many people, including former DWTS pro dancer Sharna Burgess, feeling a bit upset. Speaking Out Loud Sharna Burgess used her podcast, “Old-ish”, to share her thoughts. She was really surprised when she found out that Adrian Peterson, a famous football player, was joining the new season of “Dancing with the Stars.” “Why?” you might ask. Well, in 2014, Peterson was in big trouble. He got charged with child abuse. He had used a switch (a thin tree branch) to spank his young son, who was only four years old at that time. The child had lots of cuts and bruises. Later, in 2018, Peterson said in an interview that he still uses a belt to punish his son. For Burgess, this was really hard to hear. She said, “The man has been charged with child abuse… and that is just devastating for me.” She even mentioned that if she were still on the show and got paired up with Peterson, she would just leave. Other Troubles Earlier this year, Peterson had another problem. He was arrested at an airport. There was a report that he and his wife, Ashley, had a big argument on a plane. However, later, the couple shared happy news: they were expecting their third child. Many fans of “Dancing with the Stars” are not happy with Peterson joining the show. When they found out he’d be dancing with pro dancer Britt Stewart, lots of them went online to share their feelings. Britt’s Instagram account got many negative comments. Why All This Matters This story shows us how choices made by TV shows can stir feelings and debates. Some people think that Peterson should get a second chance. Others feel that his past actions should keep him off the show. It’s a reminder that the world of entertainment is not just about fun and games; it can also spark important discussions about right and wrong.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Auto Workers Rally for Wage Boost - Inflation’s Tight Grip on America’s Backbone</title><link href="/news/2023/09/17/Auto-Workers-Inflation/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Auto Workers Rally for Wage Boost - Inflation’s Tight Grip on America’s Backbone" /><published>2023-09-17T08:02:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-17T08:02:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/17/Auto-Workers-Inflation</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/17/Auto-Workers-Inflation/">&lt;p&gt;Amid the bustling noise of machinery and the hum of production lines, a wave of concern is growing among the backbone of America’s auto industry. Auto workers, the force behind every vehicle rolling out of factories, are calling for a wage increase. And the reason is simple – the looming specter of inflation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-call-for-fair-wages&quot;&gt;The Call for Fair Wages&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Historically, auto workers have weathered economic storms, often making concessions for the greater good. During the government bailout era, they forfeited significant portions of their salaries and pension benefits, ensuring the survival of the auto industry at a time when it faced potential bankruptcy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, with the auto industry navigating a transition to electric vehicles and the rise of robotics threatening traditional jobs, workers are rallying for a 40% wage increase. While this figure might appear daunting at first glance, they justify this as a “catch-up” move, citing massive profit margins for the industry and lucrative pay packages for CEOs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-inflation-dilemma&quot;&gt;The Inflation Dilemma&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Inflation, often described as the silent thief, has played a significant role in the current wage debate. As NBC’s Brian Cheung points out, America has grappled with unprecedented inflation rates unseen in over four decades. While wages in the automotive sector have seen a 14-15% surge since the last contract negotiation in 2019, inflation rates have overshadowed this growth with an 18% rise in prices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Simply put, the earnings of auto workers haven’t paced with inflation. The figures elucidate a narrative of wages that lag behind the skyrocketing costs of living. With contract renegotiations occurring roughly every four years, workers are keen on securing a deal that reflects the financial realities of today’s economy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-road-ahead&quot;&gt;A Road Ahead&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As negotiations progress, it’s crucial to recognize the unique challenges auto workers face. Balancing the transition to sustainable transportation, the advent of robotics, and economic inflation is no small task. The coming weeks will undoubtedly be pivotal in determining the trajectory of wages and, by extension, the well-being of countless individuals in the auto industry.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Amid the bustling noise of machinery and the hum of production lines, a wave of concern is growing among the backbone of America’s auto industry. Auto workers, the force behind every vehicle rolling out of factories, are calling for a wage increase. And the reason is simple – the looming specter of inflation. The Call for Fair Wages Historically, auto workers have weathered economic storms, often making concessions for the greater good. During the government bailout era, they forfeited significant portions of their salaries and pension benefits, ensuring the survival of the auto industry at a time when it faced potential bankruptcy. Now, with the auto industry navigating a transition to electric vehicles and the rise of robotics threatening traditional jobs, workers are rallying for a 40% wage increase. While this figure might appear daunting at first glance, they justify this as a “catch-up” move, citing massive profit margins for the industry and lucrative pay packages for CEOs. The Inflation Dilemma Inflation, often described as the silent thief, has played a significant role in the current wage debate. As NBC’s Brian Cheung points out, America has grappled with unprecedented inflation rates unseen in over four decades. While wages in the automotive sector have seen a 14-15% surge since the last contract negotiation in 2019, inflation rates have overshadowed this growth with an 18% rise in prices. Simply put, the earnings of auto workers haven’t paced with inflation. The figures elucidate a narrative of wages that lag behind the skyrocketing costs of living. With contract renegotiations occurring roughly every four years, workers are keen on securing a deal that reflects the financial realities of today’s economy. A Road Ahead As negotiations progress, it’s crucial to recognize the unique challenges auto workers face. Balancing the transition to sustainable transportation, the advent of robotics, and economic inflation is no small task. The coming weeks will undoubtedly be pivotal in determining the trajectory of wages and, by extension, the well-being of countless individuals in the auto industry.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">DeSantis Takes On 2024 - ‘You’ve Got to Earn It’</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/17/DeSantis-Nomination/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="DeSantis Takes On 2024 - ‘You’ve Got to Earn It’" /><published>2023-09-17T07:11:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-17T07:11:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/17/DeSantis-Nomination</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/17/DeSantis-Nomination/">&lt;p&gt;Governor Ron DeSantis of Florida recently shared some strong opinions about the upcoming 2024 presidential election. He firmly believes that no candidate should automatically get a nomination. Everyone has to earn their spot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During a chat on the “America Reports” show on Fox News, DeSantis spoke about his game plan. He believes his campaign is ready to go the distance. Even though his current poll numbers might not be super high, he’s still giving it his all. He thinks there are many people in states like Iowa who haven’t made up their minds on who to vote for. This means there’s still a chance for him to get their support.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The key issues for voters, according to DeSantis, are the economy, border security, crime rates, education, and the role of government. He believes he knows what people care about. The real challenge? Finding out who’s the best person to handle all these issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DeSantis is super excited about his team in the early voting states. He believes they have what it takes to go all the way. He stated, “A lot of voters haven’t made a firm decision. They may be leaning one way or another. So, I think this is very fluid, and I think someone’s got to go out there and grab it.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His main point? Nobody should expect to be handed the nomination on a silver platter. They need to show up, work hard, and earn every single vote. And that’s exactly what DeSantis plans to do.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Governor Ron DeSantis of Florida recently shared some strong opinions about the upcoming 2024 presidential election. He firmly believes that no candidate should automatically get a nomination. Everyone has to earn their spot. During a chat on the “America Reports” show on Fox News, DeSantis spoke about his game plan. He believes his campaign is ready to go the distance. Even though his current poll numbers might not be super high, he’s still giving it his all. He thinks there are many people in states like Iowa who haven’t made up their minds on who to vote for. This means there’s still a chance for him to get their support. The key issues for voters, according to DeSantis, are the economy, border security, crime rates, education, and the role of government. He believes he knows what people care about. The real challenge? Finding out who’s the best person to handle all these issues. DeSantis is super excited about his team in the early voting states. He believes they have what it takes to go all the way. He stated, “A lot of voters haven’t made a firm decision. They may be leaning one way or another. So, I think this is very fluid, and I think someone’s got to go out there and grab it.” His main point? Nobody should expect to be handed the nomination on a silver platter. They need to show up, work hard, and earn every single vote. And that’s exactly what DeSantis plans to do.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ohio Fugitive Confronts Armed Georgia Homeowner - A Glimpse Into a Night of Valor</title><link href="/news/2023/09/17/Ohio-Man-Georgia-Home-Invasion/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ohio Fugitive Confronts Armed Georgia Homeowner - A Glimpse Into a Night of Valor" /><published>2023-09-17T06:06:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-17T06:06:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/17/Ohio-Man-Georgia-Home-Invasion</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/17/Ohio-Man-Georgia-Home-Invasion/">&lt;p&gt;Late into the night, in a quiet Georgia neighborhood, an ordinary family found themselves in a harrowing situation. A man, wanted in Ohio for murder, had broken into their home. Little did he realize, the homeowner was prepared and determined to protect his loved ones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-invasion&quot;&gt;The Invasion&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Michael James Brooks II, known for his involvement in a series of crimes including a fatal stabbing in Ohio, broke into a residence in Georgia. However, the family man of the house was ready. Armed with a firearm and keen instincts, he confronted Brooks, who was wielding a knife, in his basement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Upon spotting the intruder, the homeowner didn’t immediately resort to force. He issued a warning to Brooks. But as events escalated, he had to fire two shots to defend himself and his family. This quick thinking and bravery potentially saved multiple lives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;prompt-police-response&quot;&gt;Prompt Police Response&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Fayette County Sheriff’s Office (FCSO) was alerted to the situation by a security alarm triggered at the house. With deputies just three minutes away, the homeowner made a strategic move. He took a defensive position on the second-floor staircase, preparing for any possible confrontation as Brooks made his way upwards. By the time the police arrived, Brooks had sustained two gunshot wounds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Brooks is currently in medical care. Once released, he is set to face a series of charges including burglary, home invasion, and theft in Georgia, along with murder charges in Ohio.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;connecting-the-dots&quot;&gt;Connecting The Dots&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The connection between Brooks and the crime scene was made clear when a Ford truck, reported stolen from Kettering, Ohio, was found outside the burglarized home in Georgia. It was this lead that confirmed Brooks’ involvement. The vehicle had plates different from the original, indicating a possible attempt to conceal his tracks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Investigators also believe that Brooks might have approached several homes in the Georgia neighborhood before zeroing in on the residence he invaded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-glimpse-into-brooks-past&quot;&gt;A Glimpse into Brooks’ Past&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Columbus Division of Police identified Brooks as the main suspect in another home invasion that resulted in the tragic death of 77-year-old Emily Foster. This invasion took place in the city’s University District on September 9.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The exact motivations and means by which Brooks moved from Ohio to Georgia remain a matter of investigation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-importance-of-preparedness&quot;&gt;The Importance of Preparedness&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This incident, though harrowing, stands as a testament to the importance of being prepared. The homeowner’s swift action and dedication to safeguarding his family underscore the value of personal safety and the right to defend one’s home and loved ones.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Late into the night, in a quiet Georgia neighborhood, an ordinary family found themselves in a harrowing situation. A man, wanted in Ohio for murder, had broken into their home. Little did he realize, the homeowner was prepared and determined to protect his loved ones. The Invasion Michael James Brooks II, known for his involvement in a series of crimes including a fatal stabbing in Ohio, broke into a residence in Georgia. However, the family man of the house was ready. Armed with a firearm and keen instincts, he confronted Brooks, who was wielding a knife, in his basement. Upon spotting the intruder, the homeowner didn’t immediately resort to force. He issued a warning to Brooks. But as events escalated, he had to fire two shots to defend himself and his family. This quick thinking and bravery potentially saved multiple lives. Prompt Police Response The Fayette County Sheriff’s Office (FCSO) was alerted to the situation by a security alarm triggered at the house. With deputies just three minutes away, the homeowner made a strategic move. He took a defensive position on the second-floor staircase, preparing for any possible confrontation as Brooks made his way upwards. By the time the police arrived, Brooks had sustained two gunshot wounds. Brooks is currently in medical care. Once released, he is set to face a series of charges including burglary, home invasion, and theft in Georgia, along with murder charges in Ohio. Connecting The Dots The connection between Brooks and the crime scene was made clear when a Ford truck, reported stolen from Kettering, Ohio, was found outside the burglarized home in Georgia. It was this lead that confirmed Brooks’ involvement. The vehicle had plates different from the original, indicating a possible attempt to conceal his tracks. Investigators also believe that Brooks might have approached several homes in the Georgia neighborhood before zeroing in on the residence he invaded. A Glimpse into Brooks’ Past The Columbus Division of Police identified Brooks as the main suspect in another home invasion that resulted in the tragic death of 77-year-old Emily Foster. This invasion took place in the city’s University District on September 9. The exact motivations and means by which Brooks moved from Ohio to Georgia remain a matter of investigation. The Importance of Preparedness This incident, though harrowing, stands as a testament to the importance of being prepared. The homeowner’s swift action and dedication to safeguarding his family underscore the value of personal safety and the right to defend one’s home and loved ones.</summary></entry></feed>