<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-10-05T19:15:55-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/05/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-05T19:15:55-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-05T19:15:55-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/05/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/05/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Sage Steele Sheds Light on Biden’s Mental State in Maher Interview</title><link href="/news/2023/10/05/Sage-Steele-Biden-Revelation/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sage Steele Sheds Light on Biden’s Mental State in Maher Interview" /><published>2023-10-05T17:45:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-05T17:45:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/05/Sage-Steele-Biden-Revelation</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/05/Sage-Steele-Biden-Revelation/">&lt;p&gt;Sage Steele, the ex-ESPN anchor, stirred up headlines recently when she divulged a disconcerting interaction with President Biden during an interview on Bill Maher’s “Club Random” podcast.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Steele shed light on an episode in March 2021 when she interviewed the President. She conveyed her concerns regarding what she believed was Biden’s cognitive decline, particularly when he “trailed off” during a chat before their scheduled recording.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I was trying just to fill time. And he said, ‘You know, I used to play football’… And so he started to tell football stories of his greatness… He said ‘I was good’ and then he went silent and he goes ‘Uhh… never mind,’” recalled Steele.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maher, known for his candid observations, drew comparisons to a scene from a ‘Naked Gun’ movie. Steele’s poignant description left many wondering about the President’s fitness for office, given the high demands of the role.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But Steele’s revelations didn’t stop there. She went on to discuss her unexpected encounter with former President Trump at his Bedminster golf course. Their connection revolved around their shared love for football and Trump’s endeavors to rejuvenate sports post-COVID. Steele also confessed to being “thoroughly entertained” by Trump’s audacious tweets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maher’s astonishment was palpable as he found out that Steele didn’t cast her vote for either Biden or Barack Obama in previous elections. Steele was quick to clarify, “I don’t love [Trump]. There’s a big difference in voting for someone and loving them.” She emphasized the importance of differentiating between politicians’ personal attributes and their policies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This recent revelation from Steele, combined with the ever-politicized climate, further underscores the need for transparency and candid discussions about our nation’s leaders. As the public digests Steele’s unsettling observations, questions regarding the competency of those in power remain at the forefront.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Sage Steele, the ex-ESPN anchor, stirred up headlines recently when she divulged a disconcerting interaction with President Biden during an interview on Bill Maher’s “Club Random” podcast. Steele shed light on an episode in March 2021 when she interviewed the President. She conveyed her concerns regarding what she believed was Biden’s cognitive decline, particularly when he “trailed off” during a chat before their scheduled recording. “I was trying just to fill time. And he said, ‘You know, I used to play football’… And so he started to tell football stories of his greatness… He said ‘I was good’ and then he went silent and he goes ‘Uhh… never mind,’” recalled Steele. Maher, known for his candid observations, drew comparisons to a scene from a ‘Naked Gun’ movie. Steele’s poignant description left many wondering about the President’s fitness for office, given the high demands of the role. But Steele’s revelations didn’t stop there. She went on to discuss her unexpected encounter with former President Trump at his Bedminster golf course. Their connection revolved around their shared love for football and Trump’s endeavors to rejuvenate sports post-COVID. Steele also confessed to being “thoroughly entertained” by Trump’s audacious tweets. Maher’s astonishment was palpable as he found out that Steele didn’t cast her vote for either Biden or Barack Obama in previous elections. Steele was quick to clarify, “I don’t love [Trump]. There’s a big difference in voting for someone and loving them.” She emphasized the importance of differentiating between politicians’ personal attributes and their policies. This recent revelation from Steele, combined with the ever-politicized climate, further underscores the need for transparency and candid discussions about our nation’s leaders. As the public digests Steele’s unsettling observations, questions regarding the competency of those in power remain at the forefront.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Questionable Accusations Highlighted in Trump’s Civil Fraud Trial</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/05/Trump-Trial-Defense/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Questionable Accusations Highlighted in Trump’s Civil Fraud Trial" /><published>2023-10-05T16:34:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-05T16:34:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/05/Trump-Trial-Defense</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/05/Trump-Trial-Defense/">&lt;p&gt;Former President Donald Trump once again showcased his unyielding spirit in the face of the New York civil fraud trial that many are describing as politically motivated. This Wednesday, Trump’s adept legal team persistently sought clarity from accountant Donald Bender, whose preparation of the financial statements is currently in the spotlight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The lawsuit, propelled by New York Attorney General Letitia James, accuses Trump and his renowned business of overstating his wealth in financial documents provided to financial institutions. Many observers see this as a politically charged move against the former president. In a striking revelation, Bender admitted that the Trump Organization hadn’t always been provided with comprehensive guidelines for these documents. Rather than accepting accountability for possible oversights, Bender tried to shift the blame elsewhere.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Defense attorney Jesus M. Suarez brilliantly highlighted a pivotal moment, referencing a pretrial video testimony. Bender, caught off guard, expressed doubt about having consulted with any specialists when forming Trump’s financial statements. The defense rightly pinpointed an overlooked detail about the size of Trump’s Trump Tower apartment, suggesting that the burden of this miscalculation should not fall squarely on the Trump Organization. In response, Bender appeared to backtrack, suggesting the oversight was a collective error.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the trial proceedings intensified, Judge Arthur Engoron seemed impatient with Trump’s defense team’s thorough line of questioning. In a surprising move, he attempted to expedite the questioning, which the defense rightfully argued would restrict their ability to adequately represent the former president.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This trial, perceived by many as an extension of political maneuvering, could have broad implications. Although Judge Engoron hastily ruled that Trump allegedly inflated the value of certain assets, Trump’s lawyers have launched an appeal. Many believe this ruling, which could jeopardize Trump’s ownership of properties like the Trump Tower, seems heavy-handed given the trial’s politically charged backdrop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Making headlines is Trump’s unwavering commitment to clearing his name. Despite being in the midst of his 2024 presidential campaign trail, Trump chose to be present at the trial. Outside the court, he voiced his concerns about the proceedings, describing James as “incompetent” and emphasizing his desire to shed light on the perceived injustices of the trial.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James was quick to counter, but her remarks came across as more of a rehearsed political statement than a genuine retort. She labeled Trump’s involvement as a “political stunt,” a claim that seems ironic given the nature of the lawsuit itself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump’s candid remarks outside the court, especially directed towards Engoron’s team, eventually led to a restraining order on his comments. In line with his commitment to transparency and fairness, Trump promptly complied by removing a post that was deemed offensive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the trial set to decide upon potential penalties of up to $250 million and possible restrictions on Trump’s business operations in New York, many see it as an attempt to sideline the former president. But as always, Trump remains resolute in the face of adversity.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Former President Donald Trump once again showcased his unyielding spirit in the face of the New York civil fraud trial that many are describing as politically motivated. This Wednesday, Trump’s adept legal team persistently sought clarity from accountant Donald Bender, whose preparation of the financial statements is currently in the spotlight. The lawsuit, propelled by New York Attorney General Letitia James, accuses Trump and his renowned business of overstating his wealth in financial documents provided to financial institutions. Many observers see this as a politically charged move against the former president. In a striking revelation, Bender admitted that the Trump Organization hadn’t always been provided with comprehensive guidelines for these documents. Rather than accepting accountability for possible oversights, Bender tried to shift the blame elsewhere. Defense attorney Jesus M. Suarez brilliantly highlighted a pivotal moment, referencing a pretrial video testimony. Bender, caught off guard, expressed doubt about having consulted with any specialists when forming Trump’s financial statements. The defense rightly pinpointed an overlooked detail about the size of Trump’s Trump Tower apartment, suggesting that the burden of this miscalculation should not fall squarely on the Trump Organization. In response, Bender appeared to backtrack, suggesting the oversight was a collective error. As the trial proceedings intensified, Judge Arthur Engoron seemed impatient with Trump’s defense team’s thorough line of questioning. In a surprising move, he attempted to expedite the questioning, which the defense rightfully argued would restrict their ability to adequately represent the former president. This trial, perceived by many as an extension of political maneuvering, could have broad implications. Although Judge Engoron hastily ruled that Trump allegedly inflated the value of certain assets, Trump’s lawyers have launched an appeal. Many believe this ruling, which could jeopardize Trump’s ownership of properties like the Trump Tower, seems heavy-handed given the trial’s politically charged backdrop. Making headlines is Trump’s unwavering commitment to clearing his name. Despite being in the midst of his 2024 presidential campaign trail, Trump chose to be present at the trial. Outside the court, he voiced his concerns about the proceedings, describing James as “incompetent” and emphasizing his desire to shed light on the perceived injustices of the trial. James was quick to counter, but her remarks came across as more of a rehearsed political statement than a genuine retort. She labeled Trump’s involvement as a “political stunt,” a claim that seems ironic given the nature of the lawsuit itself. Trump’s candid remarks outside the court, especially directed towards Engoron’s team, eventually led to a restraining order on his comments. In line with his commitment to transparency and fairness, Trump promptly complied by removing a post that was deemed offensive. With the trial set to decide upon potential penalties of up to $250 million and possible restrictions on Trump’s business operations in New York, many see it as an attempt to sideline the former president. But as always, Trump remains resolute in the face of adversity.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Decades-Long Mystery Resolved: ‘Happy Face’ Killer’s 8th Victim Named</title><link href="/news/2023/10/05/Happy-Face-Victim-Identified/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Decades-Long Mystery Resolved: ‘Happy Face’ Killer’s 8th Victim Named" /><published>2023-10-05T15:18:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-05T15:18:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/05/Happy-Face-Victim-Identified</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/05/Happy-Face-Victim-Identified/">&lt;p&gt;Florida investigators have cracked a long-standing mystery, identifying Suzanne Kjellenberg as the eighth victim of the infamous “Happy Face” serial killer, Keith Jesperson.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jesperson’s reign of terror spanned the 1990s. His moniker, “Happy Face,” was derived from the eerie smiley-face signature he left on letters sent to media outlets, where he chillingly detailed his crimes. These heinous acts were committed across various states, while he worked as a long-haul trucker.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a recent, unexpected interview with Okaloosa authorities at the Oregon State Penitentiary, Jesperson made a shocking confession. He revealed details about meeting Kjellenberg at a truck rest stop, stating she was on her way to Lake Tahoe and seeking a ride. The two journeyed together to Cairo, Georgia, even sharing a meal. Their trip took a dark turn on the return leg to Florida. After an altercation in the driver’s lounge of his truck, Jesperson brutally ended Kjellenberg’s life, then dumped her body along the interstate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jesperson had hinted at this killing previously. After his arrest in 1996, he spoke of murdering a woman named either “Susan” or “Suzette” in August 1994. It wasn’t until the Okaloosa Sheriff’s Office (OSO) made a formal announcement that Kjellenberg’s identity came to light, three decades post the tragic discovery of her remains by an inmate worker crew off Interstate 10.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;OSO’s relentless pursuit of the truth saw them partnering with Othram, a leading forensic genetic genealogy lab, in 2022. This collaboration aimed to identify the remains found 28 years earlier. After providing samples to Othram in 2023, a genealogical profile, funded by the National Missing and Unidentified Persons System (NamUs), delivered the leads that eventually named Suzanne Kjellenberg.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;District 1 Chief Medical Examiner Dr. Deanna Oleske mentioned the entire process took a mere six weeks. On the back of this breakthrough, authorities officially charged Jesperson with Kjellenberg’s murder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sheriff Eric Aden expressed his gratitude for the perseverance shown over the years. He stated, “Thanks to the tireless efforts of so many over so long, the remains of Suzanne Kjellenberg, the final unidentified victim of Jesperson’s cross-country murder sprees, can finally leave the Medical Examiner’s Office, and return home.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The harrowing tale of Keith Jesperson and his victims serves as a haunting reminder of the secrets that sometimes lay hidden for decades, only to resurface when least expected.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Florida investigators have cracked a long-standing mystery, identifying Suzanne Kjellenberg as the eighth victim of the infamous “Happy Face” serial killer, Keith Jesperson. Jesperson’s reign of terror spanned the 1990s. His moniker, “Happy Face,” was derived from the eerie smiley-face signature he left on letters sent to media outlets, where he chillingly detailed his crimes. These heinous acts were committed across various states, while he worked as a long-haul trucker. In a recent, unexpected interview with Okaloosa authorities at the Oregon State Penitentiary, Jesperson made a shocking confession. He revealed details about meeting Kjellenberg at a truck rest stop, stating she was on her way to Lake Tahoe and seeking a ride. The two journeyed together to Cairo, Georgia, even sharing a meal. Their trip took a dark turn on the return leg to Florida. After an altercation in the driver’s lounge of his truck, Jesperson brutally ended Kjellenberg’s life, then dumped her body along the interstate. Jesperson had hinted at this killing previously. After his arrest in 1996, he spoke of murdering a woman named either “Susan” or “Suzette” in August 1994. It wasn’t until the Okaloosa Sheriff’s Office (OSO) made a formal announcement that Kjellenberg’s identity came to light, three decades post the tragic discovery of her remains by an inmate worker crew off Interstate 10. OSO’s relentless pursuit of the truth saw them partnering with Othram, a leading forensic genetic genealogy lab, in 2022. This collaboration aimed to identify the remains found 28 years earlier. After providing samples to Othram in 2023, a genealogical profile, funded by the National Missing and Unidentified Persons System (NamUs), delivered the leads that eventually named Suzanne Kjellenberg. District 1 Chief Medical Examiner Dr. Deanna Oleske mentioned the entire process took a mere six weeks. On the back of this breakthrough, authorities officially charged Jesperson with Kjellenberg’s murder. Sheriff Eric Aden expressed his gratitude for the perseverance shown over the years. He stated, “Thanks to the tireless efforts of so many over so long, the remains of Suzanne Kjellenberg, the final unidentified victim of Jesperson’s cross-country murder sprees, can finally leave the Medical Examiner’s Office, and return home.” The harrowing tale of Keith Jesperson and his victims serves as a haunting reminder of the secrets that sometimes lay hidden for decades, only to resurface when least expected.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Biden’s Nomination Sparks Controversy: Ties to Hunter’s Former Colleague</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/05/Biden-Special-Counsel-Nomination/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Biden’s Nomination Sparks Controversy: Ties to Hunter’s Former Colleague" /><published>2023-10-05T13:42:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-05T13:42:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/05/Biden-Special-Counsel-Nomination</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/05/Biden-Special-Counsel-Nomination/">&lt;p&gt;In what some might call a controversial move, President Joe Biden has proposed Hampton Dellinger, a past colleague of Hunter Biden, for the prestigious role of White House Special Counsel. This nomination comes at a critical juncture, as the Office of the Special Counsel currently oversees federal whistleblower protections and the investigation of executive branch corruption, including the Justice Department’s inquiries into Hunter Biden.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dellinger shares more than just a professional connection with Hunter; both are Yale Law School graduates. They worked together at Boies Schiller Flexner, a law firm where Hunter Biden notably sought representation for Burisma Holdings. For those unaware, Burisma Holdings, a Ukrainian energy company, made payments of $83,000 per month to Hunter for his position on their board. There are allegations, backed by an FBI FD-1023 file and seconded by IRS whistleblower Joseph Ziegler, of bribes amounting to $5 million each for both Joe and Hunter Biden from a Burisma executive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It remains a matter of speculation whether Dellinger provided legal services for Burisma.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The implications of this nomination are weighty. If Dellinger secures the role, he would have jurisdiction over the investigations concerning any retaliation claims by the DOJ against two IRS whistleblowers who argued that the DOJ’s inquiry into Hunter Biden was politically influenced.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recent developments had seen Sen. Chuck Grassley (R-IA) and Rep. Jim Jordan (R-OH) calling on the current Special Counsel, Henry Kerner, to look into alleged meddling. They voiced concerns, stating, “Two IRS whistleblowers and their team faced removal from the Hunter Biden case, seemingly as a retaliation for their legal interactions with Congress.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adding fuel to the fire, Hunter Biden’s legal representative, Abbe Lowell, targeted these IRS whistleblowers a few months ago, hinting at possible legal action by the DOJ for releasing Hunter Biden’s tax details to the House Ways and Means Committee. This incident led to Hunter suing the IRS in September, claiming improper information disclosure by these whistleblowers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In an era where whistleblowing is deemed essential, IRS Commissioner Daniel Werfel emphasizes that IRS employees should be the first to highlight alarming issues. He envisions a proactive environment, encouraging a “see something, say something” approach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While President Biden’s nomination of Dellinger is under intense scrutiny given the intricate web of connections and ongoing investigations, the broader implication is clear: the forthcoming days in U.S. politics are set to be tumultuous and heavily watched.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In what some might call a controversial move, President Joe Biden has proposed Hampton Dellinger, a past colleague of Hunter Biden, for the prestigious role of White House Special Counsel. This nomination comes at a critical juncture, as the Office of the Special Counsel currently oversees federal whistleblower protections and the investigation of executive branch corruption, including the Justice Department’s inquiries into Hunter Biden. Dellinger shares more than just a professional connection with Hunter; both are Yale Law School graduates. They worked together at Boies Schiller Flexner, a law firm where Hunter Biden notably sought representation for Burisma Holdings. For those unaware, Burisma Holdings, a Ukrainian energy company, made payments of $83,000 per month to Hunter for his position on their board. There are allegations, backed by an FBI FD-1023 file and seconded by IRS whistleblower Joseph Ziegler, of bribes amounting to $5 million each for both Joe and Hunter Biden from a Burisma executive. It remains a matter of speculation whether Dellinger provided legal services for Burisma. The implications of this nomination are weighty. If Dellinger secures the role, he would have jurisdiction over the investigations concerning any retaliation claims by the DOJ against two IRS whistleblowers who argued that the DOJ’s inquiry into Hunter Biden was politically influenced. Recent developments had seen Sen. Chuck Grassley (R-IA) and Rep. Jim Jordan (R-OH) calling on the current Special Counsel, Henry Kerner, to look into alleged meddling. They voiced concerns, stating, “Two IRS whistleblowers and their team faced removal from the Hunter Biden case, seemingly as a retaliation for their legal interactions with Congress.” Adding fuel to the fire, Hunter Biden’s legal representative, Abbe Lowell, targeted these IRS whistleblowers a few months ago, hinting at possible legal action by the DOJ for releasing Hunter Biden’s tax details to the House Ways and Means Committee. This incident led to Hunter suing the IRS in September, claiming improper information disclosure by these whistleblowers. In an era where whistleblowing is deemed essential, IRS Commissioner Daniel Werfel emphasizes that IRS employees should be the first to highlight alarming issues. He envisions a proactive environment, encouraging a “see something, say something” approach. While President Biden’s nomination of Dellinger is under intense scrutiny given the intricate web of connections and ongoing investigations, the broader implication is clear: the forthcoming days in U.S. politics are set to be tumultuous and heavily watched.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump Dismisses Speaker of the House Buzz: ‘Eyes Set on the Presidency’</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/05/Trump-Speakership-Focus/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump Dismisses Speaker of the House Buzz: ‘Eyes Set on the Presidency’" /><published>2023-10-05T12:25:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-05T12:25:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/05/Trump-Speakership-Focus</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/05/Trump-Speakership-Focus/">&lt;p&gt;Amidst the swirl of political rumors, former President Donald Trump makes his stance clear, sidelining the possibility of eyeing the Speaker of the House role, and reaffirming his commitment to once again securing the presidency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During a candid interaction at the New York State courthouse, Trump quashed speculation surrounding his potential candidacy for the House’s top spot. “While numerous people have approached me regarding the speakership role,” Trump stated, “My overarching focus remains on the presidency and reigniting our national motto, ‘Make America Great Again’. Our nation is facing setbacks, and that is where my attention is drawn.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This public proclamation by Trump arises as the House of Representatives grapples with a significant shift in leadership dynamics. The recent ousting of former House Speaker Kevin McCarthy (R-CA) by a decisive vote of 216-210 has left the coveted position up for grabs. Notably, the vote saw eight of McCarthy’s fellow Republicans joining the Democrat caucus in the decision.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the position now vacant, some GOP frontrunners, such as Judiciary Chair Jim Jordan (R-OH), Majority Leader Steve Scalise (R-LA), and Rep. Tom Emmer (R-MN), the majority whip, are all seen as contenders. While Trump acknowledges the potential and capabilities of these “great people” within the Republican Party, he remains committed to his presidential aspirations. “When it comes to the race for president, my current lead by 50 points reflects my focus and where I believe my efforts are best suited,” Trump emphasized.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The recent tumult in the House reached fever pitch when McCarthy’s apparent belief in receiving support from Rep. Nancy Pelosi (D-CA) was left unmet. Addressing this political maneuvering, McCarthy expressed during a press conference, “I perceive today’s outcome as a strategic decision by the Democrats.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a statement prior to the vote, Pelosi underscored the established process, saying, “In this Congress, it is the onus of House Republicans to nominate and elect the Speaker on the Floor. At this juncture, I see no grounds to deviate from this longstanding tradition.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the political landscape continues its unpredictable trajectory, Trump’s renewed commitment to the presidential race undoubtedly sets the stage for what promises to be an intense political season ahead.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Amidst the swirl of political rumors, former President Donald Trump makes his stance clear, sidelining the possibility of eyeing the Speaker of the House role, and reaffirming his commitment to once again securing the presidency. During a candid interaction at the New York State courthouse, Trump quashed speculation surrounding his potential candidacy for the House’s top spot. “While numerous people have approached me regarding the speakership role,” Trump stated, “My overarching focus remains on the presidency and reigniting our national motto, ‘Make America Great Again’. Our nation is facing setbacks, and that is where my attention is drawn.” This public proclamation by Trump arises as the House of Representatives grapples with a significant shift in leadership dynamics. The recent ousting of former House Speaker Kevin McCarthy (R-CA) by a decisive vote of 216-210 has left the coveted position up for grabs. Notably, the vote saw eight of McCarthy’s fellow Republicans joining the Democrat caucus in the decision. With the position now vacant, some GOP frontrunners, such as Judiciary Chair Jim Jordan (R-OH), Majority Leader Steve Scalise (R-LA), and Rep. Tom Emmer (R-MN), the majority whip, are all seen as contenders. While Trump acknowledges the potential and capabilities of these “great people” within the Republican Party, he remains committed to his presidential aspirations. “When it comes to the race for president, my current lead by 50 points reflects my focus and where I believe my efforts are best suited,” Trump emphasized. The recent tumult in the House reached fever pitch when McCarthy’s apparent belief in receiving support from Rep. Nancy Pelosi (D-CA) was left unmet. Addressing this political maneuvering, McCarthy expressed during a press conference, “I perceive today’s outcome as a strategic decision by the Democrats.” In a statement prior to the vote, Pelosi underscored the established process, saying, “In this Congress, it is the onus of House Republicans to nominate and elect the Speaker on the Floor. At this juncture, I see no grounds to deviate from this longstanding tradition.” As the political landscape continues its unpredictable trajectory, Trump’s renewed commitment to the presidential race undoubtedly sets the stage for what promises to be an intense political season ahead.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Urgent Manhunt in Oklahoma: Suspect Wanted for Deputy Shooting and Stray Bullet Fatality</title><link href="/news/2023/10/05/Oklahoma-Manhunt/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Urgent Manhunt in Oklahoma: Suspect Wanted for Deputy Shooting and Stray Bullet Fatality" /><published>2023-10-05T11:15:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-05T11:15:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/05/Oklahoma-Manhunt</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/05/Oklahoma-Manhunt/">&lt;p&gt;A grave turn of events has gripped Oklahoma as the Oklahoma State Bureau of Investigations (OSBI), supported by multiple law enforcement agencies, spearheads a manhunt for Kameron Jenkins, a 25-year-old suspect. Jenkins is implicated in the alleged shooting of a Cleveland County deputy and the inadvertent killing of a motorist due to a stray bullet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The incident transpired during what started as a regular traffic stop, but quickly escalated into a chase. This altercation took place near the 60-mile marker of Interstate 35. The injured deputy, after being shot, was promptly airlifted to a nearby medical facility where he has been reported to be in stable condition. However, the incident took a tragic turn when an uninvolved motorist was fatally hit by a stray bullet, believed to be from the suspect’s firearm as he was shooting at the police.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kameron Jenkins, currently the focal point of this intensive manhunt, has been described by the OSBI as a Black man standing at approximately 6-foot-4, weighing around 170–200 pounds. Distinctive features include his black dreadlocks and brown eyes. The last outfit he was seen wearing was a white shirt. The severity of the situation is underlined by warnings from the Oklahoma State Highway Patrol, emphasizing that Jenkins is not only armed and dangerous but may also be carrying a semi-automatic weapon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Local news outlet FOX 25 in Oklahoma City shed further light, mentioning that Jenkins might be in a white trailer towed by a black pickup truck.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Diving deeper into Jenkins’ past, his criminal record presents several red flags. In 2015, he faced a maiming charge which was eventually dismissed. By 2017, he pleaded guilty to assault and battery charges. Not stopping there, Jenkins also entered guilty pleas for DUI and marijuana-related charges in 2019.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Law enforcement agencies are urging citizens to exercise extreme caution. The prevailing advice for anyone who spots Jenkins or has information about his whereabouts is to promptly call 911. Engaging with Jenkins or attempting to approach him can be perilous due to his considered armed and potentially volatile status.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This event has sent shockwaves across Oklahoma, with residents anxiously hoping for a swift resolution and the prevention of further incidents. With the collective efforts of the OSBI and other enforcement agencies, the goal remains to bring Jenkins into custody and ensure the safety of the public.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">A grave turn of events has gripped Oklahoma as the Oklahoma State Bureau of Investigations (OSBI), supported by multiple law enforcement agencies, spearheads a manhunt for Kameron Jenkins, a 25-year-old suspect. Jenkins is implicated in the alleged shooting of a Cleveland County deputy and the inadvertent killing of a motorist due to a stray bullet. The incident transpired during what started as a regular traffic stop, but quickly escalated into a chase. This altercation took place near the 60-mile marker of Interstate 35. The injured deputy, after being shot, was promptly airlifted to a nearby medical facility where he has been reported to be in stable condition. However, the incident took a tragic turn when an uninvolved motorist was fatally hit by a stray bullet, believed to be from the suspect’s firearm as he was shooting at the police. Kameron Jenkins, currently the focal point of this intensive manhunt, has been described by the OSBI as a Black man standing at approximately 6-foot-4, weighing around 170–200 pounds. Distinctive features include his black dreadlocks and brown eyes. The last outfit he was seen wearing was a white shirt. The severity of the situation is underlined by warnings from the Oklahoma State Highway Patrol, emphasizing that Jenkins is not only armed and dangerous but may also be carrying a semi-automatic weapon. Local news outlet FOX 25 in Oklahoma City shed further light, mentioning that Jenkins might be in a white trailer towed by a black pickup truck. Diving deeper into Jenkins’ past, his criminal record presents several red flags. In 2015, he faced a maiming charge which was eventually dismissed. By 2017, he pleaded guilty to assault and battery charges. Not stopping there, Jenkins also entered guilty pleas for DUI and marijuana-related charges in 2019. Law enforcement agencies are urging citizens to exercise extreme caution. The prevailing advice for anyone who spots Jenkins or has information about his whereabouts is to promptly call 911. Engaging with Jenkins or attempting to approach him can be perilous due to his considered armed and potentially volatile status. This event has sent shockwaves across Oklahoma, with residents anxiously hoping for a swift resolution and the prevention of further incidents. With the collective efforts of the OSBI and other enforcement agencies, the goal remains to bring Jenkins into custody and ensure the safety of the public.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">FBI’s Delicate Balancing Act: Monitoring Trump Supporters Ahead of 2024 Elections</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/05/FBI-Trump-Supporters/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="FBI’s Delicate Balancing Act: Monitoring Trump Supporters Ahead of 2024 Elections" /><published>2023-10-05T09:34:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-05T09:34:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/05/FBI-Trump-Supporters</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/05/FBI-Trump-Supporters/">&lt;p&gt;A recent Newsweek investigation has revealed that the FBI is discreetly monitoring supporters of former President Donald Trump in the lead-up to the 2024 elections. The move aims to prevent any significant civil disturbances similar to those witnessed on January 6, 2021.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The report, based on inputs from over a dozen current and former government officials specializing in terrorism, paints a picture of the ongoing domestic-security landscape. Furthermore, it evaluates the Biden administration’s approach to the issue they label as “domestic terrorism.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One anonymous FBI official highlighted the Bureau’s delicate task of ensuring safety without infringing upon Americans’ constitutional rights. The FBI’s concentrated focus on Trump supporters could inadvertently spark anti-government activities that the Bureau strives to mitigate. “It has to tread very carefully,” the official emphasized.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;President Biden’s vocal criticism of Trump supporters, coupled with his administration’s portrayal of them as threats to democracy, intensifies the ongoing debate. Such narratives could push certain groups to adopt more extreme measures, especially if they feel marginalized by the system. It’s a delicate balance, with heightened stakes on both sides.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Newsweek’s access to classified FBI and Department of Homeland Security data led them to question if “terrorism” is the most accurate term to describe these domestic issues. Equally, whether strategies developed in response to global extremist groups like al-Qaida are appropriate for addressing domestic concerns remains debatable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A notable revelation from the investigation was the FBI’s introduction of a new subcategory in 2022: “AGAAVE-Other.” This classification encompasses “domestic violent extremists” driven by anti-government or anti-authority motivations. It specifically covers those inclined to target individuals based on their perceived political affiliations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though not explicitly stated, insiders have confirmed that the “AGAAVE-Other” title relates to politically-motivated violence stemming from Trump supporters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the FBI has been clear in its stance. They stated that the AGAAVE threat umbrella covers a range of violent extremists, targeting both Republican and Democratic affiliations. This point reaffirms that the investigations are not solely focused on Trump supporters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet, another senior intelligence official candidly shared with Newsweek that Trump’s supporters represent a significant domestic threat. The FBI’s primary role is to address this potential for violence, they asserted. But the broader question of whether Trump and his followers pose a threat to the nation’s fabric is a complex one. The responsibility of answering that, they believe, falls on the entire country, not just the FBI.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">A recent Newsweek investigation has revealed that the FBI is discreetly monitoring supporters of former President Donald Trump in the lead-up to the 2024 elections. The move aims to prevent any significant civil disturbances similar to those witnessed on January 6, 2021. The report, based on inputs from over a dozen current and former government officials specializing in terrorism, paints a picture of the ongoing domestic-security landscape. Furthermore, it evaluates the Biden administration’s approach to the issue they label as “domestic terrorism.” One anonymous FBI official highlighted the Bureau’s delicate task of ensuring safety without infringing upon Americans’ constitutional rights. The FBI’s concentrated focus on Trump supporters could inadvertently spark anti-government activities that the Bureau strives to mitigate. “It has to tread very carefully,” the official emphasized. President Biden’s vocal criticism of Trump supporters, coupled with his administration’s portrayal of them as threats to democracy, intensifies the ongoing debate. Such narratives could push certain groups to adopt more extreme measures, especially if they feel marginalized by the system. It’s a delicate balance, with heightened stakes on both sides. Newsweek’s access to classified FBI and Department of Homeland Security data led them to question if “terrorism” is the most accurate term to describe these domestic issues. Equally, whether strategies developed in response to global extremist groups like al-Qaida are appropriate for addressing domestic concerns remains debatable. A notable revelation from the investigation was the FBI’s introduction of a new subcategory in 2022: “AGAAVE-Other.” This classification encompasses “domestic violent extremists” driven by anti-government or anti-authority motivations. It specifically covers those inclined to target individuals based on their perceived political affiliations. Though not explicitly stated, insiders have confirmed that the “AGAAVE-Other” title relates to politically-motivated violence stemming from Trump supporters. However, the FBI has been clear in its stance. They stated that the AGAAVE threat umbrella covers a range of violent extremists, targeting both Republican and Democratic affiliations. This point reaffirms that the investigations are not solely focused on Trump supporters. Yet, another senior intelligence official candidly shared with Newsweek that Trump’s supporters represent a significant domestic threat. The FBI’s primary role is to address this potential for violence, they asserted. But the broader question of whether Trump and his followers pose a threat to the nation’s fabric is a complex one. The responsibility of answering that, they believe, falls on the entire country, not just the FBI.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">California Teacher Arrested for Teaching While Intoxicated</title><link href="/news/2023/10/05/Drunk-Teacher-Arrested/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="California Teacher Arrested for Teaching While Intoxicated" /><published>2023-10-05T08:24:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-05T08:24:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/05/Drunk-Teacher-Arrested</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/05/Drunk-Teacher-Arrested/">&lt;p&gt;A shocking incident at Nuestro Elementary School in Live Oak, California, has drawn considerable attention and concern. Wendy Munson, 57, a second-grade teacher at the school, was arrested on charges of teaching while under the influence of alcohol.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Responding to a report on Monday morning, sheriff’s deputies found Munson visibly impaired during her teaching hours. Following this discovery, she was subjected to a sobriety test which she subsequently failed. Munson was then arrested at approximately 8:20 a.m. and charged with driving with a blood alcohol content exceeding .08 percent, drunk driving, and child abuse with potential for severe bodily injury, as outlined in a Sutter County Sheriff’s Department press release.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The alarming incident came to light when a co-worker at the school contacted local law enforcement. The arresting officers stated that when they arrived at the scene, Munson was actively teaching her class. It was later revealed that her blood alcohol level was nearly double the legal limit, even two hours after the initial interaction with the deputies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Baljinder Dhillon, Nuestro Elementary School District Superintendent, promptly addressed the matter by sending a letter to parents, assuring them of their children’s safety. He mentioned that Munson was taken into custody without any disturbances, ensuring that the students did not witness the unsettling arrest. The letter also highlighted the school’s proactive approach by stating, “Your 2nd graders will have a long-term substitute. Our students’ safety and well-being remain our highest priority.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kaitlynn Conley, a concerned parent, expressed her disbelief in an interview with CBS News. “I thought it was crazy,” she stated. Adding her perspective on Munson’s actions, she said, “I think she should’ve called out of work. I know people have fun weekends, but that was definitely not okay as an educator.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to these reports, the sheriff’s office confirmed the existence of footage capturing Munson driving to school in her inebriated state.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wendy Munson’s arraignment is set for 3 p.m. Wednesday. As of now, there is no confirmation regarding her legal representation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The incident at Nuestro Elementary underscores the need for schools to maintain strict safety and professional standards, ensuring an optimal environment for both students and staff.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">A shocking incident at Nuestro Elementary School in Live Oak, California, has drawn considerable attention and concern. Wendy Munson, 57, a second-grade teacher at the school, was arrested on charges of teaching while under the influence of alcohol. Responding to a report on Monday morning, sheriff’s deputies found Munson visibly impaired during her teaching hours. Following this discovery, she was subjected to a sobriety test which she subsequently failed. Munson was then arrested at approximately 8:20 a.m. and charged with driving with a blood alcohol content exceeding .08 percent, drunk driving, and child abuse with potential for severe bodily injury, as outlined in a Sutter County Sheriff’s Department press release. The alarming incident came to light when a co-worker at the school contacted local law enforcement. The arresting officers stated that when they arrived at the scene, Munson was actively teaching her class. It was later revealed that her blood alcohol level was nearly double the legal limit, even two hours after the initial interaction with the deputies. Baljinder Dhillon, Nuestro Elementary School District Superintendent, promptly addressed the matter by sending a letter to parents, assuring them of their children’s safety. He mentioned that Munson was taken into custody without any disturbances, ensuring that the students did not witness the unsettling arrest. The letter also highlighted the school’s proactive approach by stating, “Your 2nd graders will have a long-term substitute. Our students’ safety and well-being remain our highest priority.” Kaitlynn Conley, a concerned parent, expressed her disbelief in an interview with CBS News. “I thought it was crazy,” she stated. Adding her perspective on Munson’s actions, she said, “I think she should’ve called out of work. I know people have fun weekends, but that was definitely not okay as an educator.” In addition to these reports, the sheriff’s office confirmed the existence of footage capturing Munson driving to school in her inebriated state. Wendy Munson’s arraignment is set for 3 p.m. Wednesday. As of now, there is no confirmation regarding her legal representation. The incident at Nuestro Elementary underscores the need for schools to maintain strict safety and professional standards, ensuring an optimal environment for both students and staff.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Rep. Steve Scalise Jumps into the Race for House Speaker</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/05/Scalise-Speaker-Bid/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rep. Steve Scalise Jumps into the Race for House Speaker" /><published>2023-10-05T07:19:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-05T07:19:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/05/Scalise-Speaker-Bid</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/05/Scalise-Speaker-Bid/">&lt;p&gt;In a significant development in the political arena, Rep. Steve Scalise (R-LA) has declared his intent to run for the Speaker of the House. The House Majority Leader made the announcement on Wednesday, expressing that he seeks the nomination with “a strong sense of responsibility and purpose.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Scalise, a prominent figure from Louisiana, enjoys considerable support and affection from his fellow lawmakers. His announcement places him as a leading contender for the esteemed position. Many in the political circles remember Scalise for his tragic injury in 2017 when he was shot during a practice for a Republican baseball team. His resilience post the injury, including an extended recovery period and ongoing health challenges, is often viewed as a testament to his commitment to public service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Congressman’s credentials are impressive, having served as the Republican Whip for nearly ten years. He was also the Chairman of the Republican Conservative Committee (RSC), recognized as the most extensive conservative group within the House. The current chair of the RSC, Rep. Kevin Hern (R-OK), is speculated to join the race too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The dynamics of Scalise’s bid are fascinating, especially considering the recent events within the House Republican Conference. Rep. Kevin McCarthy’s (R-CA) recent ousting from the top House position has set the stage for new leadership. Despite Scalise and McCarthy showcasing a publicly amicable relationship, they weren’t particularly close allies. In crucial situations, McCarthy often leaned on Rep. Garrett Graves (R-LA) and Speaker Pro Tem Patrick McHenry (R-NC) instead of top deputies like Scalise and Majority Whip Tom Emmer (R-MN). This distance from McCarthy might turn out to be a strategic advantage for Scalise in the upcoming Speaker race.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, Scalise’s health might be a point of consideration for some colleagues. The Congressman recently shared the distressing news of a cancer diagnosis. While this could raise concerns about his ability to shoulder the demanding role, many peers have lauded his decision to run for the position.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Jim Jordan (R-OH) has also expressed his intent to vie for the Speaker post, adding more intrigue to the unfolding political drama.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the coming days, as the race for the Speaker of the House intensifies, Scalise’s leadership qualities, experience, and resilience will undoubtedly be at the forefront of discussions. His entry has certainly set the stage for a captivating contest.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a significant development in the political arena, Rep. Steve Scalise (R-LA) has declared his intent to run for the Speaker of the House. The House Majority Leader made the announcement on Wednesday, expressing that he seeks the nomination with “a strong sense of responsibility and purpose.” Scalise, a prominent figure from Louisiana, enjoys considerable support and affection from his fellow lawmakers. His announcement places him as a leading contender for the esteemed position. Many in the political circles remember Scalise for his tragic injury in 2017 when he was shot during a practice for a Republican baseball team. His resilience post the injury, including an extended recovery period and ongoing health challenges, is often viewed as a testament to his commitment to public service. The Congressman’s credentials are impressive, having served as the Republican Whip for nearly ten years. He was also the Chairman of the Republican Conservative Committee (RSC), recognized as the most extensive conservative group within the House. The current chair of the RSC, Rep. Kevin Hern (R-OK), is speculated to join the race too. The dynamics of Scalise’s bid are fascinating, especially considering the recent events within the House Republican Conference. Rep. Kevin McCarthy’s (R-CA) recent ousting from the top House position has set the stage for new leadership. Despite Scalise and McCarthy showcasing a publicly amicable relationship, they weren’t particularly close allies. In crucial situations, McCarthy often leaned on Rep. Garrett Graves (R-LA) and Speaker Pro Tem Patrick McHenry (R-NC) instead of top deputies like Scalise and Majority Whip Tom Emmer (R-MN). This distance from McCarthy might turn out to be a strategic advantage for Scalise in the upcoming Speaker race. However, Scalise’s health might be a point of consideration for some colleagues. The Congressman recently shared the distressing news of a cancer diagnosis. While this could raise concerns about his ability to shoulder the demanding role, many peers have lauded his decision to run for the position. Rep. Jim Jordan (R-OH) has also expressed his intent to vie for the Speaker post, adding more intrigue to the unfolding political drama. In the coming days, as the race for the Speaker of the House intensifies, Scalise’s leadership qualities, experience, and resilience will undoubtedly be at the forefront of discussions. His entry has certainly set the stage for a captivating contest.</summary></entry></feed>