<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-09-07T04:19:40-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/09/07/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-09-07T04:19:40-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-07T04:19:40-04:00</updated><id>/2023/09/07/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/07/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Neglecting Parental Rights - Chino Valley’s Controversial Notification Policy</title><link href="/news/2023/09/06/Parental-Notification-Policy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Neglecting Parental Rights - Chino Valley’s Controversial Notification Policy" /><published>2023-09-06T19:41:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-06T19:41:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/06/Parental-Notification-Policy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/06/Parental-Notification-Policy/">&lt;p&gt;It’s common sense: Parents have the right to know what’s happening in their children’s lives, especially when it involves significant decisions at school. But the Chino Valley Unified School District thinks otherwise, as evidenced by their new policy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Parental Rights Overlooked&lt;/strong&gt;
The Chino Valley Unified School District has come under fire with a recent policy, aiming to notify parents only if students specifically request a change in gender pronouns or identities. Thankfully, a California judge, showing a profound understanding of the importance of parental involvement, issued a temporary restraining order against this misguided attempt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Attorney General Rob Bonta may argue that the policy “rightfully upholds the state rights of our LGBTQ+ student community,” but what about the fundamental rights of parents? Aren’t they stakeholders in their children’s well-being, too?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dangers of Non-Disclosure&lt;/strong&gt;
The notion that the district could be putting the well-being of transgender and gender-nonconforming students at risk is not in question. The real peril, however, lies in sidelining parents from these crucial discussions. Such decisions about gender identity can have deep emotional, psychological, and even medical implications. Parents should be allies in these journeys, not kept in the dark.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bonta alleges dangers from “forced disclosures,” but what about the dangers of keeping secrets? Many families offer safe environments where children can freely discuss their identities. Assuming all parents are adversaries can be just as damaging.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Widespread Concerns&lt;/strong&gt;
Bonta’s press releases underline the “threats” posed by policies like Chino Valley’s. But it’s critical to note that several districts, such as Anderson Union High School and Murrieta Valley Unified, are also under scrutiny for similar protocols. Why is there a push for secrecy? It raises the question: What’s the bigger agenda at play?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conclusion&lt;/strong&gt;
The ongoing battle around parental notification, with a preliminary injunction hearing set for Oct. 13, promises to be contentious. But one thing remains crystal clear: sidelining parents from the narratives of their children’s lives is a dangerous game. It’s high time school districts recognize this and prioritize open, transparent dialogues that involve all stakeholders.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">It’s common sense: Parents have the right to know what’s happening in their children’s lives, especially when it involves significant decisions at school. But the Chino Valley Unified School District thinks otherwise, as evidenced by their new policy. Parental Rights Overlooked The Chino Valley Unified School District has come under fire with a recent policy, aiming to notify parents only if students specifically request a change in gender pronouns or identities. Thankfully, a California judge, showing a profound understanding of the importance of parental involvement, issued a temporary restraining order against this misguided attempt. Attorney General Rob Bonta may argue that the policy “rightfully upholds the state rights of our LGBTQ+ student community,” but what about the fundamental rights of parents? Aren’t they stakeholders in their children’s well-being, too? Dangers of Non-Disclosure The notion that the district could be putting the well-being of transgender and gender-nonconforming students at risk is not in question. The real peril, however, lies in sidelining parents from these crucial discussions. Such decisions about gender identity can have deep emotional, psychological, and even medical implications. Parents should be allies in these journeys, not kept in the dark. Bonta alleges dangers from “forced disclosures,” but what about the dangers of keeping secrets? Many families offer safe environments where children can freely discuss their identities. Assuming all parents are adversaries can be just as damaging. Widespread Concerns Bonta’s press releases underline the “threats” posed by policies like Chino Valley’s. But it’s critical to note that several districts, such as Anderson Union High School and Murrieta Valley Unified, are also under scrutiny for similar protocols. Why is there a push for secrecy? It raises the question: What’s the bigger agenda at play? Conclusion The ongoing battle around parental notification, with a preliminary injunction hearing set for Oct. 13, promises to be contentious. But one thing remains crystal clear: sidelining parents from the narratives of their children’s lives is a dangerous game. It’s high time school districts recognize this and prioritize open, transparent dialogues that involve all stakeholders.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">From Red Carpets to Car Interiors - The Bleak Reality of Striking Hollywood Workers</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/06/Hollywood-Strikes/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="From Red Carpets to Car Interiors - The Bleak Reality of Striking Hollywood Workers" /><published>2023-09-06T18:32:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-06T18:32:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/06/Hollywood-Strikes</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/06/Hollywood-Strikes/">&lt;p&gt;As the long-drawn Hollywood strikes remain unresolved, many actors and writers find themselves in dire circumstances. The growing repercussions are evident, with numerous workers facing evictions, and in some unfortunate cases, resorting to living in their cars.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Charitable entities that have been aiding the striking Hollywood community with grants reported a rising wave of housing issues impacting not just the actors and writers, but also the crew members who often work behind the scenes. The detailed account from &lt;em&gt;The Hollywood Reporter&lt;/em&gt; reflects the far-reaching effects of the strikes, which have rendered thousands, from lighting experts to makeup artists, unemployed for extended durations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the glitz and glamour of Hollywood often overshadow the struggles of non-celebrity actors, the strikes have been a financial catastrophe for many. Actor David Baach opened up to &lt;em&gt;The Hollywood Reporter&lt;/em&gt; about his hardships, sharing, “The strike has had a massive impact on my housing situation. I worked one day in May, and since then all the work has stopped. I’ve almost depleted my entire savings, and I’ve faced eviction.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Leading Hollywood charities, the Entertainment Community Fund and the Motion Picture &amp;amp; Television Fund (MPTF), disclosed the grim realities workers are facing. Bob Beitcher, MPTF president, and CEO stated, “People are becoming unhoused, evicted, and even living in their cars, sometimes with their families.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although the MPTF is extending a helping hand by offering $1,500 grants, such sums are meager in cities as pricey as Los Angeles, leaving many still grappling with unpaid bills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The impasse between actors, writers, and Hollywood studios shows no sign of a resolution, with both parties unwavering on pivotal negotiating points, especially around streaming compensation. As a result, TV and movie productions across the nation have almost come to a standstill. This stalemate doesn’t only impact the film industry, but also reverberates through local economies from coast to coast.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">As the long-drawn Hollywood strikes remain unresolved, many actors and writers find themselves in dire circumstances. The growing repercussions are evident, with numerous workers facing evictions, and in some unfortunate cases, resorting to living in their cars. Charitable entities that have been aiding the striking Hollywood community with grants reported a rising wave of housing issues impacting not just the actors and writers, but also the crew members who often work behind the scenes. The detailed account from The Hollywood Reporter reflects the far-reaching effects of the strikes, which have rendered thousands, from lighting experts to makeup artists, unemployed for extended durations. While the glitz and glamour of Hollywood often overshadow the struggles of non-celebrity actors, the strikes have been a financial catastrophe for many. Actor David Baach opened up to The Hollywood Reporter about his hardships, sharing, “The strike has had a massive impact on my housing situation. I worked one day in May, and since then all the work has stopped. I’ve almost depleted my entire savings, and I’ve faced eviction.” Leading Hollywood charities, the Entertainment Community Fund and the Motion Picture &amp;amp; Television Fund (MPTF), disclosed the grim realities workers are facing. Bob Beitcher, MPTF president, and CEO stated, “People are becoming unhoused, evicted, and even living in their cars, sometimes with their families.” Although the MPTF is extending a helping hand by offering $1,500 grants, such sums are meager in cities as pricey as Los Angeles, leaving many still grappling with unpaid bills. The impasse between actors, writers, and Hollywood studios shows no sign of a resolution, with both parties unwavering on pivotal negotiating points, especially around streaming compensation. As a result, TV and movie productions across the nation have almost come to a standstill. This stalemate doesn’t only impact the film industry, but also reverberates through local economies from coast to coast.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hunter Biden’s Legal Woes Deepen - A Stain on the Biden Presidency?</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/06/Hunter-Biden-Controversy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hunter Biden’s Legal Woes Deepen - A Stain on the Biden Presidency?" /><published>2023-09-06T17:19:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-06T17:19:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/06/Hunter-Biden-Controversy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/06/Hunter-Biden-Controversy/">&lt;p&gt;Hunter Biden, already a controversial figure due to past indiscretions, is once again under the legal microscope, casting a shadow on the Biden presidency. As Special Counsel David Weiss’ team gears up to potentially indict him on federal gun charges, many are left wondering if this is a reflection of deeper issues within the Biden administration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A plea deal that would have seemingly swept Hunter’s legal troubles under the rug crumbled recently. The strategy to plead guilty to two misdemeanor counts of tax evasion, potentially shielding him from a more severe felony gun charge, hit a brick wall. U.S. District Judge Maryellen Noreika saw through what many are calling a “sweetheart deal,” rejecting it as potentially unconstitutional and deviating from standard legal practices. Such maneuverings raise concerns about preferential treatment for the President’s son.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Attorney General Merrick Garland’s decision to appoint Weiss as the special counsel overseeing the Hunter Biden saga is viewed by some as a last-ditch attempt to manage the spiraling situation. Given the ties between the Bidens and various members of the establishment, can the public expect a truly unbiased investigation?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The roots of Hunter’s legal troubles trace back to 2018 when he seemingly acted with recklessness. A firearm owned by him was discovered discarded near a school, and the connection of this incident to Hunter’s past, including his Navy discharge due to a positive cocaine test in 2014, paints a portrait of carelessness at best and criminality at worst.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adding to the controversy, his denial of drug use on a firearm transaction form blatantly contrasts with his known history, suggesting either a profound lack of judgement or an audacious belief in his invincibility due to his familial ties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As this legal drama unfolds, it’s not just Hunter Biden’s reputation that’s on the line. The integrity and credibility of President Biden’s administration face public scrutiny. The question many are asking: If the President cannot manage the actions and ethics of his own family, how can the nation trust him to lead with clarity, honesty, and integrity?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Hunter Biden, already a controversial figure due to past indiscretions, is once again under the legal microscope, casting a shadow on the Biden presidency. As Special Counsel David Weiss’ team gears up to potentially indict him on federal gun charges, many are left wondering if this is a reflection of deeper issues within the Biden administration. A plea deal that would have seemingly swept Hunter’s legal troubles under the rug crumbled recently. The strategy to plead guilty to two misdemeanor counts of tax evasion, potentially shielding him from a more severe felony gun charge, hit a brick wall. U.S. District Judge Maryellen Noreika saw through what many are calling a “sweetheart deal,” rejecting it as potentially unconstitutional and deviating from standard legal practices. Such maneuverings raise concerns about preferential treatment for the President’s son. Attorney General Merrick Garland’s decision to appoint Weiss as the special counsel overseeing the Hunter Biden saga is viewed by some as a last-ditch attempt to manage the spiraling situation. Given the ties between the Bidens and various members of the establishment, can the public expect a truly unbiased investigation? The roots of Hunter’s legal troubles trace back to 2018 when he seemingly acted with recklessness. A firearm owned by him was discovered discarded near a school, and the connection of this incident to Hunter’s past, including his Navy discharge due to a positive cocaine test in 2014, paints a portrait of carelessness at best and criminality at worst. Adding to the controversy, his denial of drug use on a firearm transaction form blatantly contrasts with his known history, suggesting either a profound lack of judgement or an audacious belief in his invincibility due to his familial ties. As this legal drama unfolds, it’s not just Hunter Biden’s reputation that’s on the line. The integrity and credibility of President Biden’s administration face public scrutiny. The question many are asking: If the President cannot manage the actions and ethics of his own family, how can the nation trust him to lead with clarity, honesty, and integrity?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Rand Paul Slams Reintroduced D.C. Mask Mandates - Claims ‘Crime Against Children’</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/06/Mask-Mandate-Critique/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rand Paul Slams Reintroduced D.C. Mask Mandates - Claims ‘Crime Against Children’" /><published>2023-09-06T15:57:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-06T15:57:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/06/Mask-Mandate-Critique</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/06/Mask-Mandate-Critique/">&lt;p&gt;Sen. Rand Paul (R-KY) has thrown a spotlight on the reintroduced school mask mandates in Washington, D.C., terming them as a “crime against children.” The renewed debate over mask mandates and vaccine policies, especially for the youth, continues to stir emotions and cause friction in the political landscape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During his recent stint on FNC’s “Jesse Watters Primetime,” Sen. Paul conveyed his strong disapproval of the measures. In a direct response to the mention that a D.C. elementary school had reverted to masks after a few kids tested positive, he emphasized that children should not be made to wear masks again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Kentucky Republican’s concerns go beyond just mask mandates. He highlighted an ongoing tussle with the Senate physician over the proposal to administer three vaccines to Senate pages, many of whom are just 18 years old. In a compelling argument, Sen. Paul pointed out that no healthy child in the U.S. has succumbed to COVID-19, a statement that he believes underscores the irrelevance of pushing multiple vaccines onto the young population.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Delving further into the potential risks, Sen. Paul mentioned the heightened incidence of heart inflammation in children subjected to multiple vaccines. Branding the push for three vaccines as “malpractice,” the Senator expressed his commitment to countering this move, especially since, in his opinion, it goes against sound medical advice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The remarks by Sen. Paul provide a vivid illustration of the dilemmas and disagreements that continue to permeate discussions around COVID-19 health policies. With concerns on both sides of the aisle regarding the long-term effects of these measures on children, it’s clear that this debate will remain at the forefront of public discourse for some time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reintroduction of mask mandates and vaccine policies, especially for the young demographic, has rekindled debates and further divided opinions. As political leaders, health experts, and communities grapple with the best way forward, the ultimate priority should remain the health and well-being of all citizens.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Sen. Rand Paul (R-KY) has thrown a spotlight on the reintroduced school mask mandates in Washington, D.C., terming them as a “crime against children.” The renewed debate over mask mandates and vaccine policies, especially for the youth, continues to stir emotions and cause friction in the political landscape. During his recent stint on FNC’s “Jesse Watters Primetime,” Sen. Paul conveyed his strong disapproval of the measures. In a direct response to the mention that a D.C. elementary school had reverted to masks after a few kids tested positive, he emphasized that children should not be made to wear masks again. The Kentucky Republican’s concerns go beyond just mask mandates. He highlighted an ongoing tussle with the Senate physician over the proposal to administer three vaccines to Senate pages, many of whom are just 18 years old. In a compelling argument, Sen. Paul pointed out that no healthy child in the U.S. has succumbed to COVID-19, a statement that he believes underscores the irrelevance of pushing multiple vaccines onto the young population. Delving further into the potential risks, Sen. Paul mentioned the heightened incidence of heart inflammation in children subjected to multiple vaccines. Branding the push for three vaccines as “malpractice,” the Senator expressed his commitment to countering this move, especially since, in his opinion, it goes against sound medical advice. The remarks by Sen. Paul provide a vivid illustration of the dilemmas and disagreements that continue to permeate discussions around COVID-19 health policies. With concerns on both sides of the aisle regarding the long-term effects of these measures on children, it’s clear that this debate will remain at the forefront of public discourse for some time. The reintroduction of mask mandates and vaccine policies, especially for the young demographic, has rekindled debates and further divided opinions. As political leaders, health experts, and communities grapple with the best way forward, the ultimate priority should remain the health and well-being of all citizens.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Sharon Osbourne Reveals All - Unmasking the Facelift Fiasco</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/06/Osbournes-Plastic-Surgery/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sharon Osbourne Reveals All - Unmasking the Facelift Fiasco" /><published>2023-09-06T14:52:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-06T14:52:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/06/Osbournes-Plastic-Surgery</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/06/Osbournes-Plastic-Surgery/">&lt;p&gt;In the glitz and glamour of Hollywood, the conversation around cosmetic procedures can be a muddled one. But leave it to Sharon Osbourne, the straight-shooting TV personality, to clear the air.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Teaming up with her iconic family for the return of “The Osbournes Podcast,” premiering on September 12, Osbourne pulls no punches discussing her own experiences going under the knife. Comparing these cosmetic procedures to car tune-ups, Sharon’s son, Jack Osbourne, light-heartedly remarked that his mom goes in for a “tuneup” every “5,000 miles.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the jokes, Sharon stresses the importance of honesty surrounding plastic surgery. After a botched facelift in 2021 left her physically and emotionally traumatized, she advocates for understanding the risks that come with these procedures. Her experience, unfortunately, led to asymmetrical eyes, scarring, and additional surgery to correct the misstep.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In candid reflections, Osbourne shared how the ordeal played out with the surgeon she trusted. “I looked like a Cyclops. It was the worst thing ever,” she stated, emphasizing the importance of researching procedures thoroughly and being prepared for any outcome. No matter how skilled the surgeon, nothing is guaranteed in the world of plastic surgery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sharon’s openness resonates strongly with many, including her own daughter, Kelly Osbourne. Although Kelly admires her mom’s confidence, she remains hesitant about undergoing procedures herself, especially after giving birth in 2022.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For Sharon, the decision to go under the knife is deeply personal, and the stigma often associated with it is unwarranted. With cosmetic surgery now a worldwide phenomenon, she encourages individuals to embrace their choices and reject the shame often cast upon them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a world where age-defying treatments are evolving rapidly, perhaps the most valuable takeaway from Sharon’s story is not what you choose to do with your body, but how you choose to own and express those decisions.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">In the glitz and glamour of Hollywood, the conversation around cosmetic procedures can be a muddled one. But leave it to Sharon Osbourne, the straight-shooting TV personality, to clear the air. Teaming up with her iconic family for the return of “The Osbournes Podcast,” premiering on September 12, Osbourne pulls no punches discussing her own experiences going under the knife. Comparing these cosmetic procedures to car tune-ups, Sharon’s son, Jack Osbourne, light-heartedly remarked that his mom goes in for a “tuneup” every “5,000 miles.” Despite the jokes, Sharon stresses the importance of honesty surrounding plastic surgery. After a botched facelift in 2021 left her physically and emotionally traumatized, she advocates for understanding the risks that come with these procedures. Her experience, unfortunately, led to asymmetrical eyes, scarring, and additional surgery to correct the misstep. In candid reflections, Osbourne shared how the ordeal played out with the surgeon she trusted. “I looked like a Cyclops. It was the worst thing ever,” she stated, emphasizing the importance of researching procedures thoroughly and being prepared for any outcome. No matter how skilled the surgeon, nothing is guaranteed in the world of plastic surgery. Sharon’s openness resonates strongly with many, including her own daughter, Kelly Osbourne. Although Kelly admires her mom’s confidence, she remains hesitant about undergoing procedures herself, especially after giving birth in 2022. For Sharon, the decision to go under the knife is deeply personal, and the stigma often associated with it is unwarranted. With cosmetic surgery now a worldwide phenomenon, she encourages individuals to embrace their choices and reject the shame often cast upon them. In a world where age-defying treatments are evolving rapidly, perhaps the most valuable takeaway from Sharon’s story is not what you choose to do with your body, but how you choose to own and express those decisions.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Tuberville’s Standoff - Military Promotions Held Hostage Over Abortion Policy</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/06/Tuberville-Abortion-Policy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tuberville’s Standoff - Military Promotions Held Hostage Over Abortion Policy" /><published>2023-09-06T13:43:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-06T13:43:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/06/Tuberville-Abortion-Policy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/06/Tuberville-Abortion-Policy/">&lt;p&gt;In a remarkable show of dissent, Sen. Tommy Tuberville, R-Ala., firmly signals his intention to thwart military promotions, raising alarms over the Pentagon’s newly introduced abortion policy. The move, which is seen as a direct challenge to President Joe Biden’s leadership, underscores the heated battle lines on Capitol Hill over taxpayer-funded abortion perks in the military.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tuberville, in his conversation with Newsmax, clarifies that his primary concern isn’t military readiness, as some have suggested, but the legislative overreach by the Biden administration. Labeling the President as “Pinocchio Joe”, Tuberville denounces the apparent trend of “legislating from the White House” and emphasizes that any significant policy change regarding abortion within the military domain should necessitate a Senate vote.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The policy that has become the bone of contention involves the Pentagon extending three weeks of administrative leave, along with travel and transportation allowances, to those seeking abortion. An apparent incentive, as critics argue, to promote abortions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tuberville’s skepticism, shared by many, arises from the sudden change in policy without any evident grievances or complaints against the prior regulations. By his account, the rationale given for the shift - readiness and recruitment - seems unfounded, especially when juxtaposed with the fact that there were no qualms regarding the old policy for over three decades.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Supporting his stance, Tuberville cites that a significant 60% of Americans, encompassing both Democrats and Republicans, are against diverting taxpayer money towards abortion. This majority sentiment indicates that Tuberville’s objections might not be just personal but resonate with a broader section of the population.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it’s not just abortion policies that have the Senator concerned. The alleged influx of ‘woke’ policies into the military, which he believes began during the Obama era, threatens military readiness more than any of his holds. His assertion that the military should primarily focus on recruiting “the best of the best” reflects his worries about the dilution of standards and the potential impact on national security.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In essence, Sen. Tuberville’s standoff serves as a grim reminder of the widening chasms within the American political landscape, particularly on sensitive issues like abortion. Whether or not this deadlock will be resolved amicably remains to be seen. But for now, Tuberville stands firm, championing the voice of many who believe that certain policy changes should not be dictated by the White House but instead be a product of bipartisan consensus.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a remarkable show of dissent, Sen. Tommy Tuberville, R-Ala., firmly signals his intention to thwart military promotions, raising alarms over the Pentagon’s newly introduced abortion policy. The move, which is seen as a direct challenge to President Joe Biden’s leadership, underscores the heated battle lines on Capitol Hill over taxpayer-funded abortion perks in the military. Tuberville, in his conversation with Newsmax, clarifies that his primary concern isn’t military readiness, as some have suggested, but the legislative overreach by the Biden administration. Labeling the President as “Pinocchio Joe”, Tuberville denounces the apparent trend of “legislating from the White House” and emphasizes that any significant policy change regarding abortion within the military domain should necessitate a Senate vote. The policy that has become the bone of contention involves the Pentagon extending three weeks of administrative leave, along with travel and transportation allowances, to those seeking abortion. An apparent incentive, as critics argue, to promote abortions. Tuberville’s skepticism, shared by many, arises from the sudden change in policy without any evident grievances or complaints against the prior regulations. By his account, the rationale given for the shift - readiness and recruitment - seems unfounded, especially when juxtaposed with the fact that there were no qualms regarding the old policy for over three decades. Supporting his stance, Tuberville cites that a significant 60% of Americans, encompassing both Democrats and Republicans, are against diverting taxpayer money towards abortion. This majority sentiment indicates that Tuberville’s objections might not be just personal but resonate with a broader section of the population. However, it’s not just abortion policies that have the Senator concerned. The alleged influx of ‘woke’ policies into the military, which he believes began during the Obama era, threatens military readiness more than any of his holds. His assertion that the military should primarily focus on recruiting “the best of the best” reflects his worries about the dilution of standards and the potential impact on national security. In essence, Sen. Tuberville’s standoff serves as a grim reminder of the widening chasms within the American political landscape, particularly on sensitive issues like abortion. Whether or not this deadlock will be resolved amicably remains to be seen. But for now, Tuberville stands firm, championing the voice of many who believe that certain policy changes should not be dictated by the White House but instead be a product of bipartisan consensus.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Rolling Stones Rock London - Unveil ‘Hackney Diamonds’</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/06/Rolling-Stones-New-Album/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Rolling Stones Rock London - Unveil ‘Hackney Diamonds’" /><published>2023-09-06T12:59:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-06T12:59:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/06/Rolling-Stones-New-Album</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/06/Rolling-Stones-New-Album/">&lt;p&gt;The streets of London’s Hackney district were thrumming with excitement as The Rolling Stones geared up to announce their brand new album, “Hackney Diamonds.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By early Wednesday, a wave of devoted fans began gathering outside the historical Hackney Empire. The illustrious venue has hosted legends like Charlie Chaplin and Stan Laurel in its storied past. Adding to the day’s allure, none other than “The Tonight Show” host Jimmy Fallon was set to interview the iconic trio - Mick Jagger, Keith Richards, and Ronnie Wood - in a much-anticipated livestream event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Inside the Hackney Empire, a venue steeped in history, the members of the legendary rock band - Jagger (80), Richards (79), and Wood (76) - shared insights into their latest work. This marks the Stones’ first studio album containing original songs since “A Bigger Bang” dropped in 2005, although they did grace fans with a blues cover album, “Blue &amp;amp; Lonesome,” in 2016.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of significant note, “Hackney Diamonds” is the first album since the passing of the band’s esteemed drummer, Charlie Watts, in 2021. Despite this loss, his contributions to the album, recorded prior to his demise, ensure his legacy shines on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Among the sea of fans, Brazilian enthusiast Taric Fioravanti from Sao Paulo expressed his deep-rooted admiration for the band and voiced his anticipation for the album. He remarked, “Keith Richards is one of the biggest guitar heroes in the history of rock music.” He further emphasized the band’s unparalleled vitality, pointing out that “they’re 80 years old. Most bands have stopped making new music” by that age.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adding to the album’s aura, the Stones embarked on a cryptic teaser campaign where their emblematic mouth and tongue logo graced landmarks in cities like New York, London, and Paris. The story behind their choice of Hackney for the album title may find roots in its rich tapestry of talent, having birthed legends like playwright Harold Pinter and actor Idris Elba.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a nod to the title, “Hackney Diamonds,” which refers to shattered glass in slang, the band ingeniously teased an ad in the local Hackney Gazette for a fictional glass repair enterprise, reading, “When you say gimme shelter, we’ll fix your shattered windows.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though formed in 1962, The Rolling Stones’ zest for music and live performances remains insatiable. They celebrated their 60th anniversary with a European tour last year, with Steve Jordan stepping in for Watts on drums. As they unveil “Hackney Diamonds,” their legacy as rock’s immortal luminaries is further cemented.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">The streets of London’s Hackney district were thrumming with excitement as The Rolling Stones geared up to announce their brand new album, “Hackney Diamonds.” By early Wednesday, a wave of devoted fans began gathering outside the historical Hackney Empire. The illustrious venue has hosted legends like Charlie Chaplin and Stan Laurel in its storied past. Adding to the day’s allure, none other than “The Tonight Show” host Jimmy Fallon was set to interview the iconic trio - Mick Jagger, Keith Richards, and Ronnie Wood - in a much-anticipated livestream event. Inside the Hackney Empire, a venue steeped in history, the members of the legendary rock band - Jagger (80), Richards (79), and Wood (76) - shared insights into their latest work. This marks the Stones’ first studio album containing original songs since “A Bigger Bang” dropped in 2005, although they did grace fans with a blues cover album, “Blue &amp;amp; Lonesome,” in 2016. Of significant note, “Hackney Diamonds” is the first album since the passing of the band’s esteemed drummer, Charlie Watts, in 2021. Despite this loss, his contributions to the album, recorded prior to his demise, ensure his legacy shines on. Among the sea of fans, Brazilian enthusiast Taric Fioravanti from Sao Paulo expressed his deep-rooted admiration for the band and voiced his anticipation for the album. He remarked, “Keith Richards is one of the biggest guitar heroes in the history of rock music.” He further emphasized the band’s unparalleled vitality, pointing out that “they’re 80 years old. Most bands have stopped making new music” by that age. Adding to the album’s aura, the Stones embarked on a cryptic teaser campaign where their emblematic mouth and tongue logo graced landmarks in cities like New York, London, and Paris. The story behind their choice of Hackney for the album title may find roots in its rich tapestry of talent, having birthed legends like playwright Harold Pinter and actor Idris Elba. As a nod to the title, “Hackney Diamonds,” which refers to shattered glass in slang, the band ingeniously teased an ad in the local Hackney Gazette for a fictional glass repair enterprise, reading, “When you say gimme shelter, we’ll fix your shattered windows.” Though formed in 1962, The Rolling Stones’ zest for music and live performances remains insatiable. They celebrated their 60th anniversary with a European tour last year, with Steve Jordan stepping in for Watts on drums. As they unveil “Hackney Diamonds,” their legacy as rock’s immortal luminaries is further cemented.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Unearthing the Bidens - Unmasking the Collusion Allegations</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/06/Biden-Collusion-Claims/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Unearthing the Bidens - Unmasking the Collusion Allegations" /><published>2023-09-06T12:02:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-06T12:02:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/06/Biden-Collusion-Claims</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/06/Biden-Collusion-Claims/">&lt;p&gt;Doubts and suspicions around then-Vice President Joe Biden’s mingling with his son Hunter Biden’s business associates continue to deepen. As per the recent developments, House Oversight Committee Chairman Rep. James Comer, R-Ky., has put forth a request to the National Archives, demanding unredacted emails highlighting the extent of communication between Biden’s VP office and Hunter’s business contacts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given the legal obligation of the National Archives and Records Administration (NARA) to store crucial governmental communication, Comer seeks access to a specific record, dubbed “Records on Hunter Biden, James Biden, and Their Foreign Business Dealings.” This record gained visibility following an active Freedom of Information Act lawsuit by America First Legal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Comer’s demand does not stop at just emails. In a bid to potentially uncover evidence of impropriety, the letter specifically calls for unredacted emails that spotlight the engagement between Biden’s VP office aides and business contacts from Hunter’s former firm, Rosemont Seneca Partners, and the contentious Ukrainian energy corporation, Burisma Holdings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One noteworthy excerpt from the provided documents reveals an email correspondence between Eric Schwerin, a known Biden family business associate, and Kate Bedingfield, a staffer in the VP’s office. The exchange details quotes for the White House to use in defending Hunter’s involvement with Burisma. The approval came directly from the VP, further exacerbating concerns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Comer’s allegations are severe. He insinuates not just an overlap but “evidence of collusion” between Biden’s official duties and his son’s business pursuits. According to Comer, the VP’s office was a revolving door for Hunter’s business affiliates. Moreover, Biden’s vehement public stand against corruption in Ukraine starkly contrasts with the alleged back-door dealings concerning Burisma’s corruption.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The scrutiny doesn’t end with just the Bidens. Comer’s letter has also asked for executive calendars from Biden’s tenure as Vice President. The motive behind this, as stated by Comer, is to mold potential legislation to address glaring ethical oversights concerning the financial interests of immediate family members of high-ranking officials. These deficiencies, as Comer suggests, might be endangering American national security and broader interests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Drawing the curtains on the issue, Comer asserts the need for accountability, emphasizing that Americans deserve transparency, especially when it pertains to potential misuse of governmental office for personal gains.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the Oversight Committee stays committed to unearthing the truth, it remains to be seen how these allegations will play out in the grand scheme of American politics and what repercussions, if any, the Bidens might face.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Doubts and suspicions around then-Vice President Joe Biden’s mingling with his son Hunter Biden’s business associates continue to deepen. As per the recent developments, House Oversight Committee Chairman Rep. James Comer, R-Ky., has put forth a request to the National Archives, demanding unredacted emails highlighting the extent of communication between Biden’s VP office and Hunter’s business contacts. Given the legal obligation of the National Archives and Records Administration (NARA) to store crucial governmental communication, Comer seeks access to a specific record, dubbed “Records on Hunter Biden, James Biden, and Their Foreign Business Dealings.” This record gained visibility following an active Freedom of Information Act lawsuit by America First Legal. Comer’s demand does not stop at just emails. In a bid to potentially uncover evidence of impropriety, the letter specifically calls for unredacted emails that spotlight the engagement between Biden’s VP office aides and business contacts from Hunter’s former firm, Rosemont Seneca Partners, and the contentious Ukrainian energy corporation, Burisma Holdings. One noteworthy excerpt from the provided documents reveals an email correspondence between Eric Schwerin, a known Biden family business associate, and Kate Bedingfield, a staffer in the VP’s office. The exchange details quotes for the White House to use in defending Hunter’s involvement with Burisma. The approval came directly from the VP, further exacerbating concerns. Comer’s allegations are severe. He insinuates not just an overlap but “evidence of collusion” between Biden’s official duties and his son’s business pursuits. According to Comer, the VP’s office was a revolving door for Hunter’s business affiliates. Moreover, Biden’s vehement public stand against corruption in Ukraine starkly contrasts with the alleged back-door dealings concerning Burisma’s corruption. The scrutiny doesn’t end with just the Bidens. Comer’s letter has also asked for executive calendars from Biden’s tenure as Vice President. The motive behind this, as stated by Comer, is to mold potential legislation to address glaring ethical oversights concerning the financial interests of immediate family members of high-ranking officials. These deficiencies, as Comer suggests, might be endangering American national security and broader interests. Drawing the curtains on the issue, Comer asserts the need for accountability, emphasizing that Americans deserve transparency, especially when it pertains to potential misuse of governmental office for personal gains. As the Oversight Committee stays committed to unearthing the truth, it remains to be seen how these allegations will play out in the grand scheme of American politics and what repercussions, if any, the Bidens might face.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The AI Overlords - Will Americans Soon Be Working for Machines?</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/06/2023-09-06-AI-Workforce-Concerns/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The AI Overlords - Will Americans Soon Be Working for Machines?" /><published>2023-09-06T10:52:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-06T10:52:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/06/2023-09-06-AI-Workforce-Concerns</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/06/2023-09-06-AI-Workforce-Concerns/">&lt;p&gt;The rapid advancement of artificial intelligence (AI) is reshaping industries, businesses, and our way of life. As technological marvels are celebrated, concerns over AI’s impact on the future of employment are also growing. One prominent voice adding to this discourse is former Labor Secretary Robert Reich, who recently shared his perspective on how AI could redefine the dynamics of the American workplace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a candid interview, Reich, who held the labor secretary position during the Clinton era, highlighted the potential upheavals AI could bring to the employer-employee relationship. Emphasizing a significant shift, Reich said, “We’re not going to be working for big companies. We’re going to be working for AI intermediaries and platforms.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Such platforms, according to Reich, might determine pay rates based on spot auctions — gauging demand and supply at any given moment. While this approach might enhance efficiency, the unpredictability it introduces could be “extremely destabilizing” for workers. It could also threaten labor protections painstakingly achieved over the last 120 years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recent studies have echoed similar concerns. A Pew Research survey uncovered that an increasing number of Americans are apprehensive about the pervasive role of AI in daily life. The findings revealed that many are “more concerned than excited” about the growing dominance of such technology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Senator Chuck Schumer, D-NY, is among the lawmakers cognizant of the challenges and potential pitfalls of unchecked AI growth. In a recent letter, Schumer expressed the gravity of the situation, comparing the importance of addressing AI’s challenges with matters of national security, job creation, and civil liberties. He urged for a robust regulatory framework to ensure the responsible evolution of this technology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As solutions for these looming challenges are sought, Reich reintroduces the idea of a universal basic income (UBI). He argues that as AI platforms and machines take over more roles, resulting in numerous people no longer being vital to the workforce, there needs to be a way to ensure they have sufficient income. “People have got to have enough money in their pockets to buy all the things that the new economy is capable of producing,” Reich remarked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The progression of AI offers immense possibilities, but it’s evident that it also brings about fundamental questions concerning employment, income, and societal norms. As the debate continues, it’s crucial to strike a balance that not only propels technological advancements but also safeguards the livelihoods and well-being of the workforce.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">The rapid advancement of artificial intelligence (AI) is reshaping industries, businesses, and our way of life. As technological marvels are celebrated, concerns over AI’s impact on the future of employment are also growing. One prominent voice adding to this discourse is former Labor Secretary Robert Reich, who recently shared his perspective on how AI could redefine the dynamics of the American workplace. In a candid interview, Reich, who held the labor secretary position during the Clinton era, highlighted the potential upheavals AI could bring to the employer-employee relationship. Emphasizing a significant shift, Reich said, “We’re not going to be working for big companies. We’re going to be working for AI intermediaries and platforms.” Such platforms, according to Reich, might determine pay rates based on spot auctions — gauging demand and supply at any given moment. While this approach might enhance efficiency, the unpredictability it introduces could be “extremely destabilizing” for workers. It could also threaten labor protections painstakingly achieved over the last 120 years. Recent studies have echoed similar concerns. A Pew Research survey uncovered that an increasing number of Americans are apprehensive about the pervasive role of AI in daily life. The findings revealed that many are “more concerned than excited” about the growing dominance of such technology. Senator Chuck Schumer, D-NY, is among the lawmakers cognizant of the challenges and potential pitfalls of unchecked AI growth. In a recent letter, Schumer expressed the gravity of the situation, comparing the importance of addressing AI’s challenges with matters of national security, job creation, and civil liberties. He urged for a robust regulatory framework to ensure the responsible evolution of this technology. As solutions for these looming challenges are sought, Reich reintroduces the idea of a universal basic income (UBI). He argues that as AI platforms and machines take over more roles, resulting in numerous people no longer being vital to the workforce, there needs to be a way to ensure they have sufficient income. “People have got to have enough money in their pockets to buy all the things that the new economy is capable of producing,” Reich remarked. The progression of AI offers immense possibilities, but it’s evident that it also brings about fundamental questions concerning employment, income, and societal norms. As the debate continues, it’s crucial to strike a balance that not only propels technological advancements but also safeguards the livelihoods and well-being of the workforce.</summary></entry></feed>