<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-10-09T08:33:20-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/09/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-09T08:33:20-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-09T08:33:20-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/09/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/09/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/09/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-09T08:33:20-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-09T08:33:20-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/09/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/09/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/">&lt;p&gt;Recent surprise attacks by Hamas on Israel has fueled ongoing tensions between staunchly conservative commentators and the progressive “Squad” Democrats known for criticizing Israel. The intensity of the backlash highlights the deep political divide over foreign policy in the Middle East.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Hamas’ shocking attack, several members of the “Squad,” including Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.), called for a “ceasefire and de-escalation,” condemning the violence. The absence of a statement from Rep. Rashida Tlaib (D-Mich.) was notably called out by conservative media outlets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;South Carolina GOP Rep. Nancy Mace quickly labeled Ocasio-Cortez a “Hamas apologist” in response to her call for peace and de-escalation. Rep. Ilhan Omar (D-Minn.), no stranger to controversy surrounding her views on Israel, echoed the call for de-escalation and ceasefire. Omar’s prior statements comparing the US and Israel to terrorist groups like Hamas and the Taliban resurfaced in the debate, fueling more criticisms. Omar’s 2019 tweet, where she opined that “Israel has hypnotized the world,” also continues to haunt her political career, often cited by critics to challenge her stance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conservative commentators have been especially vocal. “FOX &amp;amp; Friends Weekend” co-host Rachel Campos-Duffy took aim at Omar, saying she fails to recognize the peace in the Middle East under Trump’s administration. Conservative pundit John Hasson also called out Omar, claiming she insinuated that attacks on IDF forces were acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Massachusetts Democrat Rep. Ayanna Pressley’s concerns over the “devastating attacks on Israelis” were met with skepticism. A prominent conservative online personality, Comfortably Smug, accused the “Squad” of advising Israel to back down after the nation suffered massive attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Jamaal Bowman’s call for an end to the Gaza blockade, in addition to condemning the Hamas attacks, was met with criticism from conservative radio host Jason Rantz. He accused Bowman of pairing his condemnation of terrorism with unwarranted criticisms of Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Cori Bush emphasized the urgent need for a ceasefire, while pushing for an end to “U.S. support for Israeli military occupation and apartheid.” Defense attorney Marina Medvin criticized Bush, suggesting that she equates the death of Palestinian terrorists to the horrific acts committed against Jewish civilians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amidst the political turmoil and intense debate, the attacks have taken a heavy toll. Israeli media report over 300 dead due to the wide-ranging assault. Gaza health officials note that at least 200 Palestinians have perished in the retaliatory Israeli air strikes following the initial Hamas attack. As the situation remains volatile, both sides continue to count their casualties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This divisive issue showcases the challenge America faces in crafting a unified approach to foreign policy, with deeply entrenched political divides at play. As the situation develops, the debate is bound to intensify, shedding light on the complexities of U.S. politics in the global arena.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Court Drama: ‘Rust’ Producers to Release Documents in Baldwin Case</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/09/Rust-Production-Documents/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Court Drama: ‘Rust’ Producers to Release Documents in Baldwin Case" /><published>2023-10-09T08:16:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-09T08:16:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/09/Rust-Production-Documents</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/09/Rust-Production-Documents/">&lt;p&gt;A new chapter unfolds in the high-profile ‘Rust’ case, with a New Mexico judge recently demanding that film producers provide critical documents that may further implicate actor Alec Baldwin in the tragic on-set death of cinematographer Halyna Hutchins in 2021.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The western movie’s production company, Rust Movie Productions, is under intense scrutiny after the accidental shooting. Their reluctance to share requested documents has heightened suspicions. According to an L.A. Times report, the production company had opposed a subpoena that sought documents, including Baldwin’s contract.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Attorney Abigail R. Wolberg, representing Rust Movie Productions, voiced concerns about the nature of these demands, noting, “The state has made it very clear in its statements that it’s still considering bringing charges against Alec Baldwin.” On the other hand, special prosecutor Kari T. Morrissey countered, emphasizing how Rust Productions “cut corners every chance they could”, jeopardizing crew members’ safety.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The pivotal focus now is on the extent of Baldwin’s role as a producer. State officials aim to ascertain his knowledge about the film’s budgetary constraints and crew management. The underlying concern revolves around the alleged unsafe atmosphere on set, possibly stemming from cost-cutting measures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An ongoing debate centers around Hannah Gutierrez-Reed, the film’s armorer. She has claimed that the movie’s producers declined her proposal for extended firearm training for Baldwin. Such training would have covered the usage of the .45 Colt pistol that was central to the fatal incident. The requested documents would likely shed light on Baldwin’s actions leading up to the unfortunate event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, internal communication has revealed that Gutierrez-Reed was stretched thin, juggling dual roles as both the armorer and props assistant. Morrissey alleged that cost-cutting motives influenced this decision, explaining, “We have a situation where Rust Production is doing everything it can to keep costs low so that it can keep profits high.” With Baldwin as one of the film’s producers, he would potentially benefit from these cost-saving actions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another contentious point raised by Morrissey is the rapid involvement of Rust Productions’ legal counsel following the accident, suggesting that potential witnesses were approached by a company lawyer almost immediately after the shooting, possibly even before the police could intervene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although manslaughter charges against Baldwin were dropped earlier this year, the case remains very much active, with potential for further developments. The tragic accident in October 2021 resulted from a real bullet mistakenly loaded into a prop gun handed to Baldwin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As investigations continue, the entertainment world and fans globally await more revelations on this heartbreaking incident.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">A new chapter unfolds in the high-profile ‘Rust’ case, with a New Mexico judge recently demanding that film producers provide critical documents that may further implicate actor Alec Baldwin in the tragic on-set death of cinematographer Halyna Hutchins in 2021. The western movie’s production company, Rust Movie Productions, is under intense scrutiny after the accidental shooting. Their reluctance to share requested documents has heightened suspicions. According to an L.A. Times report, the production company had opposed a subpoena that sought documents, including Baldwin’s contract. Attorney Abigail R. Wolberg, representing Rust Movie Productions, voiced concerns about the nature of these demands, noting, “The state has made it very clear in its statements that it’s still considering bringing charges against Alec Baldwin.” On the other hand, special prosecutor Kari T. Morrissey countered, emphasizing how Rust Productions “cut corners every chance they could”, jeopardizing crew members’ safety. The pivotal focus now is on the extent of Baldwin’s role as a producer. State officials aim to ascertain his knowledge about the film’s budgetary constraints and crew management. The underlying concern revolves around the alleged unsafe atmosphere on set, possibly stemming from cost-cutting measures. An ongoing debate centers around Hannah Gutierrez-Reed, the film’s armorer. She has claimed that the movie’s producers declined her proposal for extended firearm training for Baldwin. Such training would have covered the usage of the .45 Colt pistol that was central to the fatal incident. The requested documents would likely shed light on Baldwin’s actions leading up to the unfortunate event. Furthermore, internal communication has revealed that Gutierrez-Reed was stretched thin, juggling dual roles as both the armorer and props assistant. Morrissey alleged that cost-cutting motives influenced this decision, explaining, “We have a situation where Rust Production is doing everything it can to keep costs low so that it can keep profits high.” With Baldwin as one of the film’s producers, he would potentially benefit from these cost-saving actions. Another contentious point raised by Morrissey is the rapid involvement of Rust Productions’ legal counsel following the accident, suggesting that potential witnesses were approached by a company lawyer almost immediately after the shooting, possibly even before the police could intervene. Although manslaughter charges against Baldwin were dropped earlier this year, the case remains very much active, with potential for further developments. The tragic accident in October 2021 resulted from a real bullet mistakenly loaded into a prop gun handed to Baldwin. As investigations continue, the entertainment world and fans globally await more revelations on this heartbreaking incident.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Turbulence in the Capitol: Republicans Scramble for New Speaker Amidst Israel Crisis</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/09/Republican-Crisis-House-Speaker/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Turbulence in the Capitol: Republicans Scramble for New Speaker Amidst Israel Crisis" /><published>2023-10-09T07:07:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-09T07:07:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/09/Republican-Crisis-House-Speaker</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/09/Republican-Crisis-House-Speaker/">&lt;p&gt;As Israel grapples with a massive surprise attack by Hamas militants, House Republicans back home are facing their own battle: the unexpected ouster of former House Speaker Kevin McCarthy and the ensuing leadership vacuum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Mike Lawler, R-N.Y., didn’t hold back, taking to social media to vent his frustration: “This is why you don’t remove a Speaker mid-term without cause. What an unmitigated s— show.” Lawler underscored the need for stability and direction, especially given the escalating situation in Israel. He emphasized, “We need to elect a Speaker.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the face of adversity, Israel’s Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu has displayed determination, vowing to eliminate threats posed by Hamas. “All of the places which Hamas is deployed, hiding, and operating in that wicked city, we will turn them into rubble,” Netanyahu warned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet, in stark contrast, the political landscape within the U.S. House of Representatives is marked by uncertainty and disarray. For the first time in U.S. history, a House Speaker has been removed, paralyzing Congress’s decision-making abilities during a pivotal international crisis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;House Financial Services Chairman Patrick McHenry, R-N.C., has taken the reins as interim speaker, but his true extent of power remains uncertain. Traditionally, the Speaker is a key part of the “Gang of Eight”, a select group of top congressional leaders privy to classified intelligence briefings. Without a definitive Speaker, there’s a possible intelligence gap during this delicate period.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Former House Speaker Kevin McCarthy raised similar concerns in a recent interview, “There is nothing the House can do until they elect a speaker… why would you ever remove a speaker during a term to raise doubt around the world?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the search for a new leader intensifies, House Majority Leader Steve Scalise, R-La., and Judiciary Chairman Jim Jordan, R-Ohio, have emerged as frontrunners. Kevin Hern, R-Okla., who previously contemplated running, urged the party to swiftly come together, emphasizing the urgency of the situation, “We cannot allow the narrative to be chaos and confusion on Capitol Hill.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Marc Molinaro echoed the sentiments, emphasizing the immediate need for a permanent speaker. “Israel is at war [and] its people are being terrorized. We cannot let uncertainty in the Capitol get in the way of helping Israel. There’s no time to waste,” he asserted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;House Republicans are expected to make a decisive move in the coming days, with speaker elections scheduled for Wednesday, following pivotal meetings early in the week. As the world watches the Israeli conflict unfold, the pressure is on for House Republicans to unite, lead, and address the pressing matters at hand.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">As Israel grapples with a massive surprise attack by Hamas militants, House Republicans back home are facing their own battle: the unexpected ouster of former House Speaker Kevin McCarthy and the ensuing leadership vacuum. Rep. Mike Lawler, R-N.Y., didn’t hold back, taking to social media to vent his frustration: “This is why you don’t remove a Speaker mid-term without cause. What an unmitigated s— show.” Lawler underscored the need for stability and direction, especially given the escalating situation in Israel. He emphasized, “We need to elect a Speaker.” In the face of adversity, Israel’s Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu has displayed determination, vowing to eliminate threats posed by Hamas. “All of the places which Hamas is deployed, hiding, and operating in that wicked city, we will turn them into rubble,” Netanyahu warned. Yet, in stark contrast, the political landscape within the U.S. House of Representatives is marked by uncertainty and disarray. For the first time in U.S. history, a House Speaker has been removed, paralyzing Congress’s decision-making abilities during a pivotal international crisis. House Financial Services Chairman Patrick McHenry, R-N.C., has taken the reins as interim speaker, but his true extent of power remains uncertain. Traditionally, the Speaker is a key part of the “Gang of Eight”, a select group of top congressional leaders privy to classified intelligence briefings. Without a definitive Speaker, there’s a possible intelligence gap during this delicate period. Former House Speaker Kevin McCarthy raised similar concerns in a recent interview, “There is nothing the House can do until they elect a speaker… why would you ever remove a speaker during a term to raise doubt around the world?” As the search for a new leader intensifies, House Majority Leader Steve Scalise, R-La., and Judiciary Chairman Jim Jordan, R-Ohio, have emerged as frontrunners. Kevin Hern, R-Okla., who previously contemplated running, urged the party to swiftly come together, emphasizing the urgency of the situation, “We cannot allow the narrative to be chaos and confusion on Capitol Hill.” Rep. Marc Molinaro echoed the sentiments, emphasizing the immediate need for a permanent speaker. “Israel is at war [and] its people are being terrorized. We cannot let uncertainty in the Capitol get in the way of helping Israel. There’s no time to waste,” he asserted. House Republicans are expected to make a decisive move in the coming days, with speaker elections scheduled for Wednesday, following pivotal meetings early in the week. As the world watches the Israeli conflict unfold, the pressure is on for House Republicans to unite, lead, and address the pressing matters at hand.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Israel’s Struggle: The Low Private Gun Ownership Debate</title><link href="/news/2023/10/09/Israel-Gun-Ownership/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Israel’s Struggle: The Low Private Gun Ownership Debate" /><published>2023-10-09T06:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-09T06:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/09/Israel-Gun-Ownership</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/09/Israel-Gun-Ownership/">&lt;p&gt;With rising tensions and violent attacks witnessed in Israel, particularly from groups like Hamas, it brings to the forefront a pressing debate on private gun ownership. Unlike the United States, which boasts of the Second Amendment that champions an individual’s right to bear arms, Israel’s private gun ownership landscape paints a starkly different picture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As per reports from the BC, merely 2% of the Israeli population own guns. This is a far cry from the United States, where a study from Rutgers University’s New Jersey Gun Violence Research Center posits that approximately six in ten Americans are gun owners.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The primary distinguishing factor here is the Second Amendment in the U.S. Constitution. This amendment safeguards an American’s right to gun ownership from birth. In stark contrast, Israelis can own firearms only to the extent permitted by their government. Not just this, Israel sets strict limits on the type of firearms and the amount of ammunition one can possess. To put it into perspective, while an Israeli might typically be permitted a pistol with a cap of 50 bullets, Americans, depending on the state they reside in, can own a plethora of guns and amass as much ammunition as their pockets allow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Highlighting the sheer volume of firearms in America, it’s estimated that nearly 25 million semi-automatic rifles, such as the AR-15s and AK-47s, are in circulation. This statistic means there are more of these firearms in the U.S. than “Ford F-Series trucks on the road.” Summing up all firearm categories, America sees an astounding figure of over 434 million privately-owned guns. Meanwhile, Israel’s limitations confine citizens mostly to handguns with limited bullets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the debate rages on, the University of Sydney’s Gun Policy center has underlined that unlike the U.S., Israel does not legally guarantee the right to private gun ownership. However, in the face of increasing threats, there’s been a notable surge in the number of Israelis seeking gun licenses. From 19,000 applications in 2021, the figure jumped to 42,236 the following year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a bid to counteract terrorism and bolster civilian safety, earlier this year, Israel’s security cabinet endorsed measures that streamline the process for civilians to carry firearms. The changes even encompassed rescinding the residency and citizenship of identified terrorists. Sources indicate that the high-level security cabinet is mulling over augmenting the response mechanisms against terrorism. This might include enhancing the funding for firearm purchases and fast-tracking the issuance of gun licenses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the wake of recent events, some analysts speculate that Israeli authorities could potentially expand the gamut of weapons that its citizens can privately own. Whether this shift would significantly alter the security landscape of the nation remains to be seen. But one thing’s for certain, as terror threats loom large, Israel’s gun ownership policies are under intense scrutiny, and changes, if any, will reverberate on the global stage.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">With rising tensions and violent attacks witnessed in Israel, particularly from groups like Hamas, it brings to the forefront a pressing debate on private gun ownership. Unlike the United States, which boasts of the Second Amendment that champions an individual’s right to bear arms, Israel’s private gun ownership landscape paints a starkly different picture. As per reports from the BC, merely 2% of the Israeli population own guns. This is a far cry from the United States, where a study from Rutgers University’s New Jersey Gun Violence Research Center posits that approximately six in ten Americans are gun owners. The primary distinguishing factor here is the Second Amendment in the U.S. Constitution. This amendment safeguards an American’s right to gun ownership from birth. In stark contrast, Israelis can own firearms only to the extent permitted by their government. Not just this, Israel sets strict limits on the type of firearms and the amount of ammunition one can possess. To put it into perspective, while an Israeli might typically be permitted a pistol with a cap of 50 bullets, Americans, depending on the state they reside in, can own a plethora of guns and amass as much ammunition as their pockets allow. Highlighting the sheer volume of firearms in America, it’s estimated that nearly 25 million semi-automatic rifles, such as the AR-15s and AK-47s, are in circulation. This statistic means there are more of these firearms in the U.S. than “Ford F-Series trucks on the road.” Summing up all firearm categories, America sees an astounding figure of over 434 million privately-owned guns. Meanwhile, Israel’s limitations confine citizens mostly to handguns with limited bullets. As the debate rages on, the University of Sydney’s Gun Policy center has underlined that unlike the U.S., Israel does not legally guarantee the right to private gun ownership. However, in the face of increasing threats, there’s been a notable surge in the number of Israelis seeking gun licenses. From 19,000 applications in 2021, the figure jumped to 42,236 the following year. In a bid to counteract terrorism and bolster civilian safety, earlier this year, Israel’s security cabinet endorsed measures that streamline the process for civilians to carry firearms. The changes even encompassed rescinding the residency and citizenship of identified terrorists. Sources indicate that the high-level security cabinet is mulling over augmenting the response mechanisms against terrorism. This might include enhancing the funding for firearm purchases and fast-tracking the issuance of gun licenses. In the wake of recent events, some analysts speculate that Israeli authorities could potentially expand the gamut of weapons that its citizens can privately own. Whether this shift would significantly alter the security landscape of the nation remains to be seen. But one thing’s for certain, as terror threats loom large, Israel’s gun ownership policies are under intense scrutiny, and changes, if any, will reverberate on the global stage.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Germany Halts Palestine Aid Amidst Surging Violence</title><link href="/news/2023/10/08/Germany-Suspends-Aid-to-Palestine/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Germany Halts Palestine Aid Amidst Surging Violence" /><published>2023-10-08T16:45:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-08T16:45:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/08/Germany-Suspends-Aid-to-Palestine</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/08/Germany-Suspends-Aid-to-Palestine/">&lt;p&gt;In the aftermath of a severe terror assault on Israel by Hamas militants, Germany has put a hold on its humanitarian aid payments to Palestine. The decision comes as Berlin embarks on a thorough review of all support payments to ensure they align with its political and humanitarian objectives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Germany, recognized as “one of the largest donors in the Palestinian territories,” had earmarked a whopping €250 million (equivalent to approximately $265 million) for Palestine’s assistance over the next two years. Half of this aid was slated for the United Nations Relief and Works Agency for Palestine Refugees in the Near East (UNRWA). This funding typically covers pivotal projects focused on bettering water quality, healthcare, food security, and job opportunities. Despite being channeled to Palestine, many of these initiatives are perceived to benefit Israel too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, in light of the recent wave of violence that shocked the region, Svenja Schulze, the German government’s development minister, articulated the nation’s concerns. “These attacks on Israel are a terrible turning point. We will therefore examine our entire commitment to the Palestinian territories,” Schulze commented, as quoted by the German broadcaster, NTV.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Federal Finance Minister Christian Lindner echoed these sentiments, pressing for an expedited determination concerning the aid designated for Palestine. Highlighting the gravity of the situation, Lindner remarked, “The terror is shocking. We shouldn’t just react to it with words.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moreover, the chorus of dissent wasn’t restricted to government quarters. Opposition MP, Roderich Kiesewetter of the Christian Democratic Union (CDU), took a sterner stance, advocating for an immediate cessation of the millions funneled into Palestine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amid these turbulent times, German Chancellor Olaf Scholz reached out to Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu. Their conversation underscored Berlin’s unwavering support for Israel and its inherent right to self-defence, especially against the “barbaric attacks” orchestrated by Hamas. Furthermore, Chancellor Scholz is expected to liaise with Egyptian President Abdel Fattah el-Sissi, aiming to tap into Cairo’s potential mediating role to broker peace in this volatile scenario.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, on the home front, Chancellor Scholz vehemently condemned the pro-Palestine demonstrations in Berlin. He expressed his dismay, asserting, “We do not accept it when the hideous attacks against Israel are celebrated here on our streets… The suffering, the destruction and the death of so many people cannot be a cause for joy for anyone.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This escalating conflict, coinciding with the Jewish holiday of Shemini Atzeret, has taken a tragic toll. The Israeli government’s latest data indicates a harrowing loss, with over 600 fatalities attributed to Hamas since Saturday, while thousands more nurse their injuries and over a hundred remain captive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Germany’s aid suspension, while significant, is just one facet of a multi-dimensional crisis that demands international attention and swift resolutions.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In the aftermath of a severe terror assault on Israel by Hamas militants, Germany has put a hold on its humanitarian aid payments to Palestine. The decision comes as Berlin embarks on a thorough review of all support payments to ensure they align with its political and humanitarian objectives. Germany, recognized as “one of the largest donors in the Palestinian territories,” had earmarked a whopping €250 million (equivalent to approximately $265 million) for Palestine’s assistance over the next two years. Half of this aid was slated for the United Nations Relief and Works Agency for Palestine Refugees in the Near East (UNRWA). This funding typically covers pivotal projects focused on bettering water quality, healthcare, food security, and job opportunities. Despite being channeled to Palestine, many of these initiatives are perceived to benefit Israel too. However, in light of the recent wave of violence that shocked the region, Svenja Schulze, the German government’s development minister, articulated the nation’s concerns. “These attacks on Israel are a terrible turning point. We will therefore examine our entire commitment to the Palestinian territories,” Schulze commented, as quoted by the German broadcaster, NTV. Federal Finance Minister Christian Lindner echoed these sentiments, pressing for an expedited determination concerning the aid designated for Palestine. Highlighting the gravity of the situation, Lindner remarked, “The terror is shocking. We shouldn’t just react to it with words.” Moreover, the chorus of dissent wasn’t restricted to government quarters. Opposition MP, Roderich Kiesewetter of the Christian Democratic Union (CDU), took a sterner stance, advocating for an immediate cessation of the millions funneled into Palestine. Amid these turbulent times, German Chancellor Olaf Scholz reached out to Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu. Their conversation underscored Berlin’s unwavering support for Israel and its inherent right to self-defence, especially against the “barbaric attacks” orchestrated by Hamas. Furthermore, Chancellor Scholz is expected to liaise with Egyptian President Abdel Fattah el-Sissi, aiming to tap into Cairo’s potential mediating role to broker peace in this volatile scenario. Meanwhile, on the home front, Chancellor Scholz vehemently condemned the pro-Palestine demonstrations in Berlin. He expressed his dismay, asserting, “We do not accept it when the hideous attacks against Israel are celebrated here on our streets… The suffering, the destruction and the death of so many people cannot be a cause for joy for anyone.” This escalating conflict, coinciding with the Jewish holiday of Shemini Atzeret, has taken a tragic toll. The Israeli government’s latest data indicates a harrowing loss, with over 600 fatalities attributed to Hamas since Saturday, while thousands more nurse their injuries and over a hundred remain captive. Germany’s aid suspension, while significant, is just one facet of a multi-dimensional crisis that demands international attention and swift resolutions.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Biden’s Iran Decision: A Tipping Point for Middle East Stability?</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/08/Biden-Complicit-in-Iran-Attacks/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Biden’s Iran Decision: A Tipping Point for Middle East Stability?" /><published>2023-10-08T14:57:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-08T14:57:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/08/Biden-Complicit-in-Iran-Attacks</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/08/Biden-Complicit-in-Iran-Attacks/">&lt;p&gt;Sen. Tim Scott (R-S.C.) has voiced his concerns loud and clear: he believes that President Joe Biden’s decision to release $6 billion to Iran has indirectly, if not directly, funded terrorism in the Middle East. A resounding accusation that demands attention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This isn’t the first time that Iran’s involvement with funding terroristic activities has been a point of contention. History has shown that they’ve been consistently linked to supporting groups like Hamas. As Scott pointed out, Iran is the primary funder of this group. Their involvement has sparked major controversies, especially when the welfare of U.S. allies is at stake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“The $6 billion he paid to Iran now being used once again in a terrorist attack. We’ve seen time and time again that Iran continues to fund terrorism in the Middle East. The No. 1 funder of Hamas is, of course, Iran,” said Scott.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Scott’s criticism doesn’t stop at financial concerns. He has called out the Biden administration for its messaging and decisions, especially concerning Israel. For many, Israel represents a beacon of democracy in the Middle East, and any threat to its sovereignty is viewed with grave concern.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A controversial move by Biden’s State Department saw them warning Israel against retaliation in the wake of a Hamas terrorist attack. Even though the tweet was eventually deleted, the message was clear and the damage was done. Scott minced no words, stating that such a suggestion amounted to an abdication of responsibility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“This is not a Republican or Democrat issue. This is an issue about the sovereignty of Israel and whether or not we have good solid leadership in the White House that understands that we cannot have daylight between the United States of America and our allies, especially in the moment of conflict,” Scott emphasized.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This recent situation casts a shadow on the Biden administration, questioning its commitment to the long-standing alliance with Israel. If the U.S. were to falter in its support, the consequences for Middle East stability could be dire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In an era where unity and decisive leadership are crucial, Scott’s remarks resonate with many who believe that the U.S. needs to stand “shoulder to shoulder and back to back” with its allies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Biden’s decisions concerning Iran have opened a debate about U.S. foreign policy. As the implications of this choice unravel, it will be crucial to see if the administration acknowledges these concerns and adapts its strategy accordingly. The stability of the Middle East might very well depend on it.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Sen. Tim Scott (R-S.C.) has voiced his concerns loud and clear: he believes that President Joe Biden’s decision to release $6 billion to Iran has indirectly, if not directly, funded terrorism in the Middle East. A resounding accusation that demands attention. This isn’t the first time that Iran’s involvement with funding terroristic activities has been a point of contention. History has shown that they’ve been consistently linked to supporting groups like Hamas. As Scott pointed out, Iran is the primary funder of this group. Their involvement has sparked major controversies, especially when the welfare of U.S. allies is at stake. “The $6 billion he paid to Iran now being used once again in a terrorist attack. We’ve seen time and time again that Iran continues to fund terrorism in the Middle East. The No. 1 funder of Hamas is, of course, Iran,” said Scott. Scott’s criticism doesn’t stop at financial concerns. He has called out the Biden administration for its messaging and decisions, especially concerning Israel. For many, Israel represents a beacon of democracy in the Middle East, and any threat to its sovereignty is viewed with grave concern. A controversial move by Biden’s State Department saw them warning Israel against retaliation in the wake of a Hamas terrorist attack. Even though the tweet was eventually deleted, the message was clear and the damage was done. Scott minced no words, stating that such a suggestion amounted to an abdication of responsibility. “This is not a Republican or Democrat issue. This is an issue about the sovereignty of Israel and whether or not we have good solid leadership in the White House that understands that we cannot have daylight between the United States of America and our allies, especially in the moment of conflict,” Scott emphasized. This recent situation casts a shadow on the Biden administration, questioning its commitment to the long-standing alliance with Israel. If the U.S. were to falter in its support, the consequences for Middle East stability could be dire. In an era where unity and decisive leadership are crucial, Scott’s remarks resonate with many who believe that the U.S. needs to stand “shoulder to shoulder and back to back” with its allies. Biden’s decisions concerning Iran have opened a debate about U.S. foreign policy. As the implications of this choice unravel, it will be crucial to see if the administration acknowledges these concerns and adapts its strategy accordingly. The stability of the Middle East might very well depend on it.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Mayor Johnson’s Leadership Questioned Amidst Chicago’s Shooting Epidemic</title><link href="/news/2023/10/08/Chicago-Violence/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Mayor Johnson’s Leadership Questioned Amidst Chicago’s Shooting Epidemic" /><published>2023-10-08T12:15:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-08T12:15:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/08/Chicago-Violence</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/08/Chicago-Violence/">&lt;p&gt;Under the ostensibly ineffective leadership of Mayor Brandon Johnson, Chicago faced a harrowing weekend where at least 19 individuals became victims of gunfire, with two succumbing to their injuries. This surge in violence serves as a distressing testament to the city’s deteriorating safety conditions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Friday evening, the ABC 7 / Chicago Sun-Times shed light on the beginning of the tragic weekend spree. Around 6:30 p.m., in an alley in the “10200 block of South Carpenter Street,” a 43-year-old man was ruthlessly shot in the chest and head, leading to his immediate death.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saturday didn’t bring any reprieve. By 10:45 a.m., in the “1500 block of East 74th Street,” a group targeted a young couple, a 23-year-old woman and a 24-year-old man, resulting in the tragic death of the woman. The man, although wounded, refused medical aid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The alarming frequency of these incidents brings to the forefront the pressing questions about Mayor Johnson’s capabilities. A database from the Sun-Times underscores this dire scenario, highlighting that from January 1, 2023, to date, 455 individuals have lost their lives to gun violence in Chicago.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overwhelming spike in crime under Mayor Johnson’s watch is not just a statistic—it’s an alarming reality for the city’s residents. These continual violent outbreaks are prompting both local and national discussions, questioning Mayor Johnson’s strategies and effectiveness in addressing the escalating gun violence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the Windy City yearns for safety and stability, there is a rising demand for better leadership, one that can offer tangible solutions and restore peace to the beleaguered streets of Chicago.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Under the ostensibly ineffective leadership of Mayor Brandon Johnson, Chicago faced a harrowing weekend where at least 19 individuals became victims of gunfire, with two succumbing to their injuries. This surge in violence serves as a distressing testament to the city’s deteriorating safety conditions. On Friday evening, the ABC 7 / Chicago Sun-Times shed light on the beginning of the tragic weekend spree. Around 6:30 p.m., in an alley in the “10200 block of South Carpenter Street,” a 43-year-old man was ruthlessly shot in the chest and head, leading to his immediate death. Saturday didn’t bring any reprieve. By 10:45 a.m., in the “1500 block of East 74th Street,” a group targeted a young couple, a 23-year-old woman and a 24-year-old man, resulting in the tragic death of the woman. The man, although wounded, refused medical aid. The alarming frequency of these incidents brings to the forefront the pressing questions about Mayor Johnson’s capabilities. A database from the Sun-Times underscores this dire scenario, highlighting that from January 1, 2023, to date, 455 individuals have lost their lives to gun violence in Chicago. The overwhelming spike in crime under Mayor Johnson’s watch is not just a statistic—it’s an alarming reality for the city’s residents. These continual violent outbreaks are prompting both local and national discussions, questioning Mayor Johnson’s strategies and effectiveness in addressing the escalating gun violence. As the Windy City yearns for safety and stability, there is a rising demand for better leadership, one that can offer tangible solutions and restore peace to the beleaguered streets of Chicago.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Republicans Decry Biden’s $6 Billion Release to Iran Preceding Hamas Assault on Israel</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/08/Republican-Critique-on-Biden-Iran-Funding/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Republicans Decry Biden’s $6 Billion Release to Iran Preceding Hamas Assault on Israel" /><published>2023-10-08T07:45:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-08T07:45:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/08/Republican-Critique-on-Biden-Iran-Funding</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/08/Republican-Critique-on-Biden-Iran-Funding/">&lt;p&gt;In the aftermath of a fierce attack on Israel, leading Republican figures voice harsh criticism against the Biden administration for releasing $6 billion of frozen Iranian assets, arguing a potential link to the escalated Hamas aggression.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Republicans from both the House and Senate have pointed fingers at the timing of the asset release, which occurred a few months prior to the sudden surge in Hamas terrorism in Israel. The assault witnessed a barrage of rockets launched into Israeli territories, accompanied by a ground invasion that resulted in significant casualties. Reportedly, over 100 Israelis perished in these unexpected attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tennessee Senator Marsha Blackburn expressed her dismay, connecting the release of funds to Iran with the bloodshed in Israel, asserting, “Just weeks ago, the Biden administration handed over $6 billion to Iran, and today, innocent Israelis were murdered by Iran-backed terrorists.” Such sentiments resonate strongly with various Republican voices that see the unfreezing of assets as an indirect support to Iran’s historical backing of Hamas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In defense, the Biden administration clarifies that the $6 billion, transferred from South Korea to accounts in Qatar, is explicitly earmarked for humanitarian efforts, with stringent U.S. oversight ensuring its appropriate use. However, critiques question the genuine nature of such restrictions, highlighting the inherent malleability of finances that could potentially support Iran-sponsored terrorism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Highlighting Iran’s perennial backing of Hamas, the State Department acknowledges the allocation of roughly $100 million annually by Iran to Palestinian militant groups. This revelation strengthens the skepticism surrounding the released funds, with critics insisting on a direct correlation between the assets’ unfreezing and the subsequent Hamas-initiated violence in Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a digital outburst, Florida Senator Rick Scott encapsulated the Republican dismay: “This is exactly why so many Americans &amp;amp; Israelis were DISGUSTED to see [President Biden] give the Iranian regime $6 billion last month.” Similar sentiments, iterating the perceived funding-terrorism connection, echoed across various digital platforms and statements by Republican leaders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the debate intensifies, the crux remains the safety and security of Israel and its citizens. With increased global scrutiny, the Biden administration’s approach towards foreign relations, especially with stakeholders in the Middle East, will be a pivotal facet in shaping future geopolitical dynamics.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In the aftermath of a fierce attack on Israel, leading Republican figures voice harsh criticism against the Biden administration for releasing $6 billion of frozen Iranian assets, arguing a potential link to the escalated Hamas aggression. Republicans from both the House and Senate have pointed fingers at the timing of the asset release, which occurred a few months prior to the sudden surge in Hamas terrorism in Israel. The assault witnessed a barrage of rockets launched into Israeli territories, accompanied by a ground invasion that resulted in significant casualties. Reportedly, over 100 Israelis perished in these unexpected attacks. Tennessee Senator Marsha Blackburn expressed her dismay, connecting the release of funds to Iran with the bloodshed in Israel, asserting, “Just weeks ago, the Biden administration handed over $6 billion to Iran, and today, innocent Israelis were murdered by Iran-backed terrorists.” Such sentiments resonate strongly with various Republican voices that see the unfreezing of assets as an indirect support to Iran’s historical backing of Hamas. In defense, the Biden administration clarifies that the $6 billion, transferred from South Korea to accounts in Qatar, is explicitly earmarked for humanitarian efforts, with stringent U.S. oversight ensuring its appropriate use. However, critiques question the genuine nature of such restrictions, highlighting the inherent malleability of finances that could potentially support Iran-sponsored terrorism. Highlighting Iran’s perennial backing of Hamas, the State Department acknowledges the allocation of roughly $100 million annually by Iran to Palestinian militant groups. This revelation strengthens the skepticism surrounding the released funds, with critics insisting on a direct correlation between the assets’ unfreezing and the subsequent Hamas-initiated violence in Israel. In a digital outburst, Florida Senator Rick Scott encapsulated the Republican dismay: “This is exactly why so many Americans &amp;amp; Israelis were DISGUSTED to see [President Biden] give the Iranian regime $6 billion last month.” Similar sentiments, iterating the perceived funding-terrorism connection, echoed across various digital platforms and statements by Republican leaders. While the debate intensifies, the crux remains the safety and security of Israel and its citizens. With increased global scrutiny, the Biden administration’s approach towards foreign relations, especially with stakeholders in the Middle East, will be a pivotal facet in shaping future geopolitical dynamics.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Washington D.C. Sees Staggering Surge in Carjackings: An Alarming 111% Rise!</title><link href="/news/2023/10/08/DC-Carjackings-Surge/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Washington D.C. Sees Staggering Surge in Carjackings: An Alarming 111% Rise!" /><published>2023-10-08T06:34:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-08T06:34:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/08/DC-Carjackings-Surge</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/08/DC-Carjackings-Surge/">&lt;p&gt;In a startling revelation, carjackings in Washington D.C. skyrocketed by an astounding 111% in the first ten months of 2023, compared to the same period in 2022. Police, while still piecing together the ‘why,’ highlight a noteworthy detail: the majority of the arrested individuals are below 18 years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2023, the U.S. capital reported a whopping 760 carjackings. In contrast, there were only 360 in the same time frame last year. To put things into perspective, the carjackings this year alone surpassed the total of 2018, 2019, and 2020 combined. These alarming figures suggest a deep-rooted issue that law enforcement and the justice system must address.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most carjackings reportedly occur around the &lt;strong&gt;H Street Corridor&lt;/strong&gt; and the regions adjacent to the &lt;strong&gt;Anacostia River bordering Maryland&lt;/strong&gt;. Police data emphasizes that a staggering &lt;strong&gt;65% of those involved in these thefts are juveniles&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s not just the age of the culprits that’s concerning. U.S. Attorney for D.C., Matthew Graves, admitted that the majority of individuals arrested for such crimes are young. However, his office often does not prosecute them, especially if they are under 16. In 2022, Graves &lt;strong&gt;refused to prosecute 67%&lt;/strong&gt; of those who could have been tried in the D.C. Superior Court. This number is notably high when considering juvenile crimes, where he did not press charges for 26%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One might wonder if this trend of non-prosecution is contributing to the surge. D.C.’s juvenile court has jurisdiction over various offenses, from drug-related crimes to property offenses. Yet, to try a juvenile as an adult, prosecutors need to initiate a transfer. The U.S. Attorney’s Office only prosecutes the serious crimes listed in the statute.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Graves’ office can potentially prosecute 16 and 17-year-olds as adults, they seem to prioritize certain cases. The police affirm that the U.S. Attorney’s Office holds the initial right to decide on the prosecution. If they refuse, the case gets presented to the office of the Attorney General.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Police officials, like Assistant Chief of the Investigative Services Bureau Carlos Heraud, are still trying to pinpoint the exact reasons for this surge. Is it due to influence from social media, a lack of perceived consequences, or peer discussions at schools? The exact cause remains elusive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This surge in crime isn’t isolated to carjackings. The entire District witnessed a significant escalation in violent crimes this year. The rates have soared up by nearly &lt;strong&gt;40%&lt;/strong&gt; year over year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The city’s deteriorating safety was further underscored when Rep. Henry Cuellar (D-TX) faced a carjacking near the Capitol Building. He described the horrifying ordeal, stating that while he has a black belt, facing multiple guns left him with no choice but to hand over his vehicle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As D.C. grapples with this unsettling rise in crime, the immediate focus should be on understanding the underlying causes and implementing robust preventive measures. Only then can residents hope for safer streets.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a startling revelation, carjackings in Washington D.C. skyrocketed by an astounding 111% in the first ten months of 2023, compared to the same period in 2022. Police, while still piecing together the ‘why,’ highlight a noteworthy detail: the majority of the arrested individuals are below 18 years. In 2023, the U.S. capital reported a whopping 760 carjackings. In contrast, there were only 360 in the same time frame last year. To put things into perspective, the carjackings this year alone surpassed the total of 2018, 2019, and 2020 combined. These alarming figures suggest a deep-rooted issue that law enforcement and the justice system must address. Most carjackings reportedly occur around the H Street Corridor and the regions adjacent to the Anacostia River bordering Maryland. Police data emphasizes that a staggering 65% of those involved in these thefts are juveniles. It’s not just the age of the culprits that’s concerning. U.S. Attorney for D.C., Matthew Graves, admitted that the majority of individuals arrested for such crimes are young. However, his office often does not prosecute them, especially if they are under 16. In 2022, Graves refused to prosecute 67% of those who could have been tried in the D.C. Superior Court. This number is notably high when considering juvenile crimes, where he did not press charges for 26%. One might wonder if this trend of non-prosecution is contributing to the surge. D.C.’s juvenile court has jurisdiction over various offenses, from drug-related crimes to property offenses. Yet, to try a juvenile as an adult, prosecutors need to initiate a transfer. The U.S. Attorney’s Office only prosecutes the serious crimes listed in the statute. While Graves’ office can potentially prosecute 16 and 17-year-olds as adults, they seem to prioritize certain cases. The police affirm that the U.S. Attorney’s Office holds the initial right to decide on the prosecution. If they refuse, the case gets presented to the office of the Attorney General. Police officials, like Assistant Chief of the Investigative Services Bureau Carlos Heraud, are still trying to pinpoint the exact reasons for this surge. Is it due to influence from social media, a lack of perceived consequences, or peer discussions at schools? The exact cause remains elusive. This surge in crime isn’t isolated to carjackings. The entire District witnessed a significant escalation in violent crimes this year. The rates have soared up by nearly 40% year over year. The city’s deteriorating safety was further underscored when Rep. Henry Cuellar (D-TX) faced a carjacking near the Capitol Building. He described the horrifying ordeal, stating that while he has a black belt, facing multiple guns left him with no choice but to hand over his vehicle. As D.C. grapples with this unsettling rise in crime, the immediate focus should be on understanding the underlying causes and implementing robust preventive measures. Only then can residents hope for safer streets.</summary></entry></feed>