<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-09-06T13:13:38-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/09/06/2023-08-10-King-of-the-Hill-Actor-Johnny-Hardwick-Passes/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-09-06T13:13:38-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-06T13:13:38-04:00</updated><id>/2023/09/06/2023-08-10-King-of-the-Hill-Actor-Johnny-Hardwick-Passes</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/06/2023-08-10-King-of-the-Hill-Actor-Johnny-Hardwick-Passes/">&lt;p&gt;The entertainment industry is mourning the loss of Johnny Hardwick, the acclaimed voice actor renowned for his portrayal of Dale Gribble in the popular animated series “King of the Hill.” At the age of 64, Hardwick’s demise has left many in shock.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The distressing news was confirmed by the Austin (Texas) Police Department, which attended a welfare check on Tuesday, leading to the tragic discovery of Hardwick’s lifeless body. While the circumstances surrounding his death are still shrouded in mystery, the Austin police have categorically stated that it isn’t a homicide case. Further details pertaining to the cause will be unveiled once the Travis County Medical Examiner finalizes their findings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hardwick’s role as Dale Gribble began in 1997 with the show’s premiere episode and lasted until its conclusion in 2010, spanning an impressive 259 episodes. His outstanding contribution to “King of the Hill” earned him an Emmy Award in 1999, followed by nominations in 2001 and 2002. The animated masterpiece was the brainchild of creators Mike Judge and Greg Daniels, with a cast ensemble including talents like Judge himself, Kathy Najimy, Stephen Root, and Pamela Adlon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earlier this year, fans rejoiced upon learning about a forthcoming revival of “King of the Hill,” with Hardwick’s involvement confirmed. Craig Erwich, the executive at the helm of ABC Entertainment, Hulu, and Disney Branded Television Streaming Originals, expressed enthusiasm about resuming the show’s narrative to reflect on our contemporary world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond his notable voice acting career, Hardwick was also a gifted stand-up comedian, making a mark in the comedy circuits during the 1990s.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/09/06/2023-08-12-Ian-Watkins-Assault/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-09-06T13:13:38-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-06T13:13:38-04:00</updated><id>/2023/09/06/2023-08-12-Ian-Watkins-Assault</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/06/2023-08-12-Ian-Watkins-Assault/">&lt;p&gt;Ian Watkins, the controversial former lead singer of the rock band Lostprophets, faced a brutal assault inside HMP Wakefield, where he’s currently serving a 29-year sentence for grave child sex crimes. According to sources, Watkins is in critical condition following the incident.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reports from the Mirror shed light on the gruesome nature of the assault. Allegedly, Watkins was accosted and held hostage by three inmates, subjected to hours of physical abuse, and eventually stabbed multiple times. Officers discovered the critically injured singer only hours later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Watkins was held for a lengthy period by the prisoners and endured a severe beating before the stabbing. The entire ordeal is under investigation,” conveyed the officials from HMP Wakefield. Fortunately, in a subsequent update from law enforcement, it was clarified that Watkins’ injuries, while severe, were not life-threatening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lostprophets, active from the late ’90s to the early 2000s, witnessed their downfall following the shocking revelations of Watkins’ depravities. In 2013, he faced charges for thirteen appalling sex offenses against children, which included the attempted rape of a one-year-old girl. The case revealed that Watkins administered drugs to children, plotting their sexual abuse, and even filmed some of his heinous acts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Confronted with overwhelming evidence, Watkins pleaded guilty to multiple counts of rape, sex with minors, and the possession of disturbing explicit content. His conviction in December 2013 led to the disintegration of the Lostprophets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jo Mjadzelics, one of Watkins’ former partners, expressed her shock at the recent attack, stating to the Mirror, “It’s surprising that such a brutal attack took so long, especially in a prison like Wakefield.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The broader implications of the attack on Watkins underline the volatile dynamics within prison systems, especially for individuals convicted of particularly reviled crimes. The repercussions of his crimes, it seems, continue to echo both for Watkins and for those who were once associated with him.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/09/06/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-09-06T13:13:38-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-06T13:13:38-04:00</updated><id>/2023/09/06/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/06/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/09/06/2023-08-29-Consumer-Confidence-Drop/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-09-06T13:13:38-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-06T13:13:38-04:00</updated><id>/2023/09/06/2023-08-29-Consumer-Confidence-Drop</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/06/2023-08-29-Consumer-Confidence-Drop/">&lt;p&gt;As the summer season draws to a close, Americans are beginning to tighten their purse strings, reacting to high prices, surging interest rates, and a potentially cooling job market. Economic indicators released on Tuesday revealed a decline in U.S. job openings, dropping to 8.8 million in July from 9.2 million in June, according to the U.S. Labor Department.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bankrate’s Senior Economic Analyst, Mark Hamrick, remarked to Newsmax Finance, “That translates to roughly 1.5 job openings for every unemployed individual in the U.S. We’ve also observed a reduction in the number and rate of job resignations.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further exacerbating concerns, The Conference Board, a notable business research group, announced that its consumer confidence index plummeted to 106.1 in August, down from July’s revised 114. This dip in confidence has seemingly mirrored the stock market’s own decline during the month, undoing the gains observed in June and July.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The data provides insights into the public’s view on both the present-day economic landscape and their anticipations for the coming half-year, with both dimensions witnessing sharp decreases in August. While the assessment of the current economic climate decreased to 144.8 from 153, the expectations for the future plunged to 80.2 from July’s 88. Historically, any value below 80 in future expectations is a potential harbinger of a recession within the ensuing year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given that consumer spending propels approximately 70% of U.S. economic activities, fluctuations in their sentiment serve as a barometer for the nation’s economic health.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The late spring had witnessed a resurgence in consumer confidence as inflationary pressures eased in light of the Federal Reserve’s 11 consecutive interest rate hikes. However, August’s downturn underscores the prevailing consumer trepidation about purchasing non-essential items, more so if these purchases necessitate the use of high-interest credit cards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The chief economist at The Conference Board, Dana Peterson, shared, “Write-in responses have highlighted a renewed consumer focus on surging prices, particularly in essential sectors such as groceries and gasoline.” Peterson further noted the evident decline in consumer confidence across all demographic groups.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This caution in expenditure is clearly visible in the quarterly reports of numerous renowned retailers. For instance, Target posted its inaugural quarterly sales dip in six years earlier in August, a result of conservative consumer spending. Similarly, Home Depot, America’s premier home improvement retailer, observed persistent sales declines, particularly in high-value items necessitating financing. Furthermore, Best Buy’s recent disclosures reveal reduced sales and profits for Q2, attributing the decline to reduced gadget expenditure, a marked contrast to the pandemic era splurge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though the U.S. economy, the globe’s most substantial, has displayed unexpected resilience despite soaring borrowing costs, with employers registering an impressive 278,000 job additions per month this year, recent indicators suggest a potential shift. As families and individuals recalibrate their budgets for the upcoming school year and in anticipation of the holiday season, the economic trajectory for the remaining year remains uncertain.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/09/06/2023-09-05-Disney-Wokeness/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-09-06T13:13:38-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-06T13:13:38-04:00</updated><id>/2023/09/06/2023-09-05-Disney-Wokeness</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/06/2023-09-05-Disney-Wokeness/">&lt;p&gt;Disney, the once-celebrated beacon of childhood wonder and family entertainment, now seems to be sinking in the quicksand of modern-day “wokeness.” With a series of missteps that some argue deviate from its core values, the entertainment titan is undergoing significant turbulence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From Fairy Tales to Identity Politics&lt;/strong&gt;
For a century, Disney was synonymous with magical adventures and fairy tales. But the present-day Disney appears more engrossed in pushing identity politics and heavy themes of sexuality and gender than in weaving universal tales of wonder. This radical shift from delighting audiences to lecturing them could be the root of their recent challenges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stocks Dive in the Wake of Wokeness&lt;/strong&gt;
If the stock market is any indication, the “woke” direction hasn’t served Disney well. From a prosperous value of around $200 two years ago, the stock has plummeted to a concerning $81.84, marking almost a ten-year low. This decline showcases a clear investor response to the company’s modern-day stances.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disney+ or Disney Minus?&lt;/strong&gt;
The launch of Disney+ promised a new era of streaming, but instead, it seems to have become a showcase for the company’s new “woke” approach. Legal action from investors alleges the company has been less than transparent about its profitability forecasts, with some suggesting that this new content direction is a significant factor in the platform’s economic underperformance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Box Office Reflects the Mood&lt;/strong&gt;
Out of the six major releases this year, five either bombed or missed the mark significantly. When familiar stories are laced with overt political messaging and identity agendas, it’s clear audiences are choosing to stay away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Theme Parks – Lost in Translation?&lt;/strong&gt;
The magic of Disney’s theme parks seems to be fizzling out, with dwindling visitors and a sense that the classic Disney experience is being overshadowed by a more controversial narrative.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Once-Loved Franchises Suffer&lt;/strong&gt;
The new approach has seeped into acquisitions, with giants like Star Wars, Marvel, Indiana Jones, and Pixar facing backlash for their recent content. The magic that once surrounded these franchises is waning, replaced by divisive storylines and characters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Disney’s transformation from an entertainment powerhouse to a platform seemingly more concerned with being “woke” than with universal storytelling is evident. If the recent setbacks are any indication, it might be time for the corporation to reflect on its roots and consider if being “woke” is worth the cost.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">The Rolling Stones Rock London - Unveil ‘Hackney Diamonds”’</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/06/Rolling-Stones-New-Album/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Rolling Stones Rock London - Unveil ‘Hackney Diamonds”’" /><published>2023-09-06T12:59:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-06T12:59:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/06/Rolling-Stones-New-Album</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/06/Rolling-Stones-New-Album/">&lt;p&gt;The streets of London’s Hackney district were thrumming with excitement as The Rolling Stones geared up to announce their brand new album, “Hackney Diamonds.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By early Wednesday, a wave of devoted fans began gathering outside the historical Hackney Empire. The illustrious venue has hosted legends like Charlie Chaplin and Stan Laurel in its storied past. Adding to the day’s allure, none other than “The Tonight Show” host Jimmy Fallon was set to interview the iconic trio - Mick Jagger, Keith Richards, and Ronnie Wood - in a much-anticipated livestream event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Inside the Hackney Empire, a venue steeped in history, the members of the legendary rock band - Jagger (80), Richards (79), and Wood (76) - shared insights into their latest work. This marks the Stones’ first studio album containing original songs since “A Bigger Bang” dropped in 2005, although they did grace fans with a blues cover album, “Blue &amp;amp; Lonesome,” in 2016.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of significant note, “Hackney Diamonds” is the first album since the passing of the band’s esteemed drummer, Charlie Watts, in 2021. Despite this loss, his contributions to the album, recorded prior to his demise, ensure his legacy shines on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Among the sea of fans, Brazilian enthusiast Taric Fioravanti from Sao Paulo expressed his deep-rooted admiration for the band and voiced his anticipation for the album. He remarked, “Keith Richards is one of the biggest guitar heroes in the history of rock music.” He further emphasized the band’s unparalleled vitality, pointing out that “they’re 80 years old. Most bands have stopped making new music” by that age.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adding to the album’s aura, the Stones embarked on a cryptic teaser campaign where their emblematic mouth and tongue logo graced landmarks in cities like New York, London, and Paris. The story behind their choice of Hackney for the album title may find roots in its rich tapestry of talent, having birthed legends like playwright Harold Pinter and actor Idris Elba.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a nod to the title, “Hackney Diamonds,” which refers to shattered glass in slang, the band ingeniously teased an ad in the local Hackney Gazette for a fictional glass repair enterprise, reading, “When you say gimme shelter, we’ll fix your shattered windows.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though formed in 1962, The Rolling Stones’ zest for music and live performances remains insatiable. They celebrated their 60th anniversary with a European tour last year, with Steve Jordan stepping in for Watts on drums. As they unveil “Hackney Diamonds,” their legacy as rock’s immortal luminaries is further cemented.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">The streets of London’s Hackney district were thrumming with excitement as The Rolling Stones geared up to announce their brand new album, “Hackney Diamonds.” By early Wednesday, a wave of devoted fans began gathering outside the historical Hackney Empire. The illustrious venue has hosted legends like Charlie Chaplin and Stan Laurel in its storied past. Adding to the day’s allure, none other than “The Tonight Show” host Jimmy Fallon was set to interview the iconic trio - Mick Jagger, Keith Richards, and Ronnie Wood - in a much-anticipated livestream event. Inside the Hackney Empire, a venue steeped in history, the members of the legendary rock band - Jagger (80), Richards (79), and Wood (76) - shared insights into their latest work. This marks the Stones’ first studio album containing original songs since “A Bigger Bang” dropped in 2005, although they did grace fans with a blues cover album, “Blue &amp;amp; Lonesome,” in 2016. Of significant note, “Hackney Diamonds” is the first album since the passing of the band’s esteemed drummer, Charlie Watts, in 2021. Despite this loss, his contributions to the album, recorded prior to his demise, ensure his legacy shines on. Among the sea of fans, Brazilian enthusiast Taric Fioravanti from Sao Paulo expressed his deep-rooted admiration for the band and voiced his anticipation for the album. He remarked, “Keith Richards is one of the biggest guitar heroes in the history of rock music.” He further emphasized the band’s unparalleled vitality, pointing out that “they’re 80 years old. Most bands have stopped making new music” by that age. Adding to the album’s aura, the Stones embarked on a cryptic teaser campaign where their emblematic mouth and tongue logo graced landmarks in cities like New York, London, and Paris. The story behind their choice of Hackney for the album title may find roots in its rich tapestry of talent, having birthed legends like playwright Harold Pinter and actor Idris Elba. As a nod to the title, “Hackney Diamonds,” which refers to shattered glass in slang, the band ingeniously teased an ad in the local Hackney Gazette for a fictional glass repair enterprise, reading, “When you say gimme shelter, we’ll fix your shattered windows.” Though formed in 1962, The Rolling Stones’ zest for music and live performances remains insatiable. They celebrated their 60th anniversary with a European tour last year, with Steve Jordan stepping in for Watts on drums. As they unveil “Hackney Diamonds,” their legacy as rock’s immortal luminaries is further cemented.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Unearthing the Bidens - Unmasking the Collusion Allegations</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/06/Biden-Collusion-Claims/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Unearthing the Bidens - Unmasking the Collusion Allegations" /><published>2023-09-06T12:02:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-06T12:02:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/06/Biden-Collusion-Claims</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/06/Biden-Collusion-Claims/">&lt;p&gt;Doubts and suspicions around then-Vice President Joe Biden’s mingling with his son Hunter Biden’s business associates continue to deepen. As per the recent developments, House Oversight Committee Chairman Rep. James Comer, R-Ky., has put forth a request to the National Archives, demanding unredacted emails highlighting the extent of communication between Biden’s VP office and Hunter’s business contacts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given the legal obligation of the National Archives and Records Administration (NARA) to store crucial governmental communication, Comer seeks access to a specific record, dubbed “Records on Hunter Biden, James Biden, and Their Foreign Business Dealings.” This record gained visibility following an active Freedom of Information Act lawsuit by America First Legal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Comer’s demand does not stop at just emails. In a bid to potentially uncover evidence of impropriety, the letter specifically calls for unredacted emails that spotlight the engagement between Biden’s VP office aides and business contacts from Hunter’s former firm, Rosemont Seneca Partners, and the contentious Ukrainian energy corporation, Burisma Holdings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One noteworthy excerpt from the provided documents reveals an email correspondence between Eric Schwerin, a known Biden family business associate, and Kate Bedingfield, a staffer in the VP’s office. The exchange details quotes for the White House to use in defending Hunter’s involvement with Burisma. The approval came directly from the VP, further exacerbating concerns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Comer’s allegations are severe. He insinuates not just an overlap but “evidence of collusion” between Biden’s official duties and his son’s business pursuits. According to Comer, the VP’s office was a revolving door for Hunter’s business affiliates. Moreover, Biden’s vehement public stand against corruption in Ukraine starkly contrasts with the alleged back-door dealings concerning Burisma’s corruption.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The scrutiny doesn’t end with just the Bidens. Comer’s letter has also asked for executive calendars from Biden’s tenure as Vice President. The motive behind this, as stated by Comer, is to mold potential legislation to address glaring ethical oversights concerning the financial interests of immediate family members of high-ranking officials. These deficiencies, as Comer suggests, might be endangering American national security and broader interests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Drawing the curtains on the issue, Comer asserts the need for accountability, emphasizing that Americans deserve transparency, especially when it pertains to potential misuse of governmental office for personal gains.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the Oversight Committee stays committed to unearthing the truth, it remains to be seen how these allegations will play out in the grand scheme of American politics and what repercussions, if any, the Bidens might face.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Doubts and suspicions around then-Vice President Joe Biden’s mingling with his son Hunter Biden’s business associates continue to deepen. As per the recent developments, House Oversight Committee Chairman Rep. James Comer, R-Ky., has put forth a request to the National Archives, demanding unredacted emails highlighting the extent of communication between Biden’s VP office and Hunter’s business contacts. Given the legal obligation of the National Archives and Records Administration (NARA) to store crucial governmental communication, Comer seeks access to a specific record, dubbed “Records on Hunter Biden, James Biden, and Their Foreign Business Dealings.” This record gained visibility following an active Freedom of Information Act lawsuit by America First Legal. Comer’s demand does not stop at just emails. In a bid to potentially uncover evidence of impropriety, the letter specifically calls for unredacted emails that spotlight the engagement between Biden’s VP office aides and business contacts from Hunter’s former firm, Rosemont Seneca Partners, and the contentious Ukrainian energy corporation, Burisma Holdings. One noteworthy excerpt from the provided documents reveals an email correspondence between Eric Schwerin, a known Biden family business associate, and Kate Bedingfield, a staffer in the VP’s office. The exchange details quotes for the White House to use in defending Hunter’s involvement with Burisma. The approval came directly from the VP, further exacerbating concerns. Comer’s allegations are severe. He insinuates not just an overlap but “evidence of collusion” between Biden’s official duties and his son’s business pursuits. According to Comer, the VP’s office was a revolving door for Hunter’s business affiliates. Moreover, Biden’s vehement public stand against corruption in Ukraine starkly contrasts with the alleged back-door dealings concerning Burisma’s corruption. The scrutiny doesn’t end with just the Bidens. Comer’s letter has also asked for executive calendars from Biden’s tenure as Vice President. The motive behind this, as stated by Comer, is to mold potential legislation to address glaring ethical oversights concerning the financial interests of immediate family members of high-ranking officials. These deficiencies, as Comer suggests, might be endangering American national security and broader interests. Drawing the curtains on the issue, Comer asserts the need for accountability, emphasizing that Americans deserve transparency, especially when it pertains to potential misuse of governmental office for personal gains. As the Oversight Committee stays committed to unearthing the truth, it remains to be seen how these allegations will play out in the grand scheme of American politics and what repercussions, if any, the Bidens might face.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The AI Overlords - Will Americans Soon Be Working for Machines?</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/06/2023-09-06-AI-Workforce-Concerns/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The AI Overlords - Will Americans Soon Be Working for Machines?" /><published>2023-09-06T10:52:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-06T10:52:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/06/2023-09-06-AI-Workforce-Concerns</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/06/2023-09-06-AI-Workforce-Concerns/">&lt;p&gt;The rapid advancement of artificial intelligence (AI) is reshaping industries, businesses, and our way of life. As technological marvels are celebrated, concerns over AI’s impact on the future of employment are also growing. One prominent voice adding to this discourse is former Labor Secretary Robert Reich, who recently shared his perspective on how AI could redefine the dynamics of the American workplace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a candid interview, Reich, who held the labor secretary position during the Clinton era, highlighted the potential upheavals AI could bring to the employer-employee relationship. Emphasizing a significant shift, Reich said, “We’re not going to be working for big companies. We’re going to be working for AI intermediaries and platforms.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Such platforms, according to Reich, might determine pay rates based on spot auctions — gauging demand and supply at any given moment. While this approach might enhance efficiency, the unpredictability it introduces could be “extremely destabilizing” for workers. It could also threaten labor protections painstakingly achieved over the last 120 years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recent studies have echoed similar concerns. A Pew Research survey uncovered that an increasing number of Americans are apprehensive about the pervasive role of AI in daily life. The findings revealed that many are “more concerned than excited” about the growing dominance of such technology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Senator Chuck Schumer, D-NY, is among the lawmakers cognizant of the challenges and potential pitfalls of unchecked AI growth. In a recent letter, Schumer expressed the gravity of the situation, comparing the importance of addressing AI’s challenges with matters of national security, job creation, and civil liberties. He urged for a robust regulatory framework to ensure the responsible evolution of this technology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As solutions for these looming challenges are sought, Reich reintroduces the idea of a universal basic income (UBI). He argues that as AI platforms and machines take over more roles, resulting in numerous people no longer being vital to the workforce, there needs to be a way to ensure they have sufficient income. “People have got to have enough money in their pockets to buy all the things that the new economy is capable of producing,” Reich remarked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The progression of AI offers immense possibilities, but it’s evident that it also brings about fundamental questions concerning employment, income, and societal norms. As the debate continues, it’s crucial to strike a balance that not only propels technological advancements but also safeguards the livelihoods and well-being of the workforce.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">The rapid advancement of artificial intelligence (AI) is reshaping industries, businesses, and our way of life. As technological marvels are celebrated, concerns over AI’s impact on the future of employment are also growing. One prominent voice adding to this discourse is former Labor Secretary Robert Reich, who recently shared his perspective on how AI could redefine the dynamics of the American workplace. In a candid interview, Reich, who held the labor secretary position during the Clinton era, highlighted the potential upheavals AI could bring to the employer-employee relationship. Emphasizing a significant shift, Reich said, “We’re not going to be working for big companies. We’re going to be working for AI intermediaries and platforms.” Such platforms, according to Reich, might determine pay rates based on spot auctions — gauging demand and supply at any given moment. While this approach might enhance efficiency, the unpredictability it introduces could be “extremely destabilizing” for workers. It could also threaten labor protections painstakingly achieved over the last 120 years. Recent studies have echoed similar concerns. A Pew Research survey uncovered that an increasing number of Americans are apprehensive about the pervasive role of AI in daily life. The findings revealed that many are “more concerned than excited” about the growing dominance of such technology. Senator Chuck Schumer, D-NY, is among the lawmakers cognizant of the challenges and potential pitfalls of unchecked AI growth. In a recent letter, Schumer expressed the gravity of the situation, comparing the importance of addressing AI’s challenges with matters of national security, job creation, and civil liberties. He urged for a robust regulatory framework to ensure the responsible evolution of this technology. As solutions for these looming challenges are sought, Reich reintroduces the idea of a universal basic income (UBI). He argues that as AI platforms and machines take over more roles, resulting in numerous people no longer being vital to the workforce, there needs to be a way to ensure they have sufficient income. “People have got to have enough money in their pockets to buy all the things that the new economy is capable of producing,” Reich remarked. The progression of AI offers immense possibilities, but it’s evident that it also brings about fundamental questions concerning employment, income, and societal norms. As the debate continues, it’s crucial to strike a balance that not only propels technological advancements but also safeguards the livelihoods and well-being of the workforce.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Delta’s Poopy Predicament - The Flight That Couldn’t Hold It!</title><link href="/news/2023/09/06/2023-09-06-Delta-Diarrhea-Disaster/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Delta’s Poopy Predicament - The Flight That Couldn’t Hold It!" /><published>2023-09-06T09:45:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-06T09:45:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/06/2023-09-06-Delta-Diarrhea-Disaster</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/06/2023-09-06-Delta-Diarrhea-Disaster/">&lt;p&gt;Ever been in a situation where your stomach lets out a monstrous growl, signaling the imminent approach of a bathroom emergency? Now, imagine that while cruising at 30,000 feet with no escape. One passenger on a Delta flight to Barcelona can attest to this misadventure, proving once and for all that the phrase “shit happens” is not just a metaphor!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To Barcelona, and… Back?&lt;/strong&gt;
Just two hours into its eight-hour transatlantic journey, the Delta flight was forced into a U-turn back to Atlanta. Why, you ask? A diarrhea disaster of epic proportions. As per the official announcement from the cockpit, “This is a biohazard issue.” Well, that’s one way to make a splash on an international flight!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After already enduring a two-hour delay before take-off, this Delta flight couldn’t seem to catch a break. A word of advice? Maybe it’s time to rethink the in-flight menu.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Social Media Flies High on The News&lt;/strong&gt;
As expected, the story quickly took off on the internet, with one Reddit post showcasing the Federal Aviation Administration (FAA) flight strip for Flight DL194 – the infamous diarrhea flight. To no one’s surprise, the plane required a thorough scrub-down before embarking on its doo-doo-free journey to Spain once more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What remained a mystery, however, was whether the “culprit” was aboard the plane for its second attempt. One can only hope that they packed a change of clothes… and maybe some Pepto-Bismol.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Delta’s “Crap-tastic” Week&lt;/strong&gt;
To add to the stink of the situation, this messy incident came right on the heels of another Delta hiccup. Just three days prior, extreme turbulence on a Delta flight from Milan to Atlanta sent 11 passengers to the hospital. Quite the roller-coaster (or should we say, toilet-bowl swirl?) week for Delta!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Delta, ever the professionals, addressed the “doo-doo” incident with an official statement: “Our teams worked as quickly and safely as possible to thoroughly clean the airplane and get our customers to their final destination.” They also expressed their sincere apologies for the “delay and inconvenience to their travel plans.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And to the brave passenger at the center of this incident? Next time, maybe opt for the train. Less air time, and more… restroom options!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Ever been in a situation where your stomach lets out a monstrous growl, signaling the imminent approach of a bathroom emergency? Now, imagine that while cruising at 30,000 feet with no escape. One passenger on a Delta flight to Barcelona can attest to this misadventure, proving once and for all that the phrase “shit happens” is not just a metaphor! To Barcelona, and… Back? Just two hours into its eight-hour transatlantic journey, the Delta flight was forced into a U-turn back to Atlanta. Why, you ask? A diarrhea disaster of epic proportions. As per the official announcement from the cockpit, “This is a biohazard issue.” Well, that’s one way to make a splash on an international flight! After already enduring a two-hour delay before take-off, this Delta flight couldn’t seem to catch a break. A word of advice? Maybe it’s time to rethink the in-flight menu. Social Media Flies High on The News As expected, the story quickly took off on the internet, with one Reddit post showcasing the Federal Aviation Administration (FAA) flight strip for Flight DL194 – the infamous diarrhea flight. To no one’s surprise, the plane required a thorough scrub-down before embarking on its doo-doo-free journey to Spain once more. What remained a mystery, however, was whether the “culprit” was aboard the plane for its second attempt. One can only hope that they packed a change of clothes… and maybe some Pepto-Bismol. Delta’s “Crap-tastic” Week To add to the stink of the situation, this messy incident came right on the heels of another Delta hiccup. Just three days prior, extreme turbulence on a Delta flight from Milan to Atlanta sent 11 passengers to the hospital. Quite the roller-coaster (or should we say, toilet-bowl swirl?) week for Delta! Delta, ever the professionals, addressed the “doo-doo” incident with an official statement: “Our teams worked as quickly and safely as possible to thoroughly clean the airplane and get our customers to their final destination.” They also expressed their sincere apologies for the “delay and inconvenience to their travel plans.” And to the brave passenger at the center of this incident? Next time, maybe opt for the train. Less air time, and more… restroom options!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Crime Spikes in Wisconsin - Liberal Policies to Blame?</title><link href="/news/2023/09/06/2023-09-06-Democrats-Crime-Wisconsin/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Crime Spikes in Wisconsin - Liberal Policies to Blame?" /><published>2023-09-06T08:58:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-06T08:58:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/06/2023-09-06-Democrats-Crime-Wisconsin</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/06/2023-09-06-Democrats-Crime-Wisconsin/">&lt;p&gt;In a chilling reminder of the potential consequences of liberal policies, Madison – Wisconsin’s progressive capital – witnessed a brutal assault on a female student from the University of Wisconsin-Madison, sparking widespread concerns regarding city safety.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;De-funding the Police: A Recipe for Disaster?&lt;/strong&gt;
The unsettling attack occurred shortly after the Badgers football team’s victory, leaving the victim with life-threatening injuries. A mere stone’s throw away from Lake Monona, the attack occurred during the early morning hours at the intersection of South Bedford and West Wilson streets. As the victim fought for her life, one couldn’t help but ponder the repercussions of Madison’s decision to slash police funds in 2020. In a move heralded by many left-leaning activists, Madison reduced the police budget by $2 million, as reported by the city’s weekly newspaper, the Capital Times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The decision, which came in the wake of protests against alleged police brutality, has now left many questioning the Democrats’ approach to community safety. It seems ironic that a city which purportedly championed progressive ideals has now had to increase police patrols in the aftermath of such a heinous act.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Cry for Safety&lt;/strong&gt;
The victim’s ordeal paints a grim picture – abducted off the sidewalk and subjected to unimaginable cruelty. The fact that this took place in a college town, where young minds are expected to pursue their dreams in safety, adds to the tragedy. Police continue their hunt for the perpetrators, urging residents to share any security footage that could provide valuable leads.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But the haunting question remains. Could Madison’s slide into crime have been avoided if the Democrats had adopted a more balanced approach, rather than bowing to pressure and drastically reducing the police budget? The incident calls into sharp focus the wisdom of defunding the police – a move many conservatives argue leaves communities vulnerable and potentially, in harm’s way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reflecting on this incident, one can’t help but remember a post from a concerned young woman on Reddit last year, questioning the safety of walking alone late at night in Madison. The top reply, a simple “No,” now seems prophetic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As Madison grapples with the consequences of its policies, residents are now urged to remain vigilant, avoid walking alone at night, and always stay aware of their surroundings. This incident stands as a testament to the potential dangers of embracing radical reforms without fully considering the potential ramifications for community safety.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In a chilling reminder of the potential consequences of liberal policies, Madison – Wisconsin’s progressive capital – witnessed a brutal assault on a female student from the University of Wisconsin-Madison, sparking widespread concerns regarding city safety. De-funding the Police: A Recipe for Disaster? The unsettling attack occurred shortly after the Badgers football team’s victory, leaving the victim with life-threatening injuries. A mere stone’s throw away from Lake Monona, the attack occurred during the early morning hours at the intersection of South Bedford and West Wilson streets. As the victim fought for her life, one couldn’t help but ponder the repercussions of Madison’s decision to slash police funds in 2020. In a move heralded by many left-leaning activists, Madison reduced the police budget by $2 million, as reported by the city’s weekly newspaper, the Capital Times. The decision, which came in the wake of protests against alleged police brutality, has now left many questioning the Democrats’ approach to community safety. It seems ironic that a city which purportedly championed progressive ideals has now had to increase police patrols in the aftermath of such a heinous act. The Cry for Safety The victim’s ordeal paints a grim picture – abducted off the sidewalk and subjected to unimaginable cruelty. The fact that this took place in a college town, where young minds are expected to pursue their dreams in safety, adds to the tragedy. Police continue their hunt for the perpetrators, urging residents to share any security footage that could provide valuable leads. But the haunting question remains. Could Madison’s slide into crime have been avoided if the Democrats had adopted a more balanced approach, rather than bowing to pressure and drastically reducing the police budget? The incident calls into sharp focus the wisdom of defunding the police – a move many conservatives argue leaves communities vulnerable and potentially, in harm’s way. Reflecting on this incident, one can’t help but remember a post from a concerned young woman on Reddit last year, questioning the safety of walking alone late at night in Madison. The top reply, a simple “No,” now seems prophetic. As Madison grapples with the consequences of its policies, residents are now urged to remain vigilant, avoid walking alone at night, and always stay aware of their surroundings. This incident stands as a testament to the potential dangers of embracing radical reforms without fully considering the potential ramifications for community safety.</summary></entry></feed>