<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-10-17T19:15:12-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/17/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-17T19:15:12-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-17T19:15:12-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/17/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/17/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/10/17/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-10-17T19:15:12-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-17T19:15:12-04:00</updated><id>/2023/10/17/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/10/17/2023-10-08-Squad-Controversy-Israel/">&lt;p&gt;Recent surprise attacks by Hamas on Israel has fueled ongoing tensions between staunchly conservative commentators and the progressive “Squad” Democrats known for criticizing Israel. The intensity of the backlash highlights the deep political divide over foreign policy in the Middle East.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Hamas’ shocking attack, several members of the “Squad,” including Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.), called for a “ceasefire and de-escalation,” condemning the violence. The absence of a statement from Rep. Rashida Tlaib (D-Mich.) was notably called out by conservative media outlets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;South Carolina GOP Rep. Nancy Mace quickly labeled Ocasio-Cortez a “Hamas apologist” in response to her call for peace and de-escalation. Rep. Ilhan Omar (D-Minn.), no stranger to controversy surrounding her views on Israel, echoed the call for de-escalation and ceasefire. Omar’s prior statements comparing the US and Israel to terrorist groups like Hamas and the Taliban resurfaced in the debate, fueling more criticisms. Omar’s 2019 tweet, where she opined that “Israel has hypnotized the world,” also continues to haunt her political career, often cited by critics to challenge her stance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conservative commentators have been especially vocal. “FOX &amp;amp; Friends Weekend” co-host Rachel Campos-Duffy took aim at Omar, saying she fails to recognize the peace in the Middle East under Trump’s administration. Conservative pundit John Hasson also called out Omar, claiming she insinuated that attacks on IDF forces were acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Massachusetts Democrat Rep. Ayanna Pressley’s concerns over the “devastating attacks on Israelis” were met with skepticism. A prominent conservative online personality, Comfortably Smug, accused the “Squad” of advising Israel to back down after the nation suffered massive attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Jamaal Bowman’s call for an end to the Gaza blockade, in addition to condemning the Hamas attacks, was met with criticism from conservative radio host Jason Rantz. He accused Bowman of pairing his condemnation of terrorism with unwarranted criticisms of Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rep. Cori Bush emphasized the urgent need for a ceasefire, while pushing for an end to “U.S. support for Israeli military occupation and apartheid.” Defense attorney Marina Medvin criticized Bush, suggesting that she equates the death of Palestinian terrorists to the horrific acts committed against Jewish civilians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amidst the political turmoil and intense debate, the attacks have taken a heavy toll. Israeli media report over 300 dead due to the wide-ranging assault. Gaza health officials note that at least 200 Palestinians have perished in the retaliatory Israeli air strikes following the initial Hamas attack. As the situation remains volatile, both sides continue to count their casualties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This divisive issue showcases the challenge America faces in crafting a unified approach to foreign policy, with deeply entrenched political divides at play. As the situation develops, the debate is bound to intensify, shedding light on the complexities of U.S. politics in the global arena.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump Vehemently Opposes California’s New Gender Law</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/17/Trump-California-Gender-Law/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump Vehemently Opposes California’s New Gender Law" /><published>2023-10-17T16:15:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-17T16:15:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/17/Trump-California-Gender-Law</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/17/Trump-California-Gender-Law/">&lt;p&gt;In a fervent address, former President Donald Trump expressed his strong disapproval of California’s recent “sanctuary law” for children undergoing transgender-related medical treatments without parental consent. Trump, eyeing a return to the Oval Office in 2024, pledged to use federal laws, including those against child abuse and kidnapping, to counteract this state legislation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;California’s controversial law allows children to travel to the state for transgender-related procedures even if their parents from other states oppose it. Describing the legislation as a “horrific scheme,” Trump asserted that it permits “barbaric and irreversible” treatments that infringe upon parental rights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It’s sick,” said the 45th president, emphasizing the disbelief many share about the existence of such a law. Trump described the act of overriding parents’ rights as a sterilization of children. “The state of California has no right to take your children away from parents and to sterilize them, which is exactly what they’re doing,” Trump stressed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further elaborating on his stance, Trump promised that if reelected, he would address the issue on his first day in office. “Upon my inauguration, we will aggressively challenge these perverted California laws that strip parents of their rights and that encourage minors to be transported across state lines for sexual mutilation purposes,” he voiced with a sense of urgency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Throughout his address, Trump reiterated his commitment to ensuring the safety and well-being of the nation’s youth. “I will protect your youth. I will protect your children. I will protect the right of parents to make decisions on behalf of their children,” he passionately declared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expressing a broader concern for the nation’s trajectory, Trump concluded by saying, “We’re in a failing nation. This nation is failing. We’re not going to let it fail any longer. We’re going to make America great again.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The evolving dialogue and growing acceptance of transgenderism and “non-binary” concepts have raised eyebrows, especially concerning the youth. Recent studies indicate that social contagion may play a role in younger generations identifying as transgender. Disturbing reports, such as the one indicating that over 600 underage girls underwent breast removal in Canada for transgender purposes, further fuel the debate around this sensitive issue.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a fervent address, former President Donald Trump expressed his strong disapproval of California’s recent “sanctuary law” for children undergoing transgender-related medical treatments without parental consent. Trump, eyeing a return to the Oval Office in 2024, pledged to use federal laws, including those against child abuse and kidnapping, to counteract this state legislation. California’s controversial law allows children to travel to the state for transgender-related procedures even if their parents from other states oppose it. Describing the legislation as a “horrific scheme,” Trump asserted that it permits “barbaric and irreversible” treatments that infringe upon parental rights. “It’s sick,” said the 45th president, emphasizing the disbelief many share about the existence of such a law. Trump described the act of overriding parents’ rights as a sterilization of children. “The state of California has no right to take your children away from parents and to sterilize them, which is exactly what they’re doing,” Trump stressed. Further elaborating on his stance, Trump promised that if reelected, he would address the issue on his first day in office. “Upon my inauguration, we will aggressively challenge these perverted California laws that strip parents of their rights and that encourage minors to be transported across state lines for sexual mutilation purposes,” he voiced with a sense of urgency. Throughout his address, Trump reiterated his commitment to ensuring the safety and well-being of the nation’s youth. “I will protect your youth. I will protect your children. I will protect the right of parents to make decisions on behalf of their children,” he passionately declared. Expressing a broader concern for the nation’s trajectory, Trump concluded by saying, “We’re in a failing nation. This nation is failing. We’re not going to let it fail any longer. We’re going to make America great again.” The evolving dialogue and growing acceptance of transgenderism and “non-binary” concepts have raised eyebrows, especially concerning the youth. Recent studies indicate that social contagion may play a role in younger generations identifying as transgender. Disturbing reports, such as the one indicating that over 600 underage girls underwent breast removal in Canada for transgender purposes, further fuel the debate around this sensitive issue.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Supreme Court Oversteps with ‘Ghost Gun’ Directive</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/17/Ghost-Gun-Regulation-Critique/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Supreme Court Oversteps with ‘Ghost Gun’ Directive" /><published>2023-10-17T15:02:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-17T15:02:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/17/Ghost-Gun-Regulation-Critique</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/17/Ghost-Gun-Regulation-Critique/">&lt;p&gt;In what some view as an alarming overreach, the Supreme Court has dictated that two internet-based gun part vendors comply with a regulation championed by the Biden administration, targeting so-called ‘ghost guns’. These firearms, which lack serial numbers, have been portrayed by some as a looming threat, despite arguments from advocates about the importance of individual freedom and rights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earlier this year, the court, by a narrow margin of 5-4, opted to maintain the regulation after it had been sensibly negated by a lower-tier court. This recent verdict is made even more contentious given that no justice offered public dissent on Monday’s directive. This ruling, however, contradicts the decision of a federal Texas judge who rightfully exempted Blackhawk Manufacturing Group and Defense Distributed from this arguably intrusive regulation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hoping to justify this expansion of government oversight, the Biden administration communicated to the Supreme Court that other gun part producers were in line seeking similar legal protections.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Solicitor General Elizabeth Prelogar, in a somewhat fear-mongering tone, cautioned, “Without this Court’s interference, ghost guns would be accessible to anyone with a computer and a credit card, completely bypassing the need for a background check.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a dramatic regulatory shift, the Biden administration has broadened the definition of a firearm to include even unfinished parts, like a frame or a receiver. This move ostensibly aims for easier tracking, but in effect, burdens manufacturers and possibly infringes upon Second Amendment rights. These parts now need licensing and serial numbers, adding layers of bureaucracy to a once straightforward process. The rule also mandates background checks prior to any sale, equating these parts with commercial firearms – a false equivalence for many.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This regulation, alarmingly, doesn’t limit its reach, encapsulating all means of firearm production, including those from individual parts, kits, or even 3D printers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While this overreaching regulation remains active, the Biden administration plans to challenge the Texas judge’s decision at the 5th U.S. Circuit Court of Appeals in New Orleans. Many anticipate, with bated breath, the potential for this divisive issue to echo once again within the walls of the Supreme Court.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In what some view as an alarming overreach, the Supreme Court has dictated that two internet-based gun part vendors comply with a regulation championed by the Biden administration, targeting so-called ‘ghost guns’. These firearms, which lack serial numbers, have been portrayed by some as a looming threat, despite arguments from advocates about the importance of individual freedom and rights. Earlier this year, the court, by a narrow margin of 5-4, opted to maintain the regulation after it had been sensibly negated by a lower-tier court. This recent verdict is made even more contentious given that no justice offered public dissent on Monday’s directive. This ruling, however, contradicts the decision of a federal Texas judge who rightfully exempted Blackhawk Manufacturing Group and Defense Distributed from this arguably intrusive regulation. Hoping to justify this expansion of government oversight, the Biden administration communicated to the Supreme Court that other gun part producers were in line seeking similar legal protections. Solicitor General Elizabeth Prelogar, in a somewhat fear-mongering tone, cautioned, “Without this Court’s interference, ghost guns would be accessible to anyone with a computer and a credit card, completely bypassing the need for a background check.” In a dramatic regulatory shift, the Biden administration has broadened the definition of a firearm to include even unfinished parts, like a frame or a receiver. This move ostensibly aims for easier tracking, but in effect, burdens manufacturers and possibly infringes upon Second Amendment rights. These parts now need licensing and serial numbers, adding layers of bureaucracy to a once straightforward process. The rule also mandates background checks prior to any sale, equating these parts with commercial firearms – a false equivalence for many. This regulation, alarmingly, doesn’t limit its reach, encapsulating all means of firearm production, including those from individual parts, kits, or even 3D printers. While this overreaching regulation remains active, the Biden administration plans to challenge the Texas judge’s decision at the 5th U.S. Circuit Court of Appeals in New Orleans. Many anticipate, with bated breath, the potential for this divisive issue to echo once again within the walls of the Supreme Court.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Biden’s Spendthrift Strategy: Pouring Billions into Migrant Welfare?</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/17/Biden-Migrant-Costs/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Biden’s Spendthrift Strategy: Pouring Billions into Migrant Welfare?" /><published>2023-10-17T13:45:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-17T13:45:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/17/Biden-Migrant-Costs</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/17/Biden-Migrant-Costs/">&lt;p&gt;The Biden administration, in a controversial move, is poised to provide 5.7 million migrants with free medical services, food, and housing, according to leaked government documents. This announcement raises significant concerns about the administration’s financial prudence and its impact on U.S. taxpayers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overseen by Immigration and Customs Enforcement (ICE), the current number of migrants has spiked by an alarming 2.4 million since Biden took office. Buried in documentation concerning the “Release and Reporting Management” (RRM) program, these figures further highlight the administration’s arguably lax approach to border management.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ICE’s plan leans on private companies to track migrants using means like ankle monitors, phone apps, and in-person check-ins, showcasing a preference for outsourcing over streamlined federal operations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Former ICE Director Tom Homan, sounding the alarm, estimated that Biden’s proposal would run into “billions,” effectively turning into a “welfare” system for non-detained migrants awaiting court hearings. Homan didn’t mince words, asserting, “The RRM is essentially a green light to provide welfare benefits to nearly 6 million people on the taxpayer’s dime.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;RRM’s ambitious scope is set to “replace all of ICE’s nondetained programs” and be applied uniformly to the entire nondetained population. Notably, the 5.7 million estimation excludes migrants who are being processed or awaiting deportation — indicating that the true financial burden might be even more substantial.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A Request for Information (RFI) form detailed an expansive array of services under RRM: from legal assistance, therapeutic interventions, food, clothing, to housing. Additionally, services span information on public transport, parental and educational resources, and even repatriation. Such extensive offerings raise questions about the plan’s feasibility and long-term sustainability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Homan was particularly critical of the provision to offer legal aid to undocumented immigrants at the taxpayers’ expense, framing it as a “massive giveaway.” His apprehensions were underscored by the potential for this initiative to run into “billions of dollars.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the RRM remains in the planning phase, the Biden administration’s intent to introduce it as a successor to the “Alternatives to Detention” program from 2004 suggests that additional taxpayer funds will be diverted from other vital areas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As Biden forges ahead with this arguably lavish plan, the real cost — both financially and politically — remains to be seen. With such initiatives in the pipeline, questions about fiscal responsibility and prioritizing American citizens’ needs are bound to dominate political discourse.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">The Biden administration, in a controversial move, is poised to provide 5.7 million migrants with free medical services, food, and housing, according to leaked government documents. This announcement raises significant concerns about the administration’s financial prudence and its impact on U.S. taxpayers. Overseen by Immigration and Customs Enforcement (ICE), the current number of migrants has spiked by an alarming 2.4 million since Biden took office. Buried in documentation concerning the “Release and Reporting Management” (RRM) program, these figures further highlight the administration’s arguably lax approach to border management. ICE’s plan leans on private companies to track migrants using means like ankle monitors, phone apps, and in-person check-ins, showcasing a preference for outsourcing over streamlined federal operations. Former ICE Director Tom Homan, sounding the alarm, estimated that Biden’s proposal would run into “billions,” effectively turning into a “welfare” system for non-detained migrants awaiting court hearings. Homan didn’t mince words, asserting, “The RRM is essentially a green light to provide welfare benefits to nearly 6 million people on the taxpayer’s dime.” RRM’s ambitious scope is set to “replace all of ICE’s nondetained programs” and be applied uniformly to the entire nondetained population. Notably, the 5.7 million estimation excludes migrants who are being processed or awaiting deportation — indicating that the true financial burden might be even more substantial. A Request for Information (RFI) form detailed an expansive array of services under RRM: from legal assistance, therapeutic interventions, food, clothing, to housing. Additionally, services span information on public transport, parental and educational resources, and even repatriation. Such extensive offerings raise questions about the plan’s feasibility and long-term sustainability. Homan was particularly critical of the provision to offer legal aid to undocumented immigrants at the taxpayers’ expense, framing it as a “massive giveaway.” His apprehensions were underscored by the potential for this initiative to run into “billions of dollars.” While the RRM remains in the planning phase, the Biden administration’s intent to introduce it as a successor to the “Alternatives to Detention” program from 2004 suggests that additional taxpayer funds will be diverted from other vital areas. As Biden forges ahead with this arguably lavish plan, the real cost — both financially and politically — remains to be seen. With such initiatives in the pipeline, questions about fiscal responsibility and prioritizing American citizens’ needs are bound to dominate political discourse.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">HHS Champions Gender Identity: Mandates Pronoun Use for Employees</title><link href="/news/2023/10/17/Gender-Pronoun-Mandate/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="HHS Champions Gender Identity: Mandates Pronoun Use for Employees" /><published>2023-10-17T12:38:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-17T12:38:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/17/Gender-Pronoun-Mandate</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/17/Gender-Pronoun-Mandate/">&lt;p&gt;In an effort to champion a more inclusive and diverse workspace, President Joe Biden’s Department of Health and Human Services (HHS) has rolled out a new mandate. The latest guidance instructs the department’s considerable workforce of 80,000 to address transgender colleagues using their preferred pronouns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The “Gender Identity and Non-Discrimination Guidance” disseminated recently emphasizes the respect and recognition every employee is entitled to, regarding their gender identity. A reported HHS communication to its personnel specified that coworkers must be referred to by the names and pronouns they personally identify with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Complementing this, HHS Secretary Andrea Palm unveiled an “unlisted” video on YouTube emphasizing the essence of the policy. She underscores the department’s commitment to fostering an environment where everyone feels valid, appreciated, and can present their genuine selves, irrespective of their gender identity, sexual orientation, ethnicity, religion, or disability status. Yet, the stance on accommodating employees with religious objections to this new mandate remains ambiguous.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Admiral Rachel Levine, HHS Assistant Secretary for Health, who identifies as a transgender woman, is an ardent supporter of the policy. Levine stresses its pivotal role in ensuring all HHS personnel, inclusive of transgender and nonbinary individuals, experience a workplace devoid of discrimination. The onus of upholding and implementing this inclusive directive also rests on the department’s supervisors and managers, Levine added.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, this move has not been without its detractors. Roger Severino, who led the HHS Office for Civil Rights during Trump’s tenure, censured the department, asserting that they are imposing “compelled speech” and supplanting scientific evidence with gender ideologies. Severino, currently serving as the vice president of domestic policy at the Heritage Foundation, fears that this policy might be weaponized against Christian employees. He ardently argues that the First Amendment is under threat as the new policy seems to infringe on free speech and religious liberties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The newly instituted policy goes beyond just pronoun usage. It allows employees the freedom to choose clothing and access restrooms aligning with their gender identity. Moreover, the policy advises overhauling the department’s IT systems to reflect an employee’s transgender status accurately.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the new directive is hailed by many as a significant step toward fostering inclusion and diversity, questions remain. The primary concerns are the potential implications for free speech and the religious freedoms of employees. The HHS’s future course of action and its response to these concerns will be pivotal in shaping the discourse on inclusivity, freedom of speech, and religion in the workplace.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">In an effort to champion a more inclusive and diverse workspace, President Joe Biden’s Department of Health and Human Services (HHS) has rolled out a new mandate. The latest guidance instructs the department’s considerable workforce of 80,000 to address transgender colleagues using their preferred pronouns. The “Gender Identity and Non-Discrimination Guidance” disseminated recently emphasizes the respect and recognition every employee is entitled to, regarding their gender identity. A reported HHS communication to its personnel specified that coworkers must be referred to by the names and pronouns they personally identify with. Complementing this, HHS Secretary Andrea Palm unveiled an “unlisted” video on YouTube emphasizing the essence of the policy. She underscores the department’s commitment to fostering an environment where everyone feels valid, appreciated, and can present their genuine selves, irrespective of their gender identity, sexual orientation, ethnicity, religion, or disability status. Yet, the stance on accommodating employees with religious objections to this new mandate remains ambiguous. Admiral Rachel Levine, HHS Assistant Secretary for Health, who identifies as a transgender woman, is an ardent supporter of the policy. Levine stresses its pivotal role in ensuring all HHS personnel, inclusive of transgender and nonbinary individuals, experience a workplace devoid of discrimination. The onus of upholding and implementing this inclusive directive also rests on the department’s supervisors and managers, Levine added. However, this move has not been without its detractors. Roger Severino, who led the HHS Office for Civil Rights during Trump’s tenure, censured the department, asserting that they are imposing “compelled speech” and supplanting scientific evidence with gender ideologies. Severino, currently serving as the vice president of domestic policy at the Heritage Foundation, fears that this policy might be weaponized against Christian employees. He ardently argues that the First Amendment is under threat as the new policy seems to infringe on free speech and religious liberties. The newly instituted policy goes beyond just pronoun usage. It allows employees the freedom to choose clothing and access restrooms aligning with their gender identity. Moreover, the policy advises overhauling the department’s IT systems to reflect an employee’s transgender status accurately. While the new directive is hailed by many as a significant step toward fostering inclusion and diversity, questions remain. The primary concerns are the potential implications for free speech and the religious freedoms of employees. The HHS’s future course of action and its response to these concerns will be pivotal in shaping the discourse on inclusivity, freedom of speech, and religion in the workplace.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Brussels Terror Alert Soars as Swedes Gunned Down</title><link href="/news/2023/10/17/Terror-Alert-Brussels/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Brussels Terror Alert Soars as Swedes Gunned Down" /><published>2023-10-17T11:25:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-17T11:25:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/10/17/Terror-Alert-Brussels</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/10/17/Terror-Alert-Brussels/">&lt;p&gt;Brussels was rocked with fear and anxiety as two Swedish nationals were ruthlessly shot on a day when football enthusiasts from Belgium and Sweden were eagerly anticipating their clash on the pitch. As the city braced for the soccer matchup, tragedy struck, casting a dark shadow over the festivities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Belgian government swiftly escalated its terror alert to the most critical level following the attack. Adding to the apprehension, a video surfaced on social media where a man claims to be the perpetrator, linking himself to the notorious terrorist organization, Islamic State.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prime Minister Alexander de Croo, expressing his grief over the heinous act, took to the social media platform X, once Twitter, to convey his condolences. He acknowledged the victims were Swedish but remained tight-lipped on the exact number. The so-called assailant, introducing himself as Abdesalem Al Guilani, contested official reports, suggesting there were three victims, not just two.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Football enthusiasts awaiting the Euro 2024 qualifying match between Belgium and Sweden were left disheartened, as officials halted the match at halftime for security precautions. UEFA’s official site teased forthcoming details on the situation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The alarming episode in Brussels adds to a worrying trend seen across some European nations. The Israel-Hamas conflict has put regions on high alert, with nations such as France stepping up their security apparatus after tragic incidents of their own. The French nation witnessed a harrowing incident where a teacher was fatally stabbed in an act that President Emmanuel Macron labeled as “barbaric Islamic terrorism.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although official sources remain reserved, initial reports suggest the Brussels shooter might have been targeting soccer fans. Videos circulating among local media show a man in an orange jacket, wielding a rifle, brazenly shooting in broad daylight and subsequently seeking shelter in a building.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Witness accounts retrieved by a Belgian newspaper claimed that the shooter cried out “Allahu Akbar” before embarking on his violent spree.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The self-proclaimed assailant’s video message sheds further light on his motivations and affiliations. Abdesalem Al Guilani introduces himself as a soldier of Allah and a dedicated member of the Islamic State, emphasizing his commitment to their cause. The chilling proclamation involves a detailed account of his claimed actions, with the assassin seeking forgiveness from those he wronged and extending his forgiveness to all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the wake of the attack, France is reinforcing its borders with Belgium, signaling a heightened state of security. Simultaneously, Belgian authorities advise locals to remain cautious and abstain from any unnecessary travel within the capital.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As Europe grapples with this mounting tension, the continent finds itself at a critical juncture, seeking solutions to ensure the safety of its citizens while preserving the values of unity and tolerance.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Brussels was rocked with fear and anxiety as two Swedish nationals were ruthlessly shot on a day when football enthusiasts from Belgium and Sweden were eagerly anticipating their clash on the pitch. As the city braced for the soccer matchup, tragedy struck, casting a dark shadow over the festivities. The Belgian government swiftly escalated its terror alert to the most critical level following the attack. Adding to the apprehension, a video surfaced on social media where a man claims to be the perpetrator, linking himself to the notorious terrorist organization, Islamic State. Prime Minister Alexander de Croo, expressing his grief over the heinous act, took to the social media platform X, once Twitter, to convey his condolences. He acknowledged the victims were Swedish but remained tight-lipped on the exact number. The so-called assailant, introducing himself as Abdesalem Al Guilani, contested official reports, suggesting there were three victims, not just two. Football enthusiasts awaiting the Euro 2024 qualifying match between Belgium and Sweden were left disheartened, as officials halted the match at halftime for security precautions. UEFA’s official site teased forthcoming details on the situation. The alarming episode in Brussels adds to a worrying trend seen across some European nations. The Israel-Hamas conflict has put regions on high alert, with nations such as France stepping up their security apparatus after tragic incidents of their own. The French nation witnessed a harrowing incident where a teacher was fatally stabbed in an act that President Emmanuel Macron labeled as “barbaric Islamic terrorism.” Although official sources remain reserved, initial reports suggest the Brussels shooter might have been targeting soccer fans. Videos circulating among local media show a man in an orange jacket, wielding a rifle, brazenly shooting in broad daylight and subsequently seeking shelter in a building. Witness accounts retrieved by a Belgian newspaper claimed that the shooter cried out “Allahu Akbar” before embarking on his violent spree. The self-proclaimed assailant’s video message sheds further light on his motivations and affiliations. Abdesalem Al Guilani introduces himself as a soldier of Allah and a dedicated member of the Islamic State, emphasizing his commitment to their cause. The chilling proclamation involves a detailed account of his claimed actions, with the assassin seeking forgiveness from those he wronged and extending his forgiveness to all. In the wake of the attack, France is reinforcing its borders with Belgium, signaling a heightened state of security. Simultaneously, Belgian authorities advise locals to remain cautious and abstain from any unnecessary travel within the capital. As Europe grapples with this mounting tension, the continent finds itself at a critical juncture, seeking solutions to ensure the safety of its citizens while preserving the values of unity and tolerance.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Iowa AG Throws Weight Behind Trump’s 2024 Bid</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/17/Trump-Endorsement-Iowa/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Iowa AG Throws Weight Behind Trump’s 2024 Bid" /><published>2023-10-17T10:15:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-17T10:15:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/17/Trump-Endorsement-Iowa</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/17/Trump-Endorsement-Iowa/">&lt;p&gt;In a significant political move, Iowa Attorney General Brenna Bird has officially endorsed former President Donald Trump for his 2024 presidential run. Bird’s endorsement came during a public event at the Dallas County Fairgrounds, Adel, Iowa, signaling another noteworthy addition to Trump’s growing list of high-profile endorsements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking to the gathered crowd, Bird contrasted the current state of the nation under the Biden administration with the time when Trump was in office. She emphasized on issues like the open border situation, perceived disrespect towards law enforcement, and the administration’s alleged stance against farmers. “The border is wide open; our law enforcement are disrespected,” Bird asserted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Taking a deeper dive into international matters, Bird brought attention to the rising terror attacks on Israel, questioning whether such occurrences would have taken place under Trump’s watch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In her endorsement speech, Bird enumerated several promises she believes Trump will deliver on if elected president again. These include securing the U.S. border, confronting global terrorists, bolstering the economy, championing agricultural interests, and, most importantly, safeguarding the U.S. Constitution and the country’s cherished way of life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Echoing her deep roots in Dallas County, where she grew up and participated in 4-H projects, Bird rallied the audience to extend a hearty welcome to Trump, whom she introduced as the “next president.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gratefully acknowledging the endorsement, Trump highlighted Bird’s stature in politics, not just within Iowa but also beyond. He referred to her as one of the “most-respected” figures in the realm of politics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it isn’t just about endorsements for Trump in Iowa. He continues to dominate the political scene, especially as the pivotal Iowa caucuses inch closer. The caucuses, which are less than 100 days away, could play a crucial role in determining the GOP nominee for the 2024 presidential race. Trump seems well-positioned, as demonstrated by a recent Iowa State University/Civiqs poll. The poll pegs Trump’s support among likely GOP caucus-goers at a dominant 55 percent, leading his nearest challenger, Florida Governor Ron DeSantis, by a staggering 38 points.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the political heat steadily escalating and endorsements like Bird’s adding momentum to his campaign, the road to the 2024 presidential elections seems rife with intense competition and intriguing developments.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a significant political move, Iowa Attorney General Brenna Bird has officially endorsed former President Donald Trump for his 2024 presidential run. Bird’s endorsement came during a public event at the Dallas County Fairgrounds, Adel, Iowa, signaling another noteworthy addition to Trump’s growing list of high-profile endorsements. Speaking to the gathered crowd, Bird contrasted the current state of the nation under the Biden administration with the time when Trump was in office. She emphasized on issues like the open border situation, perceived disrespect towards law enforcement, and the administration’s alleged stance against farmers. “The border is wide open; our law enforcement are disrespected,” Bird asserted. Taking a deeper dive into international matters, Bird brought attention to the rising terror attacks on Israel, questioning whether such occurrences would have taken place under Trump’s watch. In her endorsement speech, Bird enumerated several promises she believes Trump will deliver on if elected president again. These include securing the U.S. border, confronting global terrorists, bolstering the economy, championing agricultural interests, and, most importantly, safeguarding the U.S. Constitution and the country’s cherished way of life. Echoing her deep roots in Dallas County, where she grew up and participated in 4-H projects, Bird rallied the audience to extend a hearty welcome to Trump, whom she introduced as the “next president.” Gratefully acknowledging the endorsement, Trump highlighted Bird’s stature in politics, not just within Iowa but also beyond. He referred to her as one of the “most-respected” figures in the realm of politics. However, it isn’t just about endorsements for Trump in Iowa. He continues to dominate the political scene, especially as the pivotal Iowa caucuses inch closer. The caucuses, which are less than 100 days away, could play a crucial role in determining the GOP nominee for the 2024 presidential race. Trump seems well-positioned, as demonstrated by a recent Iowa State University/Civiqs poll. The poll pegs Trump’s support among likely GOP caucus-goers at a dominant 55 percent, leading his nearest challenger, Florida Governor Ron DeSantis, by a staggering 38 points. With the political heat steadily escalating and endorsements like Bird’s adding momentum to his campaign, the road to the 2024 presidential elections seems rife with intense competition and intriguing developments.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump’s Team Sounds Off on Judge’s Gag Order Decision</title><link href="/politics/2023/10/17/Trump-Gag-Order-Controversy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump’s Team Sounds Off on Judge’s Gag Order Decision" /><published>2023-10-17T09:10:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-17T09:10:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/10/17/Trump-Gag-Order-Controversy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/10/17/Trump-Gag-Order-Controversy/">&lt;p&gt;In a recent twist in the ongoing 2020 election subversion case, U.S. District Judge Tanya Chutkan issued a &lt;em&gt;gag order&lt;/em&gt; on former President Donald Trump. The decision restricts Trump from making any public statements aimed at prosecutors, potential witnesses, and even the judge’s own staff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This move sparked an immediate and sharp rebuke from Trump’s spokesperson, who labeled the order as an “absolute abomination.” The spokesperson’s statement, relayed by Newsmax, criticizes the decision as a blatant display of partisanship. Drawing connections to current President Joe Biden, the statement suggests that this move is a targeted effort to silence “the most popular political leader in America, President Donald J. Trump.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The heated language doesn’t stop there, with the spokesperson stating that the decision is tantamount to a “partisan knife stuck in the heart of our Democracy.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the core of this controversy is the issue of freedom of speech versus the integrity of the judicial process. Judge Chutkan’s order was precipitated by concerns raised by special counsel Jack Smith’s team. The team cited numerous statements from Trump that directly disparaged prosecutors, the presiding judge, and individuals who might serve as witnesses in the case.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the prosecution’s perspective, the concern is multifaceted. On one hand, Trump’s comments, they argue, erode public trust in the court system. On the other, such comments might create an environment of harassment and intimidation, especially for potential jurors and witnesses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a bid to balance the scales between ensuring a fair trial and upholding freedom of speech, Judge Chutkan clarified that the gag order would not inhibit Trump from critiquing the Justice Department at large. Furthermore, he remains free to vocalize his belief that the case against him is driven by political motivations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The political landscape in the U.S. remains deeply polarized, and developments like these often fan the flames of partisan debates. With Trump being mentioned as a potential contender for the 2024 Presidential race, every legal and political move related to him is scrutinized and can have wide-reaching implications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s undeniable is that the tension between the former President and the judicial system remains palpable. As the 2024 elections loom closer, how this relationship unfolds could have a significant impact on the political narrative and the choices voters make.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a recent twist in the ongoing 2020 election subversion case, U.S. District Judge Tanya Chutkan issued a gag order on former President Donald Trump. The decision restricts Trump from making any public statements aimed at prosecutors, potential witnesses, and even the judge’s own staff. This move sparked an immediate and sharp rebuke from Trump’s spokesperson, who labeled the order as an “absolute abomination.” The spokesperson’s statement, relayed by Newsmax, criticizes the decision as a blatant display of partisanship. Drawing connections to current President Joe Biden, the statement suggests that this move is a targeted effort to silence “the most popular political leader in America, President Donald J. Trump.” The heated language doesn’t stop there, with the spokesperson stating that the decision is tantamount to a “partisan knife stuck in the heart of our Democracy.” At the core of this controversy is the issue of freedom of speech versus the integrity of the judicial process. Judge Chutkan’s order was precipitated by concerns raised by special counsel Jack Smith’s team. The team cited numerous statements from Trump that directly disparaged prosecutors, the presiding judge, and individuals who might serve as witnesses in the case. From the prosecution’s perspective, the concern is multifaceted. On one hand, Trump’s comments, they argue, erode public trust in the court system. On the other, such comments might create an environment of harassment and intimidation, especially for potential jurors and witnesses. In a bid to balance the scales between ensuring a fair trial and upholding freedom of speech, Judge Chutkan clarified that the gag order would not inhibit Trump from critiquing the Justice Department at large. Furthermore, he remains free to vocalize his belief that the case against him is driven by political motivations. The political landscape in the U.S. remains deeply polarized, and developments like these often fan the flames of partisan debates. With Trump being mentioned as a potential contender for the 2024 Presidential race, every legal and political move related to him is scrutinized and can have wide-reaching implications. What’s undeniable is that the tension between the former President and the judicial system remains palpable. As the 2024 elections loom closer, how this relationship unfolds could have a significant impact on the political narrative and the choices voters make.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Waka Flocka Flame Jumps Aboard the ‘Trump Train’ for 2024</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/10/17/Waka-Flocka-Trump-Endorsement/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Waka Flocka Flame Jumps Aboard the ‘Trump Train’ for 2024" /><published>2023-10-17T08:05:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-10-17T08:05:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/10/17/Waka-Flocka-Trump-Endorsement</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/10/17/Waka-Flocka-Trump-Endorsement/">&lt;p&gt;In an unexpected twist in the world of entertainment-meets-politics, rapper Waka Flocka Flame publicly declared his support for former President Donald Trump’s 2024 presidential campaign. This announcement, made to his vast audience of over 1 million X followers, emphasized his decision to support Trump’s return to the White House.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Waka Flocka Flame’s endorsement comes amidst growing concerns and debates within the African American community regarding the Biden administration. Recent policies have been criticized for alienating many black voters, particularly those in underprivileged urban regions. A point of contention has been the influx of illegal immigrants into their neighborhoods, leading to the distribution of taxpayer-funded benefits often unavailable to American citizens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One example of the rising concerns can be seen in Chicago. As highlighted by Breitbart News, a poll revealed that a significant portion of Chicago’s population opposes the city’s sanctuary policies, which support illegal aliens. These policies require taxpayers to fund housing, medical care, and food for illegal immigrants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While 49% of Chicago’s white voters believe that the sanctuary city policies are worth maintaining, this sentiment is not shared uniformly across all demographics. Only 31% of black voters and 38% of Hispanic voters in Chicago agree with the stance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recent reports from mainstream media outlets have reflected a growing anxiety. There’s a palpable fear that African American voters might not rally behind President Biden in the 2024 elections. Many have attributed this shift to mounting disillusionment with the current administration, especially in light of pressing issues like inflation, which continues to strain household budgets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Waka Flocka Flame’s endorsement of Trump, while just one among many, signifies a broader trend in the entertainment industry. Artists, influencers, and celebrities are becoming more vocal about their political leanings, using their platforms to sway public opinion or mirror the sentiments of their fanbase.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the 2024 presidential race gains momentum, such endorsements could play a pivotal role in influencing voters, particularly among younger demographics. The fusion of entertainment and politics is not new, but the weight of celebrity endorsements in swaying political outcomes remains a topic of considerable interest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Time will tell if more figures from the entertainment industry will voice their political preferences as openly as Waka Flocka Flame. For now, his “boarding the Trump train” has set the stage for intriguing political debates in both mainstream and social media channels.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">In an unexpected twist in the world of entertainment-meets-politics, rapper Waka Flocka Flame publicly declared his support for former President Donald Trump’s 2024 presidential campaign. This announcement, made to his vast audience of over 1 million X followers, emphasized his decision to support Trump’s return to the White House. Waka Flocka Flame’s endorsement comes amidst growing concerns and debates within the African American community regarding the Biden administration. Recent policies have been criticized for alienating many black voters, particularly those in underprivileged urban regions. A point of contention has been the influx of illegal immigrants into their neighborhoods, leading to the distribution of taxpayer-funded benefits often unavailable to American citizens. One example of the rising concerns can be seen in Chicago. As highlighted by Breitbart News, a poll revealed that a significant portion of Chicago’s population opposes the city’s sanctuary policies, which support illegal aliens. These policies require taxpayers to fund housing, medical care, and food for illegal immigrants. While 49% of Chicago’s white voters believe that the sanctuary city policies are worth maintaining, this sentiment is not shared uniformly across all demographics. Only 31% of black voters and 38% of Hispanic voters in Chicago agree with the stance. Recent reports from mainstream media outlets have reflected a growing anxiety. There’s a palpable fear that African American voters might not rally behind President Biden in the 2024 elections. Many have attributed this shift to mounting disillusionment with the current administration, especially in light of pressing issues like inflation, which continues to strain household budgets. Waka Flocka Flame’s endorsement of Trump, while just one among many, signifies a broader trend in the entertainment industry. Artists, influencers, and celebrities are becoming more vocal about their political leanings, using their platforms to sway public opinion or mirror the sentiments of their fanbase. As the 2024 presidential race gains momentum, such endorsements could play a pivotal role in influencing voters, particularly among younger demographics. The fusion of entertainment and politics is not new, but the weight of celebrity endorsements in swaying political outcomes remains a topic of considerable interest. Time will tell if more figures from the entertainment industry will voice their political preferences as openly as Waka Flocka Flame. For now, his “boarding the Trump train” has set the stage for intriguing political debates in both mainstream and social media channels.</summary></entry></feed>