<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-09-09T09:15:52-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Gold Backed News</title><subtitle>Information is currency</subtitle><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="/2023/09/09/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2023-09-09T09:15:52-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-09T09:15:52-04:00</updated><id>/2023/09/09/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/09/09/2023-08-28-Arleen-Sorkin-Legacy/">&lt;p&gt;Arleen Sorkin, celebrated for her portrayal of Calliope Jones on “Days of Our Lives,” and for being the original voice behind the iconic DC Comics character Harley Quinn, has passed away at the age of 67. A talent like hers, which spanned both on-screen and voice-over realms, is irreplaceable in the entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A representative for Christopher Lloyd, Sorkin’s husband and prominent figure behind “Modern Family” and “Frasier,” confirmed the sad news. The loss has left a void in the heart of Hollywood, and tributes are pouring in from across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Gunn, the director known for his work on DC’s “The Suicide Squad,” expressed his condolences on Instagram, acknowledging Sorkin’s seminal contribution to the Harley Quinn character. “Rest in Peace, Arleen Sorkin, the incredibly talented original voice of Harley Quinn, who helped to create the character so many of us love. Love to her family and friends,” he penned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark Hamill, the voice of Joker and her co-star from “Batman: The Animated Series,” reminisced about his time working with Sorkin. Through his post on X (formerly known as Twitter), Hamill highlighted not just Sorkin’s exemplary talent but her heartwarming personality. “Devastated to learn we’ve lost the brilliant Arleen Sorkin. Not just a wonderful talent, but a truly wonderful person,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Batman series, Sorkin’s voice brought Harley Quinn to life in a plethora of video games and animated series like “Justice League,” “Gotham Girls,” and “Batman: Arkham Asylum.” Harley Quinn’s prominence in the DC universe has only grown over the years, with Margot Robbie’s portrayal in movies like “Suicide Squad” and “Birds of Prey.” Kaley Cuoco and Tara Strong are among those who have since taken on the role in animated adaptations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it wasn’t just the world of animation that Arleen graced with her presence. She began her acting journey in the ’80s with roles in “Saturday Night Live” and “Trading Places,” eventually securing her memorable role in “Days of Our Lives” in 1984. The character Calliope Jones, known for her eccentricity and charm, earned Sorkin multiple awards and nominations. Her contribution to the soap opera spanned hundreds of episodes, with her final appearance in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorkin’s versatility was evident through her various roles, including her co-hosting stint on “America’s Funniest People” alongside Dave Coulier in the early ’90s. Her credits also extend to shows like “Duet,” “Open House,” and “Ted &amp;amp; Venus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world mourns the loss of such a multi-faceted talent. Arleen Sorkin is survived by her husband, Christopher Lloyd, and their two sons.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gold Backed News</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Biden’s Censorship Crusade - Overreach or Attack on Freedom?</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/09/Biden-Censorship-Debacle/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Biden’s Censorship Crusade - Overreach or Attack on Freedom?" /><published>2023-09-09T09:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-09T09:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/09/Biden-Censorship-Debacle</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/09/Biden-Censorship-Debacle/">&lt;p&gt;In a country built on the ideals of freedom and individual rights, the Biden administration’s latest act of perceived overreach has many conservatives sounding the alarm. The United States Fifth Circuit Court of Appeals, in its groundbreaking decision, has implied that President Biden and his team might have dangerously trampled upon the sacred First Amendment rights during the COVID-19 pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This isn’t just about governance; it’s about the very essence of our democracy. The court has pointed out how key figures in the administration, including those at the very top in the White House, the Surgeon General’s office, CDC, and even the FBI, seem to have used their positions to unduly and coercively influence online content moderation decisions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The three-judge panel didn’t mince words: “We find that the White House, acting in concert with the Surgeon General’s office, likely coerced the platforms to make their moderation decisions … and significantly encouraged the platforms’ decisions.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The FBI, long considered an impartial agency, was also not spared. The panel suggested that the FBI went far beyond its mandate, not only influencing platforms but also proactively inducing changes to moderation policies. Actions that, many argue, reek of constitutional infringement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the original lower court injunction was wide in its scope, the revised order now specifically targets and holds accountable these entities: the White House, Surgeon General’s office, CDC, and FBI. It’s a move that many see as the Fifth Circuit stepping up to defend the Constitution from executive overreach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;U.S. Senator Eric Schmitt didn’t hold back in his response, labeling the decision a “massive victory for free speech.” In a rallying cry to all freedom-loving Americans, he emphasized, “Because of Missouri v. Biden, the federal government is prohibited yet again from colluding with social media giants to censor freedom of speech online.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the Biden administration scrambles to respond, their attempt at defense seems weak at best. While they review the decision and weigh their options, one thing is clear: the American people are watching. With the potential for this case to be elevated to the Supreme Court, it serves as a grim reminder of the need for vigilance in defending our freedoms against potential governmental overreach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a nation that champions liberty and freedom of speech, one must wonder: How did we get here, and how do we ensure our rights remain unassailable?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">In a country built on the ideals of freedom and individual rights, the Biden administration’s latest act of perceived overreach has many conservatives sounding the alarm. The United States Fifth Circuit Court of Appeals, in its groundbreaking decision, has implied that President Biden and his team might have dangerously trampled upon the sacred First Amendment rights during the COVID-19 pandemic. This isn’t just about governance; it’s about the very essence of our democracy. The court has pointed out how key figures in the administration, including those at the very top in the White House, the Surgeon General’s office, CDC, and even the FBI, seem to have used their positions to unduly and coercively influence online content moderation decisions. The three-judge panel didn’t mince words: “We find that the White House, acting in concert with the Surgeon General’s office, likely coerced the platforms to make their moderation decisions … and significantly encouraged the platforms’ decisions.” The FBI, long considered an impartial agency, was also not spared. The panel suggested that the FBI went far beyond its mandate, not only influencing platforms but also proactively inducing changes to moderation policies. Actions that, many argue, reek of constitutional infringement. While the original lower court injunction was wide in its scope, the revised order now specifically targets and holds accountable these entities: the White House, Surgeon General’s office, CDC, and FBI. It’s a move that many see as the Fifth Circuit stepping up to defend the Constitution from executive overreach. U.S. Senator Eric Schmitt didn’t hold back in his response, labeling the decision a “massive victory for free speech.” In a rallying cry to all freedom-loving Americans, he emphasized, “Because of Missouri v. Biden, the federal government is prohibited yet again from colluding with social media giants to censor freedom of speech online.” As the Biden administration scrambles to respond, their attempt at defense seems weak at best. While they review the decision and weigh their options, one thing is clear: the American people are watching. With the potential for this case to be elevated to the Supreme Court, it serves as a grim reminder of the need for vigilance in defending our freedoms against potential governmental overreach. In a nation that champions liberty and freedom of speech, one must wonder: How did we get here, and how do we ensure our rights remain unassailable?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trump’s New Ally in 2024 - Governor Kristi Noem’s Full-Hearted Endorsement</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/09/Noem-Endorses-Trump/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump’s New Ally in 2024 - Governor Kristi Noem’s Full-Hearted Endorsement" /><published>2023-09-09T08:02:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-09T08:02:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/09/Noem-Endorses-Trump</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/09/Noem-Endorses-Trump/">&lt;p&gt;Governor Kristi Noem (R-SD) has thrown her full support behind former President Donald Trump, endorsing him as the “fighter that our country needs.” The announcement came during the South Dakota Republican Party’s Monumental Leaders Rally held in Rapid City, South Dakota, where Noem shared the stage with the former President.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Quoting Teddy Roosevelt’s renowned “Citizenship in a Republic” speech, Noem said, “It is my honor to present to you the man in the arena. He is a man of significance. He is the leader, the fighter that our country needs. He has my full and complete endorsement for president of the United States of America. I will do everything I can to help him win and save this country.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speculation had been rife leading up to the rally about Noem’s endorsement and Trump’s appearance, with many considering Noem as a possible vice-presidential candidate if Trump secures the nomination. Addressing the rally, Noem acknowledged the buzz, revealing that she had been inundated with queries about the night’s event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Highlighting the dedication of the former President, Noem described how, while many other presidential hopefuls declined invitations to attend the rally, Trump immediately pledged his attendance. She praised Trump’s dedication to Americans, stressing that “he shows up for every American and fights for us every day.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the critical issues Noem brought to the forefront was the situation at the U.S. Southern border. She praised Trump’s actions during his term, emphasizing his strategy of “peace through strength” and portraying him as the only trustworthy candidate concerning these issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In remarks prepared for the event, the former President expressed his gratitude towards Noem, calling her “one of the most successful governors in the entire nation.” Trump lauded Noem’s stance on American values and her tough position on China, while also highlighting her decision to keep South Dakota open during the pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With this significant endorsement, Trump’s campaign for the 2024 presidential race gains even more momentum, backed by a prominent Republican figure. Only time will tell how this alliance shapes the political landscape ahead.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Governor Kristi Noem (R-SD) has thrown her full support behind former President Donald Trump, endorsing him as the “fighter that our country needs.” The announcement came during the South Dakota Republican Party’s Monumental Leaders Rally held in Rapid City, South Dakota, where Noem shared the stage with the former President. Quoting Teddy Roosevelt’s renowned “Citizenship in a Republic” speech, Noem said, “It is my honor to present to you the man in the arena. He is a man of significance. He is the leader, the fighter that our country needs. He has my full and complete endorsement for president of the United States of America. I will do everything I can to help him win and save this country.” Speculation had been rife leading up to the rally about Noem’s endorsement and Trump’s appearance, with many considering Noem as a possible vice-presidential candidate if Trump secures the nomination. Addressing the rally, Noem acknowledged the buzz, revealing that she had been inundated with queries about the night’s event. Highlighting the dedication of the former President, Noem described how, while many other presidential hopefuls declined invitations to attend the rally, Trump immediately pledged his attendance. She praised Trump’s dedication to Americans, stressing that “he shows up for every American and fights for us every day.” One of the critical issues Noem brought to the forefront was the situation at the U.S. Southern border. She praised Trump’s actions during his term, emphasizing his strategy of “peace through strength” and portraying him as the only trustworthy candidate concerning these issues. In remarks prepared for the event, the former President expressed his gratitude towards Noem, calling her “one of the most successful governors in the entire nation.” Trump lauded Noem’s stance on American values and her tough position on China, while also highlighting her decision to keep South Dakota open during the pandemic. With this significant endorsement, Trump’s campaign for the 2024 presidential race gains even more momentum, backed by a prominent Republican figure. Only time will tell how this alliance shapes the political landscape ahead.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Chrisley Sentences Slashed - Reality Stars’ Prison Time Reduced</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/09/Chrisley-Prison-Term/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Chrisley Sentences Slashed - Reality Stars’ Prison Time Reduced" /><published>2023-09-09T07:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-09T07:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/09/Chrisley-Prison-Term</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/09/Chrisley-Prison-Term/">&lt;p&gt;From 19 to 15 years – that’s the new combined prison sentence for Todd and Julie Chrisley, the faces of reality show “Chrisley Knows Best.” Fox News Digital confirmed that the significant reduction in their sentences is thanks to their exemplary conduct behind bars.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to a statement from the couple’s attorney, Jay Surgent, “Todd and Julie Chrisley have been model incarcerated individuals and have been compliant with all regulations promulgated by the bureau of prisons.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prior to the revision, Todd faced 12 years, while Julie was to serve seven after their 2019 indictment on bank fraud and tax evasion charges. This announcement comes just months after the pair’s entry into prison on January 17th.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it hasn’t all been smooth sailing for the Chrisleys. Todd’s claims of prison mistreatment due to his celebrity status, and even reports of hazardous living conditions like mold, snakes, and temperature extremes have surfaced. Their children, Savannah and Chase Chrisley, expressed concerns over the “inhumane treatment” their parents faced, detailing the troubling conditions during an episode of the “Unlocked with Savannah Chrisley” podcast.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the challenges and controversies surrounding the Chrisleys, their legacy in the entertainment world remains intact. Their breakthrough show, “Chrisley Knows Best,” may have signed off in March, but the Chrisley saga continues. A new reality show focusing on the lives of Todd and Julie’s children in the aftermath of their parents’ prison sentences is on the horizon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jay Surgent hints at the future show, stating, “It will be unscripted, and it will be a pivotal next chapter … for Chase, Savannah, Grayson, Chloe, and Nanny Faye,” potentially referring to an even more candid look into the Chrisley family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the family continues to evolve, fans and critics alike will be watching, eager to see what the next chapter brings for the Chrisleys.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">From 19 to 15 years – that’s the new combined prison sentence for Todd and Julie Chrisley, the faces of reality show “Chrisley Knows Best.” Fox News Digital confirmed that the significant reduction in their sentences is thanks to their exemplary conduct behind bars. According to a statement from the couple’s attorney, Jay Surgent, “Todd and Julie Chrisley have been model incarcerated individuals and have been compliant with all regulations promulgated by the bureau of prisons.” Prior to the revision, Todd faced 12 years, while Julie was to serve seven after their 2019 indictment on bank fraud and tax evasion charges. This announcement comes just months after the pair’s entry into prison on January 17th. However, it hasn’t all been smooth sailing for the Chrisleys. Todd’s claims of prison mistreatment due to his celebrity status, and even reports of hazardous living conditions like mold, snakes, and temperature extremes have surfaced. Their children, Savannah and Chase Chrisley, expressed concerns over the “inhumane treatment” their parents faced, detailing the troubling conditions during an episode of the “Unlocked with Savannah Chrisley” podcast. Despite the challenges and controversies surrounding the Chrisleys, their legacy in the entertainment world remains intact. Their breakthrough show, “Chrisley Knows Best,” may have signed off in March, but the Chrisley saga continues. A new reality show focusing on the lives of Todd and Julie’s children in the aftermath of their parents’ prison sentences is on the horizon. Jay Surgent hints at the future show, stating, “It will be unscripted, and it will be a pivotal next chapter … for Chase, Savannah, Grayson, Chloe, and Nanny Faye,” potentially referring to an even more candid look into the Chrisley family. As the family continues to evolve, fans and critics alike will be watching, eager to see what the next chapter brings for the Chrisleys.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Governor Greg Abbott Takes a Stand - Is NYC’s Migrant Crisis Really Texas’s Fault?</title><link href="/news/2023/09/08/Abbott-Defends-Texas/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Governor Greg Abbott Takes a Stand - Is NYC’s Migrant Crisis Really Texas’s Fault?" /><published>2023-09-08T19:36:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-08T19:36:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/08/Abbott-Defends-Texas</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/08/Abbott-Defends-Texas/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Governor Greg Abbott Stands Tall Against Unfair Accusations&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Texas Governor Greg Abbott faces unwarranted criticism from New York City Mayor Eric Adams over the Lone Star State’s “Operation Lone Star” initiative. Mayor Adams might be looking for a scapegoat, but the numbers and facts reveal a different story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Defending “Operation Lone Star”&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Governor Abbott’s “Operation Lone Star” is a proactive measure to ensure border security. A component of this mission is the busing of migrants to sanctuary cities, ensuring an equitable distribution and relief for overwhelmed border towns. Contrary to Mayor Adams’ portrayal, this initiative was designed with community welfare in mind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During a September 6 town hall meeting, Mayor Adams seemed to pass the buck onto Texas, exclaiming, “It started with a madman down in Texas [who] decided he wanted to bus people up to New York City.” However, his emotional remarks paint a misleading picture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Diving Deep into the Numbers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Adams bemoans the impact on New York City, he conveniently omits the broader context. Governor Abbott was quick to point out that Texas had bused only 13,300 migrants to New York. This is a drop in the bucket compared to the numbers brought in by federal initiatives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Abbott’s press secretary, Andrew Mahaleris, shed light on this selective narrative. “Mayor Adams was proud of his sanctuary city status until Texas began busing migrants to New York City,” Mahaleris highlighted, emphasizing the hypocrisy of such a stance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, Mahaleris urged Mayor Adams to consider the bigger picture, suggesting he address concerns to President Biden’s administration. The federal government, under Biden, has been “flying planeloads of migrants all around the country, straining state and local resources,” Mahaleris noted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Beyond Finger-Pointing: The True Crisis&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Mayor Adams seems occupied with shifting blame, Governor Abbott remains focused on the core issue at hand: the safety, security, and welfare of communities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, Mayor Adams’s alarmist remarks cannot be ignored entirely. The influx from various parts of the world, the looming fiscal challenges, and the broader implications for the nation’s socio-economic fabric demand attention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What remains evident is that the challenge is a national one and not a creation of any single state’s policies. While the debate between NYC and Texas heats up, one can hope that the focus will shift from blame games to constructive solutions.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Governor Greg Abbott Stands Tall Against Unfair Accusations Texas Governor Greg Abbott faces unwarranted criticism from New York City Mayor Eric Adams over the Lone Star State’s “Operation Lone Star” initiative. Mayor Adams might be looking for a scapegoat, but the numbers and facts reveal a different story. Defending “Operation Lone Star” Governor Abbott’s “Operation Lone Star” is a proactive measure to ensure border security. A component of this mission is the busing of migrants to sanctuary cities, ensuring an equitable distribution and relief for overwhelmed border towns. Contrary to Mayor Adams’ portrayal, this initiative was designed with community welfare in mind. During a September 6 town hall meeting, Mayor Adams seemed to pass the buck onto Texas, exclaiming, “It started with a madman down in Texas [who] decided he wanted to bus people up to New York City.” However, his emotional remarks paint a misleading picture. Diving Deep into the Numbers While Adams bemoans the impact on New York City, he conveniently omits the broader context. Governor Abbott was quick to point out that Texas had bused only 13,300 migrants to New York. This is a drop in the bucket compared to the numbers brought in by federal initiatives. Abbott’s press secretary, Andrew Mahaleris, shed light on this selective narrative. “Mayor Adams was proud of his sanctuary city status until Texas began busing migrants to New York City,” Mahaleris highlighted, emphasizing the hypocrisy of such a stance. Furthermore, Mahaleris urged Mayor Adams to consider the bigger picture, suggesting he address concerns to President Biden’s administration. The federal government, under Biden, has been “flying planeloads of migrants all around the country, straining state and local resources,” Mahaleris noted. Beyond Finger-Pointing: The True Crisis While Mayor Adams seems occupied with shifting blame, Governor Abbott remains focused on the core issue at hand: the safety, security, and welfare of communities. However, Mayor Adams’s alarmist remarks cannot be ignored entirely. The influx from various parts of the world, the looming fiscal challenges, and the broader implications for the nation’s socio-economic fabric demand attention. What remains evident is that the challenge is a national one and not a creation of any single state’s policies. While the debate between NYC and Texas heats up, one can hope that the focus will shift from blame games to constructive solutions.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Pence Elevates Right to Life - ‘More Important Than Politics’</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/08/Life-Over-Politics/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Pence Elevates Right to Life - ‘More Important Than Politics’" /><published>2023-09-08T18:43:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-08T18:43:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/08/Life-Over-Politics</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/08/Life-Over-Politics/">&lt;p&gt;Former Vice President Mike Pence has resoundingly affirmed his unwavering commitment to the pro-life cause, emphasizing that the right to life holds more weight than political gamesmanship. During a candid interview with Newsmax’s “Rob Schmitt Tonight,” Pence declared that the value of life is paramount, even more so than winning an election.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a charged political environment where political calculations often override principles, Pence’s bold proclamation stands out. Challenging a common belief, Pence dismissed the notion, earlier suggested by former President Trump, that their administration lost midterm elections because of overturning Roe v. Wade. “I don’t believe that for a second,” Pence responded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More than just politics, Pence views the right to life as a deep moral conviction. He expressed concerns about some wanting to reduce the life issue to a state-level matter. “For me, right to life’s not a state issue, it’s a moral issue. I’ll be a champion for right to life in the Oval Office,” he passionately conveyed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pence’s words weren’t solely about unborn children but extended to women in distressing situations as well. His remarks highlight the compassion underlying the pro-life stance: “I think when you stand on the right to life, you stand with principle and compassion and demonstrate not just a willingness to put our arms around the unborn but around newborns and women in crisis.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Drawing parallels with international sentiment, Pence highlighted that most European nations have restrictions on abortion after the unborn child can feel pain. This aligns with the beliefs of a vast majority of Americans, with 70% sharing this sentiment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the GOP primary is unfolding with various stances and policies, Pence wants to be recognized for his unwavering conservative approach. He refrained from diving deep into the populist policies of Trump, only emphasizing that their administration had always governed with conservative principles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pence’s interview underscores his dedication to the pro-life movement. As the political sphere evolves with various narratives, Pence’s commitment to life, compassion, and moral values remains unshaken.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">Former Vice President Mike Pence has resoundingly affirmed his unwavering commitment to the pro-life cause, emphasizing that the right to life holds more weight than political gamesmanship. During a candid interview with Newsmax’s “Rob Schmitt Tonight,” Pence declared that the value of life is paramount, even more so than winning an election. In a charged political environment where political calculations often override principles, Pence’s bold proclamation stands out. Challenging a common belief, Pence dismissed the notion, earlier suggested by former President Trump, that their administration lost midterm elections because of overturning Roe v. Wade. “I don’t believe that for a second,” Pence responded. More than just politics, Pence views the right to life as a deep moral conviction. He expressed concerns about some wanting to reduce the life issue to a state-level matter. “For me, right to life’s not a state issue, it’s a moral issue. I’ll be a champion for right to life in the Oval Office,” he passionately conveyed. Pence’s words weren’t solely about unborn children but extended to women in distressing situations as well. His remarks highlight the compassion underlying the pro-life stance: “I think when you stand on the right to life, you stand with principle and compassion and demonstrate not just a willingness to put our arms around the unborn but around newborns and women in crisis.” Drawing parallels with international sentiment, Pence highlighted that most European nations have restrictions on abortion after the unborn child can feel pain. This aligns with the beliefs of a vast majority of Americans, with 70% sharing this sentiment. While the GOP primary is unfolding with various stances and policies, Pence wants to be recognized for his unwavering conservative approach. He refrained from diving deep into the populist policies of Trump, only emphasizing that their administration had always governed with conservative principles. Pence’s interview underscores his dedication to the pro-life movement. As the political sphere evolves with various narratives, Pence’s commitment to life, compassion, and moral values remains unshaken.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Huntington Beach Champions Freedom - Rejects Universal COVID Mandates</title><link href="/news/2023/09/08/Huntington-Beach-Ban/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Huntington Beach Champions Freedom - Rejects Universal COVID Mandates" /><published>2023-09-08T17:55:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-08T17:55:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/08/Huntington-Beach-Ban</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/08/Huntington-Beach-Ban/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Defying Statewide Draconian Measures, Huntington Beach Makes A Stand&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a move that sets the city apart from the rest of the state, the City of Huntington Beach, California, made a crucial decision on Wednesday: it will not impose universal mask and vaccine mandates for COVID-19. This move highlights the ever-growing divide between the freedom-centric localities and the broader state measures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Victory for Personal Choice&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The motion to ban the mandates, brought forward by Mayor Pro Tem Gracey Van Der Mark, emphasizes the importance of individual liberties. Van Der Mark critiqued past mask mandates, declaring that they “unnecessarily limited the freedoms of the citizens of Huntington Beach.” In a society where autonomy should be celebrated, these measures were seen as restrictive, especially for individuals who had no exposure or risk associated with COVID-19.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s also worth noting that the decision was not taken lightly. With a narrow 4-3 vote, the City Council showcased the weight of the debate, highlighting that while there is support for personal freedom, there are voices of caution as well. However, the motion’s successful passing signifies that, at least in Huntington Beach, the voice of liberty rings louder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Response to a Slight Rise in Cases&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the decision comes amidst a slight increase in COVID cases within the city, it stands as a testament to the city’s commitment to maintaining the rights of its citizens. The current uptick does not appear to have deterred the local government’s determination to prioritize choice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Huntington Beach - A History of Defiance&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Huntington Beach’s move isn’t surprising for those familiar with its history. Located a mere hour from Los Angeles, the city has been a beacon of resistance against statewide mask mandates throughout the pandemic’s duration. In stark contrast to California’s rigid approach, Huntington Beach opts for personal choice and autonomy, reflecting its longstanding conservative roots.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Larger Trend or a Lone Rebellion?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether other cities will follow Huntington Beach’s footsteps remains to be seen. However, the city’s latest decision cements its reputation as a bastion for conservatives and those valuing personal freedoms over sweeping state directives. As the debate surrounding COVID measures continues to polarize the nation, Huntington Beach stands as a reminder that there’s more than one way to address the challenges we face.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Defying Statewide Draconian Measures, Huntington Beach Makes A Stand In a move that sets the city apart from the rest of the state, the City of Huntington Beach, California, made a crucial decision on Wednesday: it will not impose universal mask and vaccine mandates for COVID-19. This move highlights the ever-growing divide between the freedom-centric localities and the broader state measures. A Victory for Personal Choice The motion to ban the mandates, brought forward by Mayor Pro Tem Gracey Van Der Mark, emphasizes the importance of individual liberties. Van Der Mark critiqued past mask mandates, declaring that they “unnecessarily limited the freedoms of the citizens of Huntington Beach.” In a society where autonomy should be celebrated, these measures were seen as restrictive, especially for individuals who had no exposure or risk associated with COVID-19. It’s also worth noting that the decision was not taken lightly. With a narrow 4-3 vote, the City Council showcased the weight of the debate, highlighting that while there is support for personal freedom, there are voices of caution as well. However, the motion’s successful passing signifies that, at least in Huntington Beach, the voice of liberty rings louder. A Response to a Slight Rise in Cases While the decision comes amidst a slight increase in COVID cases within the city, it stands as a testament to the city’s commitment to maintaining the rights of its citizens. The current uptick does not appear to have deterred the local government’s determination to prioritize choice. Huntington Beach - A History of Defiance Huntington Beach’s move isn’t surprising for those familiar with its history. Located a mere hour from Los Angeles, the city has been a beacon of resistance against statewide mask mandates throughout the pandemic’s duration. In stark contrast to California’s rigid approach, Huntington Beach opts for personal choice and autonomy, reflecting its longstanding conservative roots. A Larger Trend or a Lone Rebellion? Whether other cities will follow Huntington Beach’s footsteps remains to be seen. However, the city’s latest decision cements its reputation as a bastion for conservatives and those valuing personal freedoms over sweeping state directives. As the debate surrounding COVID measures continues to polarize the nation, Huntington Beach stands as a reminder that there’s more than one way to address the challenges we face.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Fulton County’s Deadly Crisis - The Jail Where Trump Was Booked Faces Disturbing Death Toll</title><link href="/news/2023/09/08/Trump-Jail-Deaths/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Fulton County’s Deadly Crisis - The Jail Where Trump Was Booked Faces Disturbing Death Toll" /><published>2023-09-08T16:48:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-08T16:48:00-04:00</updated><id>/news/2023/09/08/Trump-Jail-Deaths</id><content type="html" xml:base="/news/2023/09/08/Trump-Jail-Deaths/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fulton County Jail: A Ground Zero for Presidential Controversies and Grim Realities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the world was preoccupied with the spectacle of former President Donald Trump’s voluntary surrender at Fulton County Jail, a grave and haunting pattern of inmate deaths emerged in the shadows of the facility. Six fatalities have been reported since the end of July, intensifying concerns over the jail’s operations and management.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Presidential Surrender Overshadows a Dire Situation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The jail gained immense attention when Trump turned himself in due to charges stemming from alleged election interference in Georgia. The media fervently covered his booking and that of his 18 co-defendants. However, beneath this high-profile event, the stark reality of life in the jail came into focus with the tragic death of 24-year-old Shawndre Delmore.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DOJ’s Intervention: A Damning Indictment of Jail Conditions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Disturbing incidents, such as the death of 35-year-old Lashawn Thompson caused by apparent severe neglect, have painted a bleak picture of the facility’s conditions. This alarming environment prompted the Department of Justice (DOJ) to launch a civil investigation, addressing growing concerns over violence, deplorable living conditions, and even reports of an inmate’s body found with insect infestation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Series of Troubling Deaths within Jail Walls&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apart from Delmore, several inmates have met untimely deaths within the prison’s confines in recent weeks. Samuel Lawrence, Dayvion Blake, Alexander Hawkins, Christopher Smith, and Montay Stinson all faced tragic ends, with Blake’s fatal stabbing further emphasizing the urgent need for reform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conclusion: The Need for Transparency and Reform&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With a series of tragedies unfolding at Fulton County Jail, it’s paramount that the facility undergoes scrutiny and reforms to prevent further loss of life. While the spotlight may have been on Trump’s booking, the focus should now shift towards ensuring the safety and well-being of the inmates.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Donna Teetree</name></author><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Fulton County Jail: A Ground Zero for Presidential Controversies and Grim Realities While the world was preoccupied with the spectacle of former President Donald Trump’s voluntary surrender at Fulton County Jail, a grave and haunting pattern of inmate deaths emerged in the shadows of the facility. Six fatalities have been reported since the end of July, intensifying concerns over the jail’s operations and management. Presidential Surrender Overshadows a Dire Situation The jail gained immense attention when Trump turned himself in due to charges stemming from alleged election interference in Georgia. The media fervently covered his booking and that of his 18 co-defendants. However, beneath this high-profile event, the stark reality of life in the jail came into focus with the tragic death of 24-year-old Shawndre Delmore. DOJ’s Intervention: A Damning Indictment of Jail Conditions Disturbing incidents, such as the death of 35-year-old Lashawn Thompson caused by apparent severe neglect, have painted a bleak picture of the facility’s conditions. This alarming environment prompted the Department of Justice (DOJ) to launch a civil investigation, addressing growing concerns over violence, deplorable living conditions, and even reports of an inmate’s body found with insect infestation. A Series of Troubling Deaths within Jail Walls Apart from Delmore, several inmates have met untimely deaths within the prison’s confines in recent weeks. Samuel Lawrence, Dayvion Blake, Alexander Hawkins, Christopher Smith, and Montay Stinson all faced tragic ends, with Blake’s fatal stabbing further emphasizing the urgent need for reform. Conclusion: The Need for Transparency and Reform With a series of tragedies unfolding at Fulton County Jail, it’s paramount that the facility undergoes scrutiny and reforms to prevent further loss of life. While the spotlight may have been on Trump’s booking, the focus should now shift towards ensuring the safety and well-being of the inmates.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Duggar Divisions - When Reality TV Threatens Family Bonds</title><link href="/entertainment/2023/09/08/Duggar-Divisions/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Duggar Divisions - When Reality TV Threatens Family Bonds" /><published>2023-09-08T15:37:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-08T15:37:00-04:00</updated><id>/entertainment/2023/09/08/Duggar-Divisions</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entertainment/2023/09/08/Duggar-Divisions/">&lt;p&gt;Jill Duggar Dillard and her spouse, Derick Dillard, have recently delved into how the TLC reality series “19 Kids and Counting” — and the overbearing influence of patriarch Jim Bob Duggar — almost fragmented their marital bond.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As fans of the show may recall, the Duggar family’s journey to stardom was punctuated with not just the highs of a growing family but also the challenging lows of scandals and internal conflicts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to Jill, 32, and Derick, 34, one of the major hindrances to their marital peace was the extreme expectations surrounding obedience and submission to Jim Bob’s desires. In a heartfelt interview, Jill disclosed, “It definitely got between us… No matter your age, you are to obey your parents’ wishes, and you even have to ask them for their blessing for any major moment in your life.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Derick further recounted instances where Jim Bob allegedly attempted to “weaponize” their relationship, using it as leverage when the couple resisted his plans for the show. He lamented, “He would weaponize the relationship and say, ‘Is this you Jill, or is this you, Derick? Are you leading your wife astray and doing things that are not supportive of marriage?’”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It wasn’t just emotional manipulation that the couple faced; financial matters were also a bone of contention. Jill shed light on the fact that she was paid a mere $175,000 for a decade’s worth of filming, even though the show reportedly raked in over $8 million. The catch? The checks from TLC were directly handed over to Jim Bob.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jim Bob and Michelle Duggar, in a statement, expressed their love for all their children and emphasized their commitment to resolving conflicts honorably. However, they refrained from addressing the claims made by Jill and Derick directly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet, this isn’t the first time the Duggar family name has been steeped in controversy. The show itself was axed from TLC following a molestation scandal linked to Jill’s brother, Josh Duggar, in 2015. Matters further escalated when Josh was sentenced to over a dozen years in prison in December 2022 for child pornography charges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the future remains uncertain for the Duggars, one thing is clear: the allure of reality TV stardom often comes at a price. Whether it’s the strain on relationships, the exposure of personal scandals, or the tug-of-war over control and money, the Dillard couple’s revelations underscore the complexities of life in the limelight.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Pat Franklin</name></author><category term="Entertainment" /><summary type="html">Jill Duggar Dillard and her spouse, Derick Dillard, have recently delved into how the TLC reality series “19 Kids and Counting” — and the overbearing influence of patriarch Jim Bob Duggar — almost fragmented their marital bond. As fans of the show may recall, the Duggar family’s journey to stardom was punctuated with not just the highs of a growing family but also the challenging lows of scandals and internal conflicts. According to Jill, 32, and Derick, 34, one of the major hindrances to their marital peace was the extreme expectations surrounding obedience and submission to Jim Bob’s desires. In a heartfelt interview, Jill disclosed, “It definitely got between us… No matter your age, you are to obey your parents’ wishes, and you even have to ask them for their blessing for any major moment in your life.” Derick further recounted instances where Jim Bob allegedly attempted to “weaponize” their relationship, using it as leverage when the couple resisted his plans for the show. He lamented, “He would weaponize the relationship and say, ‘Is this you Jill, or is this you, Derick? Are you leading your wife astray and doing things that are not supportive of marriage?’” It wasn’t just emotional manipulation that the couple faced; financial matters were also a bone of contention. Jill shed light on the fact that she was paid a mere $175,000 for a decade’s worth of filming, even though the show reportedly raked in over $8 million. The catch? The checks from TLC were directly handed over to Jim Bob. Jim Bob and Michelle Duggar, in a statement, expressed their love for all their children and emphasized their commitment to resolving conflicts honorably. However, they refrained from addressing the claims made by Jill and Derick directly. Yet, this isn’t the first time the Duggar family name has been steeped in controversy. The show itself was axed from TLC following a molestation scandal linked to Jill’s brother, Josh Duggar, in 2015. Matters further escalated when Josh was sentenced to over a dozen years in prison in December 2022 for child pornography charges. While the future remains uncertain for the Duggars, one thing is clear: the allure of reality TV stardom often comes at a price. Whether it’s the strain on relationships, the exposure of personal scandals, or the tug-of-war over control and money, the Dillard couple’s revelations underscore the complexities of life in the limelight.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Biden on Shaky Ground - Multiple Republicans Surpass Him in Latest Poll</title><link href="/politics/2023/09/08/Biden-GOP-Poll/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Biden on Shaky Ground - Multiple Republicans Surpass Him in Latest Poll" /><published>2023-09-08T14:58:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-09-08T14:58:00-04:00</updated><id>/politics/2023/09/08/Biden-GOP-Poll</id><content type="html" xml:base="/politics/2023/09/08/Biden-GOP-Poll/">&lt;p&gt;CNN’s recent poll has the political scene buzzing, and the numbers don’t bode well for President Joe Biden. Facing off in hypothetical match-ups against a roster of potential GOP contenders, Biden found himself trailing in several instances.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Former President Donald Trump, South Carolina Senator Tim Scott, former Vice President Mike Pence, ex-Governor of South Carolina Nikki Haley, and former New Jersey Governor Chris Christie are some of the Republican names besting Biden in these match-ups.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a narrow contest, Trump just nudges past Biden, gathering 47% to Biden’s 46%. While Trump’s lead is within the poll’s margin of error, it underscores the political duress Biden could face.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet, Trump is not alone in this advantage. Notably, Nikki Haley surpasses Biden with a 49% to 43% lead, clearly sidestepping the poll’s margin of error. Both Pence and Scott find themselves two points ahead, holding 46% to Biden’s 44%. Chris Christie also pushes past Biden by two points, clocking in at 44% versus Biden’s 42%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, Florida Governor Ron DeSantis draws even with Biden, each amassing 47% of the hypothetical vote. Only anti-woke entrepreneur Vivek Ramaswamy seems to be on the back foot, trailing Biden by a single point — 46% to 45%. However, given the poll’s margin of error, even this matchup can be considered a virtual tie.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These numbers spell potential trouble for Biden. As the 2024 elections approach, concerns regarding his age and overall capabilities are becoming more pronounced, even among Democratic ranks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In stark contrast, Trump’s messaging remains confrontational and assertive. The former president, as active as ever on his platform, Truth Social, recently issued stark warnings, promising to address issues from his past term. Trump’s rhetoric focuses on seeking justice for perceived wrongs during his tenure, ranging from impeachment attempts to election controversies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the political scene unravels and contenders firm up their strategies, this latest CNN poll hints at an intense race ahead. Whether Biden can regain momentum remains to be seen. However, one thing is clear: the GOP field is geared up and raring to go.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Charles Standard</name></author><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">CNN’s recent poll has the political scene buzzing, and the numbers don’t bode well for President Joe Biden. Facing off in hypothetical match-ups against a roster of potential GOP contenders, Biden found himself trailing in several instances. Former President Donald Trump, South Carolina Senator Tim Scott, former Vice President Mike Pence, ex-Governor of South Carolina Nikki Haley, and former New Jersey Governor Chris Christie are some of the Republican names besting Biden in these match-ups. In a narrow contest, Trump just nudges past Biden, gathering 47% to Biden’s 46%. While Trump’s lead is within the poll’s margin of error, it underscores the political duress Biden could face. Yet, Trump is not alone in this advantage. Notably, Nikki Haley surpasses Biden with a 49% to 43% lead, clearly sidestepping the poll’s margin of error. Both Pence and Scott find themselves two points ahead, holding 46% to Biden’s 44%. Chris Christie also pushes past Biden by two points, clocking in at 44% versus Biden’s 42%. Interestingly, Florida Governor Ron DeSantis draws even with Biden, each amassing 47% of the hypothetical vote. Only anti-woke entrepreneur Vivek Ramaswamy seems to be on the back foot, trailing Biden by a single point — 46% to 45%. However, given the poll’s margin of error, even this matchup can be considered a virtual tie. These numbers spell potential trouble for Biden. As the 2024 elections approach, concerns regarding his age and overall capabilities are becoming more pronounced, even among Democratic ranks. In stark contrast, Trump’s messaging remains confrontational and assertive. The former president, as active as ever on his platform, Truth Social, recently issued stark warnings, promising to address issues from his past term. Trump’s rhetoric focuses on seeking justice for perceived wrongs during his tenure, ranging from impeachment attempts to election controversies. As the political scene unravels and contenders firm up their strategies, this latest CNN poll hints at an intense race ahead. Whether Biden can regain momentum remains to be seen. However, one thing is clear: the GOP field is geared up and raring to go.</summary></entry></feed>